<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <channel> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - Platinum Edition</title> 
<description>The new Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show, powered by M3 Records, provides listeners with various forms of entertainment ranging from theatrical audio productions of every genre of music to stimulating, precise, unscripted word schemes and critiques from the host, MaD MaxHeat. Listeners are guaranteed to receive the entertainment they come consistently to see. Nitro Edition also broadcasts marketing tips and industry interviews and spoken word. Entertainment news is supplied by The Ken McCoy Entertainment Report in California. The PG 13 show has a strong hip hop origin. No one wants to see you shine. But that is what makes the story behind the music. I was told at my first real recording session that some lines I said were at the pro level. Now everything I say is Pro Flow stated MaD MaXxx.</description> 
<link>http://www.proflowradio.com</link> 
<copyright>Copyright 2001</copyright> 
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs> 
<language>en</language> 
<atom:link href="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/AkBayPlat.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2009 01:44:39 -0500</lastBuildDate> 
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 01:31:51 -0500</pubDate> 
<webMaster>mm@maxheat.com (MaD MaXxx)</webMaster>
<generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.9) unlicensed version http://www.feedforall.com</generator> 
<itunes:subtitle>ProFlowRadio.com</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Uncut Adult Hip Hop Pop Radio including indie artists from across the World presented by MaD MaXxx</itunes:summary> 
<itunes:author>MaxHeat</itunes:author> 
 <itunes:owner> 
<itunes:name>Mike M</itunes:name> 
<itunes:email>mm@maxheat.com</itunes:email> 
</itunes:owner> 
<itunes:category text="Music" /> 
<itunes:category text="Technology" /> 
<itunes:keywords>mp3, free, rap, hip, hop, south, west, pop, rock, sex, butts</itunes:keywords> 
<itunes:image href="http://www.maxheat.com/platpro.jpg" /> 
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit> 
<itunes:block>no</itunes:block> 

 <item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - AK Bay Platinum</title> 
<description>Tune In Now for the raw west coast radio show dedicated to the music of Cali platinum producer Mike Mosley and hosted by Ohio's own Mike Mosley a.k.a. MaxHeat. The playlist will include music from Tupac, T.R.O.N., Miss Nana, E40, Bossolo, Spice 1, South Circle, Tavares Daize, The Outlawz, Spiritual Thugs, Eleven, A-Pinks, Yukmouth, WC, B Legit, Mac Mall, 4IZE, Tequila, Assassin, Richie Rich and many more talented independent artists.</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="54000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - AK Bay Platinum</title> 
<description>Tune In Now to hear MC lyte, Lil Joe, Papa Duck and the FAT freestyle segment.</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="58000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - AK Bay Platinum</title> 
<description>Tune In Now to hear the Mike Mosley tribute show for the West Coast featuring TQ, Daz, Syndrome, Bossolo, Planet Rock, JoRob, Isis Yasmeen, J Money and Scott James.</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Thur, 17 Dec 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>Raekwon Interview on the Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show</title> 
<description>Dominant Wu-Tang member Raekwon the Chef gives MaxHeat an exclusive lifetime achievement scoop.  Don't be the last to hear history in progress!</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/audio-intvw/ProFlowRadio-Raekwon-show-clean.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/audio-intvw/ProFlowRadio-Raekwon-show-clean.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Tues, 2 Mar 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - AK Bay Platinum</title> 
<description>Featuring Rick Ross, Mad Max, Raekwon, Will Spitwell, Tavares Daize, E40, Kandy Guryl, Mz Nicky, Krate Krusaders, Preacher, Rinnessy, Gutta Twins, Boosie, Lil Brod, Big Mane and the Soundchild Crew.</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - AK Bay Platinum Mike Mosley Dedication</title> 
<description>Featuring Auditory Beats, Tupac, Bone, J. Rellz, Roscoe Dash, Joe Boom, Bo deal, Ken McCoy ENT Report, Rekkless, Tavares Daize, Fokis, Cons, Chill-ILL, Wyze Sonz, Boss Hogg, Pocahontas, Spice 1, Big Maine, Collard Green and Lil Brod.  Underground hip hop countdown.</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Wed, 8 Dec 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 
</channel> 
</rss>