<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <channel> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - Nitro Edition</title> 
<description>The new Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show, powered by M3 Records, provides listeners with various forms of entertainment ranging from theatrical audio productions of every genre of music to stimulating, precise, unscripted word schemes and critiques from the host, MaD MaxHeat. Listeners are guaranteed to receive the entertainment they come consistently to see. Nitro Edition also broadcasts marketing tips and industry interviews and spoken word. Entertainment news is supplied by The Ken McCoy Entertainment Report in California. The PG 13 show has a strong hip hop origin. No one wants to see you shine. But that is what makes the story behind the music. I was told at my first real recording session that some lines I said were at the pro level. Now everything I say is Pro Flow stated MaD MaXxx.</description>
<link>http://www.proflowradio.com</link> 
<copyright>Copyright 2001</copyright> 
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs> 
<language>en</language> 
<atom:link href="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2009 01:44:39 -0500</lastBuildDate> 
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 01:31:51 -0500</pubDate> 
<webMaster>mm@maxheat.com (MaD MaXxx)</webMaster>
<generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.9) unlicensed version http://www.feedforall.com</generator> 
<itunes:subtitle>ProFlowRadio.com</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>The Internet's Audible Hot Spot hosted by MaD MaXxx.  Come check out the Underground Sound Hip Hop Countdown!!</itunes:summary> 
<itunes:image href="http://www.maxheat.com/proradio.jpg"/>
<itunes:author>Mike MaxHeat Mosley</itunes:author> 
 <itunes:owner> 
<itunes:name>Mike Mosley</itunes:name> 
<itunes:email>mm@maxheat.com</itunes:email> 
</itunes:owner> 
<itunes:category text="Music" /> 
<itunes:category text="Technology" /> 
<itunes:keywords>mp3, free, rap, hip, hop, south, west, pop, rock, sex, butts</itunes:keywords> 
<itunes:image href="http://www.maxheat.com/proitunes.jpg" /> 
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit> 
<itunes:block>no</itunes:block> 
 <item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - Nitro</title>
<description>Non stop heat from the best Independent talent alive!  Nitro is the original Pro Flow Radio show that debuted on Akron FM radio back in 2001.  It currently broadcasts the Underground Hip Hop Top Ten Countdown.  </description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="57000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<itunes:image href="http://maxheat.com/proradio.jpg"/>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>Nitro Edition Countdown</title>
<description>Features Bigg Jigg, BOOK FEATURE JOY DEJA KING, KEN MCCOY ENT REPORT, Leji, Lil Brod Ft. Big Maine, Jigz 
Crillz, and Duece Poppi.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="59000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>Nitro Edition Countdown</title>
<description>Check out the New show hosted by MaxHeat featuring Tim Benson, Jeezy, Ken McCoy, Lon Meezy, Dante Frost, Tifanii, Warren G, new music from Sade and many more!</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Thur, 17 Dec 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>Nitro Edition New Countdown Show</title>
<description>This new show is for lovers.  Featuring the music of Urban Mystic, Virginia Ashby, BG, Dave Vegas, Kevin Cossom, Jigz Crillz, Jadakiss, Fly Academ, Fospassin, Ruben Studdard, Marcus Elias, Streetz, Mr Will, King Solomon, Bohagan and the KEN McCoy Ent Report.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 


<item> 
<title>Nitro Edition New Countdown Show</title>
<description>Featuring the music of 4IZE, Ludacris, Chingy, Chris DeShield, Feddy, Young Dro, Jim Jones, Chubbie Baby, Rick Ross, DEL HARRISON, KAREEM GREEN, KBoo, yung gutta mane, South Paw, mc lYte, Boss Hogg, Wyze Sonz, MaxHeat, Syndrome, Daz Dillinger, Tavares Daize, One Dose,	Acafool, Dahlia Wakefield, Roscoe, and REKKLESS.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>Nitro Edition Show</title>
<description>Featuring the music of Lucky, Nai, Mississippi, Sammy Smash, Mack Memphis, Rosco, Nicki Minaj, Get Money Girlz, Teezy, Yo Gotti, A-PINKS, Doeboy, Souf n Gutta and J Mill.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>Pro Flow fa-Sho Show Nitro Edition</title>
<description>Hot show with Maxheat, Y.G. from Def Jam, Grind Season All Stars, Jae Millz, Preacher And P, DJ Leggs and Benzino.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 


<item> 
<title>G-Zone 88 Remixtape Showcase Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show</title> 
<description>Special 102.5 Rebel Radio Debut for London featuring P Town Moe, Blaq, Estevan, Andrew Davis, King, Ghostface, Raekwon, Twista, Gorrilla Zoe, Styles P, 4-Ize, J La P, Syndrome, Bossolo and More!</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2011 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 


<item> 
<title>RnB Latin Edition - The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show</title> 
<description>Featuring your host Maxheat and the Pro Flow All Stars such as Ms Sorel, Lisa Banton, Alexandra Bachelier, Carley C, Charlene Rennee and Lil Keke, Miguel, Elu, Jesse Johnson, Honey Brown, Bobby V, Papa Reu, Don Cali and Sade. </description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rnb.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rnb.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 


 <item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - AK Bay Platinum Mike Mosley Dedication</title> 
<description>Featuring Auditory Beats, Tupac, Bone, J. Rellz, Roscoe Dash, Joe Boom, Bo deal, Ken McCoy ENT Report, Rekkless, Tavares Daize, Fokis, Cons, Chill-ILL, Wyze Sonz, Boss Hogg, Pocahontas, Spice 1, Big Maine, Collard Green and Lil Brod.  Underground hip hop countdown.</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Wed, 8 Dec 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - G-Zone 88 Edition 1</title> 
<description>Pro Flow Radio is searching for the World's finest up and coming independent musicians and artists to  spice up the bland major radio music scene. Do you have it? Do you have Pro Flow? Send in your mixtape or remix tracks, and join us as we expose the truth about who's hotter in the industry.  If you tweak and freak remixes to major industry tracks, then you must be featured on this new G-Zone 88 radio show.  Upload your music here: http://upload.proflowradio.com.  All submissions are permitted.  No matter whether you have only one verse or no chorus, your audio will still be played on the G-Zone 88 show. This radio showcase is strictly for mixtapes and remixes of every genre.  So go ahead and mack like that's your track, subtract the wack and we will see if you are destined for platinum wax.  Rise like cream to the top with G-Zone88.  Become great!  No hate, but are you really better than them? G-Zone 88 is the home base so send your tape, make your case and let the fans decide if you are better than other industry tracks.  Jack a track like Jesse James, hold em up and holler back.  You know the code.  It's pro flow fa-sho.  Let them know that you are better than them.  The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show can be heard on www.proflowradio.com, www.maxheat.com, www.isonliveradio.com ZFM Digital, www.luver.com, Itunes, radio-freedom.com, maxheat.podomatic.com and Radio Indie Rock.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="59000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - G-Zone 88 Edition 3</title> 
<description>New show features the music of DV Alias Khryst, CHI, 4IZE, Young Za, La Femme Nikita, Congo, Lisa Banton, Brandy Li, Lordroc, Arenbee, J Nyce, Morris Fly, MaxHeat, Busta Rhymes, Taylorman, OSo Krispie and many more. </description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="59000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Tues, 10 Nov 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - G-Zone 88 Edition 4</title> 
<description>Join us as we jam to the flaming blazing tracks of Chilly C. the Paperchaser, Mark Morrison ft. DMX, Eastwood and Mr. Kane, Spice 1, Bigg Jigg, ANCOSA ADAH, Maxheat, Gurilla Myke, Kanye, Drake, Dodigatie feat. Slimm Calhoun, Rick Ross ft. Chrisette Michele, Ludacris ft. Rick Ross, Twista, 4IZE, Senor Kaos, Punchlin, Miss Nana  feat Angel Inez, Sonja Blade, Red Hot Boyz feat Yo Gotti, Tavares Daize, Auditory, Bone Thugs ft. Tupac, Eleven, ENOT.  Awesome show for real.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="61000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Sat, 6 Feb 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item>


<item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - G-Zone 88 Edition 5</title> 
<description>New Miss Cash Interview ft. DJ BLAZITA, Miss Cash, ELEVE, SoundChild Crew, T.I, .Maxheat, South Paw, Conrizzle, La Femme Nikita, LeVar Thomas, DoeBoy, Trey Songz, Bo Nasty and Busta Rhymes.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Tues, 4 May 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 


<item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - G-Zone 88</title> 
<description>Fire and Brimstone Mixtape free download http://www.maxheat.com/audio/brimstone/fire.html</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/brimstone/partone.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/brimstone/partone.mp3.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - G-Zone 88</title> 
<description>Featuring KRS One, Soullow, Kelo, Atrain, Nicki Minaj, Bigg Jigg, Soulja Boy, Drake, Rick Ross, LeVar Thomas, Red Hot Boys, Yo Gotti, Jaelife, Will I Am, Taylorman and Gucci, Ruff Ryders.  Remixtape Showcase Underground countdown.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/Luver1-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Wed, 8 Dec 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show</title> 
<description>Come and let MaD MaXxx reset the standard.  Me Gusta I Like It, Assassin LATIN GIRL ft. Nate Dog, Selena I Got A Feelin Jus Bus Nikoshouse Carnival Remi, Isis Yasmeen feat. G.A.J guage fall n love, Doza Puro Vida Latina, Kahlee Make Me Say, K Jazz Can't Keep a Sista Down</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rnb.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rnb.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 
<item> 
<title>RnB Latin Edition - The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show</title> 
<description>Featuring Lisa Banton, CHI, 1920, Carley, JaShayla, Range, Victoria Acosta, ENOT, Angel Demar, Sade, Charlene Renne, Chis Brown and I 15.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rnb.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rnb.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 
<item> 
<title>RnB Latin Edition - The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show</title> 
<description>Featuring Selena, Ms kandi, Mike Jackson, Kama Linden, Xplicit, Ahmad Belvin, R Kelly, Mizz Nina, Colby ODonis, Miguel, Kool and the Gang, Beckwith, Kristine Mirelle, Albert Gates, Aaron Wright, Mario and Stevie T.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rnb.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rnb.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - AK Bay Platinum</title> 
<description>Tune In Now for the raw west coast radio show dedicated to the music of Cali platinum producer Mike Mosley and hosted by Ohio's own Mike Mosley a.k.a. MaxHeat. The playlist will include music from Tupac, T.R.O.N., Miss Nana, E40, Bossolo, Spice 1, South Circle, Tavares Daize, The Outlawz, Spiritual Thugs, Eleven, A-Pinks, Yukmouth, WC, B Legit, Mac Mall, 4IZE, Tequila, Assassin, Richie Rich and many more talented independent artists.</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="54000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - AK Bay Platinum</title> 
<description>Tune In Now to hear MC lyte, Lil Joe, Papa Duck and the FAT freestyle segment.</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="58000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - AK Bay Platinum</title> 
<description>Tune In Now to hear the Mike Mosley tribute show for the West Coast featuring TQ, Daz, Syndrome, Bossolo, Planet Rock, JoRob, Isis Yasmeen, J Money and Scott James.</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Thur, 17 Dec 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>Raekwon Interview on the Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show</title> 
<description>Dominant Wu-Tang member Raekwon the Chef gives MaxHeat an exclusive lifetime achievement scoop.  Don't be the last to hear history in progress!</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/audio-intvw/ProFlowRadio-Raekwon-show-clean.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/audio-intvw/ProFlowRadio-Raekwon-show-clean.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Tues, 2 Mar 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - AK Bay Platinum</title> 
<description>Featuring Rick Ross, Mad Max, Raekwon, Will Spitwell, Tavares Daize, E40, Kandy Guryl, Mz Nicky, Krate Krusaders, Preacher, Rinnessy, Gutta Twins, Boosie, Lil Brod, Big Mane and the Soundchild Crew.</description> <enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/MM-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 
<item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - Rock Edition</title> 
<description>Look out for the next rock show right now!  Prepare to hear all kinds of rock hybrid music.  Artists from every continent send in great music, and you might hear the next superstar before they blow up!  What do you expect from the best radio podcast in the Universe. If you think another station has better music and interviews, then come and let MaD MaXxx reset the standard.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rock.mp3" length="54000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rock.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - Rock Edition - Minotaur Records Feature</title> 
<description>Danielle Marcus - Like Home to Me, Kevin Lee - All I Want,	RON DEAN TOMICH - Stick Around,	The Heise Bros - Don't Say Goodbye,	slombardi - young N sTUPID, Selena - Girlfriend remix,	Mutant Radio - Ghetto Rock, DOUG MAGPIONG - If You're Here, Youth Medium - What_That_Girl Has, Three Birds by The Junch, J Priest - Gypsy, Katie Todd - Face Down, Letters From the Front - Foolish Fear,	All Mighty Whispers - Mighty Whispers, Animate Objects - El Dorado, OVERSEAS FEATURE.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rock.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rock.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 


<item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - Rock Edition - Post Florida</title> 
<description>Join us as MaxHeat rocks out to Michael Stollaire Just Like Yesterday, Vendetta Valentine Let It Burn, Spiritual Machine, DUTCH DEFOE, Tequila, kool up gang, Inner Surge, Allison Thrash, Andrew Ceglio, Planet Rock, Greg Aaron, Spriyt and much more.  This is the first show since the 2010 Chairs Scholas event and Florida performance.  Features the Ken McCoy Ent Report too.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rock.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/ProFlowRadio-rock.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Mon, 5 Apr 2010 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - Paragon 360</title>
<description>Top Seven Countdown. The best banquet being served on the internet, land radio or satellite is prepared by the chef's at Millennium Music Mission records. The independent trail blazers are still turning up the heat and cooking up a delectable cuisine of talent from all over the world. M3 has delivered to the world artists from the Americas, Europe, Canada, Africa and now added to its 5 star menu the superb artistry from Asia. Yep those M3 execs have done it again rock, hip hop, rap, RnB, J pop at your service. When you think of their next step, they come up with another table shaking idea to spice and kick it up a notch, you know! The bar has been raised in the culinary art of music radio. </description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/proflowradio/ProFlowRadio-paragon.mp3" length="57000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/proflowradio/ProFlowRadio-paragon.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 01:30:31 EST</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - Paragon 360</title>
<description>Top Seven Countdown. Black Eyed Peas, X Japan, Asian Soda Pop Girls, De La Soul and DJ Honda, Carlos Santana and Michelle Branch - I'm Feeling You, Inuyasha, Nana Kitade, Se7en Ft Lil Kim-Them Girls, Namie Amuro and many more.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/proflowradio/ProFlowRadio-paragon.mp3" length="59000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/proflowradio/ProFlowRadio-paragon.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Tues, 10 Nov 2009 01:30:31 EST</pubDate> 
</item> 


<item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - Paragon 360</title>
<description>This is another 1 hour banger that is only available here.  The show is bangin.  Check out the wu tang interview!</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/proflowradio/ProFlowRadio-paragon.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/proflowradio/ProFlowRadio-paragon.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 01:30:31 EST</pubDate> 
</item> 

<item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - Paragon 360 Edition</title>
<description>Featuring 4Minute, Jin, Dirty Money, Crystal Kay, Lin Que, Yoko Ono, Rayedan, Maxheat, Norah Jones, Se7en, Utada Hikaru, BoA, Asain Girl, Rainie Yang Cheng Lin and Arashi!</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/proflowradio/ProFlowRadio-paragon.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/proflowradio/ProFlowRadio-paragon.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 01:30:31 EST</pubDate> 
</item> 


<item> 
<title>The Pro Flow Fa-Sho Show - Paragon 360 Edition</title>
<description>Featuring Arashi, Algah RHYTHM, BoA, Nicholas Baker, 4ize, Beyonce, April Oneil, Gino Mack, Mad Max, Kingdom Hearts, Mighty Mystic, Se7en, Lil Kim, Crystal Kay, Nick Hagelin and Redman.</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/proflowradio/ProFlowRadio-paragon.mp3" length="60000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/proflowradio/ProFlowRadio-paragon.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 01:30:31 EST</pubDate> 
</item> 

 <item> 
<title>Flashback Episode 104 - Nitro Edition</title>
<description>Tune in to hear a classic flashback radio show featuring true Pro Flow All Stars.  Nitro is the original Pro Flow Radio show that debuted on Akron FM radio back in 2001. This episode is archived as a 2006 broadcast with explicit lyrics rated R parent advisory. </description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3" length="59000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<link>http://www.maxheat.com/live.html</link> 
<itunes:image href="http://maxheat.com/proradio.jpg"/>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.maxheat.com/audio/nitro-ProFlowRadio.mp3</guid> 
<pubDate>Tues, 22 Mar 2011 01:30:31 -0500</pubDate> 
</item> 

</channel> 
</rss>