<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
  <channel>
    <title>MrHun In'a Blenda - Mix Tape Series</title>
    <link>http://jackumentory.podomatic.com</link>
    <description>MrHun Bio


MrHuns&#8217; fascination for the art of DJ&#8217;in began back in the mid to late 80&#8217;s at the height of the acid house revolution that was sweeping London and the rest of the UK. It was from listening to London&#8217;s pirate radio scene that was championing the an underground sound that played a massive part in his influence to music; which encouraged him at such a young age to buy records from his local high street vinyl specialist in his home of Tottenham, London. It wasn&#8217;t until around 91/92 when he started to attend warehouse parties himself that started the transition to become a DJ by watching some of the worlds now famous dj&#8217;s such as, Carl Cox, Tony Humphries, Jazzy M, Evil Eddie Richards, Terry Francis, Mr C, Kenny Ken, Jumpin&#8217; Jack Frost, Nicky Blackmarket, Frankie Feliciano just to name a few.
After a short time learning his record collection and with the guidance of his peers, he was given his first exposure under the moniker of Killa Hun, by the owners of Roller Express/Pirates Club for a fortnightly under 18&#8217;s event where he supported guest DJ&#8217;s such as The Rat Pack, Kenny Ken, SL2 etc etc. After a short stint doing this, the roller express was closed down and this left him a little lost and without direction as the sound that was dominating at the time was Jungle and Drum n Bass, and with this not being his bag and being a teenager, he begin to look at other avenues which got him in to trouble.
Still influenced by the Pirate Radio scene, a 2nd wave of house music started to influence the airwaves around 94/95. This rekindled his passion for buying music and in turn, MrHun, invested in his first pair of direct drive turntables, Sound Lab DL3&#8217;s, and set about perfecting his art. It was the next few years after where things really picked up as while out on his weekly mission to all his favourite vinyl stores he began to get offered gigs playin at student parties, squat parties, and holding down residencies at bars and clubs in and around London&#8217;s&#8217; surrounding counties under the DJ name of Nicky Santoro, playin his beloved 4x4 house and garage music.
Circa 2000 he was introduced to now long time friends SmokinGroove, who took him under their wing and introduced him to a collective of DJ&#8217;s, producers and promoters at DreemTeem&#8217;s legendary studios magic studios in Tottenham. This brought about a new world and more gigs and residencies under his DJ names of MrHun and Nicky Santoro; the beauty of this being that both are alter egos and project a different sound of house depending on the vibe of the party. After holding down a couple of residencies and spending many sleepless nights in studios  and serious partying for a couple of years, MrHun and close friends, Will Simms (The Lone Monkey) and Marko B (SmokinGroove), collaborated musically and collectively to create Not.So.French Records in 2003. The label released 2 official EP&#8217;s and 1 white label during its time, along with holding down a venue in Bristol for its monthly label parties.
In 2006 MrHun and Will Simms travelled to the Winter Music Conference in Miami to promote the labels extensive catalogue and to check out the scene. During this time, MrHun again, was inspired from the experience by meeting and talking to some of his all time favourite DJ&#8217;s, producers and label owners. This led to a change that, on his return to the UK, went on to inspire the Jackumentory Brand and the MrHun in&#8217;a Blend&#8217;a mix tape series. A year later MrHun met and established a strong friendship with DJ Camouflage (ChicagoHouseFM) and joined him in his mission by taking a radio show on his underground house music station, ChicagoHouseFM. 
MrHun has been pushing the house sound &#8211; weekly &#8211; to people all over the world for 2 yrs on ChicagoHouseFM making him one the longest running hosts on the station with his &#8220;Jackumentory Experience&#8221; radio show.  His show is about everything that involves House Music i.e.: acid, tribal, funky, deep house, etc, which best reflects his In&#8217;a Blend&#8217;a style creating a journey into all things house past and present.  Of course, when your first DJ experience at a very tender age of 14 yrs. old is Tony Humphries; you automatically know that you&#8217;re in for no ordinary ride. His insight, drive and passion when it comes to keeping this side of House Music alive, is an illustration into just why he&#8217;ll never stop. This gives MrHun the edge when commanding the decks by the clear reaction the crowd has as soon as he drops that first track, as he has the ability to be a versatile DJ by channelling his life&#8217;s journey into every beat of every set. 
To be continued....

</description>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <generator>podOmatic RSS Generator</generator>
    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 23:32:29 GMT</pubDate>
    <itunes:keywords>jackumentory,jackumentory-experience,mrhun,mrhun-jackumentory</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>MrHun-Jackumentory</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Mr Hun</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>jackumentory@googlemail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
    <itunes:image href="http://assets.podomatic.net/mymedia/thumb/1197369/600x600_1951577.jpg"/>
    <itunes:author>Mr Hun</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>MrHun Bio


MrHuns&#8217; fascination for the art of DJ&#8217;in began back in the mid to late 80&#8217;s at the height of the acid house revolution that was sweeping London and the rest of the UK. It was from listening to London&#8217;s pirate radio scene that was championing the an underground sound that played a massive part in his influence to music; which encouraged him at such a young age to buy records from his local high street vinyl specialist in his home of Tottenham, London. It wasn&#8217;t until around 91/92 when he started to attend warehouse parties himself that started the transition to become a DJ by watching some of the worlds now famous dj&#8217;s such as, Carl Cox, Tony Humphries, Jazzy M, Evil Eddie Richards, Terry Francis, Mr C, Kenny Ken, Jumpin&#8217; Jack Frost, Nicky Blackmarket, Frankie Feliciano just to name a few.
After a short time learning his record collection and with the guidance of his peers, he was given his first exposure under the moniker of Killa Hun, by the owners of Roller Express/Pirates Club for a fortnightly under 18&#8217;s event where he supported guest DJ&#8217;s such as The Rat Pack, Kenny Ken, SL2 etc etc. After a short stint doing this, the roller express was closed down and this left him a little lost and without direction as the sound that was dominating at the time was Jungle and Drum n Bass, and with this not being his bag and being a teenager, he begin to look at other avenues which got him in to trouble.
Still influenced by the Pirate Radio scene, a 2nd wave of house music started to influence the airwaves around 94/95. This rekindled his passion for buying music and in turn, MrHun, invested in his first pair of direct drive turntables, Sound Lab DL3&#8217;s, and set about perfecting his art. It was the next few years after where things really picked up as while out on his weekly mission to all his favourite vinyl stores he began to get offered gigs playin at student parties, squat parties, and holding down residencies at bars and clubs in and around London&#8217;s&#8217; surrounding counties under the DJ name of Nicky Santoro, playin his beloved 4x4 house and garage music.
Circa 2000 he was introduced to now long time friends SmokinGroove, who took him under their wing and introduced him to a collective of DJ&#8217;s, producers and promoters at DreemTeem&#8217;s legendary studios magic studios in Tottenham. This brought about a new world and more gigs and residencies under his DJ names of MrHun and Nicky Santoro; the beauty of this being that both are alter egos and project a different sound of house depending on the vibe of the party. After holding down a couple of residencies and spending many sleepless nights in studios  and serious partying for a couple of years, MrHun and close friends, Will Simms (The Lone Monkey) and Marko B (SmokinGroove), collaborated musically and collectively to create Not.So.French Records in 2003. The label released 2 official EP&#8217;s and 1 white label during its time, along with holding down a venue in Bristol for its monthly label parties.
In 2006 MrHun and Will Simms travelled to the Winter Music Conference in Miami to promote the labels extensive catalogue and to check out the scene. During this time, MrHun again, was inspired from the experience by meeting and talking to some of his all time favourite DJ&#8217;s, producers and label owners. This led to a change that, on his return to the UK, went on to inspire the Jackumentory Brand and the MrHun in&#8217;a Blend&#8217;a mix tape series. A year later MrHun met and established a strong friendship with DJ Camouflage (ChicagoHouseFM) and joined him in his mission by taking a radio show on his underground house music station, ChicagoHouseFM. 
MrHun has been pushing the house sound &#8211; weekly &#8211; to people all over the world for 2 yrs on ChicagoHouseFM making him one the longest running hosts on the station with his &#8220;Jackumentory Experience&#8221; radio show.  His show is about everything that involves House Music i.e.: acid, tribal, funky, deep house, etc, which best reflects his In&#8217;a Blend&#8217;a (continued)</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:category text="Music"/>
    <atom:link type="application/rss+xml" rel="self" href="http://jackumentory.podomatic.com/rss2.xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>MrHun In'a Blend'a Vol5 - All I Hear</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;http://assets.podomatic.net/mymedia/thumb/1197369/600x600_2932445.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;itunes pic&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jackumentory.podomatic.com/entry/2010-05-03T14_46_59-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://jackumentory.podomatic.com/entry/2010-05-03T14_46_59-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2010 20:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2010-05-03</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2010-05-03</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://jackumentory.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Mr Hun</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>acidhouse,deephouse,djmix,funkyhouse,housemix,in'a-blend'a,jackinhouse,mixtape,mrhun</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="51031562" url="http://jackumentory.podomatic.com/enclosure/2010-05-03T14_46_59-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:image href="http://assets.podomatic.net/mymedia/thumb/1197369/600x600_2932445.jpg"/>
      <itunes:duration>4252</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary></itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Jackumentory Experience | MrHun in'a Blend'a Vol4 - Against All The Odds</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;http://assets.podomatic.net/mymedia/thumb/1197369/600x600_2534247.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;itunes pic&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hello There!

Due to a number of technical issue's prior to and during my show, I had to abandon putting out the podcast. So, in its place I thought I would push my lastest mix for the just for a short time only.

So The Mix....

I've had this mix in the pipeline for sometime, in fact the last 3 -4 months.... I work on a mix 5-6 times a week, and some are good and others just dont feel right.... Not that I don't like the music I have, but for me, there are always a couple of tracks that I keep swapping in and out, and then I end up going for a classic to replace and then eventually I just drop the lot and let the music take control.... Thats what the MrHun In'A Blend'a series is fundamentally about.... For Vol4, I went for something new and something old and there were quite a few tracks that I wanted to include but I think I can get the message across with what I have put together..... So if you know the title of the tracks playin played, tag it and make the playlist for anyone else who wants to know.... Sharing is caring after all ;)

As for the intro, well, its a classic scene from national lampoons cult classic Animal House, the original college boy mischief and mayhem film that many have followed..... But when faced with adversity, as these guys where, you can sit there and look at things, and think how? and why? and also what now? because everything looks bleek and at an end, when in reality you can get up and do something about it and rebel to hit back to keep things going and alive.... Sound Famailiar, well, I can certainly say that I've felt the pinch over the last few years, and have at times thought that i have it all stacked up against me and the odds aren't looking to great! This is my way of sayin you know, FTP! It aint happening, house music lives and has so much more to give, and I have to give back.... because you only fail if you give up!

I hope you enjoy the mix.... Take care!

Rice n Beans!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jackumentory.podomatic.com/entry/2010-01-16T10_39_57-08_00</guid>
      <comments>http://jackumentory.podomatic.com/entry/2010-01-16T10_39_57-08_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2010 16:53:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2010-01-16</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2010-01-16</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://jackumentory.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Mr Hun</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>bounce,bumpty,chicago,club,dance,deep,experience,funky,hawt,house,jackin,jackumentory,jackumentory-experience,mrhun,mrhun-jackumentory,mrhunjackumentory,music,newyork,sistastroke,smokingroove,soulful</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="113781136" url="http://jackumentory.podomatic.com/enclosure/2010-01-16T10_39_57-08_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:image href="http://assets.podomatic.net/mymedia/thumb/1197369/600x600_2534247.jpg"/>
      <itunes:duration>4740</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>Hello There!

Due to a number of technical issue's prior to and during my show, I had to abandon putting out the podcast. So, in its place I thought I would push my lastest mix for the just for a short time only.

So The Mix....

I've had this mix in the pipeline for sometime, in fact the last 3 -4 months.... I work on a mix 5-6 times a week, and some are good and others just dont feel right.... Not that I don't like the music I have, but for me, there are always a couple of tracks that I keep swapping in and out, and then I end up going for a classic to replace and then eventually I just drop the lot and let the music take control.... Thats what the MrHun In'A Blend'a series is fundamentally about.... For Vol4, I went for something new and something old and there were quite a few tracks that I wanted to include but I think I can get the message across with what I have put together..... So if you know the title of the tracks playin played, tag it and make the playlist for anyone else who wants to know.... Sharing is caring after all ;)

As for the intro, well, its a classic scene from national lampoons cult classic Animal House, the original college boy mischief and mayhem film that many have followed..... But when faced with adversity, as these guys where, you can sit there and look at things, and think how? and why? and also what now? because everything looks bleek and at an end, when in reality you can get up and do something about it and rebel to hit back to keep things going and alive.... Sound Famailiar, well, I can certainly say that I've felt the pinch over the last few years, and have at times thought that i have it all stacked up against me and the odds aren't looking to great! This is my way of sayin you know, FTP! It aint happening, house music lives and has so much more to give, and I have to give back.... because you only fail if you give up!

I hope you enjoy the mix.... Take care!

Rice n Beans!</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackumentory - aNyO Special - Live in'a Blend'a</title>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;http://assets.podomatic.net/mymedia/thumb/1197369/600x600_2432817.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;itunes pic&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have a special guest joining us LIVE in the mix for this weeks Show... We have Australian House beater Anyo Castro throwing down a full session of all things house!

A little about the man him self&#8230;.
Pronounced ahnjo not ennio or anne yo!! is one of Melbourne's most sought after DJ's. Spinning a mix of Jackin, Chicago and soulful house, fused with pop and funk, has been playing to Melbourne's club scene for around7-8years &amp; constantly plays guests spots around Australia. Has supported some of the biggest names in HouseMusic, is an integral part of most underground house events in Melbourne, continues to hold a plethora of residencies at clubs both here in Melbourne and interstate. aNyO has releases on a number of the biggest underground house record labels worldwide also under the alias of Jack Castro Labels such as Hijack(AUS),Herbal Essence(USA),Aroma recordings new sub label ASecondSmell(BELGIUM),Alphabet music (USA),) Guess Who (USA),1200 TRAXX(USA) Exit Enterprises (USA) ,and currently has one of his tracks that he remixed for Greenhouse Recordings(USA) on The House of Om Summer Sessions CD mixed by Dj Heather and Onionz. His mixes and tracks are played by the worlds most renowned DJ's including Derrick Carter, DJ Heather, DJSneak, Paul Johnson ,The Sound Republic, Ken(Eascoast Boogiemen) Raoul Belmans (Swirl People), GIOM, Bobby&amp;Klein, James Curd(Greens keepers), EXIT, 1200 Warriors, Bryan Jones, Lamanex, Slater Hogan, John Larner, Honey Dijon and many more. Had also had his tracks remixed by Tigersprouts aka Swirl People , also Bobby&amp;Klein. also has a weekly show on KissFM (87.6FM) or ( http://www.kissfm.com.au ) under the name DumbCant Radio and can be heard every Thursday at 8 till 9.30pm ( AUST TIME ZONE ),has resedencies all over melbourne, including Tramp Saturdays (3til5am) and constantly plays at the renowned Eletric Circus (LIMBO)in Adelaide every few months , And also flies off to New Zealand to stir it up in kiwi land at the infamous Beats royale and parties.
So...If you want underground house in melbourne then look no further...
The show starts at 9pm GMT and carries through to the hour of 11pm&#8230;

Don&#8217;t forget you can catch Brick City House w/ hostess Sista Stroke and guest Gracie Chavez houseworking it! Show starts at 7pm and continues until 9pm&#8230;.

And then @ 11pm you have DJ Buddha, a kid who I happen to think is the future of house music&#8230;. The kid has skills and a wealth of music that would impress even the most seasoned connoisseur of house music&#8230;. It&#8217;s worth staryin up for!

All this LIVE on www.chicagohousefm.com &#8230; the station with house music for house heads!

See you tonight!

Rice and Beans

MrHun</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jackumentory.podomatic.com/entry/2009-12-11T04_11_02-08_00</guid>
      <comments>http://jackumentory.podomatic.com/entry/2009-12-11T04_11_02-08_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 17:36:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2009-12-11</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2009-12-10</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://jackumentory.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Mr Hun</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>anyocastro,chicagohouse,deephouse,housemusic,jackinhouse,jackumentory,jackumentory-experience,mrhun,mrhun-jackumentory,mrhunjackumentory,sistastroke,smokingroove</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="221237499" url="http://jackumentory.podomatic.com/enclosure/2009-12-11T04_11_02-08_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:image href="http://assets.podomatic.net/mymedia/thumb/1197369/600x600_2432817.jpg"/>
      <itunes:duration>6913</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>We have a special guest joining us LIVE in the mix for this weeks Show... We have Australian House beater Anyo Castro throwing down a full session of all things house!

A little about the man him self&#8230;.
Pronounced ahnjo not ennio or anne yo!! is one of Melbourne's most sought after DJ's. Spinning a mix of Jackin, Chicago and soulful house, fused with pop and funk, has been playing to Melbourne's club scene for around7-8years &amp; constantly plays guests spots around Australia. Has supported some of the biggest names in HouseMusic, is an integral part of most underground house events in Melbourne, continues to hold a plethora of residencies at clubs both here in Melbourne and interstate. aNyO has releases on a number of the biggest underground house record labels worldwide also under the alias of Jack Castro Labels such as Hijack(AUS),Herbal Essence(USA),Aroma recordings new sub label ASecondSmell(BELGIUM),Alphabet music (USA),) Guess Who (USA),1200 TRAXX(USA) Exit Enterprises (USA) ,and currently has one of his tracks that he remixed for Greenhouse Recordings(USA) on The House of Om Summer Sessions CD mixed by Dj Heather and Onionz. His mixes and tracks are played by the worlds most renowned DJ's including Derrick Carter, DJ Heather, DJSneak, Paul Johnson ,The Sound Republic, Ken(Eascoast Boogiemen) Raoul Belmans (Swirl People), GIOM, Bobby&amp;Klein, James Curd(Greens keepers), EXIT, 1200 Warriors, Bryan Jones, Lamanex, Slater Hogan, John Larner, Honey Dijon and many more. Had also had his tracks remixed by Tigersprouts aka Swirl People , also Bobby&amp;Klein. also has a weekly show on KissFM (87.6FM) or ( http://www.kissfm.com.au ) under the name DumbCant Radio and can be heard every Thursday at 8 till 9.30pm ( AUST TIME ZONE ),has resedencies all over melbourne, including Tramp Saturdays (3til5am) and constantly plays at the renowned Eletric Circus (LIMBO)in Adelaide every few months , And also flies off to New Zealand to stir it up in kiwi land at the infamous Beats royale and parties.
So...If you want underground house in melbourne then look no further...
The show starts at 9pm GMT and carries through to the hour of 11pm&#8230;

Don&#8217;t forget you can catch Brick City House w/ hostess Sista Stroke and guest Gracie Chavez houseworking it! Show starts at 7pm and continues until 9pm&#8230;.

And then @ 11pm you have DJ Buddha, a kid who I happen to think is the future of house music&#8230;. The kid has skills and a wealth of music that would impress even the most seasoned connoisseur of house music&#8230;. It&#8217;s worth staryin up for!

All this LIVE on www.chicagohousefm.com &#8230; the station with house music for house heads!

See you tonight!

Rice and Beans

MrHun</itunes:summary>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
