<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>JPFO Talkin&apos; to America</title>
        <description>JPFO proudly introduces &quot;Talkin&apos; to America&quot;, a periodical series of provocative, hard-hitting interviews on topics related to gun rights and freedom in America.</description>
        <link>http://www.jpfo.org/filegen-n-z/talkamerica.htm</link>
        <copyright>2005</copyright>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 16:24:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 16:24:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <ttl>1</ttl>
        <webMaster>webmaster@jpfo.org(Chris)</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.3.1) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <item>
            <title>JPFO’s Executive Director Charles Heller on Armed Armed American Radio.</title>
            <description>Charles talks 2A matters with Mark Walters of  Armed American Radio, while returning on Monday Sept 26th from the weekend Chicago Gun Rights Policy Conference.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The link supplied is to the sound file itself - or go direct to the Talkin&apos; to America page.  - http://www.jpfo.org/filegen-n-z/talkamerica.htm where there is a player option also.</description>
            <link>http://jpfo.org/media-sound2/heller-walters-s32.mp3</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">04A2EEDC-7606-4D25-9048-ACA557314768</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 17:54:04 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Talkin&apos; to America: Charles Heller speaks about &quot;Project GunWalker&quot;</title>
            <description>Charles Heller, on his Liberty Watch Radio talks about his analysis of BATFE&apos;s &quot;Operation Fast &amp; Furious,&quot; which has turned into &quot;Project GunWalker,&quot; supplying guns used in Mexico to murder, including one U.S. Agent, and probably there&apos;ll be another.</description>
            <link>http://jpfo.org/media-sound2/heller-gunwalker-6-19-11-43.mp3</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C8A57BFD-C478-4FBA-B6C2-BCB3F6FBA832</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 23:17:12 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Talkin&apos; to America: Charles Heller speaks on Radio KCAA, California</title>
            <description>Kevin Shannon on KCAA out of California talks to Charles Heller, Executive Director of JPFO, who discusses the new frontiers of JPFO, constitutional carry in Arizona and how it came about, and his status as a political refugee from Mayor Daley&apos;s gun ban.</description>
            <link>http://jpfo.org/media-sound2/heller-kcaa-20110618.mp3</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">AE79CA11-845E-41A8-8ED2-1B35171DC71B</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 23:14:13 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
