<?xml version="1.0"?>


<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	<channel>

<title>AAFP Podcasts: AAFP News Now</title>
<link>http://www.aafp.org/online/en/home/publications/news/news-now/aboutann/podcast.html</link>
<description>Rely on podcasts from AAFP News Now, the family physician's trusted source for news, for information about issues important to family physicians, family medicine residents, and medical students interested in family medicine.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2012 American Academy of Family Physicians</copyright>
<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
<itunes:owner>
	<itunes:name>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:name>
	<itunes:email>fp@aafp.org</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:image href="http://www.aafp.org/podcastimage/AAFP_logo300.jpg" />


<itunes:category text="Science &amp; Medicine" >
	<itunes:category text="Medicine" />
</itunes:category>

<itunes:category text="Government &amp; Organizations" >
	<itunes:category text="Non-Profit" />
</itunes:category>

<itunes:category text="Science &amp; Medicine" />

		<item>
			<title>ANN Weekly Podcast - Friday, Dec. 23, 2011</title> 
			<description>This week's audio news summary features a story about a bipartisan graduate medical education bill introduced in the House that would establish a pilot project to test and support primary care training models in nonhospital settings; an announcement from CMS about a demonstration project that will test the effectiveness of delivering primary care services in a home setting to Medicare patients with multiple chronic conditions; notification that the FDA has called for a risk evaluation and mitigation strategy for the oral anticoagulant drug marketed as Xarelto; and a reminder that physicians who did not implement electronic prescribing in 2011 will receive slightly lower Medicare payments in 2012.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 12:05:00 CST</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly122311.Par.0001.File.tmp/122311.mp3" length="4706694" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly122311.Par.0001.File.tmp/122311.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>ANN Weekly Podcast - Friday, Dec. 16, 2011</title> 
			<description>This week's audio news summary features a story about HHS blocking over-the-counter access to an emergency contraceptive for girls younger than 17; an announcement from CMS regarding a three-month delay in the enforcement deadline for physicians' transition to the version 5010 format for the electronic transfer of health information; coverage of the dedication of the first cell-based influenza vaccine manufacturing plant in the United States; notification about a decrease in state funding for community health centers in 2012; and an announcement about a new CDC campaign that focuses on medication safety for children.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly121611.Par.0001.File.tmp/annweekly121611.mp3" length="5417866" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly121611.Par.0001.File.tmp/annweekly121611.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>ANN Weekly Podcast - Friday, Dec. 9, 2011</title> 
			<description>This week's audio news summary features an announcement that the 2012 update of the ICD-10-CM codes set for outpatient diagnosis coding has been posted online for reference and training purposes; a reminder to physicians about the importance of immunizing pregnant and postpartum women against seasonal influenza; an update on Medicare coverage for obesity screening and counseling; notification about the launch of a new social media site that allows physicians to share their experiences implementing health information technology; a story about an FDA committee vote to expand the age indication for the 13-valent pneumococcal conjugate vaccine; and information about a new curriculum package on chronic obstructive pulmonary disease that is available free to all AAFP members. </description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly120911.Par.0001.File.tmp/120911annweekly.mp3" length="5866608" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly120911.Par.0001.File.tmp/120911annweekly.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>ANN Weekly Podcast - Friday, Dec. 02, 2011</title> 
			<description>This week's audio news summary features an announcement about the nomination of Marilyn Tavenner to replace outgoing CMS Administrator Donald Berwick, M.D.; a reminder that medical students have until Dec. 14 to complete applications for the Students to Service Loan Repayment Program; notification about the release of an AAFP Foundation report on behavioral economics and management of patients with diabetes; information about a new screening guide to help doctors target teens who may need help combating alcohol abuse; and a reminder about ANN's chapter spotlight series that in December features the Kentucky AFP.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 01:05:48 CDT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly120211.Par.0001.File.tmp/annweekly120211.mp3" length="5307126" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly120211.Par.0001.File.tmp/annweekly120211.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>ANN Weekly Podcast - Friday, Nov. 18, 2011</title> 
			<description>This week's audio news summary features coverage of a study by the Accreditation Council for Graduate Medical Education that highlights the impact of cuts to GME funding now being considered by Congress' Joint Select Committee on Deficit Reduction; an announcement from the FDA about the lack of efficacy of the cholesterol-lowering medication Trilipix; notification of technical problems with two GE Healthcare health information technology products that will delay physicians' ability to attest to meaningful use for the Medicare EHR Incentive Program; an announcement about the FDA's posting on YouTube of a consumer health video about the hazards of antibiotic overuse; and a story urging physicians to continue to help patients quit smoking.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly111811.Par.0001.File.tmp/annweekly111811new.mp3" length="6422053" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly111811.Par.0001.File.tmp/annweekly111811new.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>ANN Weekly Podcast - Friday, Nov. 11, 2011</title> 
			<description>This week's audio news summary features information about a 19-page synopsis of CMS' 189-page final rule on accountable care organizations the AAFP created to give members an overview of how ACOs could affect them; a story about the Academy's call to members to help maintain Title VII primary care health professions funding; coverage of the release of three new draft recommendations by the U.S. Preventive Services Task Force; information about the AAFP's endorsement of the American College of Physicians' clinical practice guideline on the diagnosis and treatment of erectile dysfunction; a reminder from the FDA about the Nov. 17 deadline to enroll in the Avandia-Rosiglitazone Medicines Access Program; an announcement from CMS about Medicare coverage of new preventive services intended to reduce cardiovascular disease; and notification of a National Institute on Aging campaign that aims to keep adults 50 and older more active.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 01:05:48 CDT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly111111.Par.0001.File.tmp/annweekly111111.mp3" length="9357601" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly111111.Par.0001.File.tmp/annweekly111111.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>ANN Weekly Podcast - Friday, Nov. 4, 2011</title> 
			<description>This week's audio news summary features a story about findings from a new study that indicate many primary care physicians think they provide more care than is necessary to their patients; a report written by Academy staff that summarizes 2011 National Resident Matching Program statistics and 2011 survey data from U.S. residency programs; an announcement about a makeover to the AAFP's patient education website, FamilyDoctor.org; notification of the voluntary market withdrawal of the drug Xigris by Eli Lilly and Co.; and a reminder to get involved with the AAFP Leader Voices blog.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 12:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly110411.Par.0001.File.tmp/110411weeklypodcast.mp3" length="5904088" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly110411.Par.0001.File.tmp/110411weeklypodcast.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>ANN Weekly Podcast - Friday, Oct. 28, 2011</title> 
			<description>This week's audio news summary features coverage of HHS' release of the final rule on Medicare accountable care organizations; information about the CDC's Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices vote to recommend routine administration of quadrivalent human papillomavirus vaccine to 11- to 12-year-old boys; a story about the release of new research by the Medical Group Management Association that indicates physicians may begin restricting Medicare patients' access if a scheduled 29.5 percent payment cut occurs as scheduled on Jan. 1, 2012; an update about 2011 numbers of first-time applicants to medical school, which were at an all-time high; the latest installment in the Chapter Spotlight series, which features the Indiana AFP's work with the Indiana General Assembly; and a reminder to listeners to sign up to receive updates to the AAFP Leader Voices blog.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 12:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly102811.Par.0001.File.tmp/102811annweekly.mp3" length="7022950" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/2011-ann/annweekly102811.Par.0001.File.tmp/102811annweekly.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>Implementing the TransforMED Model of Care</title> 
			<description>Myrtue Medical Center in Harlan, Iowa, is one of 33 family medicine practices around the country that are in the middle of a two-year national demonstration project established by TransforMED, AAFP's practice redesign initiative. This video features a visit to Myrtue's Harlan clinic and its three satellite clinics in neighboring towns to report on the practice's progress.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2007 12:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/video/ann/transformedharlen.Par.0001.File.tmp/transformed_harlan.mp4" length="30063748" type="video/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/video/ann/transformedharlen.Par.0001.File.tmp/transformed_harlan.mp4</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>"Transitioning Into Practice," Segment 1 of 5</title> 
			<description>Family physicians new to practice share insights about the impact of malpractice insurance and reimbursement on practice selection, learning about the practice style of potential partners, and negotiating a contract and signing bonus. (Panelists are identified in this first segment.) From the National Conference of Family Medicine Residents and Medical Students, Aug. 5, 2006.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2006 03:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/podcast.Par.0001.File.tmp/01%20AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Transitioning%20Into%20Practice,_%20Segment%201%20of%205.mp3" length="8410357" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/podcast.Par.0001.File.tmp/01%20AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Transitioning%20Into%20Practice,_%20Segment%201%20of%205.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>"Transitioning Into Practice," Segment 2 of 5</title> 
			<description>Family physicians new to practice share insights about finding a position in a community clinic, the challenges and rewards of working in such a clinic, and quality improvement and electronic health records. From the National Conference of Family Medicine Residents and Medical Students, Aug. 5, 2006.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2006 03:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/podcast2.Par.0001.File.tmp/02%20AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Transitioning%20Into%20Practice,_%20Segment%202%20of%205.mp3" length="10167619" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/podcast2.Par.0001.File.tmp/02%20AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Transitioning%20Into%20Practice,_%20Segment%202%20of%205.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>"Transitioning Into Practice," Segment 3 of 5</title> 
			<description>Family physicians new to practice share insights about what residency characteristics to look for if you're interested in community clinic practice, working as a locum tenens physician to learn about practices, finding a practice with an EHR and quality improvement program, and tips on going into academic family medicine. From the National Conference of Family Medicine Residents and Medical Students, Aug. 5, 2006.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2006 03:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/transpodcast3.Par.0001.File.tmp/03%20AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Transitioning%20Into%20Practice,_%20Segment%203%20of%205.mp3" length="9208725" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/transpodcast3.Par.0001.File.tmp/03%20AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Transitioning%20Into%20Practice,_%20Segment%203%20of%205.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>"Transitioning Into Practice," Segment 4 of 5</title> 
			<description>Family physicians new to practice share insights about documenting procedures, pros and cons of single-specialty and multispecialty practices, family physicians as hospitalists, and paying back student loans. From the National Conference of Family Medicine Residents and Medical Students, Aug. 5, 2006.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2006 03:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/transpodcast4.Par.0001.File.tmp/04%20AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Transitioning%20Into%20Practice,_%20Segment%204%20of%205.mp3" length="13054764" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/transpodcast4.Par.0001.File.tmp/04%20AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Transitioning%20Into%20Practice,_%20Segment%204%20of%205.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>"Transitioning Into Practice," Segment 5 of 5</title> 
			<description>Family physicians new to practice share insights about obstetrics fellowships, faculty development fellowships and family medicine research. From the National Conference of Family Medicine Residents and Medical Students, Aug. 5, 2006. </description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2006 01:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/transsegment5.Par.0001.File.tmp/05%20AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Transitioning%20Into%20Practice,_%20Segment%205%20of%205.mp3" length="6470102" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/transsegment5.Par.0001.File.tmp/05%20AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Transitioning%20Into%20Practice,_%20Segment%205%20of%205.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 

		<item>
			<title>"Interview With Family Medicine Resident Kelly McMullen, M.D."</title> 
			<description>As a youngster, McMullen was one of the first winners in a poster contest sponsored by Tar Wars, the tobacco-free education program that now is an AAFP initiative. McMullen talks about how the contest influenced her choice of family medicine and the way she cares for patients. From the National Conference of Family Medicine Residents and Medical Students, Aug. 2, 2006.</description>
			<itunes:author>American Academy of Family Physicians</itunes:author>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 03:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/mcmullen01.Par.0001.File.tmp/AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Interview%20With%20Family%20Medicine%20Resident%20Kelly%20McMullen,%20M.D._.mp3" length="7142737" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.aafp.org/online/etc/medialib/aafp_org/media/audio/podcasts/mcmullen01.Par.0001.File.tmp/AAFP%20News%20Now%20-%20_Interview%20With%20Family%20Medicine%20Resident%20Kelly%20McMullen,%20M.D._.mp3</guid>
		</item>	 
</channel>
</rss>


