<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Parents Magazine Podcast: Tales from the trenches, must-know-info, and expert advice!</title>
<link>http://www.parents.com/parents/story.jhtml?storyid=/templatedata/parents/story/data/1153238406676.xml</link>
<description>The Parents Magazine Podcast is an internet radio show for moms and dads. Created by the editors of Parents Magazine, each episode offers tales from the trenches, must-know-info, and expert advice.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2006, Meredith Corporation</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle>The Parents Magazine Podcast is an internet radio show for moms and dads. Created by the editors of Parents Magazine, each episode offers tales from the trenches, must-know-info, and expert advice.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>The Parents Magazine Podcast is an internet radio show for moms and dads. Created by the editors of Parents Magazine, each episode offers tales from the trenches, must-know-info, and expert advice.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Mary Finer</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>mary.finer@meredith.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://images.meredith.com/parents/images/podcast.jpg" />
<itunes:category text="Kids &amp; Family"/>
<itunes:new-feed-url>http://www.parents.com/parents/podcast/parentsmagazinepodcast.rss</itunes:new-feed-url>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>


<item>
<title>Overweight Kids, Potty Training, Back-to-School, and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A discussion of the challenges of getting kids to eat right and exercise. Plus, Pediatrician Dr. Ari Brown takes calls from parents and answers their top questions, and Parents Editor-in-Chief Sally Lee gives tips on how to ease back-to-school nerves.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Join Barrie Gillies, Senior Editor at Parents magazine, for a discussion of the problems facing today's families as they try to raise fit and healthy kids. Among the highlights: Parents Senior Editor Judy Goldberg share her struggles about her chubby child, Dr. Ari Brown, Parents adviser and author of Baby 411, and Toddler 411talks about her plan to keep your kids from gaining weight, and an 11-year-old boy talks candidly about what it's really like to be the "fat kid". Plus: Dr. Brown takes calls from parents about their most pressing questions, including potty training and discipline, and Sally Lee, Editor-in-Chief of Parents magazine, gives expert tips on coping with back-to-school anxiety.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/PMP.mp3" length="10096298" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/fc/mp3/podcast/toughlove/ToughLove1.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2006 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>21:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>childhood obesity, overweight kids, obese kids, fat kids, losing weight, diet, exercise, activity, get kids moving, being overweight, potty training, toilet training, discipline, school, back-to-school,children, parenting</itunes:keywords>
</item>



<item>
<title>Sibling Rivalry, The Best Toys of 2006, Milestones, and more!</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A discussion of sibling rivalry and solutions to stop squabbles. Plus, Parents News Editor, Kourtney Eidam, picks the best toys of 2006, and pediatrician and Parents advisor Dr. Ari Brown gives expert advice for their toughest parenting dilemmas.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Join Barrie Gillies, Senior Editor at Parents magazine, for a discussion of a common issue-sibling rivalry. Among the highlights: one family shares their struggle with competitiveness and fighting, and Mary Borowka, a child behavior expert, gives you solutions to end sibling squabbles. Plus: Kourtney Ediam, Parents News Editor and media critic, shares the inside scoop on our picks for the best toys of 2006. Dr. Ari  Brown, Parents advisor and author of Toddler 411, takes calls from parents about their most pressing questions, including speech and walking milestones, sleep issues, and separation anxiety.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/episode2.mp3" length="9391851" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/episode2.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>19:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>sibling, rivalry, sister, fight, discipline, family, advice, behavior, competitive, toy, toys, holiday, Christmas, Hanukkah, gifts, sleep, walking, milestones, development, speech, sleep, bed, children, kids, parenting</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Special Holiday Edition: Traditions, Dilemmas, Creative Play, and more!(Enhanced Version)</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle> A discussion of holiday traditions and the importance of imagination. Plus, Parents Editor-in-Chief Sally Lee shares tips on engaging your kids in imaginative play, and family therapist Jane Greer discusses holiday dilemmas.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>
The holidays are a time of joy, family, and faith-and also a time of major stress! Feeling more frazzled than festive? Take five and listen to our podcast. When you hear kids talk about how much Christmas and Hanukkah traditions mean to them, you'll see how all the effort you make this time of year really pays off! ALSO, our host, Barrie Gillies finds out why children love (and learn from) their magical make-believe worlds when she talks with child behavior expert Mary Borowka. Plus, enough with all those enrichment activities! Let kids play with their toys! Parents Editor-in-Chief Sally Lee gives the lowdown on free play. Finally, what happens when the grandparents come over for Christmas and your child doesn't want to be smothered with kisses?  Barrie and family therapist Jane Greer tackle  this and other holiday dilemmas when moms call in with their questions.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/episode3enh.m4a" length="9341312" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/episode3enh.m4a</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2006 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>18:16</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>holiday, Christmas, parents, parenting, kids, Hanukkah, spirit, traditions, issues, dilemmas, solutions, expert, gifts, joy, spiritual, family, play, creative, imagination, tips, children</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Special Holiday Edition: Traditions, Dilemmas, Creative Play, and more!</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A discussion of holiday traditions and the importance of imagination. Plus, Parents Editor-in-Chief Sally Lee shares tips on engaging your kids in imaginative play, and family therapist Jane Greer discusses holiday dilemmas.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>The holidays are a time of joy, family, and faith-and also a time of major stress! Feeling more frazzled than festive? Take five and listen to our podcast. When you hear kids talk about how much Christmas and Hanukkah traditions mean to them, you'll see how all the effort you make this time of year really pays off! ALSO, our host, Barrie Gillies finds out why children love (and learn from) their magical make-believe worlds when she talks with child behavior expert Mary Borowka. Plus, enough with all those enrichment activities! Let kids play with their toys! Parents Editor-in-Chief Sally Lee gives the lowdown on free play. Finally, what happens when the grandparents come over for Christmas and your child doesn't want to be smothered with kisses?  Barrie and family therapist Jane Greer tackle  this and other holiday dilemmas when moms call in with their questions.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/Christmas.mp3" length="8782453" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/Christmas.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2006 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>18:16</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>holiday, Christmas, parents, parenting, kids, Hanukkah, spirit, traditions, issues, dilemmas, solutions, expert, gifts, joy, spiritual, family, play, creative, imagination, tips, children</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Healthy Eating, Better Sleeping-and more!</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>We answer your toughest parenting dilemmas. Plus, Parents Editor-in-Chief Sally Lee shares practical tips on getting your kids to eat healthy.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Join our host Barrie Gillies and Pediatrician Dr. Ari Brown as they tackle tough the toughest parenting questions from listeners across the country. Plus, can you get your kid to clamor for spinach? Parents Editor-in-Chief Sally Lee thinks you can (with a few tricks). She'll tell you what's healthy for your child to snack on, why, and how to get your picky eater to choose a good-for-you snack.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/episode4.mp3" length="10212507" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/episode4.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2007 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>16:48</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>Sleep, food, toddler, parenting, kids, help, advice, issues, dilemmas, solutions, expert,  tips, answers, tale, children, magazine, stairs, crying, baby, spinach, snacks, health, safety, tough love, eating, parents, discipline</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Parenting After Divorce, Your Pet and Your New Baby, and More</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A discussion of the impact of divorce on kids. Plus, Parents Editor-in-Chief Sally Lee on helping your newborn and pets bond, and Parents Health and Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner takes questions on parenting dilemmas.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Join Barrie Gillies, Senior Editor at Parents magazine, for a discussion of the challenges of raising kids after divorce. Among the highlights: A 9-year-old and her mother share their experiences of family life after divorce and advice from therapist Gary Neuman, founder and director of Sandcastles -- a nationwide organization for kids whose parents are going through a divorce. Parents Editor-in-Chief Sally Lee gives tips on how to introduce your pet to a new baby. Plus: Health and Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner take calls from parents and answers questions about potty training and sleep issues.  And Senior Editor Judy Goldberg announces February's Blog of the Month!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcastFebruary07.mp3" length="13029652" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcastFebruary07.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2007 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>21:42</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>divorce, divorced parents, parenting, families, potty training, sleep issues, pets, bringing baby home, pets and babies, blog, baby blog</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Sleep Solutions, Easy Ways to Go Green, and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A discussion of sleep struggles and how to solve them. Plus, Parents Executive Editor Kate Lawler shares practical tips on going green, and we takes calls from parents across the country.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Sleep: It's easy to take for granted until you're not getting it! Sleep issues are the number one complaint of parents with young children: Whether it's a baby who wakes up every hour or older kids who still sleep with mom and dad, it can get seriously stressful when no one in the family is getting enough. Our host, Barrie Gillies, talks with sleep expert Jodi Mindell Ph.D. to get tips on solving the trickiest sleep struggles. Plus, Parents Executive Editor Kate Lawler shares quick ways for families to go green. Being environmentally friendly has never been easier! Finally, how do you deal with a perfectionist kid? Barrie and Parents Health and Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner tackle this and other parenting dilemmas when moms call in with their questions.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcastMarch.mp3" length="12740131" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcastMarch.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>21:13</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>Parents, magazine, kids, help, expert, advice, children, issue, solutions, sleep, struggles, night, bed, bedtime, habits, green, environment, earth, save, planet</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Food Allergies, How to Stop Yelling, and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A discussion of severe food allergies and how to cope. Plus, Parents Health &amp; Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner takes calls from parents across the country to tackle the toughest parenting dilemmas.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Food allergies are on the rise: School cafeterias across the country are going peanut-free, and these days every kid has a friend who can't eat class treats. How do parents cope when their child could have a life-threatening reaction to a bite of PB&amp;J? How do other parents deal? Our host, Barrie Gillies, talks with allergy expert John Oppenheimer MD to get practical advice for families dealing with food allergies and parents who suspect their kids might have one. Plus, Parents Editor in Chief Sally Lee shares her take on the newest addition to the Angelina Jolie's family, Pax. Finally, how do you stop yelling at your kids when they just won't listen? Barrie and Parents Health &amp; Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner tackle this and other parenting dilemmas when moms call in with questions.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcastApril.mp3" length="14608233" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcastApril.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2007 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>21:42</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>parents, magazine, kids, help, expert, advice, children, issue, solutions, allergy, allergies, food, reaction, angelina, jolie, pax, adoption, yell, yelling, walking, pacifier, binkie
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>All About The Dads</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A behind-the-scenes look at the lives of stay-at-home dads. Plus, Parents Health &amp; Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner takes calls from parents across the country to tackle the toughest parenting dilemmas.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Dads are way more hands-on these days, and more and more guys are staying at home with the kids instead of Mom. So what's different for families when Dad is the primary caregiver? How do the dads feel about being the lone guy at the playground? We go behind-the-scenes with one family, and then our host, Barrie Gillies, talks with daddy blogger Greg Allen of Daddytypes.com to explore the family-and cultural-dynamics that ensue when Dad stays home. Plus, Parents Creative Director Jeffrey Saks shares his secrets on how to stay involved as a working parent. Finally, what do you do when your daughter has a meltdown before day care-every day? Barrie and Parents Health &amp; Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner tackle this and other parenting dilemmas when moms call in with questions.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcast8_2.mp3" length="14507003" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcast8_2.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2007 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>24:10</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>parents, magazine, kids, help, expert, advice, children, issue, solutions, stay-at-home, stay, home, dad, father, care, work, parent, mom, day, care, school, separation, anxiety, clothes, cry, meltdown, upset</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>All About Safety</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A discussion of parents' fears and how to keep kids safe. Plus, Parents Health &amp; Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner takes calls from parents across the country to tackle the toughest parenting dilemmas.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Every parent worries about their kids. But which fears should you take seriously, and which ones should you chill out about? Expert Kimberly Thompson, a professor of risk analysis at the Harvard School of Public Health, shares her tips on keeping your kids safe-without driving yourself nuts! Plus, Parents Senior Editor Jessica Brown talks about how she learned CPR-and why you should too. Finally, what can a mom do to help her daughter have a healthy body image? Our host Barrie Gillies and Parents Health &amp; Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner tackle this and other parenting dilemmas when moms call in with questions.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcast9.mp3" length="10902899" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcast9.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2007 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>22:42</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>parents, magazine, kids, help, expert, advice, children, issue, solutions, safety, worry, safe, worried, scary, fears, choke, choking, CPR, body, issues, grow, hemangioma, mark, birth, Heimlich, maneuver</itunes:keywords>
</item>
 
<item>
<title>Toddler Discipline Do's and Don'ts </title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A discussion of toddler discipline that works-and punishments that don't. Plus, Parents Health &amp; Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner takes calls from parents across the country to tackle the toughest parenting dilemmas.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>When do you start to discipline your kids? What works, and what doesn't? How do you keep your cool and pick your battles? Getting tough with your kids can be tough-especially when your child's a toddler. Parent counselor and psychotherapist Yael Sank of Soho Parenting shares her tips on how to set limits with your toddler-and make those rules stick. Plus, Parents News Editor Kourtney Eidam shares her insider picks for the best new kids' books. Finally, what do you do when your preschooler fibs about everything? Our host Barrie Gillies and Parents Health &amp; Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner tackle this and other parenting dilemmas when moms call in with questions</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcast10.mp3" length="11114193" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcast10.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2007 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>22:09</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>parents, magazine, kids, help, expert, advice, children, issue, solutions, toddler, discipline, spanking, punishment, dilemmas, time, out, lying, fib, eat, meal, feeding, activities, books </itunes:keywords>
</item>
 
<item>
<title>All About Gender</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A discussion of the differences between boys and girls and how to raise well-rounded kids. Plus, Parents experts take calls from parents across the country to tackle the toughest parenting dilemmas.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>What's the deal with gender identity? With very little encouragement, boys and girls often play, learn, and interact in very different ways. To help us figure it out, Parents Articles Editor Mary Hickey (mom to a boy and a girl) shares the latest research and tips on how to raise well-rounded kids. Plus, Parents Media Editor Amanda Wolfe talks about why every mom should have a girls' night out. Finally, what do you do when your kid won't stop biting her fingernails (and toenails)? Our host Barrie Gillies and Parents Health &amp; Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner tackle this and other parenting dilemmas when moms call in with questions.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcast11.mp3" length="9558152" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcast11.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2007 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>19:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>parents, magazine, kids, help, expert, advice, children, issue, solutions, safety, behavior, discipline, gender, boys, girls, differences, raising, healthy, moms', night, out, biting, fingernail, no </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>All About Play</title>
<itunes:author>Parents editors.</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A discussion of the benefits of silly, joyful play. Plus, Parents experts take calls from listeners across the country to tackle the toughest parenting dilemmas.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We all want to get enough quality time with our kids but sometimes what kids really need is to get silly and have some good-old-fashioned fun! Dr. Kathy Hirsh-Pasek, helps us understand why simple playtime really helps our kids learn and why they need to play more. Plus, Parents Editor-in-Chief Sally Lee talks about how to teach your kids to say thank you. Finally, how do you get your kids to share a room peacefully? Our host Barrie Gillies and Parents Health and Psychology Editor Diane Debrovner tackle this and other parenting dilemmas when moms call in with questions.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcast12.mp3" length="14165195" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://images.meredith.com/parents/mp3/podcast/ParentsPodcast12.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2007 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>23:36</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>parents, magazine, kids, help, expert, advice, children, issue, solutions, safety, behavior, discipline, play, imagination, learning, fun, games, bed, sleep, room, share, siblings, thank, you, quality, time</itunes:keywords>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
