<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Allison Day Greater Orlando Florida Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real estate video tours of the Central Florida region, presented by Allison Day of Keller Williams Realty.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Allison Day of Keller Williams Realty at 407-617-2881 or 407-278-8950; or visit her online at www.AllisonDayHomes.com.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.allisondayhomes.com/</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 08:10:55 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 07:55:36 -0400</pubDate>
        <generator>FeedForAll Mac v2.1 (2.1.0.1); http://www.FeedForAll.com/</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Allison Day Greater Orlando Florida Real Estate Video Feed</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real estate video tours of the Central Florida region, presented by Allison Day of Keller Williams Realty. Allison Day and the Keller Williams Advantage Team provides exceptional customer care for sellers and buyers in the Greater Orlando area. Specializing in Central Florida's most prestigious communties of Oviedo, Winter Springs/Tuskawilla, Winter Park, Maitland and Downtown Orlando as well the surrounding areas of Lake Nona, Bella Collina and Lake Mary/Heathrow. Allison and her team offer homes and estates for all lifestyles while providing unprecendeted service to their clients through exceptional care and unmatched knowledge &amp; area expertise. For more information, contact Allison Day of Keller Williams Realty at 407-617-2881 or 407-278-8950; or visit her online at www.AllisonDayHomes.com.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Allison Day,Keller Williams Realty,Orlando,Central,Florida,real estate,homes,property,for sale,realtor,Terralago,community</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/allison-day/allison-day-300x300.jpg" />
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/allison-day/allison-day-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Allison Day Greater Orlando Florida Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.allisondayhomes.com/</link>
            <description>The Allison Day Greater Orlando Florida Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>Terraglio Homes Featured Community: Terralago - Oviedo, FL 32765</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Terraglio Homes Featured Community: Terralago - Oviedo, FL 32765.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Allison Day of Keller Williams Realty at 407-617-2881 or 407-278-8950; or visit her online at www.TerralagoOviedo.com.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/614-Terraglio-Homes-Featured-Community-Terralago-Oviedo-FL-32765.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/allison-day/Terralago.mp4" length="35655986" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">EDFA0A44-DCCC-40DA-BF69-BBA05B448DA6-971-000014F51EB2E070-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 08:10:34 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Terraglio Homes Featured Community: Terralago - Oviedo, FL 32765. For more information, contact Allison Day of Keller Williams Realty at 407-617-2881 or 407-278-8950; or visit her online at www.TerralagoOviedo.com.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Terraglio Homes Featured Community: Terralago - Oviedo, FL 32765. Property Description: Allison Day of Keller Williams Realty presents Terraglio Homes' Featured Community: Terralago - Oviedo, FL 32765. Welcome to Terralago, Oviedo’s premier luxury community offering exclusive, truly custom homes with details to suit even the most discerning buyers. This 25-home, gated community with premium pond-front and conservation home sites offers casual sophistication in a tranquil, natural setting. Terralago is the benchmark for the area’s new standard of luxury living. Located off State Road 434, this serene community sits just a quarter mile east of the 417 Greenway, within minutes of city life in Downtown Orlando. Terralago’s custom builder, Terraglio Homes, has teamed with select businesses to bring you the best, most distinctive options you desire to customize your dream home. Each home’s stunning exterior boasts truly custom features, including a tile roof, paver drive and walkways, stucco, wrought iron details, hard coated foam and cast stone Your home will impress with 10 to 12-foot ceilings, 42-inch remote controlled gas fireplace with custom mantle, architectural ceilings and details, faux painting, granite countertops throughout, and custom lighting. Terralago’s well-equipped kitchens feature striking granite countertops, 42-inch custom wood cabinets, fixtures by Moen and Kohler, GE Monogram, DCS, or SubZero stainless series appliances, and much more. Indulge in your luxurious master bathroom, which features custom wood cabinets, granite countertops, separate Kohler Jacuzzi Tub, framed mirrors, Moen fixtures, and a tankless gas water heater. All Terralago homes also include a covered lanai with summer kitchen, outdoor fireplaces and generous custom pool package to enhance your outdoor living lifestyle. Terraglio Homes can make your new home in Terralago unique with any number of luxury features, including spectacular home theatre &amp; game rooms. These fine custom-built luxury homes offer an unsurpassed range of standard features and allowances. By beginning with quality, energy efficient construction your home will be comfortable and environmentally friendly. Enjoy the opportunity to design your dream home from scratch or choose from one of the custom plans exclusively designed for Terralago and customize it to suit your needs and tastes. For more information, contact Allison Day of Keller Williams Realty at 407-617-2881 or 407-278-8950; or visit her online at www.TerralagoOviedo.com.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:09</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>Allison Day,Keller Williams Realty,Orlando,Central,Florida,real estate,Oviedo,homes,property,for sale,realtor,Terralago,community</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
