<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Atlantic Properties International, Inc. Real Estate Video Series</title>
        <description>Real estate video tours of South Florida properties presented by Carl Marzola of Atlantic Properties International, Inc..&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Carl Marzola by phone at 954-564-8182, by email at Carl@atlanticprop.com or visit Atlantic Properties International online at www.atlantic-props.com today.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.atlantic-props.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 16:50:23 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 17:59:30 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Atlantic Properties International, Inc. Real Estate Video Series. For more info, contact Carl Marzola by phone at 954-564-8182, by email at Carl@atlanticprop.com or visit Atlantic Properties International online at www.atlantic-props.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real estate video tours of South Florida properties presented by Carl  Marzola of Atlantic Properties International, Inc.

Established Luxury broker with over 50 experienced agents assisting your real estate needs in Miami Beach, Coconut Grove, SOBE, Fort Lauderdale, Wilton Manors and the Palm Beaches. We are globally
connected, locally respected as the real estate professionals in South Florida.

We\&apos;ll find you the perfect property from Luxury Oceanfront Condos, Deepwater residences, Corporate rentals, Commercial Investments, Estate Sales, Preforeclosures or Bank owned property.

Our team will guide you through the paperwork, assist you in finding you the right lender and offer complete management services with our \&quot;Elite\&quot; client conceirge program.  When it comes to South Florida real estate, there\&apos;s Only one name you need to know. Atlantic Properties International.

Contact Broker/President Carl S. Marzola  CIPS,CRS, CRB, MasterBroker.. We are just a click away!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Carl Marzola,Atlantic Properties International Inc.,South Florida,Miami,Fort Lauderdale,real estate,homes,condominiums,property,for sale</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/carl-marzola/carl-marzola-300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/carl-marzola/carl-marzola-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Atlantic Properties International, Inc. Real Estate Video Series</title>
            <link>http://www.atlantic-props.com</link>
            <description>The Atlantic Properties International, Inc. Real Estate Video Series Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>Grovenor House - 2627 South Bayshore Drive Unit 2206, Coconut Grove, FL 33133</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring the Grovenor House - 2627 South Bayshore Drive, Unit 2206, Coconut Grove, FL 33133.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
2 Bedrooms, 2 Baths.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Carl Marzola by phone at 954-564-8182, by email at Carl@atlanticprop.com or visit Atlantic Properties International online at www.atlantic-props.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/527-Grovenor-House-2627-S.-Bayshore-Drive-Unit-2206-Coconut-Grove-FL-33133.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/carl-marzola/Grovenor-House-Eng.mp4" length="32658575" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5AD5972B-478B-47FE-A7B9-8BBCEA0E4412</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 17:57:05 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring the Grovenor House - 2627 South Bayshore Drive, Unit 2206, Coconut Grove, FL 33133. For more info, contact Carl Marzola by phone at 954-564-8182, by email at Carl@atlanticprop.com or visit them at www.atlantic-props.com.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring the Grovenor House - 2627 South Bayshore Drive, Unit 2206, Coconut Grove, FL 33133.

2 Bedrooms, 2 Baths.

Property Description: Carl Marzola of Atlantic Properties International Inc. presents Grovenor House - 2627 South Bayshore Drive Unit 2206 Coconut Grove, FL 33133.

Rising above Coconut Grove and Biscayne Bay, Grovenor House has been called the “Jewel” of Coconut Grove and has earned the reputation as one of South Florida’s premiere properties, developed by internationally acclaimed Italian developer, Ugo Columbo. This magnificent tower offers 32 stories of estate sized residences with unsurpassed and commanding unprecedented water vistas of Biscayne Bay and the Atlantic Ocean. You are greeted by only the highest standards of excellence throughout this lush 3.5 acre resort which is conveniently located across from a marina for easy boating access and the finest of restaurants that are unique to Coconut Grove residents. And you&apos;re just minutes to South Beach and Coral Gables.

Coconut Grove Condominium residences maintain the highest of standards while Keeping up with the latest innovations. For those who appreciate a higher standard of living, every feature and every finish is among the finest in the world. It is imaginative and creative, yet highly sophisticated, elegant and classical. The entry lobby offers Expansive sitting areas with a nautical theme and was designed by Florentine architect, Michele Bonan. who worked for Ferragamo. Residents enjoy the comfort of the 24 hour security and concierge services at Grovenor House. Guests are greeted by the friendly attentive staff and pampered by the superlative Grovenor House Spa team, where one can enjoy a massage, or a exercise workout with a personal trainer in Grovenor’s state of the art fitness center. Perhaps enjoy a friendly match on the private tennis courts.

The Olympic mosaic infinity pool is perfect for reflecting or just simply enjoy the beauty and tranquility of the lush private gardens. The residence is accessible through your private elevator, giving you and your guests total privacy. The private foyer entrance is accent by custom Venetian plaster and 10’ custom designed Decorative entry doors. All rooms are spacious throughout this residence, offering 10’ ceilings with floor to ceiling window impact sliding glass doors that provide you full advantage of the panoramic bay and ocean vistas. The Italian Snaidero kitchen cabinetry was carefully selected, offering you the finest in kitchen cabinetry as well as amazing Italian imported granite countertops.

Only Miele appliances were used to compliment this custom kitchen. All flooring throughout the residence including the oversized terrace was carefully selected imported white marble. Separate Guest suite offers magnificent water vistas and private marble bathroom with imported European wall coverings. The private and generous Master suite offers serene Ocean vistas and a perfect enclave when you want to just relax perhaps in your Jacuzzi, or enjoy the rainforest marble shower. When you can afford not to compromise, there is no other residence that can compare to the superior quality, elegance and amenities that this Grovenor House residence has to offer.

For more information, please contact Carl Marzola by phone at 954-564-8182, by email at Carl@atlanticprop.com or visit Atlantic Properties International online at www.atlantic-props.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>4:13</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>Carl Marzola,Atlantic Properties International Inc.,Florida,real estate,Grovenor House,Coconut Grove,Miami,condominium,for sale,luxury,property</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
