<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The B&amp;D Custom Homes Real Estate Video Series</title>
        <description>Real estate video tours from Bend, Oregon presented by Robert Paterson of B&amp;D Custom Homes.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Robert Paterson of B&amp;D Custom Homes by phone at 541-280-9793.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/paterson40uci.net/</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts.com</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 18:51:07 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 18:51:07 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The B&amp;D Custom Homes Bend Oregon Real Estate Video Series</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real estate video tours from Bend, Oregon presented by Robert Paterson of B&amp;D Custom Homes.  

B&amp;D Custom Homes, building beautiful cottage style homes in central Oregon since 1999. Master builder Bob Paterson and his wife Darlene perform most of the construction from foundation, framing to finish. Rest assured your getting the best quality custom built home in the marketplace. Each home takes nearly six months to complete. It is our policy to make sure the foundation and framing have plenty of time to cure. This is important in Central Oregon, providing you a superior and longer lasting home. Please give us a call for your own personal tour. You won’t be disappointed.

For more information, please contact Robert Paterson of B&amp;D Custom Homes by phone at 541-280-9793.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>robert paterson,B&amp;D Custom Homes,Bend,Oregon,OR,real estate,for sale,realtor,homes,property,video tours,real estate video</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/robert_paterson/robert_paterson_300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/robert_paterson/robert_paterson_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The B&amp;D Custom Homes Real Estate Video Series</title>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/paterson40uci.net/</link>
            <description>The B&amp;D Custom Homes Real Estate Video Series Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>3107 Yellow Ribbon Drive Bend, OR 97701</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 3107 Yellow Ribbon Drive Bend, OR 97701.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
4 Bedrooms, 3 Bathrooms.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Robert Paterson of B&amp;D Custom Homes by phone at 541-280-9793.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/471-3107-Yellow-Ribbon-Drive-Bend-OR-97701.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/robert_paterson/3107_Yellow_Ribbon_Drive.mp4" length="20360342" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">521B8947-CB65-4E3B-AC3D-23770FC43CC8</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 09:54:39 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 3107 Yellow Ribbon Drive Bend, OR 97701. 4 Bedrooms, 3 Bathrooms. For more information, please contact Robert Paterson of B&amp;D Custom Homes by phone at 541-280-9793.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 3107 Yellow Ribbon Drive Bend, OR 97701. 

4 Bedrooms, 3 Bathrooms. 

Property Description: Robert Paterson of B&amp;D Custom Homes presents 3107 Yellow Ribbon Drive Bend, OR 97701.

Come sit, relax and enjoy mountain views from the front porch or living room. this wonderful neighborhood is close to hospital, schools, shopping and neighborhood park. This amazing custom house looks like a quaint cottage from the outside, but inside - a spectacular spacious floor plan with over 2,600 sq.ft., 4 bedrooms, 3 baths and a 30x15 ft. bonus room. The tiled entry leads to living room, kitchen and upstairs. What a stunning entertainment area with beautiful marble surrounding the fireplace and georgous alder cabinetry and woodworking.

Take your shoes off and feel the increably thick plush carpeting. Enjoy mountain views from the spacious living room. You don’t see designer kitchens like this even in million dollar homes. large enough for even the most discrimiating chef. Diamond tiled backsplash, stainless steel applicances and a dining bar that’s perfect for entertaining. The guest bathroom is very large including an oversized wash basin and big storage closet. On your way to the master bedroom are two very nice sized bedrooms. you won’t be disipointed!

The master bedroom has plenty of space and includes a big walk-in closet. Beautifully designed bathroom complete with 6 ft. soaking tub, linen closet, separate toilet room, twin lav’s and georgous tiling throughout. Upstairs the cutest bedroom you’ll see. Cape code sytle with peek a boo mt views - This room is perfect for guests, an office or that little girl in your life! Wow what a room - this spacious, 30 x 15 foot bonus room is ideal for that big screen tv, bar or pool table. really, the possibilities are endless.

...and by the way, there’s even a full bathroom upstairs

Finally, at the end of the day, in your big fenced backyard enjoy barbequing or just relaxing in your hot tub under a spacious covered patio detailed with exposed agreegate concrete.

For more information, please contact Robert Paterson of B&amp;D Custom Homes by phone at 541-280-9793.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:37</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>robert paterson,B&amp;D Custom Homes,Bend,Oregon,OR,real estate,for sale,realtor,homes,property,video tours,real estate video</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
