<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Brad Coy San Francisco Real Estate Services Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours from San Francisco California, presented by Brad Coy.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Brad Coy by phone at (415) 999-3487, by email at brad@sfres.com, or visit San Francisco Real Estate Services online at www.sfres.com.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.sfres.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 17:09:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 17:08:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Brad Coy San Francisco Real Estate Services Video Feed. For more info, contact Brad Coy at (415) 999-3487, by email at brad@sfres.com, or visit him online at www.sfres.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours from San Francisco California, presented by Brad Coy.

About Brad Coy:  I can be found working in real estate primarily on the North and South/East side of the city.  Condos, Single family homes. lofts, and Income property.  My family owns and operates one of the best known boutique offices in the city.  Just ask around, most locals know our reputation for individualized service.

I have a great deal of history  with the wonderful neighborhoods of the city.  Contact me if you are interested in putting my experience to work for you or simply have a question about San Francisco Real Estate.

For more information, contact Brad Coy by phone at (415) 999-3487, by email at brad@sfres.com, or visit San Francisco Real Estate Services online at www.sfres.com.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Brad Coy,San Francisco,real estate,services,realtor,homes,condos,for sale,boutique,California,CA</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/brad-coy/bradcoy-300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/brad-coy/bradcoy-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Brad Coy San Francisco Real Estate Services Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.sfres.com</link>
            <description>The Brad Coy San Francisco Real Estate Services Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>Brad Coy of San Francisco Real Estate Services - Agent Profile.</title>
            <description>A real estate agent profile video featuring Brad Coy of San Francisco Real Estate Services.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Brad Coy is a Real Estate agent with San Francisco Real Estate Services. He is part of the second generation of a Boutique brokerage of local Real Estate specialists that have been specializing in servicing in some of the greatest neighborhoods of the city for over 20 years.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Brad Coy by phone at (415) 999-3487, by email at brad@sfres.com, or visit San Francisco Real Estate Services online at www.sfres.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/505-Brad-Coy-of-San-Francisco-Real-Estate-Services-Agent-Profile.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/brad-coy/Brad-Coy-Agent-Profile.mp4" length="15898506" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2B6E38D2-3665-4204-A6D8-2A9815E59E48</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 10:24:23 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Brad Coy of San Francisco Real Estate Services - Agent Profile. For more info, contact Brad Coy at (415) 999-3487, by email at brad@sfres.com, or visit him online at www.sfres.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate agent profile video featuring Brad Coy of San Francisco Real Estate Services.

Agent Profile:

Hi - I&apos;m Brad Coy a Real Estate agent with San Francisco Real Estate Services. I&apos;m part of the second generation of a Boutique brokerage of local Real Estate specialists that have been specializing in service in some of the greatest neighborhoods of the city for over 20 years. Our company was formed out of the idea that we should focus on you; the consumer, by offering exceptional, personalized service by having an intimate group of highly trained, top producing agents and staff that focus on customer service. You We do this in working with you to help you in residential sales, rentals, and property management with care, professionalism, and knowledge.

The city&apos;s market is made up of several smaller micro-markets and understanding them while navigating through them can be a daunting task to say the least. I have a personal relationship with many of the fine neighborhoods that I work in with my clients. My focus is offering value for you before, during, and after a real estate transaction process. As an educated Realtor in the community I know how to navigate tricky market hurdles in the Urban market, saving you stress and money on your next home purchase or investment.

Backed by a team that has developed well established relationships within the brokerage and client community, my second generation status puts me in the seat of taking our company ethos and building the same type of integrity based service using online social networking and new media and branching out nation wide leveraging connections that reach far beyond SF in some of the best Urban markets everywhere.

I appreciate your taking the time to watch this video and allowing to give you an introduction to myself and my company San Francisco Real Estate Services. Please contact me with any and all questions with regards to your Real Estate needs and I would be more than happy to help you get started or point you in the right direction. Have a great day.

For more information, contact Brad Coy by phone at (415) 999-3487, by email at brad@sfres.com, or visit San Francisco Real Estate Services online at www.sfres.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:10</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>Brad Coy,San Francisco,real estate,services,realtor,homes,condos,for sale,boutique,California,CA,agent profile</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
