<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Pacific Century Realty Real Estate Video Series</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours from Daniel Berman of Pacific Century Realty</description>
        <link>http://www.pacific-century.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 4 Jun 2008 14:45:16 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Wed, 4 Jun 2008 14:45:14 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Pacific Century Realty Real Estate Video Series</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours from Daniel Berman of Pacific Century Realty</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Daniel Berman,Pacific Century Realty,realtor,for sale,homes,California,CA,property,discount,real estate video</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/daniel_berman/daniel_berman_300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/daniel_berman/daniel_berman_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Pacific Century Realty Real Estate Video Series</title>
            <link>http://www.pacific-century.com</link>
            <description>The Pacific Century Realty Real Estate Video Series Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>954 Castlewood Way. Hayward CA 94541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 954 Castlewood Way. Hayward CA 94541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
2 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms, MLS# 40326926&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Daniel Berman by phone at 650-888-4321, by email at db@pacific-century.com, or online at www.pacific-century.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/492-954-Castlewood-Way.-Hayward-CA-94541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/daniel_berman/954_Castlewood_Way.mp4" length="23005934" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B0D91ED8-CED5-4E9D-87E9-5899EA8E9C59</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 4 Jun 2008 14:16:03 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 954 Castlewood Way. Hayward CA 94541. For more information, contact Daniel Berman by phone at 650-888-4321, by email at db@pacific-century.com, or online at www.pacific-century.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 954 Castlewood Way. Hayward CA 94541.

2 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms, MLS# 40326926

Property Description: Daniel Berman of Pacific Century Realty presents 954 Castlewood Way. Hayward CA 94541.

Where in the San Francisco Bay Area at this time can you find a two-bedroom, two-and-a-half-bathroom townhome, with so many amenities, in true move-in condition, for less than $350,000? For a limited time only, at Skywest in Hayward, one of the Bay Area\&apos;s best-kept secrets, at number 954 Castlewood Way.

Here, you can truly make your home your castle ,,, but only if you act quickly, while this highly affordable townhome - with easy access to shopping, transportation and recreation - is still available. Nestled between Skywest Golf Course and Kennedy Public Park is a little-known enclave of townhomes that forms a veritable oasis amidst the hustle and bustle of a fast-paced urban environment. Residents at Skywest enjoy all the benefits of city living, in the context of lush surroundings and blissful serenity. The property has recently been inspected - both home and termite - and came out substantially clean, with only $100-150 in estimated Section 1 work. So many Bay Area homes have largely &quot;topped out&quot; in terms of their potential for substantial appreciation in the years immediately ahead ... but not so for 954 Castlewood Way, whose surroundings are key to what makes this property so desirable and unique.

Skywest Golf Course, adjacent to the property on one side, is a public 18-hole course, open year-round, awarded a five-star value rating by golflink.com! Set on several lush acres, adjacent to the property on the other side, John F. Kennedy Park features a small train whose tracks encircle the park. The SkyWest Commons shopping center is an easy walking distance from the property - approximately ten minutes, by foot - hosting Target, Starbucks and a UPS Store. The more established and larger-scale Southland Mall shopping center - hosting JC Penney, Macy&apos;s, Mervyns and Sears - is an additional five minutes away, by car. Also several minutes away by car are the Hayward Amtrak and BART - Bay Area Rapid Transit - stations. Large employers nearby include California State University East Bay, Chabot College, Kaiser Permanente-Hayward and St. Rose Hospital. Take advantage of the recent drop in interest rates: we can help you with your financing, too!

For more photos and further information, please visit www.954CastlewoodWay.com today!

For more information, contact Daniel Berman by phone at 650-888-4321, by email at db@pacific-century.com, or online at www.pacific-century.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:51</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>Daniel Berman,Pacific Century Realty,realtor,for sale,homes,California,CA,castlewood way,hayward,property</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
