<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The David Lessnick Las Vegas, Nevada Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real estate video tours of properties for sale or rent in the Las Vegas, Nevada region, presented by David Lessnick of Priapism II LLC.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact David Lessnick by phone at (702) 353-0104 or by email at davdlessnick@mac.com today.</description>
        <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/View-by-tag/David+Lessnick/</link>
        <copyright>c2009 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 15:29:20 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 15:29:14 -0400</pubDate>
        <generator>FeedForAll Mac v2.1 (2.1.0.1); http://www.FeedForAll.com/</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The David Lessnick Las Vegas, Nevada Real Estate Video Feed</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real estate video tours of properties for sale or rent in the Las Vegas, Nevada region, presented by David Lessnick of Priapism II LLC.

For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact David Lessnick by phone at (702) 353-0104 or by email at davdlessnick@mac.com today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>David Lessnick,Las Vegas,Nevada,NV,real estate,homes,condos,condominiums,rent,for sale,palms place</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/david-lessnick/david-lessnick-itunes-300x300.jpg" />
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/david-lessnick/david-lessnick-itunes-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The David Lessnick Las Vegas, Nevada Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/View-by-tag/David+Lessnick/</link>
            <description>The David Lessnick Las Vegas, Nevada Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>Steep 'N' Deep - 365 Deer Valley Drive, Park City, Utah 84060</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Steep 'N' Deep - 365 Deer Valley Drive, Park City, Utah 84060.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact David Lessnick by phone at (702) 353-0104or by email at davdlessnick@mac.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/891-Steep-N-Deep-365-Deer-Valley-Drive-Park-City-Utah-84060.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/david-lessnick/Steep-N-Deep.mp4" length="27138781" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4C2BB2FC-A42D-4BB0-A815-F44E36829750-3889-0000153C3E3DF518-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 15:29:16 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Steep 'N' Deep - 365 Deer Valley Drive, Park City, Utah 84060. For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact David Lessnick by phone at (702) 353-0104or by email at davdlessnick@mac.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Steep 'N' Deep - 365 Deer Valley Drive, Park City, Utah 84060. Uncompromising quality, incredible location, &amp; fantastic views. . . This newly constructed, professionally decorated townhome by renowned designer, Dana Balaban, has everything to make your family vacation unforgettable. Enjoy ski-run views from this 4 level, 5 bedroom townhome that sleeps up to 12 and has entertained the likes of Sting and sitting U.S Senators. After skiing, come home and watch one of the 8 flat screen TV's or step into the professionally designed Crestron controlled theatre room with stadium seating, and 108&quot; screen! Or, head up to the loft where you can play foosball on a professional grade table, or enjoy a game of cards on the custom built, 8 seat poker table. If you're a bit sore, take your choice between the steam shower in the master bathroom or the private jacuzzi in the backyard. No &quot;rental&quot; furniture here. Only the finest/custom built furnishings and appointments right down to original artwork and photographs. There is distributed audio throughout the house and the dining room area is complete with a custom built bar with wine refrigerator and wall mounted flat screen T.V. that can be viewed while eating or preparing a meal in the kitchen.  The boot drying room is on the lower level and the incredible master suite takes up the entire top floor. With its oversized private balcony with incredible views, cozy seating area, floor to ceiling rock fireplace and 15-foot high vaulted ceiling, you may never want to leave the top floor. While this home, known as Steep 'N' Deep, is truly amazing, the location is even better! Situated on lower Deer Valley Dr. just above the Main Street round-a-bout, you are only two minutes away from the base of either Deer Valley or Park City Resorts and only a three minute walk to Main Street where all the restaurants, shops and entertainment are. It simply doesn’t get better than this! But it does. . . the free town shuttle stops less then 30 yards from the front door and the rental price includes daily maid service! Don’t put it off. Book your Ski Vacation at Steep 'N' Deep today! You will love this property! For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact David Lessnick by phone at (702) 353-0104or by email at davdlessnick@mac.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>02:54</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>David Lessnick,Park City,Utah,UT,Steep 'n' Deep,townhouse,condo.rental,rent,property,for rent,deer valley,townhome</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>407 Westbourne Street, La Jolla, CA 92037</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 407 Westbourne Street, La Jolla, CA 92037.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact David Lessnick by phone at (702) 353-0104or by email at davdlessnick@mac.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/734-407-Westbourne-Street-La-Jolla-CA-92037.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/david-lessnick/407-Westbourne-Street.mp4" length="48078626" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">FCC658F0-9A15-4666-97E9-B3BE6747D0DC-700-0000142B3E30A962-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 14:32:14 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 407 Westbourne Street, La Jolla, CA 92037. For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact David Lessnick by phone at (702) 353-0104or by email at davdlessnick@mac.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 407 Westbourne Street, La Jolla, CA 92037.

Welcome to 407 Westbourne located just steps away from the world famous Wind’n’sea Beach in La Jolla California. This charming 2,800 square foot three bedroom three and a half bath single family home with detached casita boasts charming Spanish influenced architecture and is within easy walking distance to the La Jolla Village – home to some of the finest restaurants, shopping and art galleries in all of San Diego. This private residence is impeccably maintained and has interiors designed by renowned artist and designer, Dana Balaban. Once inside the front gate, you will enjoy a well-landscaped courtyard with a bubbling fountain serving as a focal point and a seating area to soak in the afternoon sun.

The first level of this two story home has floors of stone with a inviting fireplace in the living room opposite two sectional sofas that easily convert into a sleeping area for four. Moving into the dining room, you will enjoy family meals at a custom, handcrafted table for ten with bench seating and a bar area. The galley style kitchen features rare blue and green granite countertops, top of the line stainless steel appliances complete with double oven and warming drawer, and large walk-in pantry behind a custom stained glass door. Just above the pantry is the front gate monitor for your added security. Just off the dining area is the powder room and a few steps further down the hall is the media room. Enjoy watching your favorite show on a huge built in high definition flat projector TV. Or, plug in the Karaoke machine and host your own 'American Idol' contest. There’s plenty of room for everyone on a custom built sofa that seats ten comfortably.

Upstairs you will find all bamboo wood floors and two large master suites. The front suite, with its Asian influenced décor, has a queen bed, fireplace, separate seating area with futon chair that converts to a bed, two large closets and views of the pacific ocean. The private bathroom has a tub/shower combination and the same blue and green granite as downstairs. The other master suite is larger and has a white washed feel. With a California king bed, futon lounge that converts to a bed, TV, and large walk-in closet, you will quickly feel at home. The bathroom is finished in gorgeous stone accents with a large fully enclosed shower. The large casement windows overlook private back courtyard and casita.

And therein lies the real beauty of this residence. Enjoy the best of indoor outdoor living in the fantastic rear courtyard complete with palm thatched covers, an eating area, configurable seating including a colorful oversized chaise lounge, a fire pit, a built in BBQ, and an outdoor shower and spa. Walk into the two-car garage and go for a ride on one of the eight beach cruisers or boogie boards. All the beach toys as well as plenty of chairs and umbrellas are yours to enjoy at the beach. The large front-loading washer and dryer make doing laundry a breeze. Above the garage is a cozy one-bedroom casita that sleeps three and is appointed with its own kitchenette and bathroom with shower.

This lovely beach home has distributed audio in every room, including the rear courtyard, via a hand-held controller from Sonos. With the controller, you can adjust the volume in the different rooms and even have separate music playing in each room. Other benefits include central air-conditioning and heat, wireless internet, free unlimited long distance, satellite TV with all the HBO channels, and fax machine and printer. This La Jolla beach home is the private vacation getaway of David Lessnick and has never been offered for rent before now. You won’t find anything like this at the beach! Call David today at (702) 353-0104.

For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact David Lessnick by phone at (702) 353-0104or by email at davdlessnick@mac.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>5:00</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>David Lessnick,la jolla,california,CA,san diego,beach,house,rental,rent,property,wind n sea,home</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Palms Place - 4321 W. Flamingo Road #57304, Las Vegas, NV 89103</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Palms Place - 4321 W. Flamingo Road #57304, Las Vegas, NV 89103.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact David Lessnick by phone at (702) 353-0104or by email at davdlessnick@mac.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/706-Palms-Place-4321-W.-Flamingo-Road-57304-Las-Vegas-NV-89103.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/david-lessnick/Palms-Place.mp4" length="50056942" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2DED1E65-5B13-4F8A-8410-9315FFC02D43-384-0000049F2AD1892B-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 09:46:14 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Palms Place - 4321 W. Flamingo Road #57304, Las Vegas, NV 89103. For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact David Lessnick by phone at (702) 353-0104or by email at davdlessnick@mac.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Palms Place - 4321 W. Flamingo Road #57304, Las Vegas, NV 89103. This amazing penthouse overlooks the Las Vegas strip on the 56th floor of Palms Place - the newest tower of the world-famous Palms Hotel &amp; Casino. The Palms Casino Resort, heralded as one of Las Vegas' hippest resorts, is an all-encompassing, one-stop resort destination. The 703-room property boasts a diverse mix of bars and restaurants as well as a 95,000-square-foot casino. As you enter this luxurious 3,300 square foot penthouse you will be greeted by gorgeous custom wood and marble floors, hand crafted one-of-a-kind furniture, 12- foot ceilings, and floor-to-ceiling windows with remote control drapes that overlook the strip. The living room boasts floor to ceiling glass walls with unparalleled strip views, and shares a modern fireplace with the dining room. It is complemented by a custom designed sectional sofa, an inset floor rug, a custom designed coffee table, and custom lounge chairs and floor lamps. Completing the picture is a 42&quot; plasma screen TV and DVD player with surround sound, a low chess table with pouf seating, and direct access to the balcony's spa pool. The neighboring game room includes a custom pool table, inset floor rugs, a wall recessed plasma TV, a game table for 4 with overhead lighting, and library shelving and storage cabinets. Finally, the main living area's comfort and style is further enhanced by a cocktail lounge area with a European day bed. The kitchen and dining area features a custom dining table for 8-10 with plush upholstered seats, and a modern fireplace. It boasts a sleed bar counter with a hand sink, an under-counter wine fridge, an all stainless steel kitchen counter, an island kitchen table, and top of the line European appliances. The master suite is appointed with a custom European-style bed frame with a wooden slatted base and a premium Sealy mattress. This master king sized bed sits on an upholstered platform frame with an upholstered canopy and wall panels as a headboard. Rounding off the suite are custom designed night lights, a plasma screen with DVD, and a wonderful seating area. The master bath offers a large shower for two with a rain fall showerhead, multi-jet massage showerheads, and steam, plus a deep soaking tub under-mounted at stone plinth, a separate toilet cubicle with bidet, and dual vanity counters in stone. Other features include hard-wiring for a hair dryer, a bathrobe, a magnifying make-up mirror with light, a LCD flat screen TV, and a bathroom telephone. The walk-in closet includes full height dressing mirrors and a dressing stool along with 12 foot long closet space, a luggage rack, a nest of drawers, and a mini safe. The second bedroom features floor to ceiling glass walls, dual queen beds, an inset floor rug around the beds, and a lounging area with an armchair and an ottoman set with a side table. Also included is a walk-in closet with a wealth of appointments. The second bath is adorned with dual vanity counters in stone, a glass shower cubicle with rainfall, multi-jet massage, and hand-held showerheads, and a separate toilet cubicle. The unit also comes complete with a washer and dryer area with storage shelves and cabinets, an iron and ironing board, and a hang rail. The views and experience that it offers are truly unbelievable! As a guest in one of the finest privately owned luxury penthouses anywhere in the country, you will enjoy on-site dining with celebrity chef Kerry Simon, a private bar and lounge, resort concierge service and a full business center as well as 24 hour hotel services including valet, bell, front desk, daily housekeeping and security. Call today for your private showing! For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact David Lessnick by phone at (702) 353-0104 or by email at davdlessnick@mac.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>6:29</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>David Lessnick,Las Vegas,Nevada,NV,real estate,homes,condos,condominiums,rent,for sale,palms place,casino,strip</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
