<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Gerald Olsen Palm Beach Florida Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video  Tours from Gerald Olsen of Coldwell Banker Premier Agent, featuring luxury properties for sale in the Palm Beaches of Florida.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Jerry Olsen of Coldwell Banker Residential Real Estate by phone at 561-371-7577, by email at gerald.olsen@floridamoves.com, or visit his website online at floridamoves.com today!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://floridamoves.com/</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts.com</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 15:45:38 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 15:45:26 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Gerald Olsen Palm Beach Florida Real Estate Video Feed. Real Estate Video  Tours from Gerald Olsen of Coldwell Banker Premier Agent, featuring luxury properties for sale in the Palm Beaches of Florida.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video  Tours from Gerald Olsen of Coldwell Banker Premier Agent, featuring luxury properties for sale in the Palm Beaches of Florida.

Jerry Olsen&apos;s vast experience in sales and customer service are put to good use in the world of Real Estate. He has repeatedly been awarded \&quot;Realtor of the Month\&quot; at Coldwell Banker (Formerly Arvida Realty Services). Jerry is now designated a Premier Realtor®. This title is awarded for outstanding performance as a Coldwell Banker Agent.

About Jerry:

Jerry&apos;s many years of experience in sales have earned him many accolades as a top producer. During this time he has not lost sight of the fact that customer satisfaction is key to his success. His keen business acumen, attention to detail and his ability to communicate effectively with his clients continues to build a solid base of satisfied sellers and buyers.

Jerry&apos;s finely honed organizational skills and his focus on the needs of his clients produces transactions with the least inconvenience for the people he serves. His continuous desire for self-improvement will always set him in a class of excellence in the Real Estate industry. His concern for the needs of his customers have proved a valuable tool as can be demonstrated by the high proportion of referral business that Jerry receives from the families and friends of very satisfied clients. 

To experience this level of excellence for yourself, why not call Jerry today?

For more information, please contact Jerry Olsen of Coldwell Banker Residential Real Estate by phone at 561-371-7577, by email at gerald.olsen@floridamoves.com, or visit his website online at floridamoves.com today!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>gerald olsen,coldwell banker,Premier Agent,palm beach,florida,fl,luxury,real estate,homes,property,for sale,real estate video</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/gerald_olsen/gerald_olsen_300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/gerald_olsen/gerald_olsen_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Gerald Olsen Palm Beach Florida Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://floridamoves.com/</link>
            <description>The Gerald Olsen Palm Beach Florida Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>212 Canterbury Drive West, Palm Beach Gardens FL 33418</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 212 Canterbury Drive West, Palm Beach Gardens FL 33418.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
3 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Jerry Olsen of Coldwell Banker Residential Real Estate by phone at 561-371-7577, by email at gerald.olsen@floridamoves.com, or visit his website online at floridamoves.com today!</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/468-212-Canterbury-Drive-West-Palm-Beach-Gardens-FL-33418.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/jerry_olsen/212_Canterbury_Drive.mp4" length="29122604" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">79B20FEF-6691-4669-A15C-4657BBC61FAD</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 13:25:21 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 212 Canterbury Drive West, Palm Beach Gardens FL 33418.  For more info, contact Jerry Olsen by phone at 561-371-7577, by email at gerald.olsen@floridamoves.com, or visit his website online at floridamoves.com today!</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 212 Canterbury Drive West, Palm Beach Gardens FL 33418.

3 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms.

Welcome to your new home in Canterbury subdivision within the PGA National Resort and Spa Resort Community, located in the Heart of Palm Beach Gardens where Chic shopping and dining abound. The Canterbury Subdivision is a beautiful upscale community which offers a complete set of features for a uniquely rewarding experience, including its own private clubhouse as well as a magnificent private swimming pool and hot-tub. Canterbury is one of the most financially sound associations in the area, and provides a spectacular living environment that is truly second to none.

This beautifully appointed, wonderfully decorated 3 bedroom 2 ½ bath home is the 2 story Brentwood Model, which offers a 2 car garage along with a warm appeal and an impressive view. As you enter the home, you will immediately sense the peaceful and serene mood that it imbues. The main living area is spacious and luxurious, and offers a large dining area which features a very unique Chicago brick floor with designer inserts. The living area is wired for a surround sound to enhance your enjoyment and tranquility. The main floor also includes this wonderful room which can be used as a den, home office, nursery, or even a guest room.

The large main-level Master suite comes complete with volume high ceilings and a roomy walk in closet for your belongings. This master suite is appointed with it&apos;s own bath and shower for the utmost in privacy and convenience. The kitchen offers upgraded counter tops as well as a beautiful white motif and numerous high-quality, upgraded appliances. It also features a large preparation or cooking island for comfortably designing your meals. The upstairs is the perfect place for your family members or quests to enjoy. The large loft overlooks the main-floor living area, and presents a gorgeous view out of the large 2 story windows to the luscious palms and the large over-sized lanai.

Each of the two bedrooms upstairs is decorated with a unique and appealing designer taste, and both provide the perfect space for an elegant and relaxing retreat. An additional full bathroom is also located on the second floor for the ultimate in comfort and convenience. The included patio area is perfect for enjoying your time and care-free relaxation within its wonderful screened in enclosure. You will immediately feel the warmth and love that this home exudes, and it can be fully yours to experience along with the extraordinary fine dining, sheik shopping, and many luxurious amenities which the location provides for the most discriminating and sophisticated of taste.

For more information, please contact Jerry Olsen of Coldwell Banker Residential Real Estate by phone at 561-371-7577, by email at gerald.olsen@floridamoves.com, or visit his website online at floridamoves.com today!</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:44</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>palm beach real estate,west palm beach,gerald olsen,jerry,canterbury drive,PGA national,luxury,real estate,for sale,homes,property</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
