<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Greg Crosby Anacortes, WA Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real estate video tours of homes for sale in the Anacortes, WA region, presented by Greg Crosby of John L. Scott  Real Estate.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Greg Crosby by phone at (360) 293-2161, by email at gregoryc@johnlscott.com, or visit John L. Scott online at www.johnlscott.com/gregoryc today. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by www.AgentCasts.com</description>
        <link>http://www.johnlscott.com/gregoryc</link>
        <copyright>c2009 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2009 15:45:59 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2009 15:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
        <generator>FeedForAll Mac v2.1 (2.1.0.1); http://www.FeedForAll.com/</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Greg Crosby Anacortes, WA Real Estate Video Feed</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real estate video tours of homes for sale in the Anacortes, WA region, presented by Greg Crosby of John L. Scott Real Estate.

Greetings from beautiful Anacortes, WA, gateway to the San Juan Islands - one of the safest small towns in America. I am a corporate refugee who found the best of the best here in the Pacific Northwest -- in terms of natural beauty, planned growth, diversity, and access to great medical care. For Buyers, I offer experience and solid negotiating skills for selecting -- and securing -- your new home. I am an Accredited Buyers' Representative (ABR), a credential earned from the National Association of Realtors for professional agents who pursue excellence for their Buyer clients. For Sellers, I pride myself on special homes that require creative problem-solving and marketing skills in order to maximize their showcase potential. I think of my listings as WOW homes when the final package is presented to the public. I offer friendly professional services on your terms and welcome your questions about our homes and island lifestyle.

For more information, contact Greg Crosby by phone at (360) 293-2161, by email at gregoryc@johnlscott.com, or visit John L. Scott online at www.johnlscott.com/gregoryc today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Greg Crosby, Anacortes,WA,Washington,real estate,property,homes,for sale,realtor,house,agents,realtor</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/greg-crosby/greg-crosby-300x300.jpg" />
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/greg-crosby/greg-crosby-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Greg Crosby Anacortes, WA Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.johnlscott.com/gregoryc</link>
            <description>The Greg Crosby Anacortes, WA Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>4018 Coralroot Place, Anacortes, WA 98221</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 4018 Coralroot Place, Anacortes, WA 98221 .&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
3 Bedrooms, 4.25 Baths. MLS# 29134785.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Greg Crosby by phone at (360) 293-2161, by email at gregoryc@johnlscott.com, or visit John L. Scott online at www.johnlscott.com/gregoryc today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/greg-crosby/4018coralroot.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/greg-crosby/4018-Coralroot-Pl.m4v" length="27599296" type="video/x-m4v"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C234EFF5-FD2A-4D94-BB10-0B1948B570AA-1607-0000209D06B96FC1-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2009 15:39:02 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 4018 Coralroot Place, Anacortes, WA 98221. For more information, contact Greg Crosby by phone at (360) 293-2161, by email at gregoryc@johnlscott.com, or visit John L. Scott online at www.johnlscott.com/gregoryc today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 4018 Coralroot Place, Anacortes, WA 98221.

3 Bedrooms, 4.25 Baths. MLS# 29134785.

Architectural masterpiece is builder's commitment to honor precious resources on our delicate planet. Sleek lines rising from rock elevate the drama of this magnificent home on .34 acre. Doors that roll aside so you can drink in the views. Radiant floors of scored concrete, natural stone and three-quarter-inch quarter-sawn oak. Elegant appliances on seamless cabinets crafted from a single tree. Ultimate, understated main level luxury. 3 Bedrooms, 4.25 baths, plus private movie-ready suite for theatre/studio/teen. &quot;Green&quot;, Zen, and sturdy like the rock it's built on. Located in new low-impact (to the environment) development on the island's west side. One of 11 beautiful lots that share acres of wooded common area.

For more information, contact Greg Crosby by phone at (360) 293-2161, by email at gregoryc@johnlscott.com, or visit John L. Scott online at www.johnlscott.com/gregoryc today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:53</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>Greg Crosby,Anacortes,WA,Washington,real estate,property,homes,for sale,house,realtor,coralroot place</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
