<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Jo Ellen Nash Luxury Estates of Naples Real Estate Video Series</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours from the Naples Florida Region Presented by Jo Ellen Nash of Luxury Estates of Naples, A Downing-Frye Realty Company.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information or to schedule an appointment, please contact Jo Ellen Nash by phone at 239-692-8174, by email at jnash@nashnaples.com, or on the web at www.naplesbuzz.com today.</description>
        <link>http://www.luxuryestatesofnaples.com/</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts.com</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 09:20:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 09:20:27 -0500</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll Mac v2.1 (2.1.0.1); http://www.FeedForAll.com/</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Jo Ellen Nash Luxury Estates of Naples Real Estate Video Series</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours from the Naples Florida Region Presented by Jo Ellen Nash of Luxury Estates of Naples, A Downing-Frye Realty Company. Jo Ellen Nash established Nash &amp; Company, a real estate boutique of the highest caliber in the Vail Valley resort market, operating since 1989. Jo Ellen's highly skilled team of Realtor Partners and professionals has been nationally recognized for excellence. In November 2007, Jo Ellen Nash announced the opening of a second office located in Naples, Florida, which specializes in serving the $2 million and over luxury market. Jo Ellen was afforded the privilege of heading up the Luxury division for CKG International and began coaching for them in February 2008. Nash walked away with the two top honors at the 2008 CKG Luxury Conclave.....the Luxe awards for &quot;Best Personal Branding&quot; and &quot;Best Personal Real Estate Website&quot;. Nash has helped hundreds of agents across North America grow their business. Among her awards, Jo Ellen won the award for Overall Excellence in Marketing at the Leaders in Luxury conference in 2006 and, previously in 2004. She and her company are well-known trendsetters in the marketplace. Their service is legendary...including their Client Concierge Program, which offers free perks to their clients such as use of their company stretch limousine, their moving truck, a staging and handyman service and their Real Estate Discovery Center in Edwards. Their amazing marketing tools are considered the best in the business including their Seller and Buyer Books, Memories in the Making magazine, Market Watch reports, custom property websites, a variety of electronic newsletters, neighborhood websites and their company websites and blogs. For more information or to schedule an appointment, please contact Jo Ellen Nash by phone at 239-692-8174, by email at jnash@nashnaples.com, or on the web at www.naplesbuzz.com today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Naples Florida real estate,Jo Ellen Nash,Naples Luxury Real Estate,FL,real estate,Florida,nash and company,real estate video,video tours,realtor,for sale</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/nash_and_company/luxury_estates_of_naples_itunes_300x300.jpg" />
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/nash_and_company/luxury_estates_of_naples_itunes_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Jo Ellen Nash Luxury Estates of Naples Real Estate Video Series</title>
            <link>http://www.luxuryestatesofnaples.com/</link>
            <description>The Jo Ellen Nash Luxury Estates of Naples Real Estate Video Series Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>4501 Gulf Shore Blvd. Penthouse 502, Naples, FL 34103</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 4501 Gulf Shore Blvd. Penthouse 502, Naples, FL 34103.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
4 Bedrooms +Den, 6 Bathrooms, MLS# 208043586.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information or to schedule an appointment, please contact Jo Ellen Nash by phone at 239-692-8174, by email at JoEllen@JoEllenNash.com , or on the web at www.NashNaples.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/697-4501-Gulf-Shore-Blvd.-Penthouse-502-Naples-FL-34103.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/nash_and_company/4501-Gulf-Shore-Blvd-PH502.mp4" length="42395700" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">F291BD8C-9BB5-421B-805C-9D5E53092104-685-00000D535CC11273-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 09:20:37 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 4501 Gulf Shore Blvd. Penthouse 502, Naples, FL 34103. For more info, contact Jo Ellen Nash by phone at 239-692-8174, by email at JoEllen@JoEllenNash.com, or on the web at www.NashNaples.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 4501 Gulf Shore Blvd. Penthouse 502, Naples, FL 34103. 4 Bedrooms +Den, 6 Bathrooms, MLS# 208043586. This unforgettable property is in a class by itself. Located in Aria, the final highrise masterpiece to be built at Park Shore, Penthouse North not only offers meticulous details &amp; uncommon luxury but boasts a private rooftop terrace of more than 5000 square feet. After entering the building with its two story lobby and grand staircase, a private elevator will whisk you up to a beautiful entry foyer which sets the tone for this amazing residence to unfold. The living room hosts a wet bar with custom cabinetry, granite counters, and deep bowl stainless sink. The ceiling is adorned by a smoked glass intrically carved chandelier. Large sliding glass doors open onto a terrace that is screened and shuttered. An open yet formal dining room is separated from the kitchen by a pass through, which makes it convenient to entertain. Spectacular floor to ceiling views make any meal an occassion. Banded marble floors easily transistion to the hardwood in the kitchen. A chef's delight, the kitchen has beautiful custom cabinetry, granite counters, and gourmet stainless appliances, including a 6 burner cooktop with a griddle, dbl ovens, a warming drawer, a wine cooler &amp; a 48&quot; fridge. The elegant family room, with a marble fireplace as the focal point and sliders opening on three sides, allows for the best of indoor/outdoor living. Top of the world views will surprise and delight family and guests alike. The Cabana room is a charming entertainment area and a wonderful place to take in a movie or football game. Floor to ceiling windows and pocket sliders overlook Venetian Bay and miles away to downtown Naples. A powder room is located nearby. Two elegant guest suites each have high ceilings, fabulous views and walk in closets. The well-appointed bathrooms have creamy marble floors and burnished umber marble vanity tops with gold fixtures. There is a fully functional office with the latest technology. Hardwood floors, a tray ceiling, and a wall of glass opening to the veranda make it pleasing to work within, if you can take your eyes off the view. The master suite is just beyond the office and is secluded from the rest of the residence, allowing maximum privacy. You enter through double doors to an oasis of luxury, with tray ceilings and a wall of glass doors leading to the outdoors. The master bath has marble floors, rich wood cabinetry, his and her water closets with windows and art niches in each, dual sinks and large mirrors. Marble envelops the jetted Jacuzzi tub and floor to ceiling shower. On the terrace above, which encompasses the majority of the top of the building, you’ll find a full bath, spa, large outdoor bar and grill, shade structure, rooftop garden and multiple outdoor grouping areas. This area is perfect for hosting an exquisite gathering of four or forty, where memories will be made for a lifetime. This terrace is what puts this property in a class by itself! Additional amenities include a 3 car garage, air conditioned storage, a 65 ft swimming pool, a fitness center, men’s and women’s spa, and much, much more...the least of which is the spectacular views. All of this plus World class shopping and dining just a short walk away at Venetian Village. For more information or to schedule an appointment, please contact Jo Ellen Nash by phone at 239-692-8174, by email at JoEllen@JoEllenNash.com , or on the web at www.NashNaples.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:31</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>Naples Florida, real estate,Jo Ellen Nash,Gulf Shore Blvd,FL,real estate,Florida,real estate video,realtor,for sale,condominium</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>28346 Altessa Way, Bonita Springs FL 34135</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 28346 Altessa Way, Bonita Springs FL 34135.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
3 Bedrooms, 3 Bathrooms, MLS# 208021001.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information or to schedule an appointment, please contact Jo Ellen Nash by phone at 239-692-8174, by email at jnash@nashnaples.com, or on the web at www.naplesbuzz.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/509-28346-Altessa-Way-Bonita-Springs-Florida-34135.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/nash_and_company/28346-Altessa-Way.mp4" length="39062896" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0EA78C6C-F94B-4B13-AA3F-411D504C7AB8</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 15:05:25 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 28346 Altessa Way, Bonita Springs FL 34135. For more info, please contact Jo Ellen Nash by phone at 239-692-8174, by email at jnash@nashnaples.com, or on the web at www.naplesbuzz.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 28346 Altessa Way, Bonita Springs FL 34135.

3 Bedrooms, 3 Bathrooms, MLS# 208021001.

Property Description: Jo Ellen Nash of Downing-Frye Realty presents 28346 Altessa Way, Bonita Springs FL 34135.

Located in the popular community of Vasari, 28436 Altessa Way features a total of approximately 2,550 square feet under air, with an oversized two car garage. Recently constructed in 2006, it is one of the premium developer sites right on the lake.  Envision the home of your dreams… it is nestled along the shores of a lake and has endless waterfront views…drenched in sunshine, you feel relaxed and comfortable from the moment you step inside. The ultimate Florida lifestyle is just a step away…  From the tropical foliage that greets you at the arched entrance, to the open flowing floor plan that follows beyond, this home is perfect for the ultimate comfortable lifestyle.

You'll immediately experience a &quot;wow&quot; when entering the foyer, with custom tiled floors and an open flowing floor plan with lake views from just about every room. Timeless architectural details add a touch of class and elegance throughout.  The formal dining room allows for easy entertaining and the kitchen/living room/breakfast room combine to create a spacious feeling throughout. A large breakfast bar provides casual dining and separates the living area from the kitchen.  The functional, yet trendy kitchen is upgraded with granite countertops, beautiful cabinetry and quality stainless appliances enabling your family chef to relish their domain while being part of the activities.  The additional den/office provides a home office, reading room or additional sleeping area.

This single level home is easy to navigate and has a privately located master suite away from the others. A retreat in itself, the bedroom offers volume ceilings and sliding doors which open to the lanai and pool, providing a sense of light and airiness.  His and her walk in closets, a separate jetted tub and glassed in shower and double vanity sinks are just a few of the features of the luxurious master bath. One of two guest suites, each with its own adjacent bathroom offer a welcoming haven to visitors.  Accessible from the dining room or master suite, the beautiful private pool and spa overlooks a 40-acre lake directly to the west. Here you can enjoy a cocktail and take in the magnificent sunset views that Southwest Florida is famous for!


For more information or to schedule an appointment, please contact Jo Ellen Nash by phone at 239-692-8174, by email at jnash@nashnaples.com, or on the web at www.naplesbuzz.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:51</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>Naples Florida, real estate,Jo Ellen Nash,Luxury Estates of Naples,bonita springs,altessa way,FL,real estate,Florida,real estate video,realtor,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>9577 Gulfshore Blvd Suite #803 Naples, FL 34108</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 9577 Gulfshore Blvd Suite #803 Naples, FL 34108.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
2 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms, MLS# 208014672.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information or to schedule an appointment, please contact Jo Ellen Nash by phone at 239-692-8174, by email at jnash@nashnaples.com, or on the web at www.naplesbuzz.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/456-9577-Gulfshore-Blvd.-Suite-803-Naples-FL-34108.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/nash_and_company/9577_Gulfshore_Blvd.m4v" length="37713387" type="video/x-m4v"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B2100379-2777-4225-9F8A-8C8EB0F89942</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 17:22:34 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 9577 Gulfshore Blvd Suite #803 Naples, FL 34108.  For more info, please contact Jo Ellen Nash by phone at 239-692-8174, by email at jnash@nashnaples.com, or on the web at www.naplesbuzz.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 9577 Gulfshore Blvd Suite #803 Naples, FL 34108.

2 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms, MLS# 208014672

Property Description: Jo Ellen Nash of Naples Luxury Real Estate presents 9577 Gulfshore Blvd. Suite #803 Naples, FL 34108.

Property Description: Jo Ellen Nash of Luxury Estates of Naples Downing-Frye Realty presents 9577 Gulfshore Blvd. Suite #803 Naples, FL 34108.

Imagine the sea side home of your dreams....it has views that go on forever under sunny blue skies, cooling sea breezes, glorious sunsets and the sound of waves lapping on the shore. A complete remodel makes this home more open and flowing and consists of the highest finishes and meticulous details. The kitchen is an everyday masterpiece. You’ll delight in the custom cherry cabinets, custom tile and all new stainless steel Monogram appliances and Jenn-air range. A functional breakfast bar with gorgeous slab granite sets the stage for a gourmet performance.

Thoughtful design elements include custom wood paneling on the refrigerator, high tech lighting and a vineyard etching above the range, surrounded by custom tile like this one. Custom woodwork, coffered ceilings and a random plank hardwood floor perfectly complement the softer details, such as the custom lighting and cabinetry. The thoughtful owners replaced the original property with a masterpiece of chosen finishes that showcase the surrounding seascape and keep the home light and airy. The building was built to more recent hurricane codes, which will make it one of the safest buildings to live in when withstanding any future storms.

You'll thrill to discover the master suite, a well-appointed oasis with large walk-in closets and dramatic views under coffered ceilings and a plantation-style ceiling fan. The master bath enjoys coffered ceilings as well as a spacious Euro-style glass shower and gorgeous marble counters, his-and-hers vanities, exquisite custom cabinetry and a charming claw-foot bathtub. The guest suite is a delight with ample room for a queen bed and dresser. The guest suite features a cozy sitting area and attached bath, also with custom tile and cabinetry, and easy access to the laundry with extra storage.

One of the most exquisite homes found in the Sea Chase building, this condominium home is located high on the eighth floor to maximize views from most rooms. The building and lanai on this floor juts out to allow unobstructed views down the beach, which makes it very unique among the other condominiums offered for sale. The western exposure will ensure sizzling sunsets from the comfort of your lanai. Relax next to the sparkling shore-side swimming pool with a sundeck overlooking the Gulf of Mexico or spend your time looking for shells along beautiful Vanderbilt Beach. The beach is just a few steps away, where you can walk down the beach for cocktails at the Naples Ritz-Carlton or try the Turtle Club for a delicious seaside dinner.

For more information or to schedule an appointment, please contact Jo Ellen Nash by phone at 239-692-8174, by email at jnash@nashnaples.com, or on the web at www.naplesbuzz.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:22</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>Naples Florida real estate,condominium,Jo Ellen Nash,gulfshore blvd,Naples Luxury Real Estate,FL,real estate,Florida,real estate video,video tours,realtor,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
