<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Julie Hansen Denver Colorado Real Estate Video Tour Feed</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours in the Denver, Colorado area presented by Julie Hansen of Coldwell Banker Devonshire.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information contact Julie Hansen at 303-717-3935 or check out our website at www.GraysonPlace.com.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.NewCherryCreekHomes.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2008 14:06:38 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2008 14:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Julie Hansen Denver Colorado Real Estate Video Tour Feed. For more information contact Julie Hansen at 303-717-3935 or check out our website at www.GraysonPlace.com.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours in the Denver, Colorado area presented by Julie Hansen of Coldwell Banker Devonshire.

As a top-producing broker, marketer and developer, Julie Hansen brings a diverse background and unique set of skills to home buyers, sellers and builders.  Julie has a strong background in new home construction, from the initial planning and design stages to creating dynamic marketing and sales programs.  A current project, Grayson Place at Third Avenue, located in Denver’s Cherry Creek North neighborhood, was recently honored as “One of Denver’s Top Properties” by Colorado Homes &amp; Lifestyles Magazine.  Julie is a broker with Coldwell Banker Devonshire, Denver’s premiere real estate company strongly rooted in central Denver, and she is an active member of the Denver Board of Realtors.  As a certified Coldwell Banker Previews agent, Julie provides clients with a level of service and skills paramount to buying or selling luxury properties.

Real Estate Video Tours in the Denver, Colorado area presented by Julie Hansen of Coldwell Banker Devonshire.

For more information contact Julie Hansen at 303-717-3935 or check out our website at www.GraysonPlace.com.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>julie hansen,Coldwell Banker Devonshire,Denver,Colorado,CO,real estate,realtor,Cherry Creek North,luxury,for sale,homes,houses</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/julie-hansen/juliehansen_300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/julie-hansen/juliehansen_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Julie Hansen Denver Colorado Real Estate Video Tour Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.NewCherryCreekHomes.com</link>
            <description>The Julie Hansen Denver Colorado Real Estate Video Tour Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>570 Monroe, Denver CO 80206</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 570 Monroe, Denver CO 80206.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
2 Bedrooms, 3 Bathrooms.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information contact Julie Hansen at 303-717-3935 or check out our website at www.GraysonPlace.com.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/503-570-Monroe-Denver-CO-80206.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/julie-hansen/570-Monroe.mp4" length="27384884" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">FFB0A3F1-4253-43CF-AAB1-8EDB7C38B8AB</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2008 14:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 570 Monroe, Denver CO 80206. For more information contact Julie Hansen at 303-717-3935 or check out our website at www.GraysonPlace.com.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 570 Monroe, Denver CO 80206.

2 Bedrooms, 3 Bathrooms.

Property Description: Julie Hansen of Coldwell Banker Devonshire presents 570 Monroe, Denver CO 80206.

European flair and innovation have arrived in Cherry Creek North in these three exquisite new townhomes with private elevators and fantastic mountain views from three levels. Nine foot Mahogany doors usher you in to a light-filled private retreat resplendent with distinctive granites, magnificent stone and mill work and spectacular hardwoods, like reclaimed Hickory and Chestnut.

The main floor features a spacious open floor plan accentuated by a magnificent marble fireplace and granite wet bar. French doors open to a west-facing study with western views and unique barrel-vaulted ceilings. The kitchen features distressed pine cabinetry in an exclusive custom design and simply beautiful tile work with pewter insets. Viking appliances with cabinet finishes and a 54 inch slab granite island as fine as any piece of custom furniture complete the picture. A glass atrium off the kitchen makes for a sunny sitting room or formal dining area and provides convenient access to the outdoor barbeque terrace. More detailed craftsmanship is evident in the powder room, which features a full wall of stone, fine granite and hammered pewter or copper vessel sinks. The first floor is home to a wonderful family or media room with space for several sitting areas. It also hosts a sunny guest suite and another beautifully-designed bath, as well as the entrance to your heated, over-sized two car garage and 1000 square foot basement – custom-finished to suit your needs.

Take the elevator to your private master floor and enjoy more dramatic mountain views from your Juliette balcony under a coved ceiling. Enter your custom-galley closet through glass French doors, and prepare to be amazed. The quality and attention to detail is evident from the cabinets and storage spaces to the adjoining Italian bath, which features five different types of marble, travertine and granite, heated floors, a Bain Ultra Jet Tub and large European-style shower. But just as special are the details you don’t see: like acoustically-engineered floors and the amazing Unico energy system which provides silent and energy efficient heating and cooling. These exquisite homes feature over 4200 square feet of beautifully-designed living space with two or three bedrooms starting at $1,775,000.

For more information contact Julie Hansen at 303-717-3935 or check out our website at www.GraysonPlace.com.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:29</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>julie hansen,Coldwell Banker Devonshire,Harrison Street,Denver,Colorado,CO,real estate,realtor,Cherry Creek North,luxury,for sale,townhome</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>301 Harrison Street Denver, CO 80206</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 301 Harrison Street Denver, CO 80206.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
3 Bedrooms, 5 Bathrooms.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information contact Julie Hansen at 303-717-3935 or check out our website at www.GraysonPlace.com.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/502-301-Harrison-Street-Denver-CO-80206.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/julie-hansen/301-Harrison-Street.mp4" length="23536999" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">65CC48A1-019B-4AB6-9DE2-F711F490F89F</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 13:20:06 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 301 Harrison Street Denver, CO 80206. For more information contact Julie Hansen at 303-717-3935 or check out our website at www.GraysonPlace.com.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 301 Harrison Street Denver, CO 80206. 

3 Bedrooms, 5 Bathrooms.

Property Description: Julie Hansen of Coldwell Banker Devonshire presents 301 Harrison Street Denver, CO 80206.

Imagine a Mediterranean villa with a Rocky Mountain view – right in Cherry Creek North. Now imagine parking in front of your private elevator and taking it to four-thousand square feet of light-filled living perfection. Grayson Place at Third Avenue brings your imagination to life with six exceptional new homes combining the best of single-family living with the ease of a lock-and-leave lifestyle. Named a “Top Denver Property” by Colorado Homes &amp; Lifestyles Magazine, each home is a custom masterpiece – from the hand-selected hardwood and travertine, to the lavish use of the world’s finest granite.

The kitchen is not only gorgeous but functional. With an oversized granite island, 48 inch Viking range, double-oven, warming drawer and walk-in butler’s pantry, the most discriminating of chef’s will be pleased. Rare granites and soft-close knotty alder cabinets in a variety of beautiful finishes make it a joy for cooking or informal dining. The kitchen flows effortlessly into a king-sized great room with 22 foot ceilings, stunning fireplace, surround sound and granite wet bar. A double-set of French doors open up to a spacious west-facing patio, perfect for that outdoor kitchen, spa or terraced garden.

The over-looking loft with fireplace and custom built-ins makes an excellent study or library. Walk through French doors to a second study or media room and one of two private guest suites. Take the elevator to the third floor where your Master Retreat awaits, with his-and-her baths featuring heated floors, amazing stone work, Bain ultra jet tub and beautiful custom closets. Step out onto your private terrace and marvel at the views from Pikes Peak to Downtown Denver.

Colorado’s winters will have you appreciating the heated driveway and the 12,000 square foot heated and secured underground parking garage with space for three vehicles. Grayson Place at Third Avenue. Where your imagination comes to life. Just a short walk to the world-class shops and restaurants of Cherry Creek North. Two and three bedrooms starting at $1,795,000.

For more information contact Julie Hansen at 303-717-3935 or check out our website at www.GraysonPlace.com.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:06</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>julie hansen,Coldwell Banker Devonshire,Harrison Street,Denver,Colorado,CO,real estate,realtor,Cherry Creek North,luxury,for sale,townhome</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
