<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Karen Foust Hillsdale County Michigan Real Estate Video Tour Feed</title>
        <description>Real estate video tours of the Hillsdale County Michigan region, presented by Karen Foust of Goedert Real Estate.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information contact Karen Foust by phone at 800-644-3833, by email at karen@search4realestate.info, or visit her online at www.search4realestate.info today.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.search4realestate.info</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 10:37:58 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 14:51:27 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Karen Foust Hillsdale County Michigan Real Estate Video Tour Feed. For more information contact Karen Foust by phone at 800-644-3833, by email at karen@search4realestate.info, or visit her online at www.search4realestate.info today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real estate video tours of the Hillsdale County Michigan region, presented by Karen Foust of Goedert Real Estate.

It takes more than a sign in the yard and an ad in the classified section to succeed in real estate. It takes an expertise that is the result of an in-depth study of our industry, systematic strategies to help you accomplish your home buying and selling goals and a tradition of service beyond your expectations. When you need real estate expertise, call Goedert Real Estate. 

We take great pride in helping our clients reach their real estate goals. Our Sellers greatly appreciate being involved in the strategy of marketing their homes. Our successful career salespersons know communication is the key! 

In addition, home buyers often comment about our \&apos;no pressure\&apos; selling style. Our gratification comes from helping families find their new homes! 

By working with Goedert Real Estate, you will be working with a group of realtors that have presented a powerful image in Southern Michigan for over 50 years!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>karen foust,Goedert Real Estate,Michigan,MI,Hillsdale County,realtor,houses,homes,property,for sale</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/karen-foust/karen-foust-300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/karen-foust/karen-foust-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Karen Foust Hillsdale County Michigan Real Estate Video Tour Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.search4realestate.info</link>
            <description>The Karen Foust Hillsdale County Michigan Real Estate Video Tour Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>2513 Lilac Road Reading, Michigan 49274</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 2513 Lilac Road Reading, Michigan 49274.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
5 Bedrooms, 5 Baths, MLS# 2824192.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information contact Karen Foust by phone at 800-644-3833, by email at karen@search4realestate.info, or visit her online at www.search4realestate.info today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/538-2513-Lilac-Road-Reading-Michigan-49274.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/karen-foust/2513-Lilac-Road.mp4" length="22032086" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">50CE6BAB-8214-4693-8A26-AC03CB8BB90F</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 14:49:28 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 2513 Lilac Road Reading, Michigan 49274. For more information contact Karen Foust by phone at 800-644-3833, by email at karen@search4realestate.info, or visit her online at www.search4realestate.info today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 2513 Lilac Road Reading, Michigan 49274.

5 Bedrooms, 5 Baths, MLS# 2824192.

Property Description: Karen Foust of Goedert Real Estate presents 2513 Lilac Road Reading, Michigan 49274.

The Rose Cottage was originally built circa 1870 in Cambria, Michigan, a once bustling little town at the close of the nineteenth century near Hillsdale. Over the years, this property was used as a Grange Hall a General or Hardware Store, a Local grocery, and prior to renovation, a single family residence. In 1997, the property was purchased by a retired building contractor and his talented decorator wife. The extensive makeover began in the Spring of 1999 turning what was once a deteriorated structure into its present day beauty. The entire building was stripped of the old building materials, however, an effort was made to salvage the basic structure.

This transformed structure is now three separate apartments. A lower one bedroom one bathroom apartment, a lower two bedroom two full bathroom apartment and an upper studio apartment with two full bathrooms. All units have fully equipped kitchens, separate heating systems and washer and dryer hook-ups. Although the current owners operate this property as a Bed &amp; Breakfast, this property would also be well suited as an investment property. The owners are including all furnishings in the sale. There is plenty of covered parking available for guests or tenants.

The property is within steps of the Cambria park, located on the shores of the Cambria Mill Pond - a favorite fishing spot by many locals. Although this property is situated in a country setting, it’s just a drive to many area lakes, golf courses, antique shops and local theaters.

For more information contact Karen Foust by phone at 800-644-3833, by email at karen@search4realestate.info, or visit her online at www.search4realestate.info today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:50</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>karen foust,Goedert Real Estate,Michigan,MI,Hillsdale County,realtor,houses,homes,property,for sale,Reading,Lilac road</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
