<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Larry Revier South Florida Real Estate Video Series</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours of Properties For Sale in Broward County, Florida Presented by Larry Revier of Remax Partners.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Larry Revier by phone at (954) 396-5959, by email at  larry@trustlarry.com, or visit him online at www.TrustLarry.com today.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.trustlarry.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 09:23:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 09:22:54 -0500</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll Mac v2.1 (2.1.0.1); http://www.FeedForAll.com/</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Larry Revier South Florida Real Estate Video Series. For more info, contact Larry Revier by phone at (954) 396-5959 or visit him online at www.TrustLarry.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours of Properties For Sale in Broward County, Florida Presented by Larry Revier of Remax Partners.

For more information, contact Larry Revier by phone at (954) 396-5959, by email at  larry@trustlarry.com, or visit him online at www.TrustLarry.com today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>south florida,broward county,fort lauderdale,florida,real estate,larry revier,trustlarry,remax partners,for sale,homes,condominiums,realtor</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/larry-revier/larry-revier-300x300.jpg" />
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/larry-revier/larry-revier-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Larry Revier South Florida Real Estate Video Series</title>
            <link>http://www.trustlarry.com</link>
            <description>The Larry Revier South Florida Real Estate Video Series Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>L'Hermitage - 3200 N. Ocean Blvd #510, Fort Lauderdale, FL 33308</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring L'Hermitage - 3200 N. Ocean Blvd #510, Fort Lauderdale, FL 33308.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Sitting on ten acres of beachfront property, L’Hermitage is located on the corner of Oakland Park Blvd. and the newly renovated Galt Ocean mile in the heart of Fort Lauderdale.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Larry Revier by phone at 954-638-9052, or by e-mail at larry@trustlarry.com.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/855-L-Hermitage-3200-N.-Ocean-Blvd-510-Fort-Lauderdale-FL-33308.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/larry-revier/L%27Hermitage.mp4" length="39575158" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C7FAFB57-321C-49D6-8165-D74D2E7206DA-7828-000050A17800B4B0-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 09:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring L'Hermitage - 3200 N. Ocean Blvd #510, Fort Lauderdale, FL 33308. For more information, please contact Larry Revier by phone at 954-638-9052, or by e-mail at larry@trustlarry.com.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring L'Hermitage - 3200 N. Ocean Blvd #510, Fort Lauderdale, FL 33308.

Larry Revier of Remax Partners presents L'Hermitage - 3200 N. Ocean Blvd #510, Fort Lauderdale, FL 33308.

Sitting on ten acres of beachfront property, L’Hermitage is located on the corner of Oakland Park Blvd. and the newly renovated Galt Ocean mile in the heart of Fort Lauderdale. It is strategically positioned on 650 ft. of pristine sand beach, w/ spectacular views of the ocean, intracoastal waterway, and the Fort Lauderdale skyline.

The first impression of L’Hermitage is one of a dramatic entrance, with a personal valet parking service, a 24 hr. attended security lobby w/monitoring camera’s, a professional concierge service, and an elegantly furnished grand lobby. The L'Hermitage community features include a handsome brick paved promenade leading into the grounds; The resort like features include a tennis center with a viewing pavilion; and two acre’s of a beautifully maintained private pool club which includes two swimming pools, a sun deck with a poolside café’, a toddler pool, a whirlpool spa, a convenient dog run, a barbecue area that overlooks the ocean, and private beach cabanas w/full time attendants that are literally right on the sand!

As you enter this lovely unit, the impact of the magnificent view is immediate and confirms all the reasons you are considering an oceanfront property. The open floor design offers a feeling of a relaxed environment that quickly transports you from the outside world to an exclusive ‘at home’ experience. This is truly the L’hermitage experience! The spacious master suite w/floor to ceiling sliding glass doors leads to an oversized terrace, and includes his and her walk-in closets. The his and her's bathrooms are accentuated w/ imported marble floors, a luxurious roman tub w/whirlpool, a glass enclosed marble shower, custom vanities with marble tops, and a make-up area, making this master suite exceptional! 

The second bedroom off the master as well offers a gorgeous ocean view and is wired to accommodate office use if desired, and the spacious third bedroom has garden and ocean views and a good size closet. The kitchen is magnificently designed with custom granite counter tops, an island, and a double sink and double oven. The exclusive European style cabinetry is custom designed for L’Hermitage, and the built in pantry and marble floors are just another expression of professional quality design. When you walk out onto the balcony of this unit, it is as if you are standing on water! Day or night rain or shine the experience will certainly unleash your senses to new heights.

Additional residence features include double entry doors, nine foot ceilings, tinted glass sliding doors for maximum ocean and city skyline views, spacious wrap around terraces with glass railings, and state of the art medical and security systems. Other building features include a full equipped business center with a boardroom, a beautifully appointed card room, a sports lounge with billiards and a wide screen television, private and semi-private elevators, a covered parking garage, bicycle storage and a health and fitness spa w/state of the art equipment. 

For more information, please contact Larry Revier by phone at 954-638-9052, or by e-mail at larry@trustlarry.com.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>04:18</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>broward county,fort lauderdale,florida,real estate,L'Hermitage,waterfront,larry revier,ocean blvd,remax partners,for sale,condominium,realtor</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Playa Del Mar - 3900 Galt Ocean Drive #1503, Fort Lauderdale FL 33308</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Playa Del Mar - 3900 Galt Ocean Drive #1503, Fort Lauderdale FL 33308.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A 2 Bedrooms, 2 Bath Condominium. MLS# F929761&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Larry Revier by phone at (954) 396-5959, by email at  larry@trustlarry.com, or visit him online at www.TrustLarry.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/513-Playa-Del-Mar-3900-Galt-Ocean-Drive-1503-Fort-Lauderdale-FL-33308.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/larry-revier/Playa-Del-Mar-1503.mp4" length="37872379" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B75C02E3-348F-4216-A228-D690751936D0</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 2 Jul 2008 11:02:38 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Playa Del Mar - 3900 Galt Ocean Drive #1503, Fort Lauderdale FL 33308. For more info, contact Larry Revier by phone at (954) 396-5959 or visit him online at www.TrustLarry.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Playa Del Mar - 3900 Galt Ocean Drive #1503, Fort Lauderdale FL 33308.

A 2 Bedrooms, 2 Bath Condominium. MLS# F929761.

Property Description: Larry Revier of Remax Partners presents Playa Del Mar - 3900 Galt Ocean Drive #1503, Fort Lauderdale FL 33308.

Where do you see yourself at the end of a long day? Where do you see yourself on a perfectly blue Saturday morning, not a cloud in the sky? Where do you see yourself Sunday afternoon at about 5 p.m.? Is this what you had in mind? We think it’s the perfect place for you.

This is Playa Del Mar, one of the finest luxury condominiums on the internationally known, Galt Ocean Mile. This is where the sand meets the steps that take you to an ocean side condo tailor made for the South Floridian Soul. Once you arrive you will experience a scene that will take your breath and your mind to new horizons. A huge master suite lures you with views of the surf , a walk in closet, an extra closet, AND a linen closet to complete the package. Neutral colors lend to a peaceful bright feel Add to that the well designed bedroom/ den built-ins , and you’ve got a winner!

The recently renovated stunning glass balcony of your new residence will afford you the pleasure of enjoying your breakfast to the tune of a majestic sunrise, and the quiet of a private ocean panoramic view, what could be more magnificent! This elegant building with 24 hour front desk service, impact windows, a car wash, bike storage and brand new elevators, featuring marble walls and teak wood floors, creates an ambiance that simply says 'you're home' - oh and don’t forget to bring your pet and even your motorcycle if you feel inclined. The amenities consisting of three new gyms, a lap size pool , and a library/card playing room, make it all the more appealing to the active resident.

Welcome to Playa Del Mar...Welcome to your new home, we hope you stay awhile.

For more information, contact Larry Revier by phone at (954) 396-5959, by email at  larry@trustlarry.com, or visit him online at www.TrustLarry.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:40</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>broward county,fort lauderdale,florida,real estate,playa del mar,waterfront,larry revier,trustlarry,remax partners,for sale,condominium,realtor</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
