<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Marcos Mendiola Miami Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours from Marcos Mendiola of ReMax Advance Realty, serving the Miami areas of Brickell, Coconut Grove, Coral Gables and Miami Beach.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information on this property or to view other luxury listings in the greater Miami area, contact Marcos Mendiola at 305-331-0068. Sellers, if you&apos;d like your property superbly marketed and showcased in video, contact Marcos today.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.agentcasts.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts.com</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 10:42:21 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 10:42:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Marcos Mendiola Miami Real Estate Video Feed. For more information on this property or to view other luxury listings in the greater Miami area, contact Marcos Mendiola at 305-331-0068.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours from Marcos Mendiola of ReMax Advance Realty, serving the Miami areas of Brickell, Coconut Grove, Coral Gables and Miami Beach.

Marcos Mendiola has been in the business for about five years, and works with a team of two other agents allowing him to give proper attention to each and every client.  Marcos uses new methods of advertising and marketing such as video to keep him ahead of the competition.  His clients can expect loyalty, honesty, and commitment from him to get them into the right home quickly and without any hassle.

For more information on this property or to view other luxury listings in the greater Miami area, contact Marcos Mendiola at 305-331-0068. Sellers, if you&apos;d like your property superbly marketed and showcased in video, contact Marcos today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Miami real estate,marcos mendiola,remax advance realty,brickell key,cocount grove,coral gables,miami beach,florida,realtor,homes,condominiums</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/marcos_mendiola/marcos_mendiola_iTunes_300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/marcos_mendiola/marcos_mendiola_iTunes_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Marcos Mendiola Miami Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com</link>
            <description>The Marcos Mendiola Miami Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>Three Tequesta: 848 Brickell Key Drive #3203 Miami, FL 33131</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 848 Brickell Key Drive #3203 Miami, FL 33131 at Three Tequesta.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This condominium features 1 Bedrooms and 1.5 Baths.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information on this property or to view other luxury listings in the greater Miami area, contact Marcos Mendiola at 305-331-0068. Sellers, if you&apos;d like your property superbly marketed and showcased in video, contact Marcos today.</description>
            <link>http://sef.mlxchange.com/Pub/EmailView.asp?r=1939618018&amp;s=SEF&amp;t=SEF</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/marcos_mendiola/Tequesta_Three.mp4" length="24814096" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">01A12C70-0844-4395-86B3-44B28EEACAF4</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:47:18 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 848 Brickell Key Drive #3203 Miami, FL 33131 at Three Tequesta.  This condominium features 1 Bedrooms and 1.5 Baths.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 848 Brickell Key Drive #3203 Miami, FL 33131 at Three Tequesta.  

This condominium features 1 Bedrooms and 1.5 Baths.

Property Description: Located on the 44-acre island of Brickell Key, in Miami, Florida, Three Tequesta Point is conceived in every exquisite detail to create a luxurious residential tradition on the bay in this historic and premier location. The magnificent double height lobby is finished in European stone and mill work with a vaulted dome ceiling, colonnades and glass interior railings, and is adorned with signature Tequesta Indian bronze sculpture by Manuel Carbonell.

The 1 bedroom /1 and 1/2 bath unit features the best views in the entire building, and offers a luxurious living area which is accentuated by countless refined details, including spectacular marble throughout. The kitchen is equipped with gorgeous granite countertops and is adorned by a premium assortment of high end appliances for your convenience. It provides ample storage space to suit your lifestyle, and offers everything you&apos;d expect to find...and more. The large master bedroom serves as a relaxing and pampering retreat, offering the perfect balance between simplicity and luxury for you to unwind within. The spacious master bath is perfectly aligned as expected, with exquisite counter tops, an included bidet, and an inspiring glass shower with a premium jetted tub.

Step out onto the awe-inspiring balcony for endless, incredible bay, city and ocean views complimented by year-round bay breezes. The panorama of the Miami skyline is truly yours, with a depth and perspective that is certain to amaze time and time again. The amenities at Three Tequesta are truly second to none. Enjoy the sun in the 30 meter heated pool which is surrounded by gardens, poolside pergolas, a convenient barbecue and grille area, and 2 whirlpool spas, or take in a quality game of tennis on the 5th floor courts to stay on your game. The building&apos;s Health Club features state-of-the-art exercise equipment, an aerobics studio, saunas and even message therapy for the utmost in rejuvenation. 2 squash and 2 racquetball courts are also included for sport, play and enjoyment.

Tequesta Point is situated within the wealth of Brickell Key amenities including shops, restaurants, and waterfront promenades. It is linked to the city of Miami&apos;s abundant cultural and commercial attractions mere moments away by a short scenic causeway - placing you just seconds from all the amenities Miami has to offer but safe and secure on Brickell Key.

For more information on this property or to view other luxury listings in the greater Miami area, contact Marcos Mendiola at 305-331-0068. Sellers, if you&apos;d like your property superbly marketed and showcased in video, contact Marcos today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:23</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>Miami real estate,marcos mendiola,remax advance realty,brickell key,three tequesta point,luxury real estate,miami beach,florida,realtor,homes,condominiums</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Carbonell: 901 Brickell Key Blvd #1209 Miami, FL 33131</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 901 Brickell Key Blvd #1209 Miami, FL 33131 at Carbonell.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This condominium features 2 Bedrooms and 2.5 Baths.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information on this property or to view other luxury listings in the greater Miami area, contact Marcos Mendiola at 305-331-0068. Sellers, if you&apos;d like your property superbly marketed and showcased in video, contact Marcos today.</description>
            <link>http://sef.mlxchange.com/Pub/EmailView.asp?r=1286145604&amp;s=SEF&amp;t=SEF</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/marcos_mendiola/Carbonell.mp4" length="26295156" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">54E0DE6C-B8CE-4D5C-B4D4-6077513C781F</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 08:40:26 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 901 Brickell Key Blvd #1209 Miami, FL 33131 at Carbonell.  This condominium features 2 Bedrooms and 2.5 Baths.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 901 Brickell Key Blvd #1209 Miami, FL 33131 at Carbonell.  

This condominium features 2 Bedrooms and 2.5 Baths.

Property Description: Of all the places and ways to live in South Florida, only one has the signature lifestyle of Carbonell, a condominium residence on Brickell Key. The Carbonell&apos;s exclusive tropical island is just a few hundred yards from the fast lane of downtown Miami and the Brickell financial district. The impressive entrance ushers you into a double height lobby accented with maple, marble and water. A dramatic lobby terrace overlooks the river, and Manuel Carbonell&apos;s signature bronze sculpture presides over all.

The 2 bedroom, 2 and a half bath unit offers a level of style and luxury which is perfectly suited in context, with water views from every room and 24 inch marble throughout. The open layout of the main living area inspires a sense of sophisticated island living, with superb attention to the smallest of details around every corner. The kitchen features Black Impala granite countertops with full height backsplashes, Italian designer cherrywood cabinets, a Wine cooler, stainless steel appliances including a Sub-Zero refrigerator, a Miele dishwasher, a Miele ceramic cooktop stove and oven, and an integrated microwave, and a Double Franke stainless sink with a disposal.

The master bedroom offers plenty of room and truly spectacular views, along with a California style walk-in closet. The master en suite features Marble vanity tops, a toilet and bidet in a separate room, an exquisite glass-enclosed shower, and even a relaxing and inviting jacuzzi. The second bedroom can be used to suit a wide variety of needs and lifestyles, and offers it&apos;s own unique and amazing view of the gorgeous Miami skyline. Stepping out onto the spectacular balcony is an awe-inspiring experience, with full sweeping water views and an entire panorama of beauty available for your senses. This majestic and tranquil landscape must be personally experienced to be fully understood.

The building&apos;s amenities are second to none, and include luxurious rooftop tennis courts, an Infinity edge, 30-meter heated bayfront pool with whirlpool spa, a Bi-level fitness center with cardiovascular and weight training equipment, Multipurpose exercise rooms for dance, yoga and other workout regimes, as well as tennis, racquetball and squash courts. The Carbonell is conveniently situated within the wealth of Brickell Key amenities – including shops, restaurants, and waterfront promenades. Pamper yourself with this perfect balance of art, design, space, and privacy. Views without end, separation without distance, and luxury without compromise.

For more information on this property or to view other luxury listings in the greater Miami area, contact Marcos Mendiola at 305-331-0068. Sellers, if you&apos;d like your property superbly marketed and showcased in video, contact Marcos today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:34</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>Miami real estate,marcos mendiola,remax advance realty,brickell key,carbonell,luxury real estate,miami beach,florida,realtor,homes,condominiums</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
