<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Mike Malferrari Alexandria Virginia Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours from Alexandria, Virginia Region Presented By Mike Malferrari of Avery Hess Realtors.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information contact Mike Malferrari of Avery Hess Realtors by phone at (703) 399-5774, by email at mmalferrari@averyhess.com, or visit him online at www.mikemalf.com.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.mikemalf.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts.com</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 4 May 2008 18:24:31 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Sun, 4 May 2008 08:50:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.9) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Mike Malferrari Alexandria Virginia Real Estate Video Feed.  For more information contact Mike Malferrari of Avery Hess Realtors by phone at (703) 399-5774, or by email at mmalferrari@averyhess.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours from Alexandria, Virginia Region Presented By Mike Malferrari of Avery Hess Realtors.

About Mike Malferrari:

My specialty is tracking the real estate market in Alexandria, Virginia - more specifically the zip codes 22315 and 22310 which comprise Kingstowne and Franconia. If you are looking to buy, sell or rent in Alexandria, I am your specialist. Other agents tout their years of experience. But experience only counts if it is relevant experience. Since I specialize in my area, the knowledge that I have of my local market is relevant and current. Other agents tout their sales volume. But this is achieved by covering a wider area. I do not spread myself thin. I will not pretend to know the market if it is not an area I cover. I would rather refer you to another specialist than lie and pretend that I have the local knowledge. Try my services, you will not be disappointed.

For more information contact Mike Malferrari of Avery Hess Realtors by phone at (703) 399-5774, by email at mmalferrari@averyhess.com, or visit him online at www.mikemalf.com.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Mike Malferrari,Avery Hess Realtors,Alexandria,Virginia,VA,real estate,for sale,kingstowne,franconia,realty,real estate video,video tours</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/mike_malferrari/malferrari_itunes_300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/mike_malferrari/malferrari_itunes_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Mike Malferrari Alexandria Virginia Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.mikemalf.com</link>
            <description>The Mike Malferrari Alexandria Virginia Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>7112 Snug Harbor Court Alexandria, VA 22315</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 7112 Snug Harbor Court Alexandria, VA 22315.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information contact Mike Malferrari of Avery Hess Realtors by phone at (703) 399-5774, by email at mmalferrari@averyhess.com, or visit him online at www.mikemalf.com.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/459-7112-Snug-Harbor-Court-Alexandria-VA-22315.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/mike_malferrari/7112_Snug_Harbor_Court.mp4" length="23388938" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">E36C624F-8EBF-41F5-AC70-E2F286F9EB88</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 4 May 2008 08:50:44 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 7112 Snug Harbor Court Alexandria, VA 22315. For more info contact Mike Malferrari by phone at (703) 399-5774, by email at mmalferrari@averyhess.com, or visit him online at www.mikemalf.com.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 7112 Snug Harbor Court Alexandria, VA 22315.

3 Bedrooms, 3.5 Baths, Listed at $449,900.

Once in a while an opportunity comes along to purchase a rare piece of real estate property – such is the case with this end-unit lakefront townhouse. There are not too many waterfront properties in Fairfax County, and here&apos;s one offered at an affordable price.

This lovely lakefront property was recently renovated and has 3 finished levels with twenty four hundred square feet of living space, making it feel like a single family home. On the main level you will find a great room, a separate dining room, and a gourmet kitchen. Cherry hardwood floors run throughout this level. The great room is perfect for living and entertaining. It has a wood burning fireplace to cozy up those winter nights. The lake is visible from the windows and the sliding glass doors.

The dining room is spacious and comes complete with a nice bay window. The renovated kitchen has a blend of 36&quot; and 42&quot; custom cabinets. Black granite is used on the countertops to punctuate the natural finish on the oak cabinets, and all stainless steel appliances complete the package. Walk out the sliding glass doors onto a two-tiered deck overlooking Lake D’Evereux. The trellis gives the perfect amount of shade from the afternoon sun. This outdoor space is great for barbecuing, relaxing, or just enjoying the lake. The hardwood floors go up the stairs and continue onto the 2nd floor hallway.

On the second level, you will find the 3 bedrooms, and 2 full baths. The master bedroom has views of the lake from the oversized windows. It has convenient walk-in and reach-in closets. The master bathroom has a double sink and a spacious shower for comfortable preparation. The second bedroom is quite spacious, and even has its own walk-in closet. The basement is fully finished and has a recreation room which can be used as a family room or an office. It also offers a 4th bedroom or a den, as well as a convenient full bath. Welcome to 7112 Snug Harbor Court. Welcome home to a marvelous waterfront property. Welcome home to serenity!

For more information contact Mike Malferrari of Avery Hess Realtors by phone at (703) 399-5774, by email at mmalferrari@averyhess.com, or visit him online at www.mikemalf.com.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:51</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>Mike Malferrari,Avery Hess Realtors,Alexandria,Virginia,VA,real estate,for sale,realty,real estate video,video tours</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>7049 Devereux Circle Drive Alexandria, VA 22315</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 7049 Devereux Circle Drive Alexandria, VA 22315.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information contact Mike Malferrari of Avery Hess Realtors by phone at (703) 399-5774, by email at mmalferrari@averyhess.com, or visit him online at www.mikemalf.com.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/418-7049-Devereux-Circle-Drive-Alexandria-VA-22315.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/mike_malferrari/7049_Devereux_Drive.m4v" length="72976427" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7C959B25-5FCA-4E26-9C9E-878FDFD4F13D</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 08:17:16 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 7049 Devereux Circle Drive Alexandria, VA 22315. For more info contact Mike Malferrari by phone at (703) 399-5774, by email at mmalferrari@averyhess.com, or visit him online at www.mikemalf.com.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 7049 Devereux Circle Drive Alexandria, VA 22315.

4 Bedrooms, 2 Baths, Listed at $619,900.

Amidst the bustle of Kingstowne, a convenient location close to town center, easy access to major commuting arteries, come home to an oasis offered by this immaculate colonial in Lake Devereux. The size of this home is ideal and the layout is perfect. The floor plan is great with living areas suitable for entertaining and private areas offering respite from the daily grind.

Enter thru these stately double doors into an inviting foyer. The hardwood floors were installed in 2005. They are wide plank maple strips. Sub-flooring supports were strengthened to lay the strips length-wise, creating a more dramatic and flowing entrance into your new home.

The formal living room beckons on the right and is perfect for welcoming a party of family and friends. The windows bring in plenty of light. But the double pane, low-e, vinyl windows also provide good insulation from outside elements.  All windows in the house were replaced in 2004. The house also received new carpeting and neutral designer paint colors in 2005.

Unwind in the step down family room with 9 foot ceilings and sliding glass doors to the deck. Fire up the gas fireplace and warm up the area during the cooler seasons. Continue the party with drinks served from the wet bar. Serve more après meal dishes in the breakfast area or sit at the pass- thru bar to the kitchen and chat while meals are prepared.

The rest of the main level contains the spacious powder room, a den which could be your fifth bedroom or an office, a laundry room and 2 car garage.  The whole house security panel is located in the laundry room and a mobile control is kept in the master bedroom. The HVAC and water heater were replaced in 2005 and are colocated in the laundry area. The second level contains the master bedroom, 3 other bedrooms, and 2 full baths.

This spacious master bedroom is lit by windows and a huge skylight.  The master bedroom has a walk-in closet and a full bathroom. The walk-in closet is gargantuan and is the size of a Manhattan apartment. The rest of the bedrooms are generously sized.

From the family room, thru the sliding glass doors, walk out to the two level deck and you are surrounded by the natural beauty of the home’s richly landscaped yard. The yard is isolated by a board on board rear and side yard fence.  This private park setting changes beautifully with each season. The cold season brings in the serenity of white snow, transforming this park to a winter wonderland. The spring season brings the blooms and the greenery and this backyard turns into a Monet landscape. Celebrate the long days of summer with backyard parties and barbecue. Relish the cool crisp autumn air with the reds, the golds of the surrounding trees and plants. The lower deck has fixed benches for guest seating and movable wood cubes do double duty as additional seating or side tables.  The upper deck has a pergola and fixed bench seating and the upper deck has been reinforced to accept a hot tub.  The yard is wired for low voltage accent lighting.

Within walking distance to the Kingstowne shops and cinemas, within 4 miles from 3 Metro Stations and one Virginia Railway Express Station, with easy access to Fort Belvoir, Coast Guard Station, Interstate 95, 495, 395 and the Fairfax County Parkway, welcome to 7049 Devereux Circle Drive. Welcome to your new home.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>5:59</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>Mike Malferrari,Avery Hess Realtors,Alexandria,Virginia,VA,real estate,for sale,realty,real estate video,video tours</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>7203 Lake Cove Drive Alexandria, VA 22315</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 7203 Lake Cove Drive Alexandria, VA 22315.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information contact Mike Malferrari of Avery Hess Realtors by phone at (703) 399-5774, by email at mmalferrari@averyhess.com, or visit him online at www.mikemalf.com.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/component/option,com_myblog/show,7203-Lake-Cove-Drive-Alexandria-VA-22315.html/Itemid,108/</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/mike_malferrari/7203_Lake_Cove_Drive.mp4" length="45572135" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7FB01B25-84C8-481A-B8C6-45E381320F4F</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 12:39:02 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 7203 Lake Cove Drive Alexandria, VA 22315.  For more information contact Mike Malferrari of Avery Hess Realtors by phone at (703) 399-5774, by email at mmalferrari@averyhess.com, or visit him online at www.mikemalf.com.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 7203 Lake Cove Drive Alexandria, VA 22315.  For more information contact Mike Malferrari of Avery Hess Realtors by phone at (703) 399-5774, by email at mmalferrari@averyhess.com, or visit him online at www.mikemalf.com.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>5:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>Mike Malferrari,Avery Hess Realtors,Alexandria,Virginia,VA,real estate,for sale,realty,real estate video,video tours</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
