<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Mitch Roye Orange County California Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real estate video tours from the Orange County, CA region presented by Mitch Roye of Pacific Oak Real Estate Solutions, LLC.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For information, please contact Mitch Roye by email at mitchroye@gmail.com or by phone at (949) 725-9282 today! &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.pacificoakres.com/</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2008 10:17:53 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2008 10:17:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <generator>FeedForAll Mac v2.1 (2.1.0.1); http://www.FeedForAll.com/</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Mitch Roye Orange, California Real Estate Video Feed</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real estate video tours from the Orange County, CA region presented by Mitch Roye of Pacific Oak Real Estate Solutions, LLC.

Real Estate Investments (REOs, Notes)

For information, please contact Mitch Roye by email at mitchroye@gmail.com or by phone at (949) 725-9282 today!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Mitch Roye,Orange County,California,CA,real estate,home,house,for sale,newport beach,realty,property,for sale</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/mitch-roye/mitch-roye-300x300.jpg" />
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/mitch-roye/mitch-roye-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Mitch Roye Orange County California Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.pacificoakres.com/</link>
            <description>The Mitch Roye Orange County California Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>88 Baycrest Court, Newport Beach, CA 92660</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 88 Baycrest Court, Newport Beach, CA 92660.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
3 Bedrooms, 3 Baths.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For information, please contact Mitch Roye by email at mitchroye@gmail.com or by phone at (949) 725-9282 today! </description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/668-88-Baycrest-Court-Newport-Beach-CA-92660.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/mitch-roye/88-Baycrest-Court.mp4" length="35828779" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">DFCF1A8A-6B70-48F9-B25E-C9DF33256344-464-0000047DD0E94CC5-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2008 10:17:51 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 88 Baycrest Court, Newport Beach, CA 92660. For information, please contact Mitch Roye by email at mitchroye@gmail.com or by phone at (949) 725-9282 today!</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 88 Baycrest Court, Newport Beach, CA 92660.

3 Bedrooms, 3 Baths.

Property Description: Mitchell Roye presents 88 Baycrest Court, Newport Beach, CA 92660.

Welcome to the Back Bay of Newport Beach, a 752 acre nature preserve with miles of trails and endless scenic views. Quietly tucked away in the Back Bay is the community of Bayview Court. This community is superbly maintained and professionally landscaped with lush foliage and well manicured greenbelts throughout. Situated in a premium view location of the community is 88 Baycrest Court, a 1,900 sq ft. 2 story home with 3 bedrooms and 3 baths.

This home is beautifully decorated with walnut hardwood floors, travertine stone, custom carpet and plantation shutters throughout. Off the main entryway is the third bedroom, which can also be used as an office, den or media room. Around the corner from the den is the laundry room and attached 2-car garage. The den is equipped with a full closet and full guest bath. Toward the main area of the home is the living room, dining room and kitchen. The living room faces the east and receives the full morning sun. A welcome addition to this living room is the wood burning fireplace with matching travertine stonework. This fireplace is also equipped for gas.

Enjoy quite entertaining on your private patio surrounded by lush tropical foliage. Conveniently located off the kitchen, the dining room can accommodate a large table for entertaining and family get togethers. The kitchen has all new appliances, including a gas stove, travertine stone floors, recessed lighting, and a breakfast nook. The two master suites are located on the second floor. Each room is equipped with full closets, full baths and high vaulted ceilings.

This second bedroom has 20 ft. vaulted ceilings, mirrored closets and a full bath. The oversized master suite is one of the largest you will find and can easily accommodate a king size bed and a full complement of furniture. 20 ft. vaulted ceilings give an air of expansiveness and spaciousness. The master bath includes a large his and her sink, and a sunken tub and shower. The master bath also includes a private bathroom and plenty of storage space. The walk in closet is well appointed with custom shelving and plenty of space. Off your master suite is the balcony which overlooks the pool and commands a superb view of the hills, the morning sun and gentle breezes. Please contact us for more information.

For information, please contact Mitch Roye by email at mitchroye@gmail.com or by phone at (949) 725-9282 today! </itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:01</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>Mitch Roye,Orange County,California,CA,Baycrest Court,real estate,townhouse,condo,home,house,for sale,newport beach,realty,property,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
