<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Rachel Trevino Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real estate video tours presented by Rachel Trevino.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, visit Rachel Trevino online at www.racheltrevino.net.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://racheltrevino.net/</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts.com</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 3 Apr 2008 17:58:53 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Thu, 3 Apr 2008 17:58:39 -0500</pubDate>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Rachel Trevino Real Estate Video Feed.  Serving the areas of Arlington, Grand Prairie, Mansfield, Fort Worth , Euless,Bedford, Grapevine, and DFW Metroplex in Texas.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real estate video tours presented by Rachel Trevino.

Professional qualifications:

DFW NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF REAL ESTATE PROFESSIONALS

RELOCATION SPECIALIST

Specializing in:

    * New Homes
    * Corporate Relocation
    * BiLingual
    * Relocation
    * Investment, Commercial &amp; Income Property
    * Buyer Representation

Languages Spoken:

    * English
    * Spanish

Contact us for Expert Advice on

    * Buying
    * Selling
    * Mortgage Loans
    * Best Deals on Mortgages
    * Low Down Payment Mortgages
    * Appraisals
    * Best Buys
    * Good Deals
    * Local Attractions
    * Local Schools
    * Local Churches
    * Best Neighborhoods
    * Great Reasons to Move Here

Specializing in these Areas

    * Arlington, Grand Prairie, Mansfield,Fort Worth , Euless,Bedford, Grapevine,DFW METROPLEX

For more information, visit Rachel Trevino online at www.racheltrevino.net</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Rachel Trevino, Dallas,Texas,TX,Arlington,real estate,realtor,grand prarie,mansfield,fort worth,bedford,grapevine</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/rachel_trevino/Rachel_Trevino_iTunes_300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/rachel_trevino/Rachel_Trevino_iTunes_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Rachel Trevino Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://racheltrevino.net/</link>
            <description>The Rachel Trevino Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>2671 Creekwood Drive Cedar Hill, TX 75104</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring  2671 Creekwood Drive Cedar Hill, TX 75104.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information contact Rachel Trevino by phone at (817) 881-9276, by email at rachel@racheltrevino.net, or visit her online at www.racheltrevino.net.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/421-2671-Creekwood-Drive-Cedar-Hill-TX-75104.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/rachel_trevino/2671Creekwood.m4v" length="52902125" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">95CDC18B-0A6F-415D-88FE-40ED05D2BE3C</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 12:01:17 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring  2671 Creekwood Drive Cedar Hill, TX 75104.  For more information contact Rachel Trevino by phone at (817) 881-9276, by email at rachel@racheltrevino.net, or visit her online at www.racheltrevino.net.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring  2671 Creekwood Drive Cedar Hill, TX 75104.  

5 Bedrooms, 4.5 Baths.

Welcome to 2671 Creekwood Drive, Cedar Hill Texas. This gorgeous 5 bedroom, 4 bath masterpiece offers 5070 feet of living space and is perfectly appointed with many luxurious upgrades.

As you enter the home, you are greeted by an amazing foyer with beautiful marble floors, a marble and granite mosaic and a large wrought iron and crystal chandelier. The office has custom wood cabinets, shutters and floors that match beautifully with the wood desk that has a granite top. There is also wayne&apos;s coating on the ceiling. The living room contains a custom slide out wood entertainment center, and a handmade wood fireplace hearth with a granite on top and around.

In the kitchen you will find custom wood cabinets, granite countertops and back splashes, you will also see many built-ins and glass shelving into the living area. Other features include stainless steel appliances, an undermount sink, ceramic tile flooring and textured paint. Here there is custom wood cabinets, granite countertops, a back splash, and custom wood flooring. The dining room contains custom wood flooring, textured paint, crystal chandelier, ceiling and wall trim. All making it a perfect place to host friends or family guests.

The bedrooms all contain shag carpeting, wall trim, ceiling fans and can lighting. The bathrooms have marble and travertine countertops, custom cabinets and glass shower doors. In the Master Bedroom, you will find shag carpeting, wood flooring, marble flooring, a fireplace, a 2 tiered ceiling with ceiling trim, beautiful lighting, and even a fan.

The Master Bathroom has travertine flooring, marble countertops, a shower and tub deck, a fireplace, and nice custom cabinets. The Gameroom comes equipped with custom wood flooring, textured paint, and waynescotting on the walls and ceiling. A wonderful wet bar is showcased featuring onyx countertops. glass shelving, a built in refrigerator, a wine glass holder, a wine rack, an undermount stainless steel sink, and in-the-wall glass and mirrored shelving. There is an upstairs balcony with a view of the pool and the back yard. There is a downstairs covered porch with gas hook up access that is perfect for an outside gas grill. The master bedroom has its own porch access. This approx. 20ft by 40 ft oversized pool with saltwater pump has stairs, two seating areas, and even a waterfall and diving board. Around the pool is a gated area with a large deck and a fireplace.

The large three car garage is perfect for your vehicle and contains custom cabinets. There is also a large attic space above the garage that can be finished out. There is a Work out room attached to the garage it features special flooring, mirrors, cabinets, countertops and a small refrigerator. The Pool bathroom is attached to the work out room. You can enter through the work out room and outside near the pool area. It has tumbled stone flooring, a partial wall and a shower. it also features a pedestal sink, a commode, a cedar bench, and cubby cabinets. in the Back yard there is a side walk to a Pavilion. The pavilion has tile flooring, ceiling fans, drop down lighting, a sink, electricity, and gas hook up access. There is a wooden Play ground by the pavilion with sand. The well maintained Front yard is beautifully landscaped with a nice pebble driveway.

For more information contact Rachel Trevino by phone at (817) 881-9276, by email at rachel@racheltrevino.net, or visit her online at www.racheltrevino.net.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>4:22</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>Rachel Trevino, Dallas,Texas,TX,real estate,realtor,cedar hill,real estate video,for sale,house,homes,video tour</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
