<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Realty 1 Lancaster Pennsylvania Real Estate Video Series</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Property Tours from the Lancaster PA region presented by Realty 1.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact Realty 1  by email at info@realty1.com, by phone at 717-735-7011, or visit them online at www.realty1.com today.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.realty1.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 16:40:37 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 17:00:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Realty 1 Lancaster Pennsylvania Real Estate Video Series. For more information or to schedule an appointment, contact Realty 1  by email at info@realty1.com, by phone at 717-735-7011, or visit them online at www.realty1.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Property Tours from the Lancaster PA region presented by Realty 1.

Realty 1 is a full service Real Estate Brokerage serving Lancaster, Berks, southern Lebanon, Dauphin, and eastern York counties. For almost a quarter century, Realty 1 has been serving our local communities with the skill, experience, knowledge, and passion that you expect from a locally owned business.

Realty 1 Relocation Services provides the corporate community local access to experienced relocation management services. Our local expertise and worldwide affiliation enables Realty 1 to serve customers and clients locally, nationally and internationally. 

Realty 1 ranks highly among the top independent brokers in the region. We offer buyer and seller services, corporate relocation services, commercial and investment properties, and many new home and retirement living communities. 

Visit our web site for easy to use search tools including local and national MLS listings, demographic information, school, weather, and crime reports through our award winning RELO HomeSearch.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Realty 1,Lancaster,Pennsylvania,real estate,Berks,Lebanon,eastern York,homes,houses,for sale,property,Dauphin</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/realty-1/realty1-300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/realty-1/realty1-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Realty 1 Lancaster Pennsylvania Real Estate Video Series</title>
            <link>http://www.realty1.com</link>
            <description>The Realty 1 Lancaster Pennsylvania Real Estate Video Series Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>2 Monument Drive Elizabethtown, PA 17022</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 2 Monument Drive Elizabethtown, PA 17022.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
4 Bedrooms, 3 Baths.  MLS# 130793&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information or to schedule an appointment, please contact Fred Brandt today by phone at 717-295-1515, by email at JustCallFred@realty1.com, or visit Realty 1 online at www.realty1.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/523-2-Monument-Drive-Elizabethtown-PA-17022.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/realty-1/2-Monument-Drive.mp4" length="26008371" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8505542D-3C0B-4EC3-9004-FFDC69EFDA33</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 16:56:34 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 2 Monument Drive Elizabethtown, PA 17022. For more info, contact Fred Brandt today by phone at 717-295-1515, by email at JustCallFred@realty1.com, or visit Realty 1 online at www.realty1.com</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 2 Monument Drive Elizabethtown, PA 17022.

4 Bedrooms, 3 Baths.  MLS# 130793

Property Description: Fred Brandt of Realty 1 presents 2 Monument Drive Elizabethtown, PA 17022.

This picture-perfect model home is a custom built 4800 Sq ft. two story, 4 bedroom contemporary built on a 4.6 acre corner lot. The home was built with superb craftsmanship from one of the region’s most sought after custom builders, and is professionally landscaped and in move-in condition. Stone Creek Estates is a pristine community conveniently located in western Lancaster County, Pennsylvania in the heart of the Susquehanna Valley that consists of 15 unique and simply magnificent luxury home sites.

As you enter the home, you will be greeted by an amazing foyer and a beautiful curved master staircase. The elegant great room offers a spectacular place to relax within and comes complete with a gas fireplace and french doors leading out to the deck. The home features magnificent hardwood floors throughout as well as gorgeous lighted crown molding. The custom, modern kitchen is perfect for preparing meals within and comes complete with stainless steel appliances. A convenient dining area sits just off the kitchen, and offers a superb view out of its windows.

The four seasons or sun room is perfect as a retreat or even an office, and delivers plenty of light as well as splendid views out to the acres of woods and fields beyond. The second floor balcony offers a wonderful view down to the foyer and perfectly compliments the open and airy feel of the home. The main floor master suite is simply stunning, with an elegant vaulted ceiling completing the picture. Also in the master bedroom is even a beautiful sitting area for enjoying both your time and the view. The well-appointed master bath is breathtaking, and features a spectacular tub for unwinding at the end of the day. There is even a marvelous rear deck with an inside/outside fireplace for relaxing with friends or family.

For more information or to schedule an appointment, please contact Fred Brandt today by phone at 717-295-1515, by email at JustCallFred@realty1.com, or visit Realty 1 online at www.realty1.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:14</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>realty 1,Fred Brandt,Elizabethtown,PA,Pennsylvania,house,home,for sale,Lancaster,realtor</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
