<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Steve Hawkins Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours presented by Steve Hawkins, serving the Alexandria and Fairfax Virginia Region.</description>
        <link>http://homesearchwebsite.com/</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts.com</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 17:42:39 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 17:37:46 -0500</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Steve Hawkins Real Estate Video Feed, featuring northern Virginia real estate information along with Alexandria VA homes for sale, Fairfax County VA homes for sale and condos in Arlington VA.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours presented by Steve Hawkins, serving the Alexandria and Fairfax Virginia Region.

You&apos;ve found it! Welcome to your premiere site for all your northern Virginia real estate information along with Alexandria VA homes for sale, Fairfax County VA homes for sale and condos in Arlington VA. If you&apos;re looking to buy, sell or relocate to this beautiful part of the country, you&apos;ve found the number one online source for up-to-the-minute information.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>steve hawkins,virginia,video tour,VA,real estate video,Lorton,Long and Foster,realtor,for sale,Alexandria,fairfax</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/steve_hawkins/Steve_Hawkins_iTunes_300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/steve_hawkins/Steve_Hawkins_iTunes_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Steve Hawkins Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://homesearchwebsite.com/</link>
            <description>The Steve Hawkins Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>8065 Winstead Manor Lane, Lorton VA 22079</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 8065 Winstead Manor Lane, Lorton VA 22079.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Steve Hawkins by phone at 703-451-9400 or by email at Steve@HomeSearchWebsite.com.  You can also visit this home&apos;s custom website online at http://homesearchwebsite.com.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.8065winstead.com</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/steve_hawkins/8065_Winstead_Manor_Ln_%20Lorton_VA_22079.m4v" length="31460175" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D600322E-D2EA-4315-8CF6-302C17F984E9</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 17:29:15 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 8065 Winstead Manor Lane, Lorton VA 22079.  For more information, please contact Steve Hawkins by phone at 703-451-9400 or by email at Steve@HomeSearchWebsite.com.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 8065 Winstead Manor Lane, Lorton VA 22079.

This gorgeous 5 bedroom 4 and a half bath home is both elegant and generously appointed.  This colonial style property sits on a 1/4 acre lot in Fairfax County / Lorton Virginia and is fully ready to be experienced.

As you enter the home, the gorgeous foyer greets you with luxury as you enter the main level.  The wide and spacious floorplan is certain to invoke both the right mood as well as the utmost in comfort.  The living room features beautiful wood floors and amazing attention to detail in every regard, making it the perfect place for entertaining.  The spectacular formal dining room awaits your family and guests, with a beautiful lighting upgrade ready to illuminate your gatherings.

A spacious den is also on the main floor, offering the perfect atmosphere for relaxing and spending quality time enjoying just about anything you&apos;d like.  The magnificent family room is perfect for the whole family, with a cozy fireplace and even a door leading out to the custom deck.  The kitchen offers the utmost in style and functionality, complete with an island, amazing counter tops, 42 inch cabinets, and room for a table to seat eight.

The upper level of the home has four bedrooms for the entire family to relax and spend their time within.  All of the upper level bedrooms are magnificent in both function and presentation, each with its own, unique charm.  The master bedroom is simply stunning, and comes complete with it&apos;s own private sitting room.  The master bathroom has a separate shower, a jetted 2 person soaking tub, a privacy area and 2 vanities.  The lower level has a 5th bedroom, complete with a walk out entrance, and a media / workout room.  There&apos;s even an extra 18x16 room that could be made into a kitchen for an in-law suite if desired.  There&apos;s also an attached 2 car garage and an amazing custom deck which backs into the trees.  The rear view of the home is simply stunning!

For more information, please contact Steve Hawkins by phone at 703-451-9400 or by email at Steve@HomeSearchWebsite.com.  You can also visit this home&apos;s custom website online at http://homesearchwebsite.com.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>02:50</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>steve hawkins,virginia,video tour,VA,real estate video,Lorton,Long and Foster,realtor,for sale,Alexandria,video tour</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
