<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacation Rental Homes Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours featuring vacation rental properties in Deep Creek Maryland, presented by Taylor-Made.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.deepcreekvacations.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts.com</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 13:53:50 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 13:53:42 -0500</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll Mac v2.1 (2.1.0.1); http://www.FeedForAll.com/</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacation Rental Homes Video Feed</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours featuring vacation rental properties in Deep Creek Maryland, presented by Taylor-Made.

Welcome to Deep Creek Lake, where you will fall in love with the area and community as the Taylor family did in 1987, when we first began vacationing here at the lake. Or perhaps you are a longtime resident of the area as the Refosco family has been since 1984. We have combined our knowledge and experience and formed a new property management company: Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations. At Deep Creek Lake, Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations is family-owned and operated to specialize in providing the most memorable family vacations. Our reservationist staff place guests in dream vacation homes every day of the year. Our knowledgeable and caring staff is dedicated to provide you with the best customer service to ensure the most of your vacation. We guarantee we will tackle any request, no matter how big or how small, with a smile. With the immense growth in the area, Deep Creek Lake is in need of a new and experienced property management company with innovative ideas. We have a combined twenty-five years of experience in the property management industry. Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations’ top grade service and high standards will allow us to provide every vacationer their special dream home. Experience does make a difference, as you will see when you let Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations create your worry-free vacation!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,rent,video tours,real estate,homes</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/taylor_made/taylor_made_300x300.jpg" />
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/taylor_made/taylor_made_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacation Rental Homes Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.deepcreekvacations.com</link>
            <description>The Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacation Rental Homes Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cozy Bear Chalet</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cozy Bear Chalet.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/911-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-Cozy-Bear-Chalet.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Cozy-Bear-Chalet.mp4" length="29290382" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9625FA3F-EF76-4979-853F-2D675A53C33B-24493-0000FC797C89D381-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 13:53:48 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cozy Bear Chalet. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cozy Bear Chalet.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>02:25</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Oakland,McHenry,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wynsome Run Lodge</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wynsome Run Lodge.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/899-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-Wynsome-Run-Lodge.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Wynsome-Run-Lodge.mp4" length="32017871" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B07AFC21-2E3E-4807-A0C8-19A1199EABA0-15265-0000997F1FF20A4D-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 16:56:16 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wynsome Run Lodge. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wynsome Run Lodge.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:39</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Oakland,McHenry,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Fir Shore</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Fir Shore.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/900-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-Fir-Sure.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Fir-Shore.mp4" length="30090791" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">752CA6D3-3264-4D96-ACB4-2CC1FF4F2273-15265-0000996F466E4DAA-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 11:35:44 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Fir Shore. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Fir Shore.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:29</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Oakland,McHenry,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Mountain Top Haven</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Mountain Top Haven.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/901-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-Mountain-Top-Haven.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Mountain-Top-Haven.mp4" length="30403458" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C0756E1C-8CD9-4786-A2FB-F62177EF8DCF-15265-00009958A90FE128-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 10:43:49 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Vacation Rentals - Mountain Top Haven. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Vacation Rentals - Mountain Top Haven.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:30</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Oakland,McHenry,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Rocky Top</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Rocky Top.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/888-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-Rocky-Top.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Rocky-Top.mp4" length="26420414" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">876B1659-7759-4C62-8BB1-799077C460EB-10311-0000580FD971E9C3-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 12:08:04 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Rocky Top. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Rocky Top.

Planning your perfect mountain getaway? Then Rocky Top is the home for you. Tucked away at the end of a cul-de-sac, this home offers privacy but is still only a short drive away from all boisterous lake activities. Imagine spending the evening soaking in the hot tub while gazing up at the celestial night sky. A perfect way to relax after a playful day tubing on the lake or snow tubing at Wisp. Grab a mug of coffee and head out to the large covered front porch where you can lounge lazily while breathing in the crisp morning air. Enjoy watching the wildlife scamper around as you take in the magnificent view of Mother Nature at her finest.

The exquisitely decorated great room is the ideal  gathering place. Light a fire, relax on the overstuffed sofa with a good book or pop in a movie for a relaxing night in. There is plenty of room here for the whole group to spread out. Kids and adults alike will fall in love with the lower level family room, where they can join in a playful game of foosball or catch the game on the large TV. The state of the art kitchen will surely please the chef in the family. With its gorgeous granite counter tops and overly stocked cabinets,  meal preparation has never been easier. Family and friends will be sure to enjoy mealtime as they gather around the large dining room table.

You will rest easily in the ample king-sized bed, and the simple yet elegant décor is sure to please. The comfortable mattresses, fresh clean linens, and sumptuous comforters will allow you to sleep peacefully. Away from the bustling sounds of the city, you and your guests will be amazed at how easily you can drift away after a long day of play. Looking for some quiet alone time? Fill up the over-sized jetted tub and prepare yourself for a nice long soak. Therapy 101 at your fingertips! Quiet, comfortable, yet luxuriously furnished, Rocky Top, will exceed your highest expectations. Call today to plan the ultimate mountain getaway that you have always dreamed of.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:09</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Rocky Top,Oakland,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Waterfront Links</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Waterfront Links.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/882-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-Waterfront-Links.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Waterfront-Links.mp4" length="35472434" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">47862873-78C2-47D5-A337-4BE70654FC3B-15949-0000A02CD62B6097-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 10:14:18 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Waterfront Links. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Waterfront Links. Welcome to vacation paradise. Waterfront Links. This exquisite, 5 bedroom home with a private pool is the ideal home for your family and friends. The immaculate, beautifully landscaped home is located in the prestigious community of Waterfront Greens, where you have access to all of its amenities. Mini-golf, tennis, a catch &amp; release pond, and a breathtaking 3 par golf course are all at your finger tips. The private indoor pool will provide hours of endless fun for everyone. Parents will love the convenient yet tastefully decorated additional furnishings in the pool room, which provides the perfect atmosphere for relaxation while the kids splash in the water. The bright yet cozy Great Room will be a favorite place to hang with your friends. The gas fireplace, large flat screen TV, and extremely comfortable furnishings provide a space where memories will surely be made. Worried about space? Don't be, as your family will absolutely fall in love with the additional Family Room. Cue up your stick and engage in a playful game of billiards or catch &quot;The Game&quot; on the wide screen TV. The extra refrigerator, wet bar, and seating make for a pleasant area for all to enjoy. The gorgeous built in gas fireplace will provide the perfect ambiance of tranquility in the winter time. The kitchen, complete with gorgeous granite countertops &amp; beautiful hardwood floors, is not only fully stocked, but boasts of an inviting floor plan. While the chef in the family works his or her magic preparing meals, the rest of the gang can rest comfortably in the dining area or additional sitting space. Plan tomorrow's trip to ASCI or perhaps a picnic at Swallow Falls State Park for your daily agenda. With 5 master suites, Waterfront Links is the ideal home for a couple's retreat. Each bedroom has been elegantly decorated with you, the renter, in mind. Large king sized beds, crisp clean linens, and plush, soft comforters ensure a restful nights sleep for all in this wonderful home. The enclosed deck is the perfect place for your morning coffee. Step away for a moment of solitude, relax, and take in the beauty of the lake before you. Summer is meant for barbecues, and the large deck off the house sets the perfect space to do just this. Afterwards, take a short stroll down the path behind the house to your slip dock where you can take a refreshing dip in the lake. Waterfront Greens is not only a stunning home brimming with all of the amenities, but it is just a short drive away from all lake activities and restaurants. Located in a wonderful community, this home is waiting for you and your loved ones. Call today to reserve Waterfront Links. For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:55</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Angler's Cove,Swanton,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Angler's Cove</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Angler's Cove.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/879-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-Angler-s-Cove.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Anglers-Cove.mp4" length="29596202" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B237BE88-67EF-4CF5-A9EE-A47510B7853C-29903-00013FF90781B03F-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 12:00:28 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Angler's Cove. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Angler's Cove. Do you need to get away from the rigorous demands of city life? Then escape to Angler's Cove, a quaint and beautiful 3 bedroom lakefront cottage located on the western end of the Deep Creek Lake. Appropriately named for its fantastic fishing area, Angler's Cove comes with its own private dock. What better way to beat the summer heat than spending your days swimming and water tubing? Even the family dog won't be able to resist a refreshing dip in the lake. Dock your boat or rent one locally - you will get to witness the stunning beauty of the lake and surrounding mountains from a whole new perspective. In the evening, relax and renew as you take a soak in the the bubbling hot tub. Covered by a stunning gazebo, you will love the serenity of nature that surrounds you. Once inside, you will connect with your nostalgic self as you step back in time to embrace the old lakefront cottage charm. Combining the wonderful characteristics of knotty pine, large wooden vaulted beams, and a grand stone fireplace, the great room will be a favorite place to gather for the whole family. The expansive floor plan allows ample room for everyone to spread out. The kids will enjoy watching a movie or playing board games in the sunny sitting area just off of the great room. Guests will also enjoy the lower level where they can partake in a friendly game of competitive billiards. With a brilliant wood-fire burning in the fireplace, winter nights will certainly be cozy and warm. Meal time is the perfect opportunity to bring friends &amp; family together, which is easily done in this charismatic and well-stocked kitchen. Whether you are serving a gourmet meal or a simple breakfast, having everyone join together around the country accented dining table will create memories for a lifetime. Each bedroom is rich in detail and accentuates the comforting cottage feel of the home. Crisp clean sheets and billowy comforters ensure a restful nights sleep for all. Morning or evening, you will love taking advantage of the two mile walking / hiking trail that borders the waterfront of the home. Imagine spending your every morning and evening embracing the fresh mountain air. It's time to get away. Call today to reserve your stay at Angler's Cove! For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:26</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Angler's Cove,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:block>yes</itunes:block>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Enchantment</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Enchantment.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/880-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-Enchantment.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Enchantment-2.mp4" length="32808480" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">076F0CE7-A887-449F-A277-CC6EC0F6AFE3-29903-00013FE22408E87A-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 12:16:41 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Enchantment. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Enchantment. At the end of a quiet gravel lane, nestled amongst the trees, the home “Enchantment” awaits your arrival. Like past guests, you will quickly become &quot;enchanted&quot; with this stunning three bedroom Tennessee log home. Imagine lazy winter afternoons gathered in the great room. A warm, inviting fire sets the backdrop as you and your family lounge comfortably on the plush leather sofa and watch the snowflakes fall gently to the ground from the large open windows. With three levels of living space, there is more than ample space for everyone in your party to spread out. The lower level family room is an ideal area for the gang to catch the big game on the wide flat screen TV. The newly decorated billiards area is newly accentuated with an exquisite wooden bar. It provides a vibrant, fun atmosphere for spending an evening indoors. Still unsure of how to spend your day? Head over to the theatre room to catch a new release on the big screen, or host a rousing card game at the poker table. The fully stocked kitchen is rich in detail and features elegant hardwood floors, and is sure to please the chef in the family. The dining area not only offers plenty of seating, but boasts beautiful views of the woodlands that surround you. Not only does each bedroom have its own TV, but they will captivate your senses with gorgeous country bedding, knotted pine &amp; groove wood beams, and walls that compliment the atmosphere. Crisp, clean linens and towels are provided for each stay, ensuring you a restful night’s sleep and a worrisome stay. Ready to partake in some adventurous summertime lake activities? Your very own dock slip is just a mere mile away. Or, enjoy the beach at Deep Creek State Park, which is located on the other side of the cove. After an invigorating day on the slopes, nothing says relaxation like a calming soak in the bubbling outdoor hot tub. Breathe deeply and appreciate the fresh mountain air! Whether its morning or evening, you will simply love spending time outside on the wrap around deck. Privacy is yours, and mother nature will surely not disappoint. Secluded and private, yet minutes away from area dining, shopping, and Wisp Resort, Enchantment boasts of all amenities. Whether you are planning a family getaway or a couple's retreat, Enchantment has everything you need for a blissful getaway. Call today to book your vacation! For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:42</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Enchantment,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - No Worries</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - No Worries.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/877-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-No-Worries.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/No-Worries.mp4" length="31392477" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4AEEFAAC-D36C-4907-ACE4-F8CD34A764CE-9989-00005978E9654D31-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 12:35:10 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - No Worries. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - No Worries.

Are you in need of an escape from the worries of everyday life? Are you looking for the perfect retreat to enjoy with family or friends? Vacationing in “No Worries” - an exquisite 5 bedroom mountain chalet with a private pool - will guarantee just that. Imagine walking up each morning to the breathtaking view of a sparkling Deep Creek Lake and the surrounding lushness of Wisp Mountain. After a long day of snow tubing and cross country skiing, you will be ready to immerse yourself in the bubbling hot tub and take in the mesmerizing view of the illuminated ski slopes.

The expansive Great Room with its stunning but simple décor provides the ideal area for the family to gather to reminisce over the day’s exciting events. Ready for a bit of friendly competition? Head to the lower level and rack up the pool balls. Combine a billiard table, a large flat screen TV, and a roaring fireplace and you have the perfect way to spend a lazy fall afternoon. Rainy day and nothing to do? Not with this spectacular private indoor swimming pool. Both the kids and adults will love playing and splashing around. Hours of entertainment are waiting for you.

The culinary artist of the family will love the large overly stocked kitchen with gorgeous granite countertops. Family meal times will be made even more memorable with everyone gathered around the large dining room table or eating outside on the large deck to enjoy the fresh the mountain air. You will rest soundlessly at night on the plush king and queen sized beds. Crisp clean linens and lavish comforters adorn the beds adding to your restful slumber.

This home is ideally located in the heart of McHenry. It is within walking distance to area restaurants, miniature golf, and even an arcade. Want to bring your boat or rent one from a local marina? No Worries is a lake access home with a dock slip that is just across the road and an easy stroll away. Stunning décor with breathtaking views, amenities galore including your own private pool, and a convenient location are all awaiting you when you stay in No Worries, your perfect vacation home. Leave your worries at home and call today to book your much deserved getaway!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Tranquility,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Claralea Lodge</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Claralea Lodge.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/876-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-Claralea-Lodge.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/2-B-R-Retreat.mp4" length="35987171" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">368B5501-8953-42F2-90E6-BA965EEC915D-4261-00001AA40BE6E8BE-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 17:15:27 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Claralea Lodge. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Claralea Lodge.

Claralea Lodge is an elegant 5 bedroom lakefront log home that is ready to open its doors and welcome you inside. Tucked amidst large pine trees and located in a quiet, serene cove on Deep Creek Lake, you and the family will love spending your time lazily lounging on the private dock. 

Located just a short stroll away from the house, this level lakefront is the perfect place to be on hot summer days. Whether you are doing cannonballs off the pier with the kids, taking the boat out for a spin, or trying to reel in the &quot;big one&quot;, countless hours of entertainment are here for you. The covered bubbling hot tub will provide much needed relaxation after a day of hiking and mountain biking. Afterwards, head down to the large outdoor fire pit for some old fashioned s'more making. 

Gather with guests and family in the expansive Great Room. Spacious and bright, it is the definition of &quot;practical&quot; elegance. Imagine curling up in front of the roaring gas fireplace and watching the gentle falling snowflakes flutter about from the large glass windows. A picture perfect way to spend a cold, winter evening. Gather the kids in the lower level and pop in one of the many dvds available from the dvd library. Looking for something a little more exciting? Challenge a pal to an animated game of air hockey. Guaranteed good times!

The chef in the family will love putting his or her culinary skills to good use in the beautiful overly stocked kitchen. Optimal lighting, top of the line appliances, and gorgeous granite countertops add to the exquisite decor of this room. Whether you’re gathering for a large festive feast or a simple light brunch, there is ample room for everyone around the dining room table. Embrace the fresh mountain air and eat out on the large wraparound deck or have lunch down by the water at the picnic table. Sharing memories of the day, family meal time just took on a whole new meaning. 

With three extravagant master suites and comfortable queen sized beds, Claralea Lodge, is also an excellent vacation home for a couple's getaway. Each bedroom is elegantly decorated and has it's own TV. Add to the mix, lovely, plush comforters and clean crisp sheets and you have the perfect combination for a night of peaceful slumber. 

Tucked away from the hustle and bustle of things, Claralea Lodge is still conveniently located near area the Wisp Resort area shopping and restaurants. This dazzling home has something to offer everyone in your group no matter what season. Call today to book this magnificent mountain chalet and prepare for the vacation of a lifetime!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:57</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Tranquility,Oakland,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cedarwoods</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cedarwoods.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/875-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-Cedarwood.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Cedarwoods.mp4" length="22921932" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9E9D6D41-9531-4EFC-BB64-8A079FED2A5D-4261-00001A780EA409B2-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 17:07:26 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cedarwoods. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cedarwoods.

In need of a mountain getaway? Cedarwoods is a beautiful 3 bedroom chalet nestled in the woods and located in the coveted community of Mountainside. After a long day of playing at Wisp Resort, you will truly enjoy spending time in this spectacular Great Room with a fire crackling in the background.

With 3 levels, there will be plenty of room for everyone to spread out and enjoy their space. Take some beverages down to the lower level and make use of the wet bar. Stuck inside on a rainy day? What a great opportunity to take advantage of the game tables on the lower level.  Are you a pool shark or a foosball wizard? No need to choose one above the other in this fabulous abode. Prepare a feast fit for a king in this spacious, overly stocked kitchen. Eat at the dining room table or take lunch outside on the large expansive deck and dine at the picnic table.

Peaceful sleep will be had by all in this home. Ultra comfortable beds, crisp linens, plush comforters and complete lack of traffic and other outside noises will assure that you sleep peacefully. Awake refreshed and rejuvenated in time to head out on the lake for the day.

Don’t forget to take advantage of the community activities that are available such as the tennis, basketball, and volleyball courts. You will be more than ready to take a soak in the hot tub after a long day of playing. Cedarwoods, your perfect relaxation destination is just a call away. Call today to book this wonderful home!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:53</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Tranquility,Oakland,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Tranquility</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Tranquility.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/857-Deep-Creek-Lake-Vacation-Rentals-Tranquility.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Tranquility.mp4" length="23822200" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B4119CBA-DDBA-47EA-A0DC-4661C3A47509-27205-00013FB051A74DB1-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 10:57:57 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Tranquility. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Tranquility.

Long overdue for a relaxing getaway? With a name that promises just that, Tranquility is the perfect home for you. This 4 bedroom home not only boasts exquisite décor, but has a view that will be sure to astound you. The large bubbling hot tub will provide much needed relaxation throughout your stay. Start your day by taking a morning soak and watch as the steam rises from the lake. Does it get any better than this?

With a picturesque fireplace burning in the background, family and friends will love spending time gathered in the Great Room for some lively conversation. Pop some popcorn and let the kids hang out in the lower level family room where they can catch a movie on the large TV. Got your game face on? Head to the lower level for a rousing game of billiards while you catch your favorite sports team on the tube.

Meal time has never been more simple to prepare than in this stately overstocked kitchen. Offering plenty of counter space, makes it a cinch for everyone to chip in and help. Memories will be created as everyone dines around the large dining table. Grilling out? No problem, as the deck access makes it that much easier.

This home is perfect for a couples getaway as the large King and Queen sized beds assure that everyone gets ample sleeping space. Each bedroom is beautifully adorned in eye pleasing colors and elegant decorations. The master bathroom in the loft has a Jacuzzi tub, which is a perfect way to rejuvenate after a long day on the ski slopes. Close to all area amenities, elegantly furnished, and with views to die for, Tranquility is the perfect vacation home for you. Call today to book your mountain getaway!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:58</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Tranquility,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cedar Shores Villa #8</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cedar Shores Villa #8.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/843-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Cedar-Shore-Villa-8.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Cedar-Shores-Villa-8.mp4" length="23282497" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">93ACB094-EBAA-469A-99E7-BD7354AB0532-220-000001288CE8F308-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 11:15:21 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cedar Shores Villa #8. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Cedar Shores Villa #8.

It’s time to escape the boisterous life and partake in some much needed me-time. Cedar Shores Villa #8 is the perfect townhome to do just that. This luxurious 4 BR townhome is perfectly positioned in the heart of Deep Creek Lake. Conveniently located, it is within walking distance to area activities such a miniature-golf and local restaurants, and is a mere 5 minute drive to Wisp Resort.

Family and friends will love hanging out in the expansive great room with it’s beautiful tongue and groove walls and its gorgeous décor. Head down to the lower level for a rousing game of foosball or take advantage of the extra game table, which is ideal for the kids to play a board game. Your inner gourmet chef will be sure to emerge in this state of the art kitchen. Fully stocked, it has everything you need to prepare that perfect meal.

The loft is conveniently equipped with a Queen sized sleeper sofa for extra sleeping space. The elegant master bedroom is located in the upper level. The large king sized bed will allow you to stretch out and slumber soundly after a long day of play. You can even relax and unwind in the over-sized jetted tub. Each bed is made with fine crisp clean linens and sumptuous comforters. And each bedroom is equipped with its own TV, which is another added bonus for your enjoyment.

Ideal location, lavish accommodations, and short stroll to the lake access make Cedar Shores Villa #8 the perfect vacation abode for you. Call today to plan your mountain getaway!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:54</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Cedar Shores Villa #8,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lazy Days</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lazy Days.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/842-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Lazy-Days.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Lazy-Days.mp4" length="20410594" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1E202A07-ACE6-43CA-8D90-C955D0842D25-220-00000101E1B723ED-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 11:13:06 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lazy Days. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lazy Days.

Need to relax and unwind? Plan your next vacation getaway at Lazy Days and spend your days doing just that. This charming 3 bedroom home is conveniently located on top of Wisp Mountain and is a short drive to the Adventure Sports Center and Wisp Resort.

Spend your evenings lounging around the Great Room reminiscing over the day or pop in a movie to watch on the large flat screen TV. Pack a picnic lunch to eat down by the water or prepare a summer barbeque in the superbly stocked kitchen. The dining room nook is the perfect place to gather for brunch before heading out for another adventurous day.

There is plenty of room for the whole family to spread out. Lounge comfortably in the large overstuffed furniture in the lower level family room. Sweet dreams will be had by all when they lie down at night in the luxurious beds. You will awake refreshed and rejuvenated after a night of snuggling into the soft crisp linens and lavish comforters.

After a long day of jet-skiing on the lake or snow tubing at Wisp, you can unwind in the bubbling covered hot tub. Breathe in the fresh mountain air and let the ambiance of Mother Nature surround you. Escape from the rigorous demands of everyday life and take time off to enjoy yourself. Once in a while, everyone just needs a lazy day!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:41</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Lazy Days,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Harvey's Leap</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Harvey's Leap.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/840-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Harvey-s-Leap.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Harvey%27s-Leap.mp4" length="35533676" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C62EE63A-5B04-4E37-91B0-78986E737598-541-00000657441EBB68-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 16:39:22 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Harvey's Leap. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Harvey's Leap.

Once you cross the threshold of this magnificent home, you’ll immediately sense its luxury. You don’t have to go far to realize you’ve made it to paradise. Warm, rich woods; large, sight-filled windows; plush, comfortable furniture and a decor that could rival any ‘home’ magazine photo is what you’ll find in this abode. Your vacation pleasure is guaranteed, as nothing has been overlooked in the motif and furnishings throughout the environs.

Elegance, warmth, and a generous sprinkle of designer touches are found everywhere. A friendly game of pool on this exquisite table will keep you and your guests occupied for hours. Experiment with your favorite recipes in this stunning, gourmet kitchen with every convenience at your fingertips. You’ll enjoy satisfying your guests with your creations—and even the clean-up will be simple. Your family and guests can savor their meal while taking in spectacular views in every direction.

Pamper yourself with a sauna, hot tub, or a relaxing bath in the sizable jacuzzi in the master suite. Your guests will be amazed with their own private area, and will feel exclusive. Every detail has been specially designed for your complete pleasure. Each bedroom contains a flat-screened T.V. And the kids room is loaded with an entertainment center and play room for their enjoyment. They’ll have so much fun and excitement that they’ll remember this outing for years to come.

In addition to being the perfect vacation spot, the amenities are just about unmatched in the vicinity. Play basketball, take a sauna, soak in the hot tub or try sled riding down the substantial hill in the backyard. Fish in the pond, watch the deer and turkey, hike, or even enjoy your own dock space to take a cruise on the lake. Whatever your pleasure, it’s here at Harvey’s Leap.

They say a picture is worth a thousand words, but you really have to see Harvey’s Leap in person to appreciate how marvelous it is. Even a thousand words can’t describe the beauty and workmanship that went into creating this masterpiece. Unique features and high-end finishes enhance the deep creek lifestyle in this lovely home. Take the ‘leap of faith’. You can rest assured that Harvey’s Leap will produce the ideal vacation spot for you, your friends and family. Call today for your ‘piece of paradise’. Take this rare opportunity to vacation in this immaculately kept home!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:55</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Harvey's Leap,Swanton,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Bear Crossing Chalet</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Bear Crossing Chalet.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/838-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Bear-Crossing-Chalet.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Bear-Crossing-Chalet.mp4" length="24094215" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">987AEDDE-0732-4154-9ACE-E3D39F358A0E-374-000003BEFA53E6D1-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2009 10:14:29 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Bear Crossing Chalet. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Bear Crossing Chalet. Need to get away for a little R&amp;R? Bear Crossing Chalet is the place for you. This quintessential mountain log home radiates warmth and comfort. Secluded and private, yet close to all major Lake activities, you will fall in the love with the sheer beauty of this property and the lush wooded view it offers. The expansive deck offers ample seating for your guests and the large gas grill is just waiting to be fired up. Have a long strenuous day playing on the slopes? What better way to unwind and loosen up then a relaxing soak in the hot tub. The family will love gathering in the Great Room to reminisce over the day. With a warm and inviting fire roaring, many more memories will certainly be made. A rainy day and not sure what to do? Head to the lower level where fun and games can be had by all. Cue up your stick and prepare to take on your opponents with a friendly game of billiards. Dinner has never been easier and more enjoyable to make then in this state-of-the art, overly stocked kitchen. Your friends will love to sit around the large dining room table as they take in the magnificent view that Mother Nature provides. Sweet Dreams will surely find you as you rest comfortably on this Queen sized bed. Each bedroom is tastefully adorned in warm inviting earth tones. Simple yet elegant suitably defines these bedrooms. Our luxurious linens and the plush comforters will provide you with the perfect sanctuary for resting up for another day of great adventure. Bear Crossing Chalet is the perfect abode for the renter that wants to get away from the hustle and bustle of everyday life. Peace of mind is just around the corner! For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:59</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Bear Crossing Chalet,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Camelot</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Camelot.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/834-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Camelot.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Camelot.mp4" length="21492935" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0584A1D8-3667-4D8F-B5A9-CA43C9E71751-384-0000038E326D70B6-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 09:53:56 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Camelot. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Camelot.

Need to get away from the hustle and bustle of everyday life? Camelot will allow you to do just that. This magnificent log home is perfectly located on a secluded cul-de-sac but still only minutes from the boisterous activities of Deep Creek Lake. Family and friends will love gathering around a roaring fire in the expansive Great Room as they reminiscence about the day’s events. Stuck inside on a rainy day? No worries. Get your game face on and head down to the Family Room for a rousing game of billiards.

Preparing a meal for the family has never been so easy with this overly stocked kitchen. The additional island counter allows you to really spread out and make use of your cooking space. Whether you are dining in or eating at the picnic table on the large expansive wraparound deck, both offer phenomenal views of Mother Nature. Want to grill up the fish you caught earlier in the day? The large gas grill is conveniently located just outside of the dining room.

Sweet dreams will surely find you as you lay your head down on this grandiose Queen size bed. These bedrooms are simple yet quaint and cozy at the same time. Want to catch your favorite late night talk show? No problem, as each bedroom has the added bonus of having its own television. Late night giggling may be faintly heard as the kids settle down for the evening. Surely they are thinking of all of the fun they had that day swimming in the lake and looking forward to more to come the next day. Even King Arthur would have to agree. Camelot is the ideal vacation home for you and your loved ones!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:46</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Camelot,Oakland,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Sweetwater's Rest</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Sweetwater's Rest.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/833-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Sweetwater-s-Rest.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Sweetwaters-Rest.mp4" length="30624278" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9110775E-7345-402C-872E-3439E2095C94-1616-00001BF2928951D4-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 17:41:12 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Sweetwater's Rest. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Sweetwater's Rest.

Prepare to leave the chaos known as everyday life behind and step into the tranquil world of Sweetwater’s Rest. This lovely lakefront cottage is perfectly located close to Wisp Resort and other area activities. The expansive back yard is perfect for the kid’s to run and play in. Tag you’re it!

In the evening, the group will enjoy winding down by sitting around the big bonfire. Toast some marshmallows and recapture the memories of the day. Whether you just want to relax and unwind or soothe your muscles after an invigorating day on the ski slopes, the outdoor hot tub is exactly what you need. Time for the big game? No problem. Stretch out in the spacious Great Room and catch it on the large flat screen TV.

Meal time will never be easier or more enjoyable than when you are cooking it up in this beautiful kitchen. More than ample counter space and extra cabinet storage are just two of the bonuses you will find. The large dining table allows everyone to sit and enjoy their meal while catching breathtaking views of the lake. This grand fireplace is a major focal point of the house. Imagine cozying up to a warm fire while watching the snowflakes dance around outside. Need some room to spread out? The kids will love the extra sitting area in the upper level. Pop some popcorn, grab a movie, and prepare to enter the world of make-believe. This room also features a gorgeous stained glass window that elegantly captures the sunlight coming off of the lake.

Rise and shine. Imagine waking up to the stunning scene of the sun sparkling off of the lake. Step out onto the deck and breathe in the fresh mountain air. This is one morning when you'll have no desire to hit the snooze button! These bedrooms are not only elegantly decorated, but you will relish the comforting feel of the high fiber linens that are provided for your comfort. The plush comforters will also help ensure a peaceful night's rest. Sweetwater's Rest has everything you need for an impeccable vacation. The perfect lakefront, the ideal location, and the beautiful house provide a complete checklist of must-haves. Call today to book Sweet Water's Rest. Your paradise awaits!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:30</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Sweetwater's Rest,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Serenity on the Mountain</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Serenity on the Mountain.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/832-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Serenity-on-the-Mountain.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Serenity-on-the-Mountain.mp4" length="50378251" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1DD83986-CC64-4FD0-9D86-99B1F0D816EC-1616-0000187093840702-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 17:01:02 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Serenity on the Mountain. For more info, contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Serenity on the Mountain.

Serenity On The Mountain is just what the name suggests. Calmness. Tranquility. Peacefulness. All this, plus a beautiful, modern home in which to experience the true meaning of a vacation. Looking for a new and invigorating way to inspire your employees? This lovely home is the ideal place for a corporate retreat. Creative juices will surely flow as your team envelops the serene nature of this abode. Time for a girl’s getaway? Friendships will only grow stronger as you and your girlfriends take in the peace and tranquility that is Serenity on the Mountain.

Relax by the fireplace in this ‘designed-for-comfort’ living area while enjoying a good book, fantastic view, or just the company you’re with. You don’t need to eat out every day. This state-of-the-art kitchen will make preparing a delicious meal easy - and your guests will take pleasure in gathering around the dinner table for a satisfying meal and casual conversation.

Staying in has never been easier or more entertaining than this. Whether it’s the family, your corporate associates, or the girls, there is plenty to do in the lower level entertainment area. The calming allure of this alcove will surely put everyone at ease, while entertaining them at the same time. Serenity's on The Mountain design and architecture has many eco-friendly features. In every season, its views, garden and indoor ambience offer you a sanctuary and opportunities for restorative healing and deep relaxation. The Serenity Den is a sanctuary carved out for reflective thoughts, creating a comforting space for 'being'. Perfect for racing minds and over active bodies; the Serenity Den is your invitation to sit and listen to your innermost feelings, to meditate, to hear soothing nature sounds, to read, or just relax. Enjoy these moments and take them home with you as a holistic, supportive practice.

Emi Mimo means pure or enlightened spirit in Yoruba, a West African language primarily spoken in Nigeria. This room reminds you of the essence of all that is. It communicates through colors, rich textures and intriguing detail. K'inan, a Mayan concept for spirit or solar energy, embraces an earth relationship that indigenous cultures of the Americas have always valued. This space brings you home to Mother Earth and invites grounding and connection with the natural world to support and strengthen your inner being. Pavitra is an ancient Sanskrit word for purity and sanctity. This Asian accented room personifies the meaning of 'Zen'. It calls forth calmness and invites body and soul on a balanced, harmonious journey. The vibrant colors celebrate rich traditions steeped in ceremony. For a little quietude, slip upstairs to the loft for some ‘me-time’, with panoramic vistas wherever you look!

Meticulously landscaped; away from the hustle and bustle of your busy life; perfectly located—you get the picture. You can’t go wrong with this vacation retreat. Serenity On The Mountain is exactly what you’ll experience when coming to Deep Creek Lake. Serenity offers a warm, contemporary architectural design created as an earth friendly, organic and artistic space - undulating, rhythmic lines, and magnificent vistas from every window offer cozy, yet spacious areas perfect for reflection and relaxation. Call today to reserve your time for contentment!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>4:06</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Serenity on the Mountain,Swanton,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Valhalla</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Valhalla.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/827-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Valhalla.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Valhalla.mp4" length="34784920" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">E1AD306E-971A-45FB-9B97-52FF4479228D-506-00000418DA6DD8CD-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 10:33:31 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Valhalla. For more info, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Valhalla.

Just in case you were wondering, Valhalla is a term from Norse Mythology which translates as a majestic, enormous place that rises ‘peacefully among the rest’ and is shining and golden from afar. Enough history though - this Valhalla is all of that and much more.  Located in a unique community on a mountainside at Deep Creek Lake, this architecturally exciting home in not only pleasing to the eye, but is also extremely stylish and efficient. Noted as one of the most awesome sites to see the lake in all its grandeur, Valhalla is bound to impress your memory with pictures you’ll never forget.

From the moment you walk into this spacious living area, you’ll know you’ve found that special vacation home that you will reminisce about forever.  Quality construction abounds, as you can see from this magnificent staircase.  Imagine making a grand entrance here! Take a peak at the lake from inside, or go out on the spacious deck to drink in the unbelievable sights that will blow your mind! Relax surrounded by rich woods and a meticulous décor as you take in the awesome views from just about every room in the house.  Looks are everything!  This gourmet kitchen is designed for a chef.  Entertain to your hearts content and clean up in no time as you enjoy the company you keep.

Recreation is the key to this great room - games, cards, a flat screen TV, and good reading material are all available at your fingertips.  Relax with your friends around the bar, curl up in front of the fireplace for some quiet time..whatever your pleasure..it’s here to enjoy. After a hard day at play, these inviting bedrooms will create the perfect environment for a good night’s rest.  You can wake up to the sounds of chirping birds, and your panoramic vista of the lake and mountains will be like none other.  Filled with morning light and open spaces…any worries you might have will seem to disappear.  Every guest or family member will feel ‘special’ in their own room.  Each area is unique in its own way.  Nothing has been overlooked in making everyone as comfortable as they can possibly be.

Whisk yourself away and get above the clouds!  Majestic, enormous, shining and golden from afar.  If you’re looking for an incredible place for that perfect get away—then Valhalla is the final stop on your tour.  It is purely delightful and you deserve the very best.  Rent your own piece of paradise!  It's guaranteed to make you feel like a king or queen of the mountain.  Valhalla - call today for even more juicy details!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:51</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Valhalla,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Sundance</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Sundance.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/823-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Sundance.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Sundance.mp4" length="25916934" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">DD9854D1-61C4-4795-87DE-3B34F5F48291-726-00000A3A33090F41-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 11:14:43 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Sundance. For more info, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Sundance.

Situated in one of the most beautiful settings at Deep Creek Lake, Sundance prides itself on its location and charm.  If you’re looking for a quiet retreat in order to relax and recharge, this home will be your final inquiry.  Not only is it close to the lake, it has all the amenities needed for that perfect vacation.  You can even enjoy a warm, lakeside campfire in the evening while planning your next day’s activities, or revitalize yourself in this spacious hot tub under the stars.

Warm environs and a meticulous décor is what Sun Dance is all about.  From the moment you walk into these spacious accommodations, you’ll hope your vacation could last forever.  Rich woods and comfortable furniture add to the magnetism of this cozy living room.  You can watch your favorite shows on TV, or curl up with a good book in front of the fireplace.  Whatever your pleasure, you’ll feel right at home.  Are you bringing lots of family and friends with you?  Everyone can find their ‘niche’ in any of the three living areas!  Entertain everybody in the recreation area with games, gatherings and good fun.

Think cooking is a chore?  Not in this modern, fully-equipped kitchen.  You can create gourmet masterpieces for your guests and serve them graciously in no time! Quiet, peaceful nights are easily attained in any of these attractive bedrooms, decorated with your comfort in mind.  You and your guests can unwind in their own private quarters and get totally rejuvenated for the next day’s action.  There's lots of room for that big family or large group of friends, so everyone will feel special. Don’t put off that reward any longer - Sundance is waiting for you.  You deserve the very best, and this home is ranked right up there!  Call today to get that special vacation started.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:08</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Sundance,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Babbling Brook</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Babbling Brook.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/822-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Babbling-Brook.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Babbling-Brook.mp4" length="24061184" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">BD9159D9-A0EA-496D-8104-43ED59C3FB97-726-00000A16511A5324-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 10:53:53 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Babbling Brook. For more info, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Babbling Brook.

Are you in need of a stress free vacation? If so, Babbling Brook is the ideal lake-front chalet for you! With extra large deck space, there is plenty of room for everyone to stretch and lounge lazily in the afternoon sun. A short stroll down the landscaped stairs will lead you to your own private dock, which is perfect for swimming or parking your rented boat for the week.

The large, colossal Great Room not only provides plenty of seating space for the family, but it also offers breathtaking views of the lake through its massive glass windows. Worried about not having enough space for everyone? You don't need to be. The warm comfortable den provides yet another sitting area for your family members to stretch out and enjoy. Get cozy in the overstuffed furniture of the lower level family room or walk out onto the lower level deck to breathe in some of the fresh mountain air. The well-equipped kitchen provides everything you'll need to prepare a gourmet feast, and is perfect for whipping up a picnic lunch to take with you on the boat. Every meal will seem special in this grand dining room, which boasts beautiful views and even offers convenient deck access.

Wake up each morning in your large cushy bed, pull open the drapes, and view Mother Nature at her finest. What a way to start the day! The kids will get a kick out of this fun bedroom with its double bunk beds. They'll also appreciate the extra sleeping space provided by the pull out trundles! Conveniently located to a wealth of amenities including the magnificent ski slopes, Babbling Brook will provide you with a utopian get-away all year around! Call today to book the vacation of a lifetime.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:59</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Babbling Brook,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Clubhouse Chalet</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Clubhouse Chalet.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/821-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Club-House-Chalet.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Club-House-Chalet.mp4" length="25517420" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0D8AB8C0-20EA-4204-B00F-6B9FCC0197BF-12581-0000F26159A8CF44-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 11:56:33 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Clubhouse Chalet. For more info, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Clubhouse Chalet.

Tennis anyone? Swimming? Fun at the Lake? Golf? Take your pick at this newly built decorative home - right in the heart of a fun vacation area! Attractions include a kid-friendly community with access to a catch and release pond, sledding hill, and a miniature golf course. And for the adults, a par-3 golf course is just a short walk away! Don’t forget your bathing suits!! There is always something to do at the Clubhouse Chalet, even on rainy and snowy days. 

Be sure to take the vacation inside with the private indoor pool which is fun for all ages. Or unwind in the steaming hot tub.  Now that is just what the doctored order! Clubhouse Chalet’s modern kitchen will have all the chefs in the family lining up to make their signature dishes.  Or take it outside and Barbecue on the covered deck while the family smells the mouth watering meal that you're preparing on the gas grill.

This property will sleep up to 14 people and has 5 bedrooms and 5 baths, giving all of your guests plenty of room for privacy and relaxation. Get the gang together over a friendly game of billiards in the family room downstairs. You can actually have it all at this vacation retreat, and the family harmony will be singing for months to come.

Don't miss out on this terrific opportunity; you'll be glad you made the right decision. You can spend active, fun-filled days doing all of your favorite things, and rest easy at night, knowing your sleep won’t be interrupted by traffic or ‘city’ noises. The Clubhouse Chalet is just a phone call away! Call now so you won’t miss out on a vacation of a lifetime.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:08</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Club House Chalet,Swanton,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Highland Heaven</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Highland Heaven.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/819-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Highland-Heaven.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Highland-Heaven.mp4" length="27338203" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D2C01E45-616B-41BF-93A8-9E76172D8A15-4942-00004D7340E42AFC-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 17:08:31 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Highland Heaven. For more info, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Highland Heaven.

Everything you’ve ever dreamed about that ‘Dream Vacation’ is right here at Highland Heaven. You don’t have to go far to get that vacation of a lifetime with your family or friends. Deep Creek Lake and the majestic Appalachian mountains welcome you every morning while enjoying your coffee on the deck.

The bright, open interior is inviting and warm. Artistically decorated from floor to ceiling…you’ll think someone needs to pinch you to wake you up! Feed your family with ease in this fully equipped kitchen, complete with everything you need to satisfy a hungry crowd. Get ready for a nice sit-down dinner in the roomy dining area. The attention to detail in this room is unmatched anywhere, and the luxurious woods make you feel good all over.

Talk about in-house recreation! Relax in front of the fireplace or watch your favorites on the huge flat-screen TV. Play games, reminisce or just spend time together in this beautiful room. Want to get away from the gang and unwind with a good book or take a nap? This lovely loft with overstuffed and comfortable furniture is just the place to go for the peace and quiet you’ve been looking for after an active day at the lake. Don’t think that just because you’re not at home you can’t get a good nights’ sleep. These luxurious bedrooms make even the most particular guest sleep in comfort. Every room is prepared with your contentment in mind. Even the largest group will enjoy their own privacy under one roof!

And now the best is saved for last! Highland Heaven is located in a perfect community where you can enjoy a refreshing dip in the pool, go to the open lodge with the huge fireplace and spectacular views, play a friendly game of tennis, or go hiking on the magnificent trails…all there for your fun and adventures. Your friends and family will thank you over and over again for introducing them to this wonderful area. Let Taylor-Made make your dream a reality. Call today for our affordable prices and availability. You deserve the best, and Highland Heaven fills that request. Let’s hear from you soon!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:15</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Highland Heaven,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Stone Mountain Vista</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Stone Mountain Vista.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/813-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Stone-Mountain-Vista.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Stone-Mountain-Vista.mp4" length="26446685" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6F773EB2-3E28-444E-BD13-C6CA74E213D1-589-0000081C90F2309D-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 11:28:42 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Stone Mountain Vista. For more info, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Stone Mountain Vista.

You'll be swept away by the majestic beauty and exceptional detail of Stone Mountain Vista. Surrounded by the stunning stone work and unique architectural details, you will bathe in bliss in this sunken hot tub. Host gracious gatherings under the stars on the patio lit by the warm glow of flames from the spectacular outdoor fireplace.

Spacious, yet warm and cozy, this great room will set the perfect tone for enjoying time with your loved ones. With vaulted ceilings, open beams, hardwood floors and a roaring fire, this is the perfect setting after a day on the slopes. The most discriminating chef will appreciate the extras that this gourmet kitchen has to offer. Granite countertops, double ovens and a built-in wine rack, just to name a few. This dining area creates an ambiance of elegance for memorable meals and entertaining. Nestle in with your morning coffee and peruse the options of fun things to do with your day in this cozy reading nook off of the kitchen. The kids will love the connecting playroom off of the bedroom which features duo bunk beds. Enjoy a challenging game of billiards in this game room that is located above the garage.

You'll find all the comforts of a luxury resort in this well appointed bedroom. Winding down is easy in this main level master suite, which is complimented by an inviting Jacuzzi tub. Four bedrooms with four king beds will ensure that every couple finds comfort and privacy in this getaway retreat. Gaze upon scenic mountain views while you unwind in this main level master suite. Two sets of duo bunk beds and one with a trundle mean plenty of room for the kids or the young at heart! After exceeding your expectations, the only fault that you will find with Stone Mountain Vista is leaving this memorable home when your stay is complete!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:11</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Stone Mountain Vista,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lakeside Retreat</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lakeside Retreat.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/809-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Lakeside-Retreat.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Lakeside-Retreat.mp4" length="24353183" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7F7395FB-68A3-456E-8EF5-83C988556E4D-1681-000015390D6BD74C-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 11:11:58 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lakeside Retreat. For more info, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lakeside Retreat.

Lakeside Retreat is the epitome of lakeside fun, making it a perfect getaway for family and friends. The large deck overlooking the lake enables you to watch the kids and dogs at play in the large grassy yard. Evenings under the starry skies will be perfect as you gather around this awesome fire-pit and listen to the waves gently lapping at the shore. Cool views of the magnificent cove will relax you as you soak in the inviting, bubbling hot-tub.

The charm and comfort of this special retreat continues indoors with overstuffed leather sofas, beautiful stonework and views of the Lake. Stainless steel appliances, granite countertops, and efficient design make preparing meals a snap! This, of course, means more time on the Lake for you! This dining room located in the open great room features a convenient wet bar for easy and enjoyable entertaining. Cozy up to the fire and read a good book, or enjoy a movie in this warm and comfy lower level sitting area. A second table in the lower level allows for more space during mealtimes or a perfect place for board and card games.

King size comfort and serene views of the lake await you in this master suite. Dreams of galactic adventures lie ahead as the kids snuggle into the duo-bunk beds. Two of the bedrooms here actually feature duo-bunk beds, so all the kids will have their own special place to enjoy their slumber. Five bedrooms, two sitting areas, and the space outdoors make this a perfect vacation home for large families. The loft is a perfect area to set up your lap-top and send those emails out with great pics of the family having the time of their life! Lakeside Retreat is the home that you will want to make an annual family event, or enjoy in all four seasons!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:00</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Lakeside Retreat,Swanton,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wispering Heights</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wispering Heights.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/802-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Wispering-Heights.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Wispering-Heights.mp4" length="20611571" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5E3A886C-15B1-4EE8-B246-5AB13F3B1225-166-00000020539E3EC2-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 11:02:39 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wispering Heights. For more info, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wispering Heights.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Wispering Heights - 345 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.

The ideal get away for rest or play awaits you within the comfort of Wispering Heights. This ski in/ski out home is close to white water rafting and star gazing, making this is a fun vacation home! Surround yourself with bliss as you relax in the bubbling hot-tub and delight in the chirping of the birds in the trees. Views of the Lake and the great outdoors can be appreciated from the comfort of plush leather sofas and a warm crackling fire as you watch snowflakes drift by.

A game of pool, or watching the game on the flat screen TV will entertain you inside the home. You will take pleasure in the surround sound and ipod deck too! Granite countertops, stainless steel appliances, and this open, well designed kitchen will be sure to please the most discriminating chef! There's plenty of room for the family and friends as you gather for meals around this spacious table adjacent to the open great room.

Luxury that's fit for a king and queen along with views of nature through the windows grace this resplendent bedroom. Ease away the stress and achy muscles after a day of activities as you soak in this cozy corner Jacuzzi tub. With four bedrooms and three and half baths, there's plenty of comfort and privacy for everyone here. The kids will enjoy and appreciate the duo-bunk beds. Toss a coin to see who gets the top! Whether you come to the mountains to relax or play, or a little bit of both, you will find the perfect retreat in Wispering Heights.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:41</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Wispering Heights,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - El Dorado</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - El Dorado.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/783-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-El-Dorado.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/El-Dorado.mp4" length="19945117" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">628B7984-6B13-439A-AF27-EE4F668E52AD-889-00000C780D89D95C-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 11:32:48 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - El Dorado. For more info, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - El Dorado.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents El Dorado - 1470 Stockslager Radd, Oakland, MD 21550.

Looking for the perfect laidback lakefront get-away? Then El Dorado is the one for you! Double decks invite you to spread out, relax and enjoy views of the Lake. No matter the season, strolls along the lakeside hiking and biking trails will be enjoyed by all, including the family dog! Take pleasure in the great outdoors in this steaming hot-tub, as well as taking in sweeping views of the Lake.

The 2 mile lakeside trail is great for a morning or evening walk and means you will not have to dodge the traffic! The warmth of knotty pine woodwork and a crackling fire in this stone fireplace will make you feel all warm and cozy inside after a day of invigorating play! Challenge the others to a game of pool or relax with a good movie as you wind down from a day filled with fun activities. Preparing delicious meals is a snap in this cozy and efficient kitchen. Serene views of the lake will entertain you as you enjoy delicious meals in the dining room.

Deck access, views of the lake, and a comfy king size bed will make you feel pretty special as you drift off to slumber. You will find the ultimate in relaxation in this bedroom with deck access, hardwood floors and knotty pine woodwork. You will only have one regret after a stay in El Dorado…packing up to go home. However, you can always come back and enjoy every season in this comfortable lakefront cottage.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:38</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,El Dorado,Oakland,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Woodpeckers Delight</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Woodpeckers Delight.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/782-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Woodpeckers-Retreat.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Woodpeckers-Delight.mp4" length="28570484" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A0C87701-0E87-44CA-BA00-B1184B6812C5-889-00000C55D13C68D7-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 11:37:19 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Woodpeckers Delight. For more info, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Woodpeckers Delight.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Woodpeckers Delight - 384 Glen Clove Road, Swanton, MD 21561.

Woodpecker’s Delight is everyone’s preferred property, and after a stay in this “delightful “ home, it will become your family's favorite too! One of the many extraordinary features is this roomy covered deck. You can enjoy open-air meals no matter what the weather! There's an abundance of room to frolic and play in this large and level grassy yard. Game of horseshoes anyone? The outdoor fire pit is perfect for a marsh mellow roast.

Woodpecker’s Delight is the epitome of mountain and lake retreats, with its immense stone fireplace and beautiful woodwork in the spacious great room. Gather around the granite countertop bar by the kitchen and regale the chef with the day’s adventures. The chef will certainly appreciate the design of the kitchen and stainless steel appliances. Convenient Deck access and majestic views of the lake add a special ambiance to this dining room. Another delightful highlight is this amazing game room! Plenty of play for everyone with a pool table, ping-pong table, foosball, pinball machines, a card table, and access to the hot tub, yard and lake is nice too! Your favorite beverage will taste even more refreshing while enjoyed at this stunning and unique wet bar adjacent to the game room.

King sized comfort awaits in this master bedroom, with access to the deck overlooking the beautiful lake. With five bedrooms and five bathrooms, there's plenty of privacy and comfort for everyone in this roomy retreat. There's lots of space for the kids to spread out with twin beds and sleeper sofas in this roomy loft. Cozy comfort will be found in this queen size bed which is tucked into an inviting nook. Spread out and relax in this open bedroom, which features a spectacular cathedral ceiling and two comfortable queen beds. Woodpecker’s Delight will easily become a family tradition for that mountain and lake get away! With so much to do inside and out of this wonderful place, weather will never cramp your style! We will see you soon!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:20</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Woodpeckers Delight,Swanon,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lakeside Lodge</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lakeside Lodge.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/781-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Lakeside-Lodge.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Lakeside-Lodge.mp4" length="16678268" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8809C191-696F-45B8-8F53-52FC113C7AD5-889-00000C2BDA057E4D-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 11:34:25 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lakeside Lodge. For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Lakeside Lodge.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Lakeside Lodge - 757 Marsh Hill Road, McHenry, MD 21541.

Built to please, this custom log and stone lakefront home will guarantee an exceptional get-away. Floor to ceiling windows and a spacious wrap around deck allow for spectacular views of the lake, inside or out! Life is made of special moments, and you will enjoy every moment relaxing in this hot tub while taking in the lake and countryside.

There is plenty of room to frolic in the grassy yard with its own private dock. Enjoy the expansive night sky as you toast marshmallows and s’ mores at the bonfire pit. The open great room is breathtaking with the bright knotty pine woodwork, cathedral ceilings, and generous windows. Even the lower level is bright and airy, yet cozy, with a gas fireplace and a cushy wrap around sofa. The discriminating chef will appreciate the detail and quality of the kitchen's stainless steel appliances and granite countertops.

Comfort and a good night’s rest awaits as you settle into the inviting queen bed in this master bedroom. Little girls will love sharing stories of their fun-filled days as they drift off to sleep in this pretty bedroom. Lakeside Lodge will ensure that every member of the family will cherish the memories of days spent together at Deep Creek Lake!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:22</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Lakeside Lodge,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Harvest Moon</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Harvest Moon.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/768-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Harvest-Moon.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Harvest-Moon.mp4" length="20526764" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4B5F333D-4DDF-4050-8D8C-DFB45FEC86E7-662-00000960A81B2608-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 10:54:38 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Harvest Moon. For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Harvest Moon.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Harvest Moon - 2544 State Park Road, Swanton, MD 21561.

Harvest Moon lets you reap the harvest of beauty of all four seasons from its spacious wrap around deck. Gaze upon the radiance of the full moon or catch a shooting star while soaking in the relaxing hot-tub. The outdoor fire pit allows you to enjoy the sound of a crackling bonfire or the smell of roasting marshmallows as you linger by the lake. Or kick up your feet indoors after retiring from the lake or slopes to enjoy the warmth of a blazing fire from the massive stone fireplace.

Whipping up delicious meals is a snap in this distinctive, sunken kitchen. This efficient kitchen features stainless steel appliances and is adjacent to the great room for enjoying the company of your friends and family. Unwind and settle into the ambiance any of the seasons in the bright and comfortable sun room. You and your guests will love chatting about the day’s adventures while gathering around the warm, gleaming wood in the dining area, which is conveniently located next to the kitchen and great room.

Beautiful hardwood floors, knotty pine walls and cheerful country quilts add a special charm to this master bedroom. The cozy fleece blankets on the twin beds will keep the kids nice and warm on cool summer evenings or brisk, wintry nights. Find total comfort in this Queen bed and enjoy the serene glow of moonlight as you drift off to the land of dreams. You'll reap a harvest of special memories and good times in the this comfy lakefront home. The unique touches and character of Harvest Moon will be sure to delight everyone in your group!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:40</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,house,home,Harvest Moon,Swanton,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:block>yes</itunes:block>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Oz</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Oz.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/767-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Oz.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Oz.mp4" length="28658101" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">02F6DFF8-6489-4347-8C35-BE8EC854403C-5703-00005A083EAAE2F0-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2009 11:15:50 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Oz. For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Oz.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Oz - 1746 Stockslager Road, Oakland, MD 21541.

Oz will be your magical “home away from home”. Over the rainbow... dreams do come true... enter the Land of Oz! Enjoy spectacular beauty inside and out. No detail has been overlooked in this elegant home designed to fill you with peace and comfort. Take a deep breath, melt into the plush leather sofas and gaze upon serene views of the lake, or the flames softly flickering in the impressive stone fireplace. Savor morning coffee in the cozy breakfast nook which will encourage you to transition into a glorious day!

Oz is a expansive property that is perfect for large family gatherings or several couples getting together. Inhale the mouthwatering scents of ham and turkey baking in the double ovens...mmmmmmm.... It's easy to envision a bountiful meal, flowers and candlelight gracing this roomy table as you and your loved ones gather around. This sunroom adds another splendid location to enjoy your meals or even a game of cards. Three regally dressed master bedrooms ensure that every couple has their own special place. Little girls will feel &quot;pretty as pink&quot; as you tuck them into this precious room...perfect for story-time with Dorothy and Toto! &quot;Jack and Jill&quot; bedrooms flank either side of the centrally located bathroom.

Everything is bigger and better in Oz and this oversized game room is no exception! Watch out for the munchkins! It may not be the &quot;yellow brick road&quot;, but you will feel you are heading to your own land of wonder as you skip over wandering streams and picturesque ponds on your way to the lake. This path is softly lit at night, adding to the magic that is apparent everywhere in Oz. Splash around in the quiet cove, or cast your line and catch the big one! The firepit will ensure that both young and old will enjoy roasting marshmallows. The lakeside gazebo with a wet bar will give you a unique place to enjoy your favorite beverages. There is plenty of room for your party to play on the expansive wrap-around deck that runs the entire length of Oz. You and yours are sure to be enchanted with Oz, as it is truly a place where wishes do come true!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:20</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,condo,Oz,Oakland,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Four Seasons</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Four Seasons.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/759-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Four-Seasons.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Four-Seasons.mp4" length="27273930" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5D7D4641-BA6B-41E1-8818-1944DC099474-3071-0000272EE17BD162-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2009 11:14:36 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Four Seasons. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Four Seasons.

Big surprises come in small packages, but do not let the looks of this entire whole bottom floor unit condo deceive you! Four Seasons is a stylish ground level condo with plenty of room inside with two master suites, on either side of the centrally located kitchen and great room. Two more bedrooms are cheerfully designed with the children in mind. This professionally decorated property with high quality furnishings invites you to relax enjoying the colors of the flames and the romance of flickering candlelight. Or, enjoy a family movie snuggled up on the plush overstuffed sofas.

Prepare gourmet meals to go with that special bottle of wine in the open and well designed kitchen, or have fun fixing your favorite family meals. The open kitchen, dining and great room ensure that everyone is part of the memorable dining experiences. This attractive condo is thoughtfully designed for ease of living. After all, isn’t that what “getting away from it all&quot; is all about? Pamper yourself in this master suite which features a 4-poster queen bed and luxurious linens. Step out onto the ground level patio and enjoy the summer breeze coming off of the nearby lake.

Kids will go “wild” with glee at the local wildlife décor in this rustic bedroom. Four Seasons of comfort await you in this queen size sleigh bed in the second master suite. This suite also offers access to the ground level patio, so enjoy sitting outside and enjoy the fresh evening mountain air. Kids will enjoy the feeling of fun in this cute room filled with the friendly faces of the local wildlife. Four Seasons of fun activities and restaurants are within walking distance of this conveniently placed condo. Let the kids challenge you to a round of mini golf and bumper boats, grab a pizza or relax with fine dining, and if you are up for more adventures check out the nearby music and nightlife! Lake access and the slopes are only a short drive away.

Take pleasure in all Four Seasons in this special retreat that welcomes you into a place of exceptional beauty and decor as soon as you cross the threshold. Ideally designed for two couples or two families to have their own privacy, you will appreciate the well-placed setting of this superior condo!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:13</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,condo,Four Seasons,McHenry,video tours,rental,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Brooke Mountain</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Brooke Mountain.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/760-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Brook-Mountain.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Brooke-Mountain.mp4" length="28006015" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7789A330-10F5-4896-9C98-A89B0B07D77C-3071-0000270E1AEEDC6B-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 14:52:18 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Brooke Mountain. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Brooke Mountain.

This hefty log home makes the big, bold statement “You have arrived!” Enjoy fun and adventure both inside and out. Within walking distance of The Adventure Sports Center, which features a man-made Whitewater course and nearby miles of hiking and biking trails, as well as access to a private community 2 acre lakeside park, you will have plenty of opportunities to keep the kids active and happy, without ever driving off the mountain. Plush seating invites you to put your feet up, and the crackling fire will comfort you as you enjoy the vistas of stars in the clear night sky or the beauty of the swirling snowflakes from this mountaintop location.

This home is built for comfort and satisfaction both inside and out! If Mother Nature is dishing out a less then desirable day, take pleasure in watching sports or movies on the huge flat screen TV. You can enjoy watching Mother Nature’s worst from the comfort of this family room that features large windows and a gas fireplace. You will feel “right at home” in the airy yet cozy well designed kitchen. The efficient design will make short work of preparing meals and give you more time to play. Create warm family memories as you share meals in the comfortable dining room or the well-situated screened-in porch.

Little kids (and the big kids too), will enjoy friendly competitions on the air hockey or foosball tables. We bet the kids beat the adults! You will feel like the King and Queen in this regal 4 –poster bed with sumptuous linens. Slip out onto the deck in your jammies and enjoy the serenade of woodland birdsong. You know you are at home with the red, white and blue of this country bedroom. Who knows? You may wake up to the scene of deer quietly nibbling grass outside your windows. Kids will enjoy the comfort of this duo-bunk. The question is “Who gets the top? Flip a coin…Heads or Tails!

This premier chalet on top of the mountain is the place that will bring the kid out in you! Fun-filled days of challenge and adventure will give you the feeling of contentment as you settle into the comfy beds at night. You will awake renewed and refreshed and ready for more days of challenges either here on the mountain or back at home.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:17</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,Brooke Mountain,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Enchantment</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Enchantment.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/756-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Enchantment.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Enchantment.mp4" length="25676791" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">896209FA-DF82-4E7C-94EA-81384F466047-2403-00002012888201AF-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 18:16:22 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Enchantment. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Enchantment.

Enchantment is the Tennessee Log Home that will give you magical memories for years to come. This brand new rustic log home nestled in the secluded woods is just the retreat that you have been looking for. Relax and release the cares of the world in this breathtaking great room with open beam ceilings, full length windows and knotty pine walls. You'll be mesmerized by the flames in the stone fireplace while also enjoying ample views of the woods and mountains.

Generous leather sofas will enfold you in cushy comfort while you melt into a place of peace. Everyone can “hang” together on the comfy wrap around sofa while watching the huge flat screen TV. A crackling fire will add cheerful charm and ambiance to this family room and large windows allow lots of light. You may be the chef, but this warm and open kitchen will allow you to be a part of the fun in the dining room and great room. Knotty pine cabinets make you feel right “at home” in the mountains. While soaking in the hot-tub encircled by the woods, you may catch a glimpse of mystical wildlife as they secretly pass by. If the Hot tub is not for you, take a break from all the fun in the sun on the covered Porch.

Enjoy a stimulating game of pool on this beautiful cherry wood pool table, complimented by the colors on the walls. The rustic comfort continues in the wrought iron king size bed which nestles you from top to bottom. The warm and cozy woodwork in this bedroom will make it easy to drift off into dreamland. Country quilts will warmly welcome you to the mountains where magical moments are a way of life. You will find yourself captivated by this magical and rustic mountain home. Enchantment will cast its spell upon you and entice you to return year after year!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:06</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,Enchantment,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wispering Woods</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wispering Woods.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/755-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Wispering-Woods.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Wispering-Woods.mp4" length="31574212" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">DFC92E19-3FDC-47AD-8F5A-4BDF6A56555A-2403-00001FB5896AEBC8-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 17:32:41 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wispering Woods. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Wispering Woods.

This gorgeous home nestled in the seclusion of the woods invites the “whispers’” of nature’s year round wooded splendor inside through the floor to ceiling windows. Take in the Winter time sparkles with views of the lights on the north side of Wisp Mountain, or enjoy viewing the stars while soaking in the hot-tub surrounded by trees. While you are off the beaten path in this peaceful property, you are only minutes away from the shops, restaurants and activities. Relax in bliss in the luxurious overstuffed leather seating as you enjoying the crackling flames and the imposing stone fireplace. Enjoy cozy warmth while sipping your favorite hot beverage while watching snowflakes drift lazily by the expansive windows, or take pleasure in the cool shadowed feel of the green canopy of leaves while you watch the play of light and shadows among the rustling leaves. This brand new home boasts classy furnishings and linens in all of the rooms.

Enjoy showing off your culinary skills while you prepare sumptuous meals in the bright and roomy state of the art kitchen with quality cabinetry and roomy countertops. This spacious kitchen with two ovens tempts you to create meals that are a culinary work of art! There's plenty of room to play inside when the weather outside is frightful! Enjoy a challenging game of pool or foosball in this spacious family room while keeping warm by the fire, or watch your favorite team on the huge plasma TV. The kids will love the universal station and they can play Wii to their heart’s content. Have fun challenging each other with the many board games that are provided, or enjoy the expansive library of books.

Enjoy the ease of hosting gatherings with a large dining room that allows for a gracious flow onto the roomy deck that is surrounded by the coolness of the whispering woods. Couples gathering together will enjoy the privacy of four master suites with impressive four poster king beds. Thick cozy bed linens will wrap you with comfort at the end of a day of playing hard on the Lake or the slopes. After your stay in the quiet beauty of Wispering Woods, you will be tempted to shout of its glories to all of your friends and family. This sure to impress home will enable you to go back to your real world renewed and refreshed ready to plan your next stay enjoying nature’s wonders!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:34</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,Wispering Woods,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Swimming Bear Lodge</title>
            <description>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Swimming Bear Lodge.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/728-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-Swimming-Bear-Lodge.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Swimming-Bear-Lodge.mp4" length="23124021" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1CA56D8B-8021-45B6-82A4-3EF984DC8E54-666-00000CDD368D3A74-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 13:15:17 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Swimming Bear Lodge. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Swimming Bear Lodge.

Wondering what to do for that special family of yours or with all of your great friends? Invite them to join you for the vacation of a lifetime at Swimming Bear Lodge!  Here you will marvel at the beauty of this gorgeous setting with its mature landscaping, and you’ll be amazed by the peace and quiet that you can enjoy on the wrap around deck.  You can get back in touch with nature while enjoying your morning coffee or reading a book in this spacious area.  Top it off with a pleasant soak in the hot tub no matter if its winter or summer! This gorgeous country setting is maintained throughout the year, and the sights and sounds are always amazing!

Once inside Swimming Bear Lodge, you’ll be greeted by a completely meticulous and perfectly kept retreat with rich woods and a country décor that will make you feel right at home. With appointed characteristics that are enhanced by the beautiful surroundings, your guests will appreciate your hospitality even more.  This modern kitchen will make feeding your group a joy instead of a chore. Equipped with everything you need to make a quick breakfast or a sit down dinner, you’ll love how easy it is to prepare your favorite meals and clean up.

Everyone will be sure to rest comfortably in the cozy bedrooms at this lodge.  Each bedroom offers a great place to relax and unwind after a full day of fun and recreation.  You’ll even have access to high speed internet, a wood fireplace, free unlimited long distance calling, a pool table, 2 DVD’s, a 50” flat screen TV and much more.  Call today for the juicy details on Swimming Bear Lodge and treat your family or friends to a vacation they’ll remember for a lifetime!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:53</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,Swimming Bear Lodge,Oakland,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>2 B R Retreat - 209 North Lake Drive, McHenry, MD 21541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 2 B R Retreat - 209 North Lake Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/721-Deep-Creek-Lake-Maryland-Vacation-Rentals-2-B-R-Retreat.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/2-B-R-Retreat.mp4" length="24978134" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">73056092-1425-423E-80CA-962E9AC3DADF-641-00000F88DC1A7AF0-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 13:05:20 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 2 B R Retreat - 209 North Lake Drive, McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 2 B R Retreat - 209 North Lake Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents 2 B R Retreat - 209 North Lake Drive, McHenry, MD 21541 .

When you first see &quot;2-B-R Retreat&quot;, you may just think “Oh, that's just another pretty rental at Deep Creek Lake - if you’ve seen one, you’ve seen them all!” Well, prepare yourself for a very pleasant surprise! In addition to being conveniently located and close to all of the 'Hot Spots' at the lake, &quot;2-B-R Retreat&quot; has many amenities that will make your vacation one to remember for a long time to come. It even comes with Two ski Passes! Once inside this immaculate home, you’ll understand the meaning of ‘built and decorated for your comfort and pleasure’. This home features wide open spaces that seem to effortlessly flow together. This is one of the nicest rental properties at the lake, offering exceptional light and space throughout the property.

The full luxury kitchen features a breakfast bar which opens up to the formal dining area for your entertaining needs. Whether you’re playing pool, cards, watching TV or just relaxing on the deck, the peace and tranquility of this beautiful home will make you feel good all over. How about a soak in the hot tub after a vigorous day on the slopes? Everything is easily accessible for your total convenience. You’ll be amazed at how easy it is to entertain your guests in this amazing retreat.

At the end of the day, everyone can relax and enjoy as much privacy as they desire. With two king master suites, and plenty of other rooms for the kids or friends, even the largest of groups can be content here. Don’t forget - Taylor-Made can take care of a lot more than just your Deep Creek lodging needs! Our experts can plan your entire trip to the lake, including lift tickets, boat rentals, restaurant reservations and more. Our packaging options provide the very best in complete vacation planning for both winter and summer. Contact us today and we’ll handle the details on your next vacation at 2 B R Retreat!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:02</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,2 B R Retreat,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Deep Creek Lake Maryland Vacation Rentals - Green Gables</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Green Gables - 319 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/708-Green-Gables-319-Highline-Drive-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Green-Gables.mp4" length="25724482" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">183622C8-C1B4-4EA2-A1AC-3F91716804A8-1097-000018DE91DF42AF-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 16:14:17 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Green Gables - 319 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Green Gables - 319 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Green Gables - 319 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.

Looking for a pleasant adventure in a place that will make you feel like you’ve found paradise? Then the new Green Gables is here for your asking. This lovely vacation home will help you to slow down and stay active all at once. Green Gables is designed in a way that perfectly blends the charm of the area with modern-day conveniences. It's a great place for the whole family to hang out - there’s lots to do even if you decide to spend the day at ‘home’.

As soon as you step into the wonderful kitchen and dining areas, you’ll be inspired to get your meal started. The dining area is tastefully decorated and understated without being bland. You’ll be proud to serve your favorite foods here, as there's plenty of room for everyone to enjoy a sit-down dinner. The recreation area is bright and airy, with loads of activities awaiting your pleasure. Watch T.V., play games, curl up by the fireplace with a good book—all of these will undoubtedly make your stay more enjoyable. You can entertain many family members or guests here without forgoing anyone’s privacy.

Each bedroom is designed with the convenience and enjoyment of the busy vacationer in mind. For quiet, peaceful nights that dawn into another exciting day, you’ll love being in your own little sanctuary. Comfort and relaxation is yours within each of the sleeping quarters. You really deserve a break after the hectic pace of your daily routine, and Green Gables offers the perfect respite, delivering peace, privacy, and exquisite scenery. An active family is a healthy family…and a truly healthy family knows how to have fun every season of the year. Whether it’s down the slopes, up a mountain trail, skimming across the lake on skis, or trudging cross country—nothing bonds a family like the great outdoors. Here you can be whatever you want to be. It just doesn’t get any better than this!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:06</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,Green Gables,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>All Seasons Getaway - 267 Mosser Road, McHenry, MD 21541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring All Seasons Getaway - 267 Mosser Road, McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/707-All-Seasons-Getaway-267-Mosser-Road-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/All-Seasons-Getaway.mp4" length="24709891" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">767F6895-B3A9-4B8A-88E9-25C8E39EC252-770-00000FD94DAF77CF-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 13:27:00 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring All Seasons Getaway - 267 Mosser Road, McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring All Seasons Getaway - 267 Mosser Road, McHenry, MD 21541.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents All Seasons Getaway - 267 Mosser Road, McHenry, MD 21541.

Are you ready for some good times, without the hassle of trying to find the perfect place to have them in? All Seasons Getaway is the ideal spot for fun and relaxation. Centrally located at beautiful Deep Creek Lake, this vacation rental has all the amenities you’ve been looking for with none of the usual hassles that you may have experienced elsewhere. Cozy and comfortable, this exquisite abode offers breath-taking views of the lake and ski slopes, while keeping your priorities in focus. Modern, yet filled with charm, this home will make you feel good all over.

One look at the handy, fully equipped kitchen will certainly make the chef happy. Everything is conveniently placed to make even the most formal dinner easy. A spacious dining area which is directly linked to the kitchen makes serving up your favorite meals a pleasure instead of a chore. Meticulously decorated, every room offers an inviting atmosphere which will help to relax even the busiest of travelers.

After an active and exciting day discovering all the adventures that the lake has to offer, your guests will be able to relax in total comfort in these picturesque bedrooms. Each is designed for complete privacy and your family or guests will be made to feel right at home. Discerningly decorated with comfort in mind, everyone will feel that they’ve found a sanctuary created just for them.

A nice soak in the hot tub is just the thing to top off a busy day on the slopes or at the lake. Outside, you will feel great and totally relaxed - what more could you want? All Seasons Getaway is ready right now for that special vacation you’ve been dreaming about. Call today and see how easy it is to be among the ‘in’ crowd at Deep Creek Lake! You deserve a good time, and it’s much easier to attain then you might think. What are you waiting for?

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:01</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,All Seasons Getaway,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Hartwood Village #2 - 2 Hartwood Village Drive, McHenry, MD 21541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Hartwood Village #2 - 2 Hartwood Village Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/705-Hartwood-Village-2-2-Hartwood-Village-Drive-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Hartwood-Village-2.mp4" length="21605747" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8B04C38C-4C2D-4C8F-9451-A340A2BCBD88-4563-0000A2F902F35459-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2009 10:22:47 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Hartwood Village #2 - 2 Hartwood Village Dr, McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Hartwood Village #2 - 2 Hartwood Village Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Hartwood Village #2 - 2 Hartwood Village Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.

As with many vacation rentals, Hartwood Village #2 is clean and attractive and big enough to make even a large group feel right at home. It is also extremely comfortable and quite pleasing to the eye. What makes Hartwood Village #2 unique however, is its central location - which makes getting anywhere at any time a snap! Warm and inviting, yet modern and convenient, this home offers everything that a vacationer could be looking for.

Entertain a a few friends or sit down for a family dinner—the kitchen and dining area will make your preparations seem like an enjoyable picnic. The spacious layout encourages relaxation and enjoyment for everyone during meals. After an active day discovering what the area has to offer, you’ll surely welcome the peace and quiet that you'll experience in the bedroom quarters. Each room has been designed with your ultimate comfort in mind.

Outstanding, unobstructed vistas of the lake are here for you to take in and absorb. The scenery is equally enticing during any season of the year. We will be happy to reserve the balcony for you to fully experience the magnificent Fireworks on the Fourth of July! There’s always something to do here—and you’ll love every minute of your vacation. Bring the whole family or all your friends! Hartwood Village #2 is the vacation rental that will keep you coming back for more. Don’t just think about it - Do it! Call today to experience that vacation of a lifetime that will create memories that will last forever.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:46</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,Hartwood Village #2,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Highland Manor - 45 Westward Way, McHenry, MD 21541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Highland Manor - 45 Westward Way, McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/688-Highland-Manor-45-Westward-Way-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Highland-Manor.mp4" length="40535778" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0D3C0A14-ACF1-4EC4-941D-38A7730EFE31-465-00000694CB2C6EF7-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 11:47:04 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Highland Manor - 45 Westward Way, McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Highland Manor - 45 Westward Way, McHenry, MD 21541.

We never thought we’d say this about one of our marvelous rentals…but…here it goes: &quot;location, Location, location!!!&quot;  Imagine being less than two miles from everything—ski slopes, restaurants, the Adventure Sports Center with white water rafting, and a fabulous 18-hole golf course!  Now picture yourself and a large group of family and friends in this gorgeous vacation home with six magnificent master suites, two additional bedrooms, your own private indoor swimming pool, and a huge kitchen for entertaining.  All within a luxurious and refined atmosphere that includes a wealth of impressive amenities.

Highland Manor simply cannot described in a sentence or two.  It is our ‘piece de resistance’ in a vacation get-away.  Loaded with personality and an exquisite décor, nothing has been overlooked.  This massive stairway which effortlessly extends to either side of the upper level is a stylish focal point that will truly astonish you and your guests.  With ample room for as many as 20 or more people, you’ll find yourself immersed in comfort, elegance and charm.  As you can easily see, the entire home has been furnished with your enjoyment and relaxation in mind.  Enjoy meals prepared in the incredible gourmet kitchen at this spohisticated and stylish dining table.  There's most certainly room for everyone here.

When you’re not outdoors exploring the many activities around the lake, you can easily entertain the entire group within this fantastic abode.  Whether it be taking a dip in the indoor pool whenever you feel like it, enjoying a friendly game of pool or ping pong, sitting in front of a warm fireplace exchanging stories, or curling up with your favorite book in the sitting area, you’ll be sure to emerge refreshed, vitalized, and most importantly…relaxed and ready to experience another wonderful day.  You may not have too much time to use them, but there are even 10 TV’s strategically placed throughout the home for your entertainment.

The bedrooms here are beautifully designed and everything has been included down to the smallest detail.  Posh and relaxing baths round off each of the luxurious suites, along with individual vanities to ensure plenty of room for everyone's morning routine.  All of your guests will feel welcomed, appreciated and special here.  The comfortable bedding and magnificent interior appointments in each bedroom will please even the most discerning of guests.  Each room here has it's own unique style and appeal for you and your family and friends to experience at the end of the day.  With this many private and inviting options to choose from, you can all expect to be pleasantly overwhelmed.  Relax and enjoy though - regardless of where you choose to retire for your nights in this magnificent vacation home, you'll be guaranteed to do so in total comfort and luxury!

Highland Manor is located in a community that offers a huge outdoor swimming pool, a playground for the kids, tennis courts, hiking trails and a first-rate pavilion - all at your disposal.  Vacation, retreat, get-away, adventure - However you choose label it:  Highland Manor will be the perfect escape for everyone.  Call Taylor-Made today and find out more about this spectacular oasis - you’ll truly have to see it to believe it!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:19</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,Highland Manor,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Bonus - 2407 Marsh Hill Road, McHenry, MD 21541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring The Bonus - 2407 Marsh Hill Road, McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/687-The-Bonus-2407-Marsh-Hill-Road-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/The-Bonus.mp4" length="22606357" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">40687F7C-62B3-40F7-8D6F-455CF9548466-25228-0001962963052066-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 13:26:38 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring The Bonus - 2407 Marsh Hill Road, McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring The Bonus - 2407 Marsh Hill Road, McHenry, MD 21541.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents The Bonus - 2407 Marsh Hill Road, McHenry, MD 21541.

The Bonus is the ideal retreat to relax, enjoy recreational activities and revel in your discovery of Deep Creek Lake. Day or night, weekend or all week long, it is an amazing place to visit.  Loaded with charm and personality, this home is bound to bring smiles to the entire family or any group of friends. Versatile, yet filled with comfort, you’ll feel you’ve finally found that perfect getaway!

With a host of breezy colors, the finely appointed great room is as stylish as it is fun. The tasteful décor inspired this room’s sophisticated look. The colors are soft and pretty, created with your comfort in mind.  Get ready to whip up your favorite meal in this open and airy kitchen, which is “modern” in the way layout flows together.  Everyone will certainly want to get in on the act here, since this centrally located room is a great place to gather.

Each bedroom is designed for total relaxation and a good night’s sleep. The master suite even has a cozy nook for relaxing or reading beside a warm fireplace.  Each room is in this vacation home is a pleasant retreat after an active day of fun and exercise.  Your guests will feel refreshed and ready to go after spending the night in their own special room. Here, everyone will be a ‘morning person’!

The Bonus overflows with scenic, breathtaking panoramas that are well-within reach.  Staying at The Bonus is something anyone who wants to ‘get away from it all’ can do. How can you put a price on ultimate relaxation complimented with all of the comforts of home? Call today for more details on The Bonus.  It’s time to reward yourself!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:52</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,The Bonus,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Rocky Adventures - 71 Lower Camp Road, McHenry, MD 21541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Rocky Adventures - 71 Lower Camp Road, McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/686-Rocky-Adventures-71-Lower-Camp-Road-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Rocky-Adventures.mp4" length="33745195" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D75C4F12-0337-42F2-BCB9-B394B03C94FF-25228-000195FC055B7963-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 13:13:33 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Rocky Adventures - 71 Lower Camp Road, McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Rocky Adventures - 71 Lower Camp Road, McHenry, MD 21541.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Rocky Adventures - 71 Lower Camp Road, McHenry, MD 21541.

Rocky Adventures is a Ski-In / Ski-Out Chalet only a few minutes walk to the slopes. Brand new and rarin’ to go, Rocky Adventure is chic, but not at all pretentious. Meticulously designed and beautifully decorated, this vacation paradise is sure to leave you with fond and lasting memories. A stretched-out plan allows for more windows and better natural light and ventilation. The interior is extremely engaging, with exposed rafters, rich, natural woods and a décor that could be featured in a magazine.

Masculine, yet strangely warm and inviting, you’ll feel comfortable and relaxed in this recreational area, filled with activities for the whole group. Not to worry if it’s raining or too cold outside…there’s plenty to do in here! You can even leave a jig saw puzzle out for days and know it’ll be there when you’re ready. Magnificent meals are no problem in this unique kitchen, planned with the busy vacationer in mind. Whether it be a simple breakfast or a seven-course dinner, the chef will be praised for days to come. There's lots of room to feed the entire group here quickly and efficiently. Clean up is as easy as the preparation, with all the modern conveniences you’ve always wanted.

Touches of elegance make their way into this master suite. Totally private and completely calm, your vigorous days will be rewarded with comfortable, peaceful nights. You can even ‘chill out’ in a soothing jetted tub in your own bathroom away from all the main activity in the house. One thing is certain: This is a serious mountain lover’s abode. Your family and guests will experience undisturbed nights in their own private spaces, where the owners most certainly did not skimp on style at all. Stunningly decorated, each room has its own unique charisma, charm and appeal. Quiet and peaceful, everyone will awake refreshed and eagerly looking forward to the days’ activities.

What better way to soothe those over-used muscles than in the big hot tub that's anxiously awaiting your arrival? This home truly feels like a haven. You don’t have to be so tense and focused—you can feel relaxed here and completely let your guard down. Believe me, you’ll live longer! You're going to have trouble deciding what you like best about Rocky Adventure. It'll be more like a top-10 list. The crowning achievement of this great adventure is its availability and affordability. You'll want to be here for simple reasons. The ultimate attraction is the natural beauty of the home and its environment. Why not pamper yourself and your family with just what the doctor ordered. Call today and we'll get you well on your way to recovery!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:46</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,Rocky Adventures,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Castle in the Sky - 201 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541. A Vacation rental home in Deep Creek Lake, Maryland.</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Castle in the Sky - 201 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/673-Castle-in-the-Sky-201-Highline-Drive-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Castle-in-the-Sky.mp4" length="36817622" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C0F57A05-7FB1-411F-A62A-D274106718ED-266-00000443CDBED82E-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 11:21:37 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Castle in the Sky - 201 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Castle in the Sky - 201 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Castle in the Sky - 201 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.

Brrr - is it cold outside? Not to worry - you’ll be warm and toasty as soon as you enter 'Castle in the Sky'! Not only is this home cozy and comfortable, it also offers some of the most spectacular views you'll ever witness. It truly *is* a castle - all that's missing is the moat! Never before have beauty and practicality been merged so gracefully - It’ll be hard to decide which is more responsible for your enjoyment in this friendly yet stunning atmosphere. The only wish you’ll be left with is the wish that you had reserved this retreat for a little bit longer.

You won't have to be concerned about whether to eat in or eat out - the cook in the family will be glad to feed the entire gang in this modern kitchen. Everything is so convenient and well-appointed that all of your meals will feel like they’re being enjoyed in a five-star restaurant! Appealing to look at and totally functional in every regard, this wonderful kitchen and dining area will be sure to please anyone enjoying their vacation here. Want to play? Relax? Read? Enjoy some time alone? The recreation area is perfect for doing just about anything you can imagine. It provides ample room for an intimate gathering or even a big party. You’ll be certain to enjoy your time within the convenience that this fantastic area offers.

What better way to top off a terrific day on the slopes than by sinking into a refreshing, good night’s sleep in any one of these five stylishly decorated bedrooms. Your guests will feel appreciated and special when you show them to their own private room in this relaxing fun-filled get-away. Bright and cheerful, yet quiet and peaceful, everyone's fun-filled days will be even further rewarded with luxurious comfort in the evening. What a combination: magical days overflowing with fun-filled activities for your whole group to enjoy - and serene, restful nights that will rejuvenate even the most exhausted of vacationers.

Enjoy your morning coffee on this glorious, furnished deck while you sit and plan your activities for the day, or perhaps even reflect on the good times here that you've already enjoyed. The breathtaking views will completely open your mind and awaken your ability to focus on the positivity that surrounds you. Picture this: There's a perfect snowfall, everyone is eager to ski, and you’re all in a hurry to get on the slopes. Here, you won't have to pack everything and everyone into the car, drive, park, unload, suit everyone up and then wait in line for a lift up to the top of the mountain. Castle in the Sky is a unique ‘ski-in, ski-out’ vacation home that allows you and your guests to get ready within the comfort of the house and then take off at your own pace, allowing you to feel the powder under your feet and the wind in your face without any of the hassle. Call today for this marvelous chance to have the vacation of a lifetime!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:00</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,ski,chad taylor,cabins,Castle in the Sky,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tall Castle - 293 Ridgewood Drive, Oakland, MD 21550</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Tall Castle - 293 Ridgewood Drive, Oakland, MD 21550.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/669-Tall-Castle-293-Ridgewood-Drive-Oakland-MD-21550.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Tall-Castle.mp4" length="28902238" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D76A9627-26E1-4734-B767-75C7CB210C09-542-00000D122AA8C916-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 16:42:15 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Tall Castle - 293 Ridgewood Drive, Oakland, MD 21550. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Tall Castle - 293 Ridgewood Drive, Oakland, MD 21550.

Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Tall Castle - 293 Ridgewood Drive, Oakland, MD 21550.

What better sight than a beautiful home reaching for the skies among lofty trees and unusual surroundings—‘Tall Castle’ stands majestically amidst one of Deep Creek Lake’s most picturesque spots. Tall Castle features panoramic views that will take your breath away—whether watching from the tremendous deck or from the inside looking out. Elegant, yet provincial - the cheerful, rich wood that makes up the interior of this home is inviting as well as pleasant to the eye. The huge, stone fireplace will warm you on cold winter nights after an invigorating day on the slopes.

There’s plenty of room for all the cooks in the house in this modern, well-equipped kitchen that will make preparing your favorite meals a pleasure instead of a chore. No one will be bored on this trip. If the weather’s not cooperating, strike up a friendly game of pool, roast marshmallows in the fireplace or catch up on your favorite TV shows in this great room that got its name for being just that—Great! What better way to top off a wonderful day by relaxing in this master suite, planned with the busy vacationer in mind. Instead of loud noises of traffic, airplanes and trains, just listen to the quietness of nature. You’ll wake refreshed and ready to start a new day. This attractive bath will be beckoning from the moment you walk in. Equipped with a large Jacuzzi, the gentle ‘jets’ will soothe you as you reflect on your day’s activities. Stay as long as you want!

Your guests and family will feel extra special in these spacious bedrooms. They won’t have to ‘draw straws’ to see who gets which room, because they all have a unique charm which will elate even the kids. Whether it’s gold, green or blue…the décor is tastefully correct for everyone. For complete immersion into nature, Tall Castle is the place you need to be. Imagine yourself on a boat dock, with a latte in one hand, your camera in the other and the dazzling lake begging for your attention. It’s the perfect location and remarkable amenities that makes this home the ideal spot for you next vacation. Call us today and let us show you how painless it is to make your dreams a reality. You won’t believe how easy it is!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:22</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,Tall Castle,Oakland,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Glen Cova - 935 Crows Point Road, Swanton, MD 21561</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Glen Cova - 935 Crows Point Road, Swanton, MD 21561.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/670-Glen-Cova-935-Crows-Point-Road-Swanton-MD-21561.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Glen-Cova.mp4" length="21934181" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">231D3ED1-7A23-4471-A72B-03D6006540E1-542-00000CEC06E1EF67-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 12:57:40 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Glen Cova - 935 Crows Point Road, Swanton, MD 21561. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Glen Cova - 935 Crows Point Road, Swanton, MD 21561.

Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Glen Cova - 935 Crows Point Road, Swanton, MD 21561.

They say beauty is only skin deep—but Glen Cova is not only beautiful, it has a great personality and is smartly built with the vacationer in mind. This shaded, level backyard is the ideal place for fun and relaxation. The quiet cove makes your day at the lake private yet exhilarating. Life is full of pleasant surprises, and once you visit Glen Cova, you’ll have one of the best! The living room brims with cushy furniture, a huge flat panel TV and lots of room and comfort.

A complete, well-equipped kitchen makes preparation for ‘eating in’ a joy. With everything at your fingertips, you can create a cuisine that will fascinate your family and friends. Magnificent views of the lake with indoor or outdoor dining compliments this bright and open area. Elegant, yet serviceable—you can catch up on your e-mails, or relax on this charming day bed while planning your future activities. Comfort abounds in this master suite, complete with gorgeous scenes of the lake and just a step outside with your morning coffee.

Every bedroom is detailed for you pleasure. You could even sneak outside for a soak in the hot tub at midnight in this one. Bring the kids along and their fun-filled days will be rewarded with restful nights. There’s even room for the in-laws! Glen Cova offers a great deal of contentment for the busy vacationer and you’ll enjoy every moment of it. You deserve to be rewarded for all your hard work, and Glen Cova is that special place where memories are created. Kick back and count your blessings. You can find heaven on earth…and it’s not that far away!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:48</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,Glen Cova,Swanton,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>On Eagles' Wings - 110 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring On Eagles' Wings - 110 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/671-On-Eagles-Wings-110-Highline-Drive-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/On-Eagles-Wings.mp4" length="30462326" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">34E2750D-D550-43AE-9E3D-B918B2F21D43-542-00000CBCE2A1CBF8-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 12:54:57 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring On Eagles' Wings - 110 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring On Eagles' Wings - 110 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.

Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents On Eagles' Wings - 110 Highline Drive, McHenry, MD 21541.

You’ll be soaring high in this fabulous home—‘On Eagles’ Wings’. Definitely one of our finest offerings, this beautiful home has modern luxury standards, all while retaining its warm character. Don’t be fooled by the demure exterior of this home. Once inside, you’ll think you’re in paradise. Loaded with charm, On Eagles’ Wings is the ideal accommodation for the big family hoping to get away from it all. Large enough for everyone to have their own space, yet cozy enough to round up the gang and have some quality time together.

You won’t have to worry about whose turn it is to cook in the magnificent kitchen. Everyone will want to get into the act! Every modern convenience has been incorporated in this room, making even cleaning up a pleasure! It’s hard to decide this home’s best bonus feature: its proximity to the slopes and the lake or the fact that it’s big enough to house all of your friends and family. Both are compelling, but the reasonable cost of staying here probably wins. After spending your afternoons discovering the lakes beauty in pristine woods, state parks and on the waterfront, you’ll be thrilled to know that your evenings will complete with a perfect resting area. Everyone can have their own private quarters in any of these tastefully decorated bedrooms. Peaceful nights are a sure thing as you listen to the quiet sounds of nature. As you can see, there’s plenty of room for all your friends and family. They’ll be thanking you for a long time after your trip is over. Dream big. Close your eyes. Smile!

As if the outside activities aren’t enough, On Eagles Wings offers entertainment for the whole family, whether it be playing ping pong or air hockey the indoor fun will enthuse the whole group. As the sun dips toward the horizon, you can always unwind on the spacious deck—soaking in the hot tub or relaxing with your favorite beverage—while experiencing breath-taking views of the country side. Never underestimate the power of nature. For complete immersion into life’s simple pleasures, complete your vacations plans by reserving On Eagles Wings today for that memorable vacation that will stay in your heart and mind forever. Eliminate the hassle and have yourself a worry-free holiday by contacting us today.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:29</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,On Eagles Wings,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bear Mountain Chalet - 44 Country Aire, McHenry, MD 21541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Bear Mountain Chalet - 44 Country Aire, McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/637-Bear-Mountain-Chalet-44-Country-Aire-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Bear-Mountain-Chalet.mp4" length="22332889" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3362B24B-0419-42FF-B19B-1A4FB627739E-640-00000B25F4F8CC85-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 11:12:52 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Bear Mountain Chalet - 44 Country Aire, McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Bear Mountain Chalet - 44 Country Aire, McHenry, MD 21541.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Bear Mountain Chalet - 44 Country Aire, McHenry, MD 21541.

Bear Mountain Chalet is a newly built chalet with gorgeous rolling mountain views, a spacious yard, and an outdoor firepit. If you’re looking forward to getting away from it all, then this Chalet is the place for you. You won’t believe how ‘at home’ you’ll feel when you vacation at this nook in the mountainside. Even though it’s not right on the lake, you’ll be only minutes away from it, plus many other activities like golf, shopping, white water rafting, spas and much more.

Cozy and comfortable, this unique design allows you to revel in the beauty of the country side and remain perfectly serene in your surroundings. Enjoy a game on the flat screen TV next to the wood fireplace. One glimpse at the kitchen will make every meal preparation a pleasure. Stressed spelled backwards spells Desserts!. You can whip up your favorite in this state-of-the-art kitchen, which features modern appliances for preparing your meals that will keep your guests coming back for more Get away from it all by entering this ascetic bedroom for the serenity and gentle tranquility you deserve.

You’ll sleep to the sounds of crickets and wake to the chirping of birds outside your window.After an undisturbed night’s sleep, you’ll feel revitalized and ready to start your new day. This bedroom has it all! Comfortable surroundings, exquisite décor, and the convenience of a master bath await you after a busy day. You might have a hard time time falling asleep with all the quiet. They’ll know what you did last summer when you show your vacation movies to your friends. Bear Mountain Chalet is a picturesque cottage that smiles with attitude. Call today for more details!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:49</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,Bear Mountain Chalet,McHenry,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Off Cape - 118 Oak Way Road Swanton, MD 21561</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Off Cape - 118 Oak Way Road Swanton, MD 21561.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/619-Off-Cape-118-Oak-Way-Road-Swanton-MD-21561.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Off-Cape.mp4" length="21524760" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0170CF64-24BA-49D5-A350-C0727D4B6B01-869-00000E63AAC3F1AD-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 15:14:22 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Off Cape - 118 Oak Way Road Swanton, MD 21561. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Off Cape - 118 Oak Way Road Swanton, MD 21561.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Off Cape - 118 Oak Way Road Swanton, MD 21561.

Off Cape is the perfect cottage for a quiet get away from the hustle and bustle of everyday life, and is ideal for a romantic escape or small family gathering.  Serene and cordial, ‘Off Cape’ is located in an exclusive area—with plush woods and cool breezes. You’ll get that homey feeling in this delightful cottage which is bursting with unassuming warmth.

The large kitchen has plenty of room for all the cooks and helpers in your party. Everything has its place.  Entertain your friends or sit down for a nice family dinner in this inviting and spacious dining area.  Why not slip into something more comfortable?  A busy day will align wonderfully with a soothing, peaceful night in this master bedroom.  The kids will love the generous amount of space in their bedroom. They’ll even get to flip a coin for the top bunk!  The loft offers the perfect spot for an additional play area, or for sleeping quarters for your guests.

Imagine soaking in the hot tub during the evening with nothing but the stars between you and the heavens above.  Enjoy your own boat slip in these sizeable docks, take a short walk to the lake, and enjoy the majestic views while dipping your feet in the lakes refreshing waters.  There is nothing to obstruct the viewpoint and perspective - you’ll truly have the ideal picture of the lake.  Hike, bike or meander down this country road which will take you on a short jaunt to your boat slip. Watch out for the squirrels, chipmunks, deer, and even wild turkeys!  For complete immersion into nature - a world apart, yet close to home - escape to  ‘Off Cape’ at Deep Creek Lake.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:45</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,Off Cape,Swanton,video tours,homes,rent</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>On The Greens - 255 Fantasy Valley McHenry, MD 21541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring On The Greens - 255 Fantasy Valley McHenry, MD 21541 .&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/618-On-The-Greens-255-Fantasy-Valley-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/On-The-Greens.mp4" length="29669915" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">12E1F9DC-C8C4-447F-880E-4B308CD6372A-4543-0000731BCEC2C5BE-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 18:58:55 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring On The Greens - 255 Fantasy Valley McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring On The Greens - 255 Fantasy Valley McHenry, MD 21541.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents On The Greens - 255 Fantasy Valley McHenry, MD 21541.

Majestic, yet warm and enticing, ‘On The Greens’ is a vacationer’s dream come true. Snuggled in glorious environs, the many extras afforded here are amazing.  A perfect view of the golf course is evident from anywhere on this expansive deck. Everything is picture perfect and within reach.  Elegant yet quite cozy, this Great room offers the idyllic setting for a tranquil visit.  You’ll be rendered speechless when you walk into this over-sized kitchen. Preparing meals will definitely be something you’ll look forward to, even though you are on vacation.

The dining room is perfect for formal meals, yet versatile enough for hot dogs and hamburgers. There's lots of room for a myriad of hungry guests.  The more the merrier! ...And the children don’t even have to sit at the ‘kiddies’ table!  This huge recreation area lends itself to a friendly game of pool, watching a movie on the Plasma TV, or simply relaxing with a good book.  Now this is what a getaway house should be! The entire home is richly connected with the surrounding landscape.  For the adventurous family on a dream vacation, you can rest easily in the impeccable bedrooms furnished for your relaxation.  Each morning you’ll awake refreshed and rarin’ to go!  You'll find that every little detail has been considered and carefully honed to perfection.  Home to the most serene surroundings, your fun-filled days will be complete with quiet, restful nights.  You’ll witness the beauty of nature with every turn—with rich wood beams and a tasteful décor.

Whether golfing, boating or fishing, watching wild life or hosting a party.  ‘On The Greens ‘ is the perfect atmosphere to do all your favorite things. Early autumn, when daylight lingers into the early evening and gray clouds have yet to engulf the sky - makes a beautiful time to visit.  Get a taste of Deep Creek in a long week-end escape. You can plan a leisurely itinerary—with coffee breaks, of course. These outdoor spaces are big enough for a crowd.  Bask in the solitude.  You can see the stress of an urban life style melt away—and a look of total peace is left in its place.  For those who can tear themselves from this home, the surrounding area offers a wealth of outdoor activities.  Come visit ‘On The Greens’ today!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:25</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,On The Green,McHenry,video tours,homes,over the rainbow</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bear-Inn-Dipity - 116 Klotz Farm Road McHenry, MD 21541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Bear-Inn-Dipity - 116 Klotz Farm Road McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/617-Bear-Inn-Dipity-116-Klotz-Farm-Road-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Bear-Inn-Dipity.mp4" length="20851295" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">61ACE2FC-74DF-410C-A138-926CB986BE20-3483-00005B24132B3BA2-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 11:41:00 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Bear-Inn-Dipity - 116 Klotz Farm Road McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Bear-Inn-Dipity - 116 Klotz Farm Road McHenry, MD 21541.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Bear-Inn-Dipity - 116 Klotz Farm Road McHenry, MD 21541.

Welcome to Bear-Inn-Dipity - a spectacular country farm house which is the perfect getaway for a family gathering or a weekend couples escape. Arriving at Bear Inn Dipity feels like a sweet reward, not only because you’re surrounded by spectacular scenery, but also because it was so easy to get to. Simple from the outside, one step inside shows the contemporary style—without being stark. It’s like a modern home that has been warmed up. When it’s time for dinner, the up-to-date kitchen will make feeding even the largest group a breeze!!

This master suite comes complete with spacious surroundings that make for peaceful and restful nights. Tastefully decorated and full of charm, you’ll definitely look forward to the end of the day. Relax for as long as you want in this deluxe garden tub. The bathroom is just as opulent as the rest of the house. Guests can enjoy their own room with impressive views. Whether they be friends or family, they’ll feel special. Each bedroom has its own unique quality. Sit and relax, or sleep in total comfort.

Bear-Inn-Dipity even a has place where the kids can kick back and enjoy themselves. Maybe best of all is sitting on the deck, just reading and enjoying the quiet amongst nature’s best. Get rid of all your problems by soaking in the hot tub while bordered by nature. A one-of-a-kind oasis is awaiting your presence. Share the laughter and the sunshine with a few good friends. Create unforgettable memories at Bear Inn Dipity!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:42</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,Bear Inn Dipity,McHenry,video tours,homes,over the rainbow</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>American Pride - 16 Lichen Lane Oakland, MD 21550</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring American Pride - 16 Lichen Lane Oakland, MD 21550.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/616-American-Pride-16-Lichen-Lane-Oakland-MD-21550.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/American-Pride.mp4" length="23889400" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">DE8A2AE5-E5F3-4B7E-965E-651A7D490FB2-3483-00005AE7BE8DC7A9-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 11:25:49 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring American Pride - 16 Lichen Lane Oakland, MD 21550. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring American Pride - 16 Lichen Lane Oakland, MD 21550.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents American Pride - 16 Lichen Lane Oakland, MD 21550.

Staying at American Pride is sure to deliver a wonderful vacation which will make you and your family feel good all over. A hot tub and gazebo go together perfectly! And when they're located in a quiet, private, woodsy environment - it makes for a relaxing atmosphere that will let you feel like you're in another world! Bright and airy, this great room is tastefully decorated to provide comfort and relaxation for all.

Whether it be a formal dinner or a laid-back breakfast, the dining area is truly exceptional for enjoying your meals within. The kitchen makes the cook feel right at home with every modern convenience right at their fingertips. Watch your favorite TV show or movie; maybe curl up in front of the fireplace with a good book, or even test your pool skills - this recreational setting is quite distinctive. You can even entertain your friends and family in this refreshing and social setting. Quiet and peaceful - this master suite will surely contribute to your total relaxation.

The huge Jacuzzi and bath are both luxurious and inviting, and make this the 'place to be' when you need to 'get the kinks out' after an active day at the lake. Friends, family - everyone - will have their own little hideaway within this amazing retreat. There is lots of room for all to unwind in and enjoy. American Pride also features completely awesome amenities - get your laps in, or watch the kids play in this attractive swimming pool. This spacious play venue is the perfect spot for fun and fresh air. Tennis anyone? How 'bout a freindly game of one-on-one? There are many activities here for everyone's enjoyment. American Pride is tactfully displayed in every regard. By the way - Mother Nature called: She wants you to discover the true meaning of a great vacation!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:58</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,American Pride,Oakland,video tours,homes,over the rainbow</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Over The Rainbow - 1140 Rock Lodge Road McHenry, MD 21541</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Over The Rainbow - 1140 Rock Lodge Road McHenry, MD 21541.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/563-Over-The-Rainbow-1140-Rock-Lodge-Road-McHenry-MD-21541.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Over-The-Rainbow.mp4" length="18179133" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D354B8BA-8D3C-4F5C-9352-ABB2E6FF064A</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 1 Aug 2008 12:40:32 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Over The Rainbow - 1140 Rock Lodge Road McHenry, MD 21541. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Over The Rainbow - 1140 Rock Lodge Road McHenry, MD 21541.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Over The Rainbow - 1140 Rock Lodge Road McHenry, MD 21541.

Over the Rain Bow is a wonderful 4 bedroom 4 bath chalet. You won't believe your eyes when you set sight on this wonderful home, which is located at one of the most beautiful spots on the lake. The backdrop of this spacious chalet features one of Deep Creek lake's precious few level lake fronts, which is filled with soaring oak trees. Dining by the lake and gazing at the stars are just a few things you simply must do at this exceptional vacation chalet. After playing hard all day, don’t forget to relax and soak yourself in the inviting, oversized Hot tub.

With plenty of spacious living areas, Over-The-Rainbow offers the perfect setting for your vacation get-away. This is much more than just a 'house on the lake' - this unique home is what fond memories are made of. It's just minutes from anything and everything...you'll truly be amazed at how worry-free your vacation is. Sit down. Relax. We'll take care of all the little details. This chalet boasts a spacious living area, an expansive deck, a level lakefront, and amazing views - you have truly found a pot of gold!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:30</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,memory lane,McHenry,video tours,homes,over the rainbow</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Memory Lane - 941 Mountainview Drive, Oakland MD 21550</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Memory Lane - 941 Mountainview Drive, Oakland MD 21550.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://deepcreekvacations.escapia.com/site/Overview/PropertyID__31023/8936/DesktopDefault.aspx</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Memory_Lane.mp4" length="25959106" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">E59DFA0D-7ECD-4DF0-93E0-2A86D6E12DDF</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 16:39:54 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Memory Lane - 941 Mountainview Drive, Oakland MD 21550. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Memory Lane - 941 Mountainview Drive, Oakland MD 21550.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Memory Lane - 941 Mountainview Drive, Oakland MD 21550.

Memory Lane received its name from the gracious, huge trees and beautifully maintained lawn which give you the comfort of home with all the amenities of community surroundings. Accommodating up to 12 people with it’s 4 bedrooms and 3.5 baths, Memory Lane will be sure to send you home with memories to last a life-time. Whether it be friends, family, or new acquaintances, the exquisite décor and conveniently designed interior will welcome every guest with friendly hospitality unmatchable in this area

The generous yard can be viewed from almost every area of the home to keep an eye on the fun in store for the children: playing in the snow or a game of hide and go seek! Take a dip in the hot tub to soothe your muscles or play a game of pool in the large family room. Nearby activities include basketball, volleyball and a picnic pavilion for use at your discretion. Within two miles, you’ll find an array of restaurants, unique shops and a movie theater for your fun and pleasure. On down the road…skiing, golf and Garrett Counties’ wondrous state parks await your visit.

All of the bedrooms are perfectly suited for you and your family's enjoyment. There's plenty of space for everyone to find comfort, serenity and relaxation. The master bath is the ultimate retreat, and it features a luxurious tub for you to enjoy. The gorgeous deck's hot tub is completely inviting and offers a spectacular view off of the deck. There is even a fire pit awaiting you, which is perfect for night-time gatherings in the great outdoors.

The docks - along with this beautiful lake view - are only a short drive away. There are even tennis courts awaiting your next game, and a basketball court for a little friendly family competition. Experience the vacation of a lifetime in Memory Lane!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:08</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,memory lane,Oakland,video tours,real estate,homes</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Wild Rose - 810 White Oak Drive, Swanton MD 21561</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Wild Rose - 810 White Oak Drive, Swanton MD 21561.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://deepcreekvacations.escapia.com/site/Overview/PropertyID__31211/8936/DesktopDefault.aspx</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Wild_Rose.mp4" length="25491323" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">E113BD35-F4D3-4458-95D5-2E542E82FF3D</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 13:55:25 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Wild Rose - 810 White Oak Drive, Swanton MD 21561. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Wild Rose - 810 White Oak Drive, Swanton MD 21561.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Wild Rose - 810 White Oak Drive, Swanton MD 21561.

Wild Rose is a newly built home located on a flat, lake-front lawn that encourages walk-in swimming in the peaceful cove, without the roar of motor boats or jet skis interrupting the serene environment. The Type A dock allows you to enjoy some great fishing right off the dock or bring your own boat to keep there during your vacation.

This property features a novel, covered deck with a gorgeous lake view from each of its king-sized bedrooms, granite countertops, and four sitting areas for the whole family to relax. The 50&quot; Plasma TV with HD DirecTV in the great room will please the sports enthusiasts, while other family members can enjoy a quiet cup of coffee and favorite book in one of the other sitting areas. Take a dip under the stars in the large hot tub that sits on the lower level patio and looks out into the lake.

Or maybe try relaxing in one of the two over-sized Jacuzzi tubs or indulge yourself in one of the two steam showers. Wild Rose accommodates up to ten people in this quiet 5 bedroom 5.5 bath home with four master suites, and boasts 3 fireplaces - perfect for you to warm up and enjoy your company.

Even though Wild Rose is tucked away from all the hustle and bustle it is only minutes from area activities such as shopping, golf, spas, horseback riding, and great restaurants. Once you've experienced the exquisite comfort of this 'Wild Rose', you will request a return visit year after year--because quality and serenity go hand in hand.

It's a 'beautiful day in the neighborhood'! Can you say copacetic? Relax! You're on vacation. Let us reserve this Wild Rose for your vacation pleasures. Call today for availability. You'll be glad you did.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:05</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,wild rose,Swanton,video tours,real estate,homes</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Clubhouse Chalet - 65 Clubhouse Road, Swanton MD 21561</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Clubhouse Chalet - 65 Clubhouse Road, Swanton MD 21561.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://deepcreekvacations.escapia.com/site/Overview/PropertyID__31255/8936/DesktopDefault.aspx</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Clubhouse_Chalet.mp4" length="16815344" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">79B6CCA2-8803-42DE-88C7-E94956ADEA23</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 12:39:25 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Clubhouse Chalet - 65 Clubhouse Road, Swanton MD 21561. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Clubhouse Chalet - 65 Clubhouse Road, Swanton MD 21561.

Property Description: Chad Taylor of Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations presents Clubhouse Chalet - 65 Clubhouse Road, Swanton MD 21561.

Tennis anyone? Swimming? Fun at the Lake? Golf? Take your pick at this newly built decorative home...right in the heart of a fun vacation area! Attractions include a kid-friendly community with access to a catch and release pond, sledding hill, and a miniature golf course. And for the adults, a Par-3 golf course is just a short walk away!

This property will sleep up to 14 people and has 5 bedrooms and 5 baths. Be sure to take the vacation inside with the private indoor pool which is fun for all ages. Or get the gang together over a game of billiards in the family room downstairs. You can actually have it all at this vacation retreat, and the family harmony will be singing for months to come.

Don't miss out on this terrific opportunity; you'll be glad you made the right decision. You can spend active, fun-filled days doing all of your favorite things, and rest easy at night, knowing your sleep won’t be interrupted by traffic or ‘city’ noises. The Clubhouse Chalet is just a phone call away! Call now so you won’t miss out on a vacation of a lifetime.

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:23</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,clubhouse chalet,Swanton,video tours,real estate,homes</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bear Necessities - 195 Basswood Way, Oakland MD 21550</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring Bear Necessities - 195 Basswood Way, Oakland MD 21550.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</description>
            <link>http://deepcreekvacations.escapia.com/site/Overview/PropertyID__30261/8936/DesktopDefault.aspx</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/taylor_made/Bear_Necessities.mp4" length="18318356" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">030EE95B-1CE7-4A7E-A298-1235B706BDD9</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 11:14:27 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring Bear Necessities - 195 Basswood Way, Oakland MD 21550. For more info, contact Taylor-Made by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring Bear Necessities - 195 Basswood Way, Oakland MD 21550.

Bear Necessities is a newly built log home nestled in the woods in the Deep Creek Lake area with access to hiking trails, a trout stream, a pavilion, and a children’s playground.  It boasts a spacious layout, and features a large screen TV over top a stone fireplace in the great room.  You can easily lose yourself in what it has to offer, only to emerge well-rested and ready for anything.

Bear Necessities encourages you to relax in its beautiful master suite, which includes an oversized Jacuzzi tub for the ultimate experience.  This cozy 4 bedroom, 3 bath log home sleeps up to 10 people, and is the perfect get-away for all seasons. It's only minutes away from the lake, state parks, golf courses and ski resort.  You’ll appreciate the cozy atmosphere, and immediately realize what total relaxation truly means.

Bear Necessities is the place to be at the lake if you’re looking for comfort, serenity, and an abundance of beautiful views to enjoy. It is the perfect place for families, and your party will be certain to have the time of their lives - and a time that will be long remembered.  Call today to reserve this retreat for a fun-filled vacation in paradise!

For more information, please contact Taylor-Made Deep Creek Vacations by phone at 866-351-1119, by email at info@deepcreekvacations.com, or visit them online at www.deepcreekvacations.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:31</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>taylor-made,vacation rentals,deep creek lake,maryland,MD,chad taylor,cabins,bear necessities,oakland,video tours,real estate,homes</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
