<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Tom Schieber of Windermere Properties of the East Bay Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours of Homes in the San Francisco East Bay Region from Tom Schieber of Windermere Properties.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Tom Schieber by phone at 925-487-3172, by email at tom@windermere.com, or visit Windermere Properties of the East Bay online at www.windermere.com today.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.windermere.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 09:35:50 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 09:34:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Tom Schieber of Windermere Properties of the East Bay California Real Estate Video Feed.  For more information, contact Tom Schieber by phone at 925-487-3172, or by email at tom@windermere.com</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours of Homes in the San Francisco East Bay Region from Tom Schieber of Windermere Properties.

About Tom Schieber:

I am a new kind of Real Estate Professional. I mix the service of a traditional, neighborhood agent with the latest technology to get your home sold fast, for the highest price with the fewest problems.
I’m a second-generation Realtor.I studied economics at Westmont College in Santa Barbara and did my graduate work at the University of Colorado at Denver. I also have a certificate in computer programming from Denver Technical College.
I’m completely mobile, I work where it’s convenient for you. We can meet at your house, Starbucks, wherever you want. Everything we need is on my laptop. 
I’m completely paperless. I have the software to generate all of my paperwork on-line, and the ability to sign electronically, either on the screen in person or remotely via secure server.

For more information, contact Tom Schieber by phone at 925-487-3172, by email at tom@windermere.com, or visit Windermere Properties of the East Bay online at www.windermere.com today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Tom Schieber,Windermere Properties of the East Bay,Brentwood,Antioch,California,CA,real estate,realtor,homes,houses,for sale,property</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/tom-schieber/tom-schieber-300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/tom-schieber/tom-schieber-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Tom Schieber of Windermere Properties of the East Bay Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.windermere.com</link>
            <description>The Tom Schieber of Windermere Properties of the East Bay Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>5038 Prairie Way Antioch, CA 94531</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 5038 Prairie Way Antioch, CA 94531.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
4 Bedrooms, 2 Baths, MLS# 40355241.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Tom Schieber by phone at 925-487-3172, by email at tom@windermere.com, or visit Windermere Properties of the East Bay online at www.windermere.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/548-5038-Prairie-Way-Antioch-CA-94531.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/tom-schieber/5038-Prairie-Way.mp4" length="32205750" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">DD914777-CFA4-45AA-85D1-BC3189F42AD0</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 09:28:21 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 5038 Prairie Way Antioch, CA 94531. For more information, contact Tom Schieber by phone at 925-487-3172, by email at tom@windermere.com, or visit Windermere Properties of the East Bay online at www.windermere.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 5038 Prairie Way Antioch, CA 94531.

4 Bedrooms, 2 Baths, MLS# 40355241.

Property Description: Tom Schieber of Windermere Properties of the East Bay presents 5038 Prairie Way Antioch, CA 94531.

This home is much more than a beautifully custom remodeled home, although it certainly is that. It&apos;s also a model of efficient and responsible living, with high-quality and comfortable amenities throughout, and money-saving efficiencies built-in to the every-day systems inside the home. 5038 Prairie Way is the East County&apos;s first totally &quot;Green&quot; re-purposed home! You&apos;ll notice that this isn&apos;t a typical home from the moment you pull up in front. This house has been completely remodeled and upgraded from the covered front porch to the professionally landscaped back yard – and of course everything in between.

The new light-colored composite roof absorbs less heat than darker shingles would, and the Radiant Barrier insulation actually repels attic heat back to the source, meaning that the systems in the house don’t have to work as hard to keep the temperature comfortable. Dual Pane windows are also found throughout the home. The home&apos;s photovoltaic solar system generates electricity from the sun’s light, so the house creates most of it’s own power. This creates this electricity whenever the sun is shining, so when you’re not home using the electricity, it actually sends the power back to the utility company for credit – offsetting your power use during peak times. This result is called “net metering” – which can save you alot of money.

All the lighting thoroughout the house is fluorescent or LED, with requires less electricity. The new laminate flooring and designer paint create a modern and friendly ambiance as soon as you walk in. The chef&apos;s kitchen features granite countertops, new GE appliances, custom cabinetry and breakfast bar is the stuff of homeowners&apos; dreams. The LED under-cabinet lights in the kitchen can be left on continuously and would only cost mere pennies a day. Remodeled baths feature custom tile work and rich fixtures, while new plush carpets line the hallways and master suite. But there&apos;s more to this beautiful home than just the expensive finishes that you can see. A tank-less hot water heater provides instant and continuous hot water on-demand, saving up to 70% in energy costs compared to a conventional electric hot water heaters.

The home&apos;s super-high efficiency Carrier heating and cooling system includes a furnace that is a third more efficient then a typical unit, recycling its own heat to improve efficiency, and a whisper-quiet AC condenser cools the house in much less time than with standard units. The electric fireplace creates a realistic flame, but gives off no emissions and can heat up to 600 sq feet – working in tandem with the furnace and cold-air return to heat the whole house quickly, without running the furnace constantly. Even the lovely backyard&apos;s landscaping is designed to use minimal water! This home&apos;s most valuable attributes are money-saving, energy efficient upgrades that may not be so easy to spot. That is, until you realize more than a 90% savings on your utility bills! That&apos;s because this home was built to be more comfortable, more responsible and more efficient than any conventional house.

For more information, contact Tom Schieber by phone at 925-487-3172, by email at tom@windermere.com, or visit Windermere Properties of the East Bay online at www.windermere.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>4:10</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>Tom Schieber,Windermere Properties of the East Bay,Brentwood,Antioch,California,CA,real estate,realtor,home,house,for sale,Prairie Way</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
