<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Vanacore Homes Real Estate Video Series</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours featuring new homes built by Vanacore Homes, serving Palm Coast, Daytona Beach, Ormond Beach, and its surrounding areas in Florida.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Vanacore Homes by phone at (386) 671-7653, or visit them online at www.vanacorehomes.com today!&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.vanacorehomes.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 9 Jun 2008 09:57:48 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Mon, 9 Jun 2008 09:57:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.2) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Vanacore Homes Real Estate Video Series</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours featuring new homes built by Vanacore Homes, serving Palm Coast, Daytona Beach, Ormond Beach, and its surrounding areas in Florida.

Vanacore Construction Inc. (CBC-058991), a new home builder in Central Florida servicing the Palm Coast, Daytona Beach, Ormond Beach, and its surrounding areas, is enjoying its 21st year in the Central Florida Volusia County area as an award-winning residential and multi-family new home builder. The company has established itself firmly in many upscale Central Florida Volusia and Flagler County communities as top rated new home builders. Todd and Scott Vanacore, owners and new home builders, believe in building every new home right, from inception to completion, by paying strict attention to quality and to the finest details. Their design and home construction expertise is evidenced by the many awards their homes have garnered.

Vanacore Construction Inc. has stepped forward in the residential building community to take on the challenges presented in the industry. They use the latest home building products, technology, and techniques to assure each customer the quality that is expected from their homebuilder.

Vanacore Construction Inc. is frequently spotlighted in the News Journal real estate section whereby our new home models and current projects have been noted for their quality and unique style. As active members of the Central Florida Volusia and Palm Coast Homeowners Association their contributions keep them in the forefront of industry issues.

The Vanacore team believes in a hands on approach when it comes to building new homes and engaging their customers. They are not afraid to roll up their sleeves and get their hands dirty to satisfy you, the customer.

We are able to tailor budgeting plans to fit the first time home builder or those who have unlimited access to their dreams. If you need assistance in attaining a mortgage for your new home we will be happy to put you in contact with a mortgage broker, lender, or bank to help you realize your dream of building your own home. We are also a real estate and development company providing multi family developments and commercial projects.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>Vanacore Homes,builders,florida,FL,daytona beach,Palm Coast,Ormond Beach,houses,construction,real estate,for sale</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/vanacore_homes/vanacore_300x300.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/vanacore_homes/vanacore_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Vanacore Homes Real Estate Video Series</title>
            <link>http://www.vanacorehomes.com</link>
            <description>The Vanacore Homes Real Estate Video Series Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>The Vanacore Homes Paris Model - Creekside Preserve, Ormond Beach FL 32174</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring The Vanacore Homes Paris Model - Creekside Preserve, Ormond Beach FL 32174.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Vanacore Homes by phone at (386) 671-7653, or visit them online at www.vanacorehomes.com today!</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/491-The-Paris-Model-Creekside-Preserve-Ormond-Beach-FL-32174.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/vanacore_homes/Vanacore_Homes_Paris.mp4" length="30711353" type="video/mp4"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">78C17129-9B53-4FA3-AD8D-7903AC3B09E3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 9 Jun 2008 09:52:34 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring The Vanacore Homes Paris Model - Creekside Preserve, Ormond Beach FL 32174. For more information, contact Vanacore Homes by phone at (386) 671-7653, or visit them online at www.vanacorehomes.com today!</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring The Vanacore Homes Paris Model - Creekside Preserve, Ormond Beach FL 32174. 

Property Description: Vanacore Homes presents The Paris Model - Creekside Preserve, Ormond Beach FL 32174.

As Ormond Beach’s newest gated community, Creekside Preserve sits in a rural environment, but has city conveniences – the beaches, schools, golf, and shopping are just minutes away! A homey community of only 65 homes, Creekside is scenic and serene. Tall pines overlook the four lakes, each with a lighted fountain, and each road ends in a cul de sac with regal palm trees adding to the ambience. Open space, ponds and conservation areas, dotted with Gazebos, a nature trail, and a handsome mixture of top value Vanacore Homes makes Creekside Preserve a delightful place to live. Vanacore Homes participates in the Florida Power and Light’s “BuildSmart” program, ensuring extra energy efficiency and savings to the Buyer. Each home has pavers in the drive and walkways; exterior stone trim and is fully landscaped and irrigated. Each lot is large enough for a pool and no home backs to another home – it backs to water, trees or conservation area.

The award winning Paris Model sets the standard for all Vanacore Homes in Creekside Preserve. With a three-car garage, front porch and designer front door it has the elegance to do its name justice. Entering the Foyer one is met with hardwood floors in the Living Room and Dining Room, with 10 foot ceilings and crown molding, establishing a sense of style and elegance for the entire house. The large Living Room area, has a designer niche and flows to the elegant and spacious Dining Room which is ample enough for the entire family to enjoy holiday dinners. Rounded archways lead to the well equipped Kitchen featuring wood cabinetry, granite counters, stone backsplash, stainless appliances, and room for little helpers. Beyond the Kitchen is a bright and cheery nook, with a door to the Lanai and multiple windows. The Paris includes a convenient desk area, and a large family room with plenty of space for a multitude of activities.

The hallway with a niche and extra large linen closet leads to two ample bedrooms and a tiled bath – perfect for family members or guests. The tiled Utility Room has a laundry tub and cabinets and leads to the three-car garage. Across the formal area is the deluxe Master Suite starting with the flex room or home office. A pocket door for privacy opens to the lavish Master Bath with glass and tiled step-in shower, garden tub, linen closet and comfort height vanity with cultured marble top and decorator lighting. Again, a pocket door opens to a hallway with two walk-in closets and then into the gorgeous Master Bedroom with a double-trayed ceiling with crown molding. This is a “King Size” room and it will accommodate large furnishings. A wall of windows and a side door offer expansive views of the back – be it trees, a pond or a pool.

The best thing about the Paris is that only the Plantation Shutters on the windows are not standard – everything else – pavers, stone trim, designer front door, hardwood floors, designer kitchen, crown molding, recessed lighting, and installed security system – is standard! With ten floor plans available – from 2000 to 3100 sq ft - there is a Vanacore Home in Creekside Preserve to meet every family’s needs. Whichever model is selected, a Vanacore Home offers the best value in Volusia County.

For more information, contact Vanacore Homes by phone at (386) 671-7653, or visit them online at www.vanacorehomes.com today!</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:52</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>Vanacore Homes,builders,florida,FL,daytona beach,Ormond Beach,houses,Paris model,real estate,for sale,creekside preserve</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
