<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Video2Impress Internet Video Podcast Feed</title>
        <description>Video content produced and presented by Video2Impress.com.  Located in central North Carolina, Video2Impress is a unique and affordable digital video and audio production service. Owner, videograher, and producer, Terri Perry, has a creative vision for bold imagery and sound that will add life and distinction to any video project.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Video2Impress by phone at (919) 625-8107, by email at terri@video2impress.com, or online at www.video2impress.com</description>
        <link>http://www.video2impress.com</link>
        <copyright>c2009 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 15:45:09 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 15:44:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <generator>FeedForAll Mac v2.1 (2.1.0.1); http://www.FeedForAll.com/</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Video2Impress Internet Video Podcast Feed</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Video content produced and presented by Video2Impress.com. Located in central North Carolina, Video2Impress is a unique and affordable digital video and audio production service. Owner, videograher, and producer, Terri Perry, has a creative vision for bold imagery and sound that will add life and distinction to any video project.

For more information, contact Video2Impress by phone at (919) 625-8107, by email at terri@video2impress.com, or online at www.video2impress.com today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>video2impress,raleigh,north carolina,NC,video,production,service,terri perry,filming,production</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/video2impress/video2impress-300x300.jpg" />
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/video2impress/video2impress-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Video2Impress Internet Video Podcast Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.video2impress.com</link>
            <description>The Video2Impress Internet Video Podcast Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>117 Crossfire Road, Holly Springs, NC 27540</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 117 Crossfire Road, Holly Springs, NC 27540.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
3 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms, MLS# 1658506.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Terri Perry by email at tperry999@earthlink.ne, or visit them online at www.McNamaraProperties.net  today!</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/740-117-Crossfire-Road-Holly-Springs-NC-27540.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/video2impress/117-Crossfire-Road.mp4" length="25013592" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">79B60704-5523-4E89-B953-EA04122130EE-863-000017DF6697EF26-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 15:45:06 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 117 Crossfire Road, Holly Springs, NC 27540. For more information, please contact Terri Perry by email at tperry999@earthlink.ney, or visit them online at www.McNamaraProperties.net today!</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 117 Crossfire Road, Holly Springs, NC 27540. 3 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms, MLS# 1658506. Gorgeous property located in one of the most desirable communities in Holly Springs, NC. The immaculate yard is fenced in the rear and has a large side yard. Inside, beautiful hardwood floors greet you at the door and flow all through the living and dining areas. Hardwood treads on the open staircase lead to the Master Suite. There is a niche and accent lights above the gas fireplace with marble hearth. The organized kitchen is open to the living and dining areas. Ceramic tile floors and kitchen backsplash are just some of the eye-catching features. The Master Suite is spacious and has a cathedral ceiling &amp; palladium window. The Master Bath features a vaulted ceiling, double vanity, completely tiled shower and a garden tub with tile surround. Plenty of light shines through between the octagonal-shaped window and window above the garden tub. The walk in closet has lots of shelving and there is also a mirror-faced mini-armoire. Bedroom 1 features a cathedral ceiling, a palladium window and a plant ledge. You'll spend all your summer days in the backyard where the over-sized deck overlooks a yard that was obviously loved! This home is very convenient to shopping, restaurants, and 3/10 of a mile from the park, complete with running trails. It also just happens to be down the block from the community’s pool and playground. For more information, please contact Terri Perry by email at tperry999@earthlink.ney, or visit them online at www.McNamaraProperties.net today!</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:57</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>Raleigh,Holly Springs,north carolina,NC,real estate,McNamara Properties,Terri Perry,house,home,for sale,Crossfire Road,property</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>130 Briar Rose Lane, Garner, NC 27529</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 130 Briar Rose Lane, Garner, NC 27529.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
4 Bedrooms, 4.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1608160 .&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Stephen Votino by email at svotino@mcnamaraproperties.net, or visit them online at www.McNamaraProperties.net  today!</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/737-130-Briar-Rose-Lane-Garner-NC-27529.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/video2impress/130-Briar-Rose.mp4" length="24209182" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">33374D6C-E716-4C40-8F5B-3B6EB8EAA258-630-000009248E050875-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 11:31:21 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 130 Briar Rose Lane, Garner, NC 27529. For more information, please contact Stephen Votino by email at svotino@mcnamaraproperties.net, or visit them online at www.McNamaraProperties.net today!</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 130 Briar Rose Lane, Garner, NC 27529. 4 Bedrooms, 4.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1608160. Brick home with all the bells &amp; whistles. Beautiful foyer with coffered ceiling; Chef's kitchen with high profile SS appliances, granite countertops, custom cabinets and 2 sink areas; Huge family room with built-ins &amp; gas fireplace; Formal Dining and Living Room; Master Suite has 3 walk-in closets and elaborate ceiling detail; Luxurious Master Bath has 2 separate vanities and a tiled shower with dual shower heads; Extensive moulding/trim and hardwood floors on the 1st floor; Irrigation system; 3 car garage; Nearly 3,000 sf. walk-in attic space; Climate-controlled walk-in crawl space; and so much more! For more information, please contact Stephen Votino by email at svotino@mcnamaraproperties.net, or visit them online at www.McNamaraProperties.net today!</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:50</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>Raleigh,Garner,north carolina,NC,real estate,McNamara Properties,Steven Votino,house,home,for sale,Briar Rose Lane,property</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>209 Travel Lite Drive, Raleigh, NC 27603</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 209 Travel Lite Drive, Raleigh, NC 27603.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
3 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1653311.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Stephen Votino by email at svotino@mcnamaraproperties.net, or visit them online at www.McNamaraProperties.net  today!</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/735-209-Travel-Lite-Drive-Raleigh-NC-27603.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/video2impress/209-Travel-Lite-Drive.mp4" length="22975245" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9CD64137-173F-4453-942D-6D6659FA2786-673-00000E6AF5F75A09-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2009 12:48:47 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 209 Travel Lite Drive, Raleigh, NC 27603. For more info, please contact Stephen Votino by email at svotino@mcnamaraproperties.net, or visit them online at www.McNamaraProperties.net today!</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 209 Travel Lite Drive, Raleigh, NC 27603. 3 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1653311. Immaculate home with open floor plan in beautiful Waverly Pointe. Kitchen has 42&quot; cabinets, dark granite countertops &amp; stainless appliances. Large family room with gas fireplace and formal trim. Large master bedroom with 2 walk-in closets and master bath with dual vanity &amp; separate shower/bath. Beautiful hardwood floors on the 1st floor, deep garage with great storage, large deck and screened porch. Incredible .69 acre home site! For more information, please contact Stephen Votino by email at svotino@mcnamaraproperties.net, or visit them online at www.McNamaraProperties.net today!</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:44</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>Raleigh,north carolina,NC,real estate,McNamara Properties,Steven Votino,house,home,for sale,Travel Lite Drive,Waverly Pointe</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>All Pro Nutrition - Sports and Health Supplements With Professional Advice</title>
            <description>All Pro Nutrition - Sports and Health Supplements With Professional Advice. Patrick Richardson, IFBB Professional Bodybuilder and owner of All Pro Nutrition in Raleigh, NC. Sports and health supplements with professional advice is far better than getting advice from some part time worker in a big chain store! Fitness competitors and US Olympic competitors trust Patrick and the staff of All Pro Nutrition. Let All Pro Nutrition get you in the right direction!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Patrick Richardson by email at info@allpronutritioninc.com, or visit All Pro Nutrition online at http://allpronutritioninc.com/index.htm today! </description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/723-All-Pro-Nutrition-Sports-and-Health-Supplements-With-Professional-Advice.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/video2impress/All-Pro-Nutrition.mp4" length="3988425" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">F4A1EC4C-EB5D-4BAF-BCF9-21066E4F72C0-558-00000A5D430C9DF1-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 15:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>All Pro Nutrition - Sports and Health Supplements With Professional Advice. For more information, please contact Patrick Richardson by email at info@allpronutritioninc.com, or visit All Pro Nutrition online at www.allpronutritioninc.com/index.htm today!</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>All Pro Nutrition - Sports and Health Supplements With Professional Advice. 

Patrick Richardson, IFBB Professional Bodybuilder and owner of All Pro Nutrition in Raleigh, NC. Sports and health supplements with professional advice is far better than getting advice from some part time worker in a big chain store! Fitness competitors and US Olympic competitors trust Patrick and the staff of All Pro Nutrition. Let All Pro Nutrition get you in the right direction!

For more information, please contact Patrick Richardson by email at info@allpronutritioninc.com, or visit All Pro Nutrition online at www.allpronutritioninc.com/index.htm today! </itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>0:31</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>all pro nutrition,sports,supplements,health,advice,patrick richardson,raleigh,north carolina,NC,store,products</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>11221 Oakcroft Drive, Raleigh, NC 27614</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 11221 Oakcroft Drive, Raleigh, NC 27614.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
4 Bedrooms, 3.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1646755.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, please contact Aquene Hernandez by email at hernandeza@hpw.comThis e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it , or visit her online today! </description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/722-11221-Oakcroft-Drive-Raleigh-NC-27614.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/video2impress/11221-Oakcroft-Drive.mp4" length="22079660" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">CDDF94FC-9699-4800-9BB2-5DB5E65E9C06-558-00000A00903BB39E-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 13:20:49 -0500</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 11221 Oakcroft Drive, Raleigh, NC 27614. For more information, please contact Aquene Hernandez by email at hernandeza@hpw.com, or visit her online today!</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 11221 Oakcroft Drive, Raleigh, NC 27614. 4 Bedrooms, 3.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1646755. Property Description: Aquene Hernandez of Coldwell Banker / Howard Perry &amp; Walston presents 11221 Oakcroft Drive, Raleigh, NC 27614. Located near beautiful Falls Lake, this 4 bedroom, first floor master bedroom has 3,139 square feet and 3.5 baths. Incredibly open plan with gorgeous hardwood floors, plush features throughout -- and includes an additional fireplace located in the first floor study. This home is situated on a spacious corner lot that is well manicured and beautifully landscaped. Previously the model home for the builder! For more information, please contact Aquene Hernandez by email at hernandeza@hpw.com, or visit her online today!</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:47</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>Raleigh,north carolina,NC,real estate,Howard Perry Walston,house,home,for sale,Coldwell Banker,Aquene Hernandez,Oakcroft Drive</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
