<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Finn Real Estate Fort Lauderdale Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real Estate Video Tours in the Fort Lauderdale, Florida region presented by Finn Real Estate Enterprises.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Zach Finn by phone at (954) 258-7967, by email at Zach@ForSaleFinn.com, or visit Finn Real Estate Enterprises online at www.forsalefinn.com today.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://forsalefinn.com/</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 09:14:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2008 12:40:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll Mac v2.1 (2.1.0.1); http://www.FeedForAll.com/</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Finn Real Estate Real Estate Video Feed. For more information, contact Zach Finn by phone at (954) 258-7967, by email at Zach@ForSaleFinn.com, or visit Finn Real Estate Enterprises online at www.forsalefinn.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate Video Tours in the Fort Lauderdale, Florida region presented by Finn Real Estate Enterprises.

When you are ready to buy a home in Fort Lauderdale, look no further than the Finn Real Estate Enterprises. Armed with intimate knowledge of the neighborhoods of East Fort Lauderdale, our agents will not rest until they find you the home of your dreams. For the truly personal touch, ask about our South Florida Real Estate Helicopter Tours.

For Sale Finn is a full service real estate brokerage that will help you get the most money possible for your home in the quickest time possible. The sale of your home involves your biggest lifetime investment; don't settle for less than the best. Our knowledgeable, connected real estate agents will provide you with the service and the protection you need when it comes to selling your home.

Trust the experts at For Sale Finn if you want to find the best Fort Lauderdale home rental for your money. Whether you are looking to rent an apartment, condo, townhome, loft, or single family home the real estate experts at For Sale Finn can help you find the property you are looking for.

For more information, contact Zach Finn by phone at (954) 258-7967, by email at Zach@ForSaleFinn.com, or visit Finn Real Estate Enterprises online at www.forsalefinn.com today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>finn real estate enterprises,zach finn,fort lauderdale,florida,real estate,for sale,homes,houses,condominiums,broward,south florida,realtor</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/zach-finn/finn-300x300.jpg" />
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/zach-finn/finn-144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Finn Real Estate Fort Lauderdale Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://forsalefinn.com/</link>
            <description>The Finn Real Estate Fort Lauderdale Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>700 SW 4th Place, Fort Lauderdale FL 33312</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 700 SW 4th Place, Fort Lauderdale FL 33312.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
4 Bedrooms, 3 Full Baths, 2 Halfs.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Zach Finn by phone at (954) 258-7967, by email at Zach@ForSaleFinn.com, or visit Finn Real Estate Enterprises online at www.forsalefinn.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/654-700-SW-4th-Place-Fort-Lauderdale-FL-33312.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/zach-finn/700-SW-4th-Place.mp4" length="31233638" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">83586876-1515-4E51-89B0-5BBD4409420E-688-00000ABF16078B3D-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 09:14:30 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 700 SW 4th Place, Fort Lauderdale FL 33312. For more information, contact Zach Finn by phone at (954) 258-7967, by email at Zach@ForSaleFinn.com, or visit Finn Real Estate Enterprises online at www.forsalefinn.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 700 SW 4th Place, Fort Lauderdale FL 33312.

4 Bedrooms, 3 Full Baths, 2 Halfs.

Property Description: Zach Finn of Finn Real Estate Enterprises presents 700 SW 4th Place, Fort Lauderdale FL 33312.

Located directly on the New River where the Historic neighborhood of Sailboat Bend meets the Arts and Entertainment district, know as Downtown Fort Lauderdale. This Estate offers the best of both worlds with the tranquil, tropical surroundings and Old World Charm that is Sailboat Bend and situated just steps from all the excitement of Downtown and River Walk, including neighboring Broward’s Center for the Performing Arts.  Your private gate opens to reveal the expansive courtyard of this exclusive and special river front home. The Spanish influenced, mission style architecture has been maintained and in keeping with the European tradition of restoration, the current owner decided to maintain the original feel of the exterior, while adding a hip and modern twist to make the interior reflect a lifestyle of today.

Entering this house gives you a refreshingly warm feeling of home, something unfound, in the all too familiar, new construction and zero lot line, Mc Mansions. The creative and eclectic theme carries inside and there is no end to the surprises that exist around every corner of this unique residence. The living room, dining room, office and kitchen all present spectacular River views. The custom Italian kitchen is equipped with a natural gas range, impressive stainless steel hood and duel under mount sink basins. The black absolute granite counter tops and built in appliances finish the space nicely.

Rich Mahogany solid wood flooring that lines the first floor main living area, continues up the stairs to the loft library and carries on throughout the entire second level.  The grand master suit opens to reveal a romantic sitting room overlooking the tropical back yard, beautiful pool area and soothing river. There are remarkable views from every area of this Master Suite, including the walk-in closet.

Open the private terrace off of this Master bathroom and relax in your warm soaking tub while having the benefit of the cool river breeze. This master bath is complete with a spacious, onyx, walk in rain shower and double vanity sinks.  A spiral staircase off the master suit provides direct access to your serine pool area and tropical landscaped back yard.  The pool, out door dining room and back yard sitting areas are intimate, yet ideal for hosting friendly gatherings. Swim with complete privacy in this 45 foot long lap pool. Step onto the dock and you will immediately see the value of this property’s fantastic location with over 100 feet of New River frontage. The new dock, two triple dolphins and new boat lift are awaiting your yacht and other water toys.

A few other important features include natural gas generators that are sufficient to run the entire house, air conditioning and pool pumps in the event of a power outage, as well as, temperature controlled garages for up to four cars. No attention to detail was missed! To set up a private viewing of this property, please call Zach today!

For more information, contact Zach Finn by phone at (954) 258-7967, by email at Zach@ForSaleFinn.com, or visit Finn Real Estate Enterprises online at www.forsalefinn.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>4:08</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>finn real estate enterprises,zach finn,fort lauderdale,florida,real estate,for sale,home,house,downtown,broward,south florida,realtor</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>26 SE 10th Avenue Fort Lauderdale, FL 33301</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 26 SE 10th Avenue Fort Lauderdale, FL 33301.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
3 Bedrooms, 3.5 Baths. MLS# F923721.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Zach Finn by phone at (954) 258-7967, by email at Zach@ForSaleFinn.com, or visit Finn Real Estate Enterprises online at www.forsalefinn.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/516-26-SE-10th-Avenue-Fort-Lauderdale-FL-33301.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/zach-finn/26-SE-10th-Ave.mp4" length="15215058" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">31C6EB7B-A8D7-4C63-BDB6-003558B435B8</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 9 Jul 2008 15:34:42 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 26 SE 10th Avenue Fort Lauderdale, FL 33301. For more info, contact Zach Finn by phone at (954) 258-7967, by email at Zach@ForSaleFinn.com, or visit them online at www.forsalefinn.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 26 SE 10th Avenue Fort Lauderdale, FL 33301.

3 Bedrooms, 3.5 Baths. MLS# F923721.

Property Description: Zach Finn of Finn Real Estate Enterprises presents 26 SE 10th Avenue Fort Lauderdale, FL 33301.

This architecturally significant and unique contemporary home is located just steps from Las Olas Boulevard. The architect and builder focused their attention on building a timeless, energy efficient, eco friendly residence - which comes across clearly in both form and function. The home offers a brilliant floor plan with over-sized rooms and a great flow, allowing for multiple uses and endless functionality.

The custom Boffi kitchen from Italy is breathtaking, and comes complete with super efficient German engineered appliances. Ebony stained hardwood floors and a yacht inspired staircase further complete the picture, adding unparalleled dimension and style. The luxurious master suite is second to none, and features a custom master bath which is adorned by numerous appointments and superb design. This home offers incredible downtown views and superior quality and craftsmanship in every detail.

For more information, contact Zach Finn by phone at (954) 258-7967, by email at Zach@ForSaleFinn.com, or visit Finn Real Estate Enterprises online at www.forsalefinn.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:17</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>finn real estate enterprises,zach finn,fort lauderdale,florida,real estate,for sale,home,house,los olas,broward,south florida,realtor</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
