<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Denise Ruiz and Sandra Barone Nashville Real Estate Video Feed</title>
        <description>Real Estate video tours from the Greater Nashville region, presented by Denise Ruiz and Sandra Barone of Zeitlin and Company Realtors.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This real estate video tour feed is presented by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.agentcasts.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;www.AgentCasts.com&lt;/a&gt;</description>
        <link>http://www.deniseruizhomes.com</link>
        <copyright>c2008 AgentCasts</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 11:14:41 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>admin@agentcasts.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 11:14:32 -0400</pubDate>
        <webMaster>admin@agentcasts.com</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll Mac v2.1 (2.1.0.1); http://www.FeedForAll.com/</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Denise Ruiz and Sandra Barone Nashville TN Real Estate Video Feed. For more info, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185 or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Real Estate video tours from the Greater Nashville region, presented by Denise Ruiz and Sandra Barone of Zeitlin and Company Realtors.

Home Buying and SellingIf you're relocating to the Nashville area, or if you already own a home and you're ready to &quot;move up&quot;, you need to work with a professional full-time Nashville area agent who knows the neighborhoods you'll want to consider!

Follow Through and Follow Up - As a career Nashville real estate agent, I make sure I provide the highest level of service to my clients.  That means following through on things that need to be done, and following up to make sure they're done right.

My clients can count on me for advice on a variety of topics, including insight on selling their homes, updates on the growth neighborhoods, local activities, dining, shopping, and the list goes on.  I even keep clients informed by providing periodic updates on home prices, real estate news and local events.

You'll be glad to work with an agent who actually answers her telephone, or returns calls within a couple hours.  And, my assistant, Carolyn Nelson, does an outstanding job of making sure that nothing gets overlooked.

If You're Buying:  I save my buyer clients a great deal of time and trouble.  My schedule is flexible to accommodate my clients' requirements.  We'll narrow down the number of homes you want to see when I send you e-mails of listings that match your requirements for your review.

You'll make the best decision for you and your family because you'll have all the information you need to make informed choices.  I'll provide you with reports on  neighborhoods and schools.  If you're relocating, a tour of the city may be just what you need to narrow your search. 

If You're Selling:    If you're selling your home, you want a quick transaction at top market value.  I'll help you achieve that goal in a number of ways.  I'll help you stage your home to prepare it for a successful sale, and provide bi-weekly updated of the activity being generated. 

Your home will get excellent exposure on the Internet, including visual tours with lots of photos or a website just for your home.  Color flyers and Just Listed postcards sent to your neighbors will promote your home in your local neighborhood.  And, if you want open houses for your home, you'll get them, too.

I'd love to have the chance to earn your business.  My philosophy is that Keeping Promises leads to Building Relationships.  You'll definitely see a difference in how smoothly a real estate transaction goes when you've built a relationship with a professional Nashville real estate agent who knows how to keep promises!

When you're ready to make a move, please call us at 615-319-9294, or complete the form below to send an e-mail.

We look forward to hearing from you!

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:category text="Business">
            <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Business"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>sandra barone,denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,TN,real estate,homes,for sale,video,houses</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:email>admin@agentcasts.com</itunes:email>
            <itunes:name>Dan Dashnaw</itunes:name>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/sandra-barone/zeitlin_300x300.jpg" />
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.agentcasts.com/clients/sandra-barone/zeitlin_144x144.jpg</url>
            <title>The Denise Ruiz and Sandra Barone Nashville Real Estate Video Feed</title>
            <link>http://www.deniseruizhomes.com</link>
            <description>The Denise Ruiz and Sandra Barone Nashville Real Estate Video Feed Image</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>144</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>2348 Haskell Drive Antioch, TN 37013</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 2348 Haskell Drive Antioch, TN 37013.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
5 Bedrooms, 4.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1016297.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/641-2348-Haskell-Drive-Antioch-TN-37013.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/denise-ruiz/2348-Haskell-Drive.mp4" length="26263497" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B99D4DE5-ACB7-4EA3-B3BD-802B7091E0DE-365-00000B15807BBCF1-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 11:14:38 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 2348 Haskell Drive Antioch, TN 37013. For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 2348 Haskell Drive Antioch, TN 37013.

5 Bedrooms, 4.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1016297.

Property Description: Denise Ruiz and of Zeitlin and Company Realtors presents 2348 Haskell Drive Antioch, TN 37013.

Welcome to 2348 Haskell Drive, located in Cane Ridge Farms. It's time to make a move. Live in a place of your own in this 2-story contemporary home. The formal living room is conveniently located and provides easy access to the second level. The tasteful dining room is adjacent to the kitchen and offers wainscoting and privacy doors. The spacious great room is the perfect place for entertaining family and friends. It is centrally located and boasts close proximity to all rooms on the main level.

Enjoy a quiet evening of relaxation around the fireplace in this 3,663 square foot home. The open floor plan provides enough room for an eat-in kitchen, breakfast area, and access to the back deck. The spacious kitchen has an abundance of counter space, stainless steel appliances, and natural sunlight. Enhance your cooking skills on the work island in this four-year-old home. You will never run out of room during family dinners or parties with all this counter space. The 24x16 master suite has a sitting area, double sinks, architectural design, and ample amounts of storage space.

The custom storage has plenty of room for linens or large wardrobes. The high ceilings make this area seem as though you are never going to run out of space. The second bedroom boasts a full bathroom, an extra large closet with double doors, and a ceiling fan. The third and fourth bedrooms also have extra large closets and neutral colored walls. The fifth bedroom could easily be converted into a home office or play area. The two tier deck overlooks a grassy lawn and has enough space for a play area for children or animals.

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:19</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,Antioch,Nashville,Haskell Drive,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>4047 Wilson Pike Franklin, TN 37067</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 4047 Wilson Pike Franklin, TN 37067 .&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
3 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms, MLS# 1014435 .&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/video/denise-ruiz/4047-Wilson-Pike.mp4</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/denise-ruiz/4047-Wilson-Pike.mp4" length="23857684" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">58F859C2-47A1-4B3D-9345-0F6FF698A332-830-000011B51789FF3B-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 16:30:08 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 4047 Wilson Pike Franklin, TN 37067. For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 4047 Wilson Pike Franklin, TN 37067.

3 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms, MLS# 1014435.

Property Description: Denise Ruiz and of Zeitlin and Company Realtors presents 4047 Wilson Pike Franklin, TN 37067.

Welcome to 4047 Wilson Pike in Franklin, TN, just outside the Brentwood City limits. This 19.58 acre lot is the perfect place for the expansion of your choice. The lot offers 600 feet of road frontage on Wilson Pike. It also offers 527 feet of road frontage on Starnes Mill Rd.

The existing home has no value, but could easily be renovated to suite your heart's desire. This lot is a picturesque building site on top of a hill. The seller is very motivated and will consider allowing multiple building sites. Imagine how convenient it would be for your future home to be minutes to Cool Springs and Williamson County schools. The pond is a bit overgrown, but with a little work, could be the perfect area for animals.

Springtime on this property would be an ideal space for outdoor bar-b-que with family and friends. What more could you ask for? Enough free space to build the home of your dreams and still have extra land with so many possibilities. During the winter, these mature trees resemble post card worthy scenery. People of all ages could find joy in relaxing in this outdoor area. This diamond spring is active year round. Don't miss this great opportunity...at this price, it won't last long!

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:00</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,Franklin,Nashville,Wilson Pike,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>1001 Tulip Blossom Drive Hermitage, TN 37076</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 1001 Tulip Blossom Drive Hermitage, TN 37076.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
3 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1012182.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/613-1001-Tulip-Blossom-Drive-Hermitage-TN-37076.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/denise-ruiz/1001-Tulip-Blossom-Drive.mp4" length="25847628" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6433DB9D-404A-4B5A-B11E-B9F5C6E06812-747-00000F9FEB421773-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 12:26:26 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 1001 Tulip Blossom Drive Hermitage, TN 37076. For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 1001 Tulip Blossom Drive Hermitage, TN 37076.

3 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1012182.

Property Description: Denise Ruiz presents 1001 Tulip Blossom Drive Hermitage, TN 37076.

Welcome to Blossom Trace, one of the most desirable neighborhoods in Hermitage, just a short distance from downtown Nashville. Experience the city life without living there when you're only a short drive away in this 3-bedroom / 2.5-bath home close to shopping and restaurants. Upon entering this contemporary 2,436 square foot home, you will notice the high volume ceilings, hardwood floors, and an abundance of sunlight.

This chic, formal dining room is perfect for family dinners or a quiet night with loved ones. This room is adjacent to the kitchen, providing easy access for preparation of family dinners or holiday gatherings. The spacious eat-in kitchen offers granite counters, stainless steel appliances, and an abundance of counter space. The breakfast bar is the perfect place for reading the paper while having your morning coffee. Large windows provide natural sunlight throughout the room. The spacious great room boats a fireplace with mantle and high ceilings. The great room also allows access to the deck or entry to the second level.

The master suite is located on the main level, and has elegant trey celings and a private bath. The master bath has a separate shower, dual sinks, tile floors, and many storage areas. The bonus room is perfect for a game room, den, or media room. Entertaining family and friends is a pleasure when you have this much open space. Create a computer lab, toss the time clock, and work from your home office. The attached garage provides enough room for 2 cars an extra storage. The deck overlooking mature trees is a great outdoor space for relaxing or enjoying the weather. Contact us to schedule your private showing today, as this low-maintenance brick home offers plenty of space at an affordable price.

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:08</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,Hermitage,Nashville,Tulip Blossom Drive,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>1126 Granny White Court Nashville, TN 37204</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 1126 Granny White Court Nashville, TN 37204.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
4 Bedrooms, 3.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1001083.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/600-1126-Granny-White-Court-Nashville-TN-37204.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/sandra-barone/1126-Granny-White-Court.mp4" length="28671090" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">99CCC178-696F-4DE8-98E1-80DBF78FCA6F</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 20:33:53 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 1126 Granny White Court Nashville, TN 37204. For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 1126 Granny White Court Nashville, TN 37204.

4 Bedrooms, 3.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1001083.

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:23</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,house,Nashville,Granny White Court,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>5005 Burke Trail Nolensville, TN 37135</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 5005 Burke Trail Nolensville, TN 37135.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
4 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1003896.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/588-5005-Burke-Trail-Nolensville-TN-37135.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/sandra-barone/5005-Burke-Trail.mp4" length="21198459" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3432C4FE-A8BB-413C-80B9-9B5A34D86790</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 10:54:12 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 5005 Burke Trail Nolensville, TN 37135. For more info, contact Denise Ruiz by phone at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 5005 Burke Trail Nolensville, TN 37135.

4 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 1003896.

Property Description: Denise Ruiz and Sandra Barone of Zeitlin and Company Realtors present 5005 Burke Trail Nolensville, TN 37135.

Welcome to 5005 Burke Trail. This easy-care model home was built by Newmark Homes. Create a place of your own in this 4-bedroom/2.5-bath home conveniently located near Cool Springs. This never lived in home has $45,000 in upgrades throughout. The combination living room boasts hardwood floors and an abundance of sunshine. The elegant entry foyer provides easy access to main level rooms and second level entry.

The classic dining room is great for entertaining family and friends. The relaxing great room has a gas fireplace and provides an ideal space for unwinding after a long day. The breakfast room is adjacent to the kitchen and allows easy access to the back patio area. The first-rate kitchen has upgraded granite countertops and all stainless steel appliances. This stainless refrigerator is included with the home. For your convenience, the washer and dryer are also included.

The kitchen has upgraded cabinets, providing plenty of counter space. The master suite is conveniently located on the main level and offers a separate shower and dual sinks. This 16X24 room is perfect for an interior expansion of your choice. This patio is ideal for quiet evenings in the nicely landscaped area. The back yard has recently been fenced to provide privacy for this 2,599 square foot home in Bent Creek.

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz by phone at 615-319-9294, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her website at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:46</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,house,Nolensville,Burke Trail,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Denise Ruiz - Market Conditions in Nashville, Tennessee.</title>
            <description>Real estate conditions in Nashville, TN reported by Denise Ruiz of Zeitlin and Co. Realtors in Nashville Tennessee.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/562-Denise-Ruiz-Video-Newsletter.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/denise-ruiz/DeniseRuiz_MCR2.mp4" length="6862251" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">14B134A4-F4B0-44A4-8BA6-DC262B50559F</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 15:19:40 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Real estate conditions in Nashville, TN reported by Denise Ruiz of Zeitlin and Co. Realtors. For more info, contact Denise Ruiz by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Real estate conditions in Nashville, TN reported by Denise Ruiz of Zeitlin and Co. Realtors in Nashville Tennessee.

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>0:47</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,nashville,market,conditions,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Denise Ruiz - Market Conditions in Franklin, Tennessee.</title>
            <description>Real estate conditions in Franklin, TN reported by Denise Ruiz of Zeitlin and Co. Realtors in Nashville Tennessee.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/562-Denise-Ruiz-Video-Newsletter.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/denise-ruiz/DeniseRuiz_MCR.mp4" length="7082534" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">FE011F18-E97B-437D-8FDC-9CE929A0B320</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 15:16:44 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Real estate conditions in Franklin, TN reported by Denise Ruiz of Zeitlin and Co. Realtors. For more info, contact Denise Ruiz by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Real estate conditions in Franklin, TN reported by Denise Ruiz of Zeitlin and Co. Realtors in Nashville Tennessee.

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>0:54</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,franklin,market,conditions,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Denise Ruiz - Agent Video</title>
            <description>A real estate agent profile video featuring Denise Ruiz of Zeitlin and Co. Realtors in Nashville Tennessee.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/562-Denise-Ruiz-Video-Newsletter.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/denise-ruiz/DeniseRuiz.mp4" length="7827218" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">233F0B3E-DF79-47FC-AC24-56B3A6552F6A</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 15:12:58 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate agent profile video featuring Denise Ruiz of Zeitlin and Co. Realtors. For more info, contact Denise Ruiz by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate agent profile video featuring Denise Ruiz of Zeitlin and Co. Realtors in Nashville Tennessee.

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit her online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>0:54</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,profile,video,agent,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>400 Warioto Way Unit D3W, Ashland City, TN 37015</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 400 Warioto Way Unit D3W, Ashland City, TN 37015.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
2 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms, MLS# 996510.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/543-400-Warioto-Way-Unit-D3W-Ashland-City-TN-37015.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/sandra-barone/400-Warioto-Way.mp4" length="22975407" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D808D59B-ED1F-4CCB-9622-1403B124A5A1</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 12:17:34 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 400 Warioto Way Unit D3W, Ashland City, TN 37015. For more info, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 400 Warioto Way Unit D3W, Ashland City, TN 37015.

2 Bedrooms, 2 Bathrooms, MLS# 996510.

Property Description: Denise Ruiz and Sandra Barone of Zeitlin and Company Realtors present 400 Warioto Way Unit D3W, Ashland City, TN 37015.

Welcome to The Braxton-Middle Tennessee's first waterfront condo/marina community. This 1371 square foot condo allows for an abundance of extra storage in the entry foyer. The combination dining room boasts river views and easy access to the open kitchen. You'll enjoy the living room with a gas fireplace for ambiance and views of the river.

This elegant, open kitchen boasts granite countertops, a stove, a microwave, a dishwasher, and a disposal. This conveniently located island is perfect for entertaining family and friends. You'll adore living on the bank of the river that runs by this 2-bedroom/2-bath low-maintenance vacation home in Ashland City. The master bath offers tiled floors, double vanities, an abundance of counter space, and contemporary fixtures. The second bathroom also has tiled floors, contemporary fixtures, and an abundance of counter space, making it seem as though you are on vacation. Both bedrooms provide you with the convenience of walk in closets, providing ample storage space.

You'll adore living on the bank of the river, with water activities at your fingertips. The 324 square foot covered terrace would be a great place to enjoy quiet evenings, listening to the water wash upon the bank. Enjoy fishing, boating or just listening to Old Man River in this low-maintenance vacation condo. This covered marina allows for a secure place for your boat or yacht. Along with a fitness center, the community also offers a pool, tennis courts, and organized events other than the wonderful marina.

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:54</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>sandra barone,denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,condominium,ashland city,warioto way,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>424 Huntington Ridge Drive Nashville, TN 37211</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 424 Huntington Ridge Drive Nashville, TN 37211.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
3 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 998728.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at sandra.barone@zeitlinrealtors.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/531-424-Huntington-Ridge-Drive-Nashville-TN-37211.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/sandra-barone/424-Huntington-Ridge-Drive.mp4" length="26698095" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">554FD04A-565E-4FC2-84FC-08FA4DA0722A</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 14:30:33 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 424 Huntington Ridge Drive Nashville, TN 37211. For more info, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185 or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 424 Huntington Ridge Drive Nashville, TN 37211.

3 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 998728.

Property Description: Sandra Barone and Denise Ruiz of Zeitlin and Company Realtors present 424 Huntington Ridge Drive Nashville, TN 37211.

Welcome to Huntington Ridge townhomes, conveniently located near I-65, shopping, and schools. This sought after community's association includes pool, tennis, water and other conveniences. This well maintained 3 bedroom 2.5 bath townhome offers a 2 car garage and over 1400 square feet.

Upon entering the home, the inviting living room with a fireplace is a great place to entertain family and friends or spend quiet nights enjoying a fire. The eat in kitchen provides plenty of storage and counter space for preparing family meals or holiday dinners. The dining area allows access to the large deck or entry to the second level. Architectural details can be found throughout this reasonably priced townhome in close proximity to Brentwood. The master bedroom is spacious and offers a great retreat from a busy day with a private bath and walk in closet. The second bedroom is a perfect room for a child or roommate with an extra large closet. The third bedroom would make a great nursery, hobby room or office. The large deck overlooking the the trees is a great outdoor space for entertaining or enjoying quite evenings. The two car garage is located in the rear of the townhome and provides plenty of room for any need storage.

Parking is available in the rear of the townhome to provide plenty of green space in the front. There is plenty of room to watch children play or to just enjoy the outdoors. There are plenty of mature trees throughout the community to enjoy on a walk to the many community amenities. Don't forget to enjoy one of the pools during the summer - what a great way to stay cool! Contact us to schedule your private showing today, as this townhome offers plenty of space at an affordable price. Huntington Ridge has so much to offer, and is perfectly situated in an extremely convenient location.

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at sandra.barone@zeitlinrealtors.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:13</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>sandra barone,denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,Nashville,huntington ridge drive,TN,real estate,townhome,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>1714 Charity Drive Brentwood, TN 37067</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 1714 Charity Drive Brentwood, TN 37067.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
4 Bedrooms, 3.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 999045.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/526-1714-Charity-Drive-Brentwood-TN-37067.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/sandra-barone/1714-Charity-Drive.mp4" length="23891824" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B53D178C-B371-41B1-AD2F-00C1989CB4A0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 13:46:33 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 1714 Charity Drive Brentwood, TN 37067. For more info, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185 or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 1714 Charity Drive Brentwood, TN 37067.

4 Bedrooms, 3.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 999045.

Property Description: Denise Ruiz and Sandra Barone of Zeitlin and Company Realtors present 732 4th Avenue North, Nashville TN 37219.

Welcome to 1714 Charity Drive located in the Highland Park community within walking distance to Kenrose Elementary School. The grand 2 story entry welcomes you into this exquisite home with newly refinished hardwood floors, 2 staircases, and more. This home offers a large study which is perfect for working at home.

The formal living room provides a nice fireplace and convenient access to the sunroom. The formal dining room is spacious enough to host those special dinners with family and friends. Just off the formal living room tucked behind a door is a wet bar which is perfect for preparing cocktails and storing wine. The cooks delight eat-in kitchen provides granite counters, stainless steel appliances, hardwood floors, a large breakfast bar, an informal dining area, and a pantry. Just off the kitchen is the large laundry room which offers access to the 3 car garage.

The rear staircase just off the kitchen is a quick way to the bonus room without disturbing the bedrooms. This oversized bonus room is perfect for family movie nights, a pool table and children's play area. The oversized master suite is extremely welcoming, and offers a trey ceiling and plenty of natural light. This master suite wouldn't be complete without a private bath that includes a jetted tub, a walk in closet, his and her vanities, and a linen closet. This custom built home sits on a large private lot with plenty of mature trees and green space for the family. Highland Park offers a pool and a walking trail, all within a nature preserve community. Come visit this gracious home at 1714 Charity Drive, you will not be disappointed!

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:59</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>sandra barone,denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,townhome,house,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>732 4th Avenue North, Nashville TN 37219</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 732 4th Avenue North, Nashville TN 37219.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
2 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 994804.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at denise@deniseruizhomes.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/512-732-4th-Avenue-North-Nashville-TN-37219.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/sandra-barone/732-4th-Avenue-North.mp4" length="22874574" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">011840EF-2492-4F2B-9679-1CA628B9DD42</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 16:22:13 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 732 4th Avenue North, Nashville TN 37219. For more info, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185 or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 732 4th Avenue North, Nashville TN 37219.

2 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 994804.

Property Description: Denise Ruiz and Sandra Barone of Zeitlin and Company Realtors present 732 4th Avenue North, Nashville TN 37219.

This downtown end-unit townhome provides wonderful views, and features 2 bedrooms and 2 and a half baths. If you're looking for that urban lifestyle with room to spread out. Come on inside and take a look. The inviting and well-designed entry provides a warm welcome to your guests. The sophisticated living room is a great place to entertain in or spend quite evenings relaxing by the fireplace.

Imagine preparing meals in this designer kitchen, which offers custom cabinets, granite counters, stainless steel appliances and a view of your private courtyard. The kitchen is large enough for a full sized table to entertain your guests while you're preparing meals. The dining room is currently being used as an office, as there's no need for a separate formal eating area since the kitchen is so spacious. The stylish open staircase leads you upstairs to where the bedroom are located. The 2nd floor hallway has an open railing, and offers a nice view to downstairs.

The large master bedroom provides plenty of windows, a walk in closet and even a private bath. Granite counters with 2 sinks and custom cabinets provide plenty of space in the master bath. The oversized tiled shower in the master bath is a wonderful place to refresh for starting or ending a day. The 2nd bedroom has its own bath and makes a great room for that new addition or for guests. Your private fenced flagstone courtyard is perfect place to enjoy family and friends and provides easy access to your 1 car garage. If you're looking for a view, you can't beat this. Schedule your private showing today and see how much you get with this almost new urban townhome.

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at sandra.barone@zeitlinrealtors.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:58</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>sandra barone,denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,townhome,town house,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>613 Copper Ridge Trail, Cane Ridge TN 37013</title>
            <description>A real estate video tour featuring 613 Copper Ridge Trail, Cane Ridge TN 37013.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
4 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 974666.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at sandra.barone@zeitlinrealtors.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</description>
            <link>http://www.agentcasts.com/498-613-Copper-Ridge-Trail-Cane-Ridge-TN-37013.html</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.agentcasts.com/video/sandra-barone/613-Copper-Ridge-Trail.mp4" length="20348615" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">391A5AA1-2511-45AC-88F7-0038E58390AE</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 14:55:14 -0400</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>A real estate video tour featuring 613 Copper Ridge Trail, Cane Ridge TN 37013. For more info, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185 or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>A real estate video tour featuring 613 Copper Ridge Trail, Cane Ridge TN 37013.

4 Bedrooms, 2.5 Bathrooms, MLS# 974666.

Property Description: Denise Ruiz and Sandra Barone of Zeitlin and Company Realtors present 613 Copper Ridge Trail, Cane Ridge TN 37013.

This spacious 4 bedroom, 2 and 1/2 bath home in Oak Highlands is only an easy drive to Nashville and is truly gorgeous. As you enter the home, you'll be greeted by beautiful hardwood floors and inviting and smart design. The main living area features a wood burning fireplace and magnificent, soaring windows. The well designed formal dining area is perfect for eating and entertaining, and comes complete with an elegant built-in hutch..

The awesome, large kitchen offers plenty of cabinet space and beautiful floors and features a convenient eating area with wonderful views through its many windows. The downstairs master bedroom has French doors and is complimented by a spectacular trey ceiling. Connected to the master bedroom is the master bath, which offers lots of closet space and a luxurious tub. This home even comes complete with a bonus room which can be used as an additional retreat or even a game room.

Love the outdoors? Enjoy the fresh air in style while relaxing on this private, extra large deck. The views from the deck are truly breathtaking and immediately inspire a sense of both freedom and enjoyment. The outside of the home features a well manicured lawn and exterior lighting, further completing this stunning picture. The community even has tennis courts, basketball courts, and wonderful walking trails for you and your family's enjoyment. Call today to setup an appointment.

For more information, contact Denise Ruiz or Sandra Barone by phone at 615-371-0185, by email at sandra.barone@zeitlinrealtors.com, or visit them online at www.deniseruizhomes.com today.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:42</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>sandra barone,denise ruiz,zeitlin and company realtors,nashville,tennessee,Cane Ridge,copper trail,TN,real estate,homes,for sale</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>AgentCasts Real Estate Video Tours</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
