<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0"> 
<channel> 
<title>Got A Bug Up Your Ass?</title>
<link>http://www.vxm.com</link>
<description>
A Podcast Mashup of Science, Religion and Politics
</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>2005</copyright>
<lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2005 18:00:00 EST</lastBuildDate>
<webMaster>fvale@vxm.com</webMaster>
<ttl>60</ttl> 
<item>
<title>Part 2: Ain't That Some Crazy Shit?</title>
<link>http://www.vxm.com/#7003</link>
<description>In Part 2: Ain't That Some Crazy Shit? Francis Vale does in the Roman Catholic Church, quantum computing, the true origins of Right Wing Christians, Dante and his Inferno, Gay Iraqi VCR-toting criminals, the possible end of our universe. New! H=S+C+V Unlocks the secret formula for happiness  http://www.vxm.com/MyGood.html
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2005 13:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.vxm.com/crazy_shit.mp3" length="30000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>Part 1: Ain't That Some Crazy Shit?</title>
<link>http://www.vxm.com/#7002</link>
<description>Part 1: Ain't That Some Crazy Shit? is a 25-minute audio riff by Francis Vale that spills the inside beans on Microsoft's plans for World Domination by taking on China and scuttling the US Navy, as well as sinking the Taiwanese. Also, how Intelligent Design is going to save America's technology ass, as well as turn your IT department's latest zillion dollar loser into a god-blessed winner. New! H=S+C+V Unlocks the secret formula for happiness  http://www.vxm.com/MyGood.html
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2005 13:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.vxm.com/MS-china.mp3" length="26000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
</item>
<item>
<title> The Death Of the Internet
And How Computers Ate The Planet podCast</title>
<link>http://www.vxm.com/#7001</link>
<description>The Death of the Internet is a fifteen minute mp3 audio by Francis Vale that explains why the Internet was DOA even before the gasping dot coms beached onto the polluted NASDAQ shores. It also explains why no matter how many holes Bush drills in his cherished half-baked Alaska, Dick and Halliburton will still come up empty thanks to power mad computers. And there is much more to hear on this provocative audio commentary. New! H=S+C+V Unlocks the secret formula for happiness  http://www.vxm.com/MyGood.html</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2005 12:30:00 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.vxm.com/NetDeath.mp3" length="13000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>George Bush, The Gambian Cowboy podCast</title>
<link>http://www.vxm.com/#7000</link>
<description>George Bush, The Gambian Cowboy is a 30-minute riff on our fearless Commander In Chief that takes no prisoners, only unconstitutional detainees. George Bush, Iraq, the economy, the NRA, healthcare, education and more get totally punked. This raucous download will ruffle every fowl bird in the Bush! This audio piece by Francis Vale was made BEFORE the invasion of Iraq, and everything on this recording has now come true. So how come others in the media didn't see this coming as well, or say something? Even the iconic too-many legged, 23-toed frog featured in this piece has now shown up a year later in Stewartville, Minnesota, which, quite frankly, is just way to eerie, and also quite scary.  New! H=S+C+V Unlocks the secret formula for happiness  http://www.vxm.com/MyGood.html   </description>
<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2005 21:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.vxm.com/Bush_GambianCowboy.mp3" length="23000000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>

