<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>Ridge Web Design - Web Design and Online Marketing Company Galway and Dublin, Ireland</title>
  <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie</link>
  <description>Galway based web design and web development company providing a  full range of Website design and Website development at Affordable prices. Our services range also includes Ecommerce development, Intranet/Extranet, Search Engine Optimisation (SEO) and Online Marketing</description> 
  <language>en-us</language>
  <copyright>Copyright: (C) 2006 Ridge Web Design. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
  <item>
    <title>Services - Creative web design, development and Internet marketing company in Galway, Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/services.html</link>
    <description>Our Services includes web design, development and Internet marketing in Galway, Ireland</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Professional web design Galway, Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/web_site_design_ireland.html</link>
    <description>Ridge's web design services are focused around both your needs and your customers needs by affordable web site design and Professional web design from Galway, Ireland. Our design team from Galway, Ireland are experts at striking the right balance between the two.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Ecommerce website development Galway, Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/ecommerce_website_development_ireland.html</link>
    <description>Ridge from Galway, Ireland specialises in Ecommerce web design and ecommerce solutions for small to medium sized companies</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Search engine optimisation Galway, Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/search_engine_optimisation_ireland.html</link>
    <description>At Ridge, Galway, Ireland we base our marketing campaigns on widely accepted techniques like Search Engine Optimisation (SEO), Search engine ranking, Web promotion, Search engine placement</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Online Marketing Galway, Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/online_marketing_ireland.html</link>
    <description>Ridge Internet marketing consultant can help you navigate the world of Pay per click management and  Online Marketing from Galway, Ireland</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Content management Galway, Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/content_management_ireland.html</link>
    <description>Ridge from Galway, Ireland custom build affordable web content management system that are designed for your exact requirements.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Web site traffic tracking and reporting Galway, Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/website_tracking_reporting_ireland.html</link>
    <description>Web site traffic tracking and reporting web site statistics form Galway, Ireland</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Irish web hosting, Register domain name Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/irish_web_hosting_ireland.html</link>
    <description>Ridge from Galway, Ireland provides web site hosting solutions like register Irish domain name based on a choice of shared or dedicated servers.Our hosting solutions are designed to be both affordable and reliable Irish web hosting</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Intranet development Ireland, Extranet software Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/intranet_extranet_ireland.html</link>
    <description>Ridge from Galway, Ireland provides Intranet development and Extranet development with high levels of security so you can be sure that there will be no unauthorised access to your confidential information</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>About Us - Professional web design company in Galway, Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/aboutus.html</link>
    <description>With offices in Galway and Dublin Ireland, Ridge Web Design works with our clients to develop Creative, Effective, High-Impact websites that meet the needs of both our clients and their end users.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Our Clients - Web design and development portfolio Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/web_design_portfolio_ireland.html</link>
    <description> Web design and development portfolio Galway, Ireland</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Website Design Company : Contact us in Dublin Road, Galway, Ireland</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/webdesign_contact_ireland.html</link>
    <description>Website Design Company Contact us in Dublin Road, Glaway, Ireland - Ridge Web Design</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Sitemap - Ridge Web Design</title>
    <link>http://www.ridge-web.ie/sitemap.html</link>
    <description>Sitemap - Ridge Web Design</description>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>