<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>

<itunes:new-feed-url>http://feeds.feedburner.com/englishbanana/podcast</itunes:new-feed-url>

<ttl>60</ttl>

<title>Learn English with English Banana.com Podcasts</title>

<link>http://www.englishbanana.com/podcasts.html</link>

<language>en-us</language>

<copyright>You can freely copy, distribute, and sell this work to make a profit</copyright>

<itunes:subtitle>Free online English lessons from English Banana.com - teaching English on the World Wide Web since 2002!</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:author>English Banana.com</itunes:author>

<itunes:summary>English Banana.com is a fun site for learners of English. We have helped millions of visitors from all around the world to learn English since 2002. Our site features free games, quizzes, and downloads for learning and teaching English.</itunes:summary>

<description>Learn English with English Banana.com - now you can hear our lessons as well as get free downloads from our website...!</description>

<itunes:owner>

<itunes:name>English Banana.com</itunes:name>

<itunes:email>info@englishbanana.com</itunes:email>

</itunes:owner>

<itunes:image href="http://www.englishbanana.com/podcast_title.jpg" />

<itunes:category text="Education">

<itunes:category text="K-12"/>

</itunes:category>

<itunes:category text="Education"/>

<item>

<title>Talk a Lot English - You are the Course Book!</title>  

<itunes:author>Matt Purland</itunes:author>

<itunes:subtitle>An effective new method for teaching English.</itunes:subtitle>
 
<itunes:summary>Topic: You are the Course Book! Level: Intermediate and above. Teacher: Matt Purland runs the popular English language resource website http://www.englishbanana.com/ He is the author of the Talk a Lot Free Spoken English course, which is a free download available from http://www.englishbanana.com/talkalot/ Material: http://www.talkalotenglish.com/ Watch: http://www.wiziq.com/online-class/822973-talk-a-lot-english-you-are-the-course-book If you enjoy this podcast, please tell a friend and leave a rating and a few comments on iTunes. Thank you!</itunes:summary>

<enclosure url="http://www.englishbanana.com/podcasts/talk-a-lot-english-you-are-the-course-book.mp3" length="51200" type="audio/mpeg" />

<guid>http://www.englishbanana.com/podcasts/talk-a-lot-english-you-are-the-course-book.mp3</guid>

<pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 18:20:00 GMT</pubDate>

<itunes:duration>00:56:02</itunes:duration>

<itunes:keywords>teacher training, teaching, free material, English, ESL, ESOL, idioms, spoken English, phonetics, phonics, pronunciation, listening skills, Matt Purland, download</itunes:keywords>

</item>
 
<itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
</channel>

</rss>