<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>San Francisco International Airport Podcast: The Sound of SFO</title>
        <description>San Francisco travel information, tips from business professionals and leisure travelers, helpful SFO information,news on SFO's sustainability programs, heartwarming and humorous stories–they're all here in a fantastic series of podcasts from the San Francisco International Airport. </description>
        <link>http://www.flysfo.com/web/page/about/news/podcasts/index.html</link>
        <category>Places &amp; Travel</category>
        <copyright>San Francisco International Airport</copyright>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 15:11:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 12:12:41 -0700</pubDate>
        <generator>FeedForAll Mac v2.1 (2.1.0.1); http://www.FeedForAll.com/</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>An entertaining series of podcasts from the San Francisco International Airport. Listen to San Francisco travel tips from business professionals and leisure travelers, helpful SFO airport information, SFO news, heartwarming and humorous stories and more.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>San Francisco travel information, tips from business professionals and leisure travelers, helpful SFO information, news on SFO's sustainability programs, heartwarming and humorous stories — they're all here in a fantastic new series of podcasts from the San Francisco International Airport.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:category text="Government &amp; Organizations"/>
        <itunes:keywords>San Francisco travel, airport podcast, SFO podcast, San Francisco International Airport, travel podcast, travel stories, travel tips</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:author>San Francisco International Airport</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:email>tom@the-m-line.com</itunes:email>
            <itunes:name>San Francisco International Airport</itunes:name>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.flysfo.com/web/page/images/SoundOfSFO_600x600.jpg" />
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <item>
            <title>SFO PODCAST: China Clipper Glory - The Dawn of Ocean Air Transport</title>
            <description>Until seventy-five years ago this week it was impossible to buy an airline ticket to fly all the way across the Pacific Ocean from San Francisco to Hong Kong, and back. On April 21, 1937, the very first revenue passengers, all seven of them, boarded a giant four-engine Pan American Airways flying boat at Alameda on San Francisco Bay. The six-day journey to Asia required overnights stays with stops at five island bases along the 8,000-mile route. The flight arrived in Hong Kong via Macao on April 28th completing the first of what then became regular weekly service. Commercial airplane service across the Atlantic would not commence for another two years.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In commemoration of this pioneering achievement in aviation, SFO Museum presents the first of a three-part podcast series titled Clipper Glory: The Dawn of Ocean Air Transport. These original interviews with Pan Am flying boat crewmembers and first-person accounts of the airline’s island bases personnel recreate the sensation and excitement of this new air service that forever changed the world and laid the foundation for today’s global air system.&lt;br /&gt;
</description>
            <link>http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-podcast-China-Clipper-75.mp4</link>
            <category>Places &amp; Travel</category>
            <enclosure url="http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-podcast-China-Clipper-75.mp4" length="829" type="video/mp4"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A52E9D87-8D02-432F-BBB2-9C45C708C7AA-21655-000229ACA76F7E15-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 15:07:41 -0700</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>SFO PODCAST: China Clipper Glory - The Dawn of Ocean Air Transport</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Until seventy-five years ago this week it was impossible to buy an airline ticket to fly all the way across the Pacific Ocean from San Francisco to Hong Kong, and back. On April 21, 1937, the very first revenue passengers, all seven of them, boarded a giant four-engine Pan American Airways flying boat at Alameda on San Francisco Bay. The six-day journey to Asia required overnights stays with stops at five island bases along the 8,000-mile route. The flight arrived in Hong Kong via Macao on April 28th completing the first of what then became regular weekly service. Commercial airplane service across the Atlantic would not commence for another two years.In commemoration of this pioneering achievement in aviation, SFO Museum presents the first of a three-part podcast series titled Clipper Glory: The Dawn of Ocean Air Transport. These original interviews with Pan Am flying boat crewmembers and first-person accounts of the airline’s island bases personnel recreate the sensation and excitement of this new air service that forever changed the world and laid the foundation for today’s global air system.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>13:45</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>SFO, airports, SFO Museum, airplanes, travel, San Francisco, San Francisco history, international travel, history, travel history</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>San Francisco International Airport and Earprint Productions</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>SFO PODCAST: SFO Achieves Carbon Neutrality</title>
            <description>Learn how the offsetting of SFO's emissions has allowed the airport to achieve carbon neutrality.</description>
            <link>http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-carbon-neutrality-podcast.mp3</link>
            <category>Places &amp; Travel</category>
            <enclosure url="http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-carbon-neutrality-podcast.mp3" length="132" type="audio/mpeg"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">F70CA229-2C95-4CEC-969C-5206FFC4E038-51490-000087D614C0AA78-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 12:10:30 -0700</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Learn how the offsetting of SFO's emissions has allowed the airport to achieve carbon neutrality.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>The offsetting of SFO's emissions has allowed the airport to achieve carbon neutrality. Carbon neutrality? Do you mean it’s as if the airport isn’t emitting any C02 at all? Find out how in this special podcast from SFO.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:12</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>SFO, airports, carbon neutrality, reducing carbon, environmentalism, San Francisco, green</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>San Francisco International Airport</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>SFO PODCAST: Reducing Consumption and Conserving Resources</title>
            <description>Learn how SFO is reducing paper, fuel and electricity usage as part of its environmental master plan</description>
            <link>http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-reducing-consumption-podcast.mp3</link>
            <category>Places &amp; Travel</category>
            <enclosure url="http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-reducing-consumption-podcast.mp3" length="122" type="audio/mpeg"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7795FC40-053E-4AF1-A6CE-B142D7124C9E-51490-00008785F1F7CAED-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 12:10:32 -0700</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Learn how SFO is reducing paper, fuel and electricity usage as part of its environmental master plan.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>SFO has reduced its paper usage by more than 50% since 1990. But saving paper is just a small part of SFO’s environmental master plan. Learn how SFO is reducing paper, fuel and electricity usage to have a positive effect on the environment.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:02</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>SFO, airports, sustainability, environmentalism, reducing consumption, San Francisco, green</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>San Francisco International Airport</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>SFO PODCAST: Carbon Offsets at SFO</title>
            <description>Learn how SFO has offset carbon emissions by 100% to have a positive impact on the environment.</description>
            <link>http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-carbon-offsetting-podcast.mp3</link>
            <category>Places &amp; Travel</category>
            <enclosure url="http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-carbon-offsetting-podcast.mp3" length="141" type="audio/mpeg"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0C827B77-C578-4CB8-82E6-A6EF93B1BB9B-51490-00008750E302FFCB-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 12:10:35 -0700</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Learn how SFO has offset carbon emissions by 100% to have a positive impact on the environment.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>SFO has offset emissions by 100%. What the heck does that mean? Learn from SFO's Deputy Director for Design and Construction how SFO is reducing its Greenhouse Gas Emissions to have a positive environmental impact. </itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:21</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>SFO, airports, sustainability, greenhouse gas emissions, reducing carbon, San Francisco, environment</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>San Francisco International Airport</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>SFO PODCAST: Planting Trees at SFO</title>
            <description>Learn how SFO is helping to reduce carbon emissions by planting more than 2,200 trees over the past eight years.</description>
            <link>http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-planting-trees-podcast.mp3</link>
            <category>Places &amp; Travel</category>
            <enclosure url="http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-planting-trees-podcast.mp3" length="78" type="audio/mpeg"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">880A12F7-BBF7-4785-B8AA-C7032854D9BB-51490-000086D6E8FCCDBB-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 12:10:37 -0700</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Learn how SFO is helping to reduce its carbon emissions by planting more than 2,200 trees over the past eight years.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>SFO is constantly striving to set standards for airports nationwide and worldwide when it comes to environmental sustainability. Learn how SFO is helping to reduce its carbon emissions by planting more than 2,200 trees over the past eight years.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:18</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>SFO, airports, sustainability, reducing carbon, planting trees, San Francisco, green</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>San Francisco International Airport</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>SFO PODCAST: Recycling at SFO</title>
            <description>Learn how recycling at SFO is helping the airport set the standard for airports nationwide and worldwide on environmental sustainability. </description>
            <link>http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-recycling-podcast.mp3</link>
            <category>Places &amp; Travel</category>
            <enclosure url="http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO-recycling-podcast.mp3" length="93" type="audio/mpeg"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D468CCFB-0D64-4DB5-9693-213DF7C8E3C0-51490-0000866601578DA4-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 15:14:06 -0700</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Learn how recycling at SFO is helping the airport set the standard for airports nationwide and worldwide on environmental sustainability.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>SFO is constantly striving to set standards for airports nationwide and worldwide when it comes to environmental sustainability. Learn how the recycling program at SFO helps the airport reduce its GHG emissions.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:33</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>SFO, airports, sustainability, recycling, San Francisco, green</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>San Francisco International Aiport and Earprint Productions</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>SFO PODCAST: Tips for a Quick Tour of San Francisco</title>
            <description>This podcast is especially recommended for anyone with a long layover who is interested in taking a quick tour into San Francisco before their next flight.  So, how do you get to San Francisco from the airport, and what are the best places to visit while in the city? Listen to this informative podcast featuring Mayor Gavin Newsom and other San Francisco locals offering their suggestions for a quick tour of the city, as well as tips on how to get to and from the city by the bay. </description>
            <link>http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO_Podcast_Tips_for_a_Quick_Tour_of_San_Francisco.mp3</link>
            <category>Places &amp; Travel</category>
            <enclosure url="http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO_Podcast_Tips_for_a_Quick_Tour_of_San_Francisco.mp3" length="437" type="audio/mpeg"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">63824FAF-CCA8-436C-AD58-861A68C01854-6291-000012655EB27EBC-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 16:29:35 -0700</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Flying into San Francisco International Airport? Find out how to get to and from the city, and get some tips on a quick tour if you have a long layover.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>You've just landed at SFO. So, how do you get to San Francisco from the airport, and what are the best places to visit while in the city? Listen to this informative podcast featuring Mayor Gavin Newsom and other San Francisco locals offering their suggestions for a quick tour of the city, as well as tips on how to get to and from the city by the bay. This podcast is especially recommended for anyone with a long layover who is interested in taking a quick jaunt into the city before their next flight. </itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>7:17</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>san francisco travel information, SFO, airport podcast, san francisco travel tips</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>San Francisco International Airport</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>SFO PODCAST: Insider Travel Tips for Your Trip Through SFO</title>
            <description>Get some fantastic insider tips from business travelers and SFO employees on how to get the most out of your visit to San Francisco International Airport. Learn the best places to park, about our award-winning local food, the beautiful art museum, the luxurious spa and more. </description>
            <link>http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO_Podcast_Insider_Tips.mp3</link>
            <category>Places &amp; Travel</category>
            <enclosure url="http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO_Podcast_Insider_Tips.mp3" length="446" type="audio/mpeg"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">E5400F45-92B5-4DEA-B8DD-75CB08B6F4D7-4586-00006466D87BBD48-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 14:31:55 -0700</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Get some fantastic insider tips from business travelers and SFO employees on how to get the most out of your visit to SFO. Learn the best places to park, about our award-winning local food, the beautiful art museum, the luxurious spa and more. </itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Get some fantastic insider tips from business travelers and SFO employees on how to get the most out of your visit to San Francisco International Airport. Learn the best places to park, about our award-winning local food, the beautiful art museum, the luxurious spa and more. </itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>6:43</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>San Francisco, San Francisco travel information, SFO podcast, San Francisco airport, travel stories</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>San Francisco International Airport</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>SFO PODCAST: The USO at SFO ... Supporting Our Troops</title>
            <description>Since its inception, the United Services Organization (USO) has been supporting our military troops, providing them with free food, beverages, entertainment, and a place to relax while traveling. Download the MP3 and hear an engaging podcast that offers insight into the wonderful ways the USO at SFO is helping to support the men and women of the United States Armed Forces.</description>
            <link>http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO_Podcast_Beagle_Brigade.mp3</link>
            <category>Places &amp; Travel</category>
            <enclosure url="http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO_Podcast_USO_at_SFO.mp3" length="335" type="audio/mpeg"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3C76B193-4E7B-47C2-8088-79B41E27C5F3-4586-0000649CF26C3DB3-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 16:40:35 -0700</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Download the MP3 and hear an engaging podcast that offers insight into the wonderful ways the USO at SFO is helping to support the men and women of the United States Armed Forces.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Since its inception, the United Services Organization (USO) has been supporting our military troops, providing them with free food, beverages, entertainment, and a place to relax while traveling. Download the MP3 and hear an engaging podcast that offers insight into the wonderful ways the USO at SFO is helping to support the men and women of the United States Armed Forces.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>5:35</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>San Francisco, USO, San Francisco travel, SFO, USO at SFO, Northern California USO, US Armed Forces</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>San Francisco International Airport</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>SFO PODCAST: The Beagle Brigade - Dogs On a Mission</title>
            <description>The Beagle Brigade is a special group of dogs that are part of the US Department of Agriculture's Animal and Plant Health Inspection Service. The beagles are trained to sniff out fruits, vegetables and meats that could pose a threat to US agriculture. Listen in on exclusive interviews with the handlers and the dogs that keep US agriculture safe while working at San Francisco International Airport.</description>
            <link>http://www.flysfo.com/pressres/podcasts/SFO_Podcast_Beagle_Brigade.mp3</link>
            <category>Places &amp; Travel</category>
            <enclosure url="http://www.flysfo.com/downloads/mp3/SFO_Podcast_Beagle_Brigade.mp3" length="447" type="audio/mpeg"  ></enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C3FEC4B8-5048-4F12-9838-F69BBB38DFD4-4586-000064B8F681A69E-FFA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 16:30:37 -0700</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>The Beagle Brigade is a special group of dogs that are part of the US Department of Agriculture's Animal and Plant Health Inspection Service. Listen to how they keep US agriculture safe.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>The Beagle Brigade is a special group of dogs that are part of the US Department of Agriculture's Animal and Plant Health Inspection Service. The beagles are trained to sniff out fruits, vegetables and meats that could pose a threat to US agriculture. Listen in on exclusive interviews with the handlers and the dogs that keep US agriculture safe.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>7:27</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:keywords>San Francisco, SFO, Beagle Brigade, dogs, agriculture, San Francisco travel, travel stories, dog stories</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:author>San Francisco International Airport</itunes:author>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
