<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/DTDs/Podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">

<channel>
<title> The Will Smith Podcast </title> 
<description> Will Smith fans from around the world bring you the latest news and discussions on Will Smith. Tune in to hear about Will Smith music, Jazzy Jeff and Fresh Prince, Fresh Prince of Bel Air, DJ Jazzy Jeff and Will Smith Movies.</description> 
<itunes:author>http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
<link> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/will-smith/podcast/index.htm </link> 
<itunes:image href="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/images/willsmithpodlogo.jpg" />
<itunes:owner>
	<itunes:name>Tim Price</itunes:name>
	<itunes:email>tim@jazzyjefffreshprince.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<pubDate> Mon, 12 Dec 2005 21:00:00 PST </pubDate>
<language>en-us</language> 
<copyright> 2005 Tim_Price </copyright> 

<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 1 </title> 
     <description> News on Pursuit of Happyness, Tonight He Comes,Fresh Prince of Bel Air Season 3 and Live 8 DVDs. We also 
discuss Will's American Music Award win, Tell Me Why's release and Bow Wow dissing Will Smith.  Also details on our new competition, listen in to win a Jazzy Jeff prize pack including his new album "the soul mixtape." </description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Mon, 12 Dec 2005 22:00:00 PST </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>20:19</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep001.mp3" length=" 9760141 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith Jazzy Jeff Fresh Prince Lost and Found</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 2 </title> 
     <description> We discuss Lost and Found and the release of Singles Switch and Party Starter as well as the potential singles Tell Me Why with Mary J Blige and Pump Ya Brakes with Snoop Dogg. </description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Fri, 16 Dec 2005 22:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>10:37</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep002.mp3" length=" 3824180 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith Party Starter Tell Me Why Switch Lost and Found</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 3 </title> 
     <description> Will Smith: The Rapper Vs The Actor, Should he choose one career over the other? Will's best and worst records and Is a 6th Jazzy Jeff and Fresh Prince album a possibility?  </description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Fri, 23 Dec 2005 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>30:58</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep003.mp3" length=" 11154662 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith Actor Rapper Jazzy Jeff Fresh Prince Code Red Big Willie Style Born To Reign</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 4 </title> 
     <description> All Hip Hop names Will Smith Person of the Year, Will Smith's son Jaden starring in Pursuit of Happyness,
Jada's band Wicked Wisdom, some Sony bashing and Podcast Feedback.  We announce the winner of our soul mixtape giveaway</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Sun, 08 Jan 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>16:11</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep004.mp3" length=" 5832704 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith Hip Hop Jaden Soul Mixtape</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 5 </title> 
     <description> News on a new Will Smith album and a new Jazzy Jeff album, Will vs the record labels, 
The Fans reactions to Will, Will and Jada's recent charity donations, record sales, radio, singles and movies in a packed podcast.</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Sun, 15 Jan 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>35:26</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep005.mp3" length=" 13410304 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith Hip Hop the return of the magnificent Jada charity jazzy jeff fresh prince pursuit of happyness</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 6 </title> 
     <description> Special Music Podcast. New Tatyana Ali and Kel Spencer tracks as we feature independant artists who have been influenced by Will Smith and Jazzy Jeff.  You will find 
a list of the artists and their web sites at http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com. This podcast contains tracks from Da Brakes, Kel Spencer, Da Ace, Fuq, MojoPlus, Koffee Blakk, Kontempt, jNite.</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Mon, 23 Jan 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>49:21</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep006.mp3" length=" 23691264 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith Hip Hop Remix Kel Spencer Tatyana Ali Independant Music</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 7 </title> 
     <description> This week we discuss:  Pursuit of Happyness Reviews.  Will Smith's new movies, It Takes A Thief and Tonight He Comes.  Bow Wow 
Sits down with Will Smith to discuss Diss.  Will Smith at the Kids Choice Awards.  Tell Me Why's Non Release and the Fan made Music Video.  DJ Jazzy Jeff's
 New Album The Return of The Magnificent.  Jazzy Jeff's Remix of Black Eyed Peas Feel It.  The Status of Will Smith's New Compilation Album.  Will Smith in India
and the latest on a Will Smith and Jazzy Jeff Tour.</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Sun, 09 Apr 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>36:25</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep007.mp3" length=" 17482155 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith Pursuit of Happyness DJ Jazzy Jeff The Return of The Magnificent Tell Me Why Bow Wow Diss To Catch A Thief Tonight He Comes Black Eyed Peas Remix</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 8 </title> 
     <description> Season 3 of The Fresh Prince of Bel Air on DVD.  What the Fresh Prince of Bel Air Cast is up to.  Tatyana Ali's New Album. The best Will Smith Albums to Buy.  Will and Jeff's 
Best and Worst Tracks.  Is Will's worst track "I Can't Stop."  Should Will Smith play a Bad Guy in a Movie and Will still sounding like Ali.</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Sun, 18 Apr 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>34:05</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep008.mp3" length=" 16367464 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith The Fresh Prince of Bel Air DVD Born To Reign Tatyana Ali Ali I Can't Stop</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 9 </title> 
     <description> Will Smith and Overbrook Producing ATL, Jada's new Wicked Wisdom Album, Switch.  Will Smith and
       Ghostwriting.  Unreleased Songs and Rare B-Sides.  Lorettas.</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Sun, 19 Apr 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>32:22</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep009.mp3" length=" 11653235 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith Loretta Jada Wicked Wisdom Unreleased B-Sides ATL Ghostwriter</itunes:keywords>
 </item>

<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 10 </title> 
     <description> We talk to an insane Will Smith fan from Sweden who wants to start his own Will Smith Religion.  We take no responsibility
 for the views expressed by this raving lunatic. Our normal Will Smith podcast will be back next episode.</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Sun, 09 May 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>40:50</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep010.mp3" length=" 9754472 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith fan crazy comedy religion sweden humour</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 11 </title> 
     <description> Will Smith and Johnny Depp in I Am Legend. Tonight He Comes Loses Director Again.  Wills new movies Seven Pounds and Greenbacks. Update on DJ Jazzy Jeff's album The
       Return of the Magnificent and we reveal who is on it! Jazzy Jeff and Fresh Prince Best of Release.  Fresh Prince of Bel Air Season 4. Pursuit of Happyness Release Dates and Will Smith's visit to Israel.  </description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Sun, 03 July 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>18:00</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep011.mp3" length=" 8640576 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith johnny depp I am legend jazzy jeff fresh prince of bel air seven pounds greenbacks movies best of compilation the return of the magnificent</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 12 </title> 
     <description> will surrounded by yes men? lost and found beats episode 10 wheres the tour season 4 of fresh prince of bel air
A Trip to Lorettaville A bad will smith joke T.I. gives Will props Will Smith vs gangsta rap different versions of greatest hits live performances on youtube
I think I Can Beat Mike Tyson Live at the Apollo</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Sun, 12 July 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>27:40</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep012.mp3" length=" 9960480 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith Lost and Found gangsta rap fresh prince of bel air tour youtube mike tyson live TI</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 13 </title> 
     <description> Live Will Smith Concert from 1986. DJ Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince perform live at Union Square in New York.  A classic moment
in hip hop history when DJ Jazzy Jeff unveils the transformer scratch at the home of hip hop for the firs time.  Will Smith was only 17 and a small piece of this performance
ended up on the DJ Jazzy Jeff and Fresh Prince album He's the DJ, I'm the Rapper.  This is the entire concert brought to you for the first time by http://jazzyjefffreshprince.com</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Tue, 08 August 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>20:02</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep013.mp3" length=" 19240797 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith hip hop rap dj jazzy jeff fresh prince concert live union square new york dj truntablism scratching freestyle</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 14 </title> 
     <description> The latest on Pursuit of Happyness. Will quits music? Will on Oprah. We reflect on Wills music career. Jazzy Jeff finalizes The Return of The Magnificent.</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Sun, 26 November 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>40:51</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep014.mp3" length=" 19609489 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith pursuit of happyness movies film music career jazzy jeff return magnificent Oprah Jaden Acting</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 15 </title> 
     <description> Will Smith and Jazzy Jeff Live Concert from 1988.  Jazzy Jeff and Fresh Prince perform Live in LA! Rare concert, classic old school hip hop.</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Thu, 30 November 2006 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>18:03</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep015.mp3" length=" 8676480 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith Jazzy Jeff Fresh Prince Old School Rap Live Hip Hop Turntablism DJ human beat box</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 16 </title> 
     <description> The Return of The Magnificent! We review DJ Jazzy Jeff's brand new album. Also the truth about those Jazzy Jeff and Fresh Prince world tour and new album rumours.</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Thu, 10 May 2007 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>33:42</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep016.mp3" length=" 16182288 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith DJ Jazzy Jeff The Return of The Magnificent Big Daddy Kane Method Man BBE Records Twone Gabz Rhymefest J Live hip hop rap</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 17 </title> 
     <description> The Return of The Magnificent Singles,I Am Legend trailer, jazzy jeff shoutout, Will's kids in the movies
I Am Legend Preview, The 5 million dollar scene, I Am Legend World Tour, Switch, Jaden wins MTV movie award, Will Smith reality show?
Is there time for Will to get in the studio, Jazzy Jeff US Tour, K-Smith, Kel Spencer,The state of hip hop</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Sun, 11 June 2007 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>33:26</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep017.mp3" length=" 16052976 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith DJ Jazzy Jeff The Return of The Magnificent I Am Legend Switch Kel Spencer Tour MTV Movie Award Single</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 18 </title> 
     <description> Looking for Good Music, Jazzy Jeff Super Producer, Jazzy Jeff at the Office , Who is Jazzy jeff , The Return of The Magnificent Skits and Album Cover
                   Switch Born To Reign, The Making of Willennium, Groupies, Hanging out with Jazzy Jeff
</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Tue, 26 June 2007 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>41:15</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep018.mp3" length=" 19806800 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith DJ Jazzy Jeff The Return of The Magnificent Willennium Groupies</itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 19 </title> 
     <description> Jazzy Jeff and Fresh Prince Live on Capitol Radio Late 80s. The world's greatest hip hop duo Fresh Prince and Jazzy Jeff rip it up Live on Tim 
Westwood's radio show.
</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Mon, 30 July 2007 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>17:54</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep019.mp3" length=" 17099546 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith DJ Jazzy Jeff Tim Westood Fresh Prince Capitol Radio Freestyle </itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 20 </title> 
     <description> We discuss bad boys 3, I Am Legend and the alternative ending. Willow in I Am Legend. Jaden in Karate Kid Remake. Will Smith and Jazzy Jeff summer concerts. Brand new funk 2k7
New roots track get busy featuring jazzy jeff. Timbaland and Will Smith? Will Smith and Hitler misreporting. Will Smith and Scientology press lies. Will Smith is not a scientologist.Haters trying to bring Will Smith down.The I Am Legend novel.
Has will smith finished with music? KSmith Will Smith's nephew's music. Will Smith begins filming new movie 7 pounds and early Hancock reviews.
</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Tue, 25 March 2008 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>25:51</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep020.mp3" length=" 12406784 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith DJ Jazzy Jeff I Am Legend Hancock Scientology Hitler Karate Kid Timbaland The Roots Peedi Crack  </itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 21 </title> 
     <description> Will Smith and Jazzy Jeff are performing in London June 18th, We preview the show. Will Smith on Ellen. Will's hunger for music. Can Will remember his lyrics? Will Smith opens scientology school? We discuss the latest controversy. Hancock goes into reshoots.
 How will the movie turn out? Is Sony promoting the movie incorrectly? Rumours of Will back in the studio recording. The possibility of a jazzy jeff fresh prince album. Why Hancock's Sydney world premiere was cancelled.
</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Mon, 02 June 2008 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>27:03</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep021.mp3" length=" 19474367 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith DJ Jazzy Jeff Premiere Hancock Scientology Ellen recording london school reshoot sony </itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 22 </title> 
     <description> We review Hancock. Will Smith and Jazzy Jeff reunite to perform in L.A. at Hancock premiere. Will and Jeff dont perform at hancock premiere in london.  Will smith performs at Nelson Mandela's birthday celebrations
Will there be an uncut dvd version of Hancock? Hancock opens with over 100 million in its first week. Will thinks hes a better actor than a rapper
Akiva Goldsman. We discuss Will's movie career.The chicaco sevens. Jada as Will's hype man. Seven Pounds.
</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Mon, 07 July 2008 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>31:19</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep022.mp3" length=" 15027264 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith DJ Jazzy Jeff Premiere Hancock review charlize theron jason bateman akiva goldsman peter berg sony </itunes:keywords>
 </item>
<item>
     <title> Will Smith Podcast: Episode 23 </title> 
     <description> Previewing Seven Pounds. I am Legend prequel. Hancock 2. Hancock unrated dvd. "Oldboy" remake with Steven Spielberg. Will quits music again
Will's quest for an oscar. Will's team of Akiva Goldsman and Gabriel Muccino. Scientology protests. Kel Spencer mixtape.
</description>
     <itunes:author> http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Mon, 08 December 2008 01:00:00 GMT </pubDate> 
     <itunes:duration>32:20</itunes:duration>
     <enclosure url="http://www.jazzyjefffreshprince.com/multimedia/podcast/willsmithpodcast_ep023.mp3" length=" 23285760 " type="audio/mpeg" />
	<itunes:keywords>Will Smith DJ Jazzy Jeff Seven Pounds Hancock 2 I am Legend Prequel Scientology steven spielberg oldboy oscars movies film akiva goldsman  </itunes:keywords>
 </item>
</channel> 
</rss>


