<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
   <channel>
      <title>eSeminars Live</title>
      <link>http://www.eseminarslive.com/</link>
      <description>Ziff Davis Internet eSeminars are dynamic and educational forums that bring together elite editors, 
	executives, analysts and guest speakers on a live presentation site. These interactive online events are developed 
	for technology professionals who are charged with helping their organizations grow.</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <generator>TechBasedMarketing.com Stat2RSS</generator>

	<item>
         <title>Virginia Hospital Discusses TCO for Email Security: Getting the Best for the Lowest Cost</title>
         <link>http://www.eseminarslive.com/article2/0,2144,1856564,00.asp</link>
         <description>With escalating email security threats, a barrage of administrative demands and increased cost and complexity of email infrastructure, IT professionals are looking to lower the total cost of email protection, without sacrificing protection. Whether the focus is on saving money spent on multiple products or reducing burdens on IT staff time, learn how Virginia Hospital Center lowered the total cost of its email security systems.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <enclosure url="http://rssnewsapps.ziffdavis.com/audioblogs/9-07-05MailFrontier-B.mp3" length="7573838" type="audio/mpeg" />
	 </item> 

	  <item>
         <title>Clearing Up Open-Source Licensing Confusion</title>
         <link>http://www.eseminarslive.com/article2/0,2144,1854903,00.asp</link>
         <description>Open Source license proliferation is becoming a problem, albeit a problem of success. While it's impressive that so many corporate entities have embraced the open source community, the issue of duplicate and/or conflicting licenses can create a legal nightmare if the problem is not addressed effectively. Even the presence of one differing license among many can cause confusion, and the threat of such a problem can cause businesses to shy away from open source altogether.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <enclosure url="http://rssnewsapps.ziffdavis.com/audioblogs/08-31-05Editorial(linux)B.mp3" length="12825600" type="audio/mpeg" />
      </item>	
    
	  <item>
         <title>Managing IT for Business Value: Part Two</title>
         <link>http://www.eseminarslive.com/article2/0,2144,1854335,00.asp</link>
         <description>This eSeminar reviews the IT business value maturity model. Experts cover two other business strategies: managing IT capability and managing IT like a business. You'll learn how these strategies, frameworks and models can be practically applied to help your organization reap the most business value from its IT investments.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <enclosure url="http://rssnewsapps.ziffdavis.com/audioblogs/08-30-05IntelB.mp3" length="14554906" type="audio/mpeg" />
      </item>
	 
      <item>
         <title>Managing IT for Business Value: Part One</title>
         <link>http://www.eseminarslive.com/article2/0,2144,1852546,00.asp</link>
         <description>The eSeminar presents an introduction to the IT Business Value Maturity model and focuses on two strategies: managing the IT budget and managing IT for business value. Following the second seminar in this series, attendees will have the opportunity to perform an organization maturity assessment that will help them accurately measure the impact of their IT investment on business value.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <enclosure url="http://rssnewsapps.ziffdavis.com/audioblogs/08-25-05IntelB.mp3" length="14424398" type="audio/mpeg" />
      </item>
	 
	 <item>
         <title>Everything Longhorn-PC Magazine Editors Dissect the New OS</title>
         <link>http://www.eseminarslive.com/article2/0,2144,1852545,00.asp</link>
         <description>PC Magazine dissects, pokes and prods the beta version of the OS. Hear their highly respected opinions regarding ease of use, functionality, security and if indeed it is a necessary step for you or your organization to take.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <enclosure url="http://rssnewsapps.ziffdavis.com/audioblogs/08-25-05Edit(Longhorn)B.mp3" length="14515513" type="audio/mpeg" />
      </item>
	 
      <item>
         <title>Virtualization-Driving Flexible and Cost-Effective Consolidation with Dual-Core Servers</title>
         <link>http://www.eseminarslive.com/article2/0,2144,1852081,00.asp</link>
         <description>The Virtual Revolution is on. Achieving IT efficiency in your organization depends on your ability to maximize computer resource utilization while minimizing administrative and infrastructure costs. Rising power and cooling requirements and the proliferation of servers are problems which can be addressed by undertaking a server consolidation and virtualization program. </description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <enclosure url="http://rssnewsapps.ziffdavis.com/audioblogs/08-24-05HPAMD-B.mp3" length="14981016" type="audio/mpeg" />
      </item>
	 
      <item>
         <title>Taking Email Security to the Max-A Corporate Defense Strategy Against Spam, Phishing and DHAs</title>
         <link>http://www.eseminarslive.com/article2/0,2144,1851662,00.asp</link>
         <description>With more than 10,000 active email users at corporate offices and retail stores across North America, OfficeMax's IT department spent 60 hours a week battling unwanted email. Despite the huge administrative effort, spam and phishing emails were still getting through.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <enclosure url="http://rssnewsapps.ziffdavis.com/audioblogs/08-23-05MailFrontier-B.mp3" length="7051807" type="audio/mpeg" />
      </item>
	 
      <item>
         <title>IP-Based SANs-Meeting the Needs of the Legal Services Industry</title>
         <link>http://www.eseminarslive.com/article2/0,2144,1851661,00.asp</link>
         <description>Information is the lifeblood of the legal services industry and today that lifeblood flows through computer networks. Research is done online, legal documents are stored, revised, backed up and archived on the network, and email and various legal applications make it all happen. A storage area network using the IP protocol over SCSI, or iSCSI, can be a perfect match for the needs of legal firms.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <enclosure url="http://rssnewsapps.ziffdavis.com/audioblogs/08-23-05EqualLogicB.mp3" length="10893479" type="audio/mpeg" />
      </item>
	 
      <item>
         <title>Increase Fiscal and Operational Efficiencies By Leveraging Next-Generation Job Scheduling</title>
         <link>http://www.eseminarslive.com/article2/0,2144,1850086,00.asp</link>
         <description>Data center operations require sophisticated techniques to efficiently and effectively manage system and application workloads, many of which are tied directly to business services. This process is referred to as workload optimization, and savvy organizations who can achieve this state can increase the differentiating advantages of their business and extract a greater return from their IT investment.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <enclosure url="http://rssnewsapps.ziffdavis.com/audioblogs/08-18-05CAUnicenterB.mp3" length="11048856" type="audio/mpeg" />
      </item>
	 
      <item>
         <title>Supporting The Frequent Changes in Today's Software Development Teams</title>
         <link>http://www.eseminarslive.com/article2/0,2144,1850087,00.asp</link>
         <description>In this live, interactive eSeminar, we will describe the types of changes that directly impact software teams, the downfalls of ineffective change management processes, and the available solutions from Borland that will help your teams overcome the high cost of change. </description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <enclosure url="http://rssnewsapps.ziffdavis.com/audioblogs/08-18-05BorlandB.mp3" length="14399321" type="audio/mpeg" />
      </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
