<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Generated by Squarespace Site Server v5.11.81 (http://www.squarespace.com/) on Wed, 06 Jun 2012 07:56:43 GMT--><rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title>ThinkJump Journal from Kim Gentes</title><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/</link><description>The blog of Kim Gentes. A place where you will find articles on worship, family, technology, church, music, and art. We promise nothing. But try to never deliver.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 07:56:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><copyright>©2007-2011 Kim Anthony Gentes</copyright><language>en-US</language><generator>Squarespace Site Server v5.11.81 (http://www.squarespace.com/)</generator><itunes:author>Kim Anthony Gentes</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>The blog of Kim Gentes</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>The blog of Kim Gentes. A place where you will find articles on worship, family, technology, church, music, and art. We promise nothing. But try to never deliver.</itunes:summary><itunes:keywords>kim,gentes,worship,music,thinkjump,art,christian,ministry,vineyard,church,church,plant</itunes:keywords><itunes:owner><itunes:name>Kim Gentes</itunes:name><itunes:email>kim@kimgentes.com</itunes:email></itunes:owner><itunes:image href="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/Gentes_Kim.jpg"/><itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality"><itunes:category text="Christianity"/></itunes:category><item><title>Can You Ask For Help? How Pride, Community and Shame Shape Our Thinking (ThinkJump Journal #73 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Church Fathers</category><category>Comfort</category><category>Commitment</category><category>Community</category><category>Direction</category><category>Family</category><category>Francis of Assisi</category><category>Gregory the Great</category><category>Guidance</category><category>History</category><category>Holy Spirit</category><category>Jobs</category><category>Leadership</category><category>Love</category><category>Prayer</category><category>Suffering</category><category>Vocation</category><category>christian</category><category>community</category><category>fear</category><category>help</category><category>prayer</category><category>pride</category><category>shame</category><category>sharing</category><category>support</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 12:46:36 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2012/6/4/can-you-ask-for-help-how-pride-community-and-shame-shape-our.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:12607683</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/askinforhelp.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1338814693838" alt="" /></span></span>Times of disorientation are often precipitated by some form of change. And it is change that seems to find us at a point of weakness, one which we hadn't anticipated on being tested. A sense of entitlement comes with past successes and we are surprised by discouraging results, feeling as though it isn't fair to be challenged in our area or moment of vulnerability. I have begun to believe through the teachings of historical writings from church leaders that much of our facing of such troubles is, in fact, a holy fire sent from God. Not all times, but even those which are sent from the enemy are ultimately forces which God's watchful eye has allowed to come and challenge us (He works all things together for the good of those who love him).</p>
<p>But you know all of that.&nbsp;Here is my single thought.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Call out to your community.</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>What I often find of many local churches in US/Canada is that, at its leadership, are some of the most humble and gifted people on planet Earth. I would say, though, that there might be a danger in our attempts to develop a humble ethos in an organization if we mistake North American/European social etiquette as good Christian manners or worse, Christian community. What am I saying? Ask your community for help. No doubt you've done this in some forms, but I'd encourage you to sound the call louder. There can be no possible greater ally to your vision, mission and people than your current community. Those whose lives have been transformed through your love and ministry will be personally interested in seeing the agent of such growth continue to impact others in their family, community and faith.</p>
<p>Perhaps you are not at the point of asking directly. &nbsp;Get to that point. Engage your community. Ask.</p>
<p>I am saying this, and in effect talking to myself. The last 1.5 years I have been personally in a situation which has had me languishing, using up most of my personal resources, and still asking God what is next. &nbsp;Through pride and personality, I have the most difficult time asking anyone for help. I feel personally obliged to pray, but unable to request help from friends and community. God has been teaching me that this is nothing more than self-centered pride mixed with some fear and shame. Gregory the Great, Francis of Assisi, Thomas &agrave; Kempis, Teresa of &Aacute;vila, Th&eacute;r&egrave;se of Lisieux, Dietrich Bonhoeffer and many others understood that there were layers of truth and disclosure to the human soul and its actions. Their writings expose to us the presumptions we live with and in which we often decieve ourselves from both our real needs and our shadowy pride, which always seeks to hide. But God has been teaching me this- to ask my brother for help is an admission of my engagement, need, and place in a community. Perhaps my reticence to ask reflects my misunderstanding of community, or worse, my rejection of involvement in it.</p>
<p>The point is this- engage your community, ask them for help. Who knows what God has prepared in the heart of a brother, sister or family that is part of the family of your community. Perhaps God has prepared in them a gift of grace for just such a time as this.</p>
<p>There are many other issues and considerations for times when we need help, but I want to leave this with just this one point of asking for help from your community. We often splinter and fragment our efforts across so many areas we neglect simply asking the church family for support. I hope this helps some to reconsider that.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>Part of the community of Jesus,</em></p>
<p><em>Kim Gentes</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em><br /></em></p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-12607683.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>Is Timeliness Next To Godliness? (ThinkJump Journal #72 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Church Meeting</category><category>Community</category><category>Leadership</category><category>Music</category><category>Sunday Services</category><category>Technology</category><category>Worship</category><category>Worship Teams</category><category>clock</category><category>godliness</category><category>late</category><category>time</category><category>timeliness</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 00:51:22 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2012/5/29/is-timeliness-next-to-godliness-thinkjump-journal-72-with-ki.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:16489782</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/time-clock.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1338351893847" alt="" /></span></span>Western society has been fascinated with time since complex geared water clocks first appeared in 1st century BC in Athens (primitive water clocks are dated from 4000BC Egypt and older). We've incorporated some of this attention to time to our corporate gatherings as church communities. Some churches handle this with great care and attention, since it is an important part of their culture. Other churches are less concerned with time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The following very brief 4 questions are just a way to look at how our congregations and leaders approach timeliness in their gatherings. &nbsp;Be sure to click the link to view the results of the survey (to date) once you have answered the questions. Please feel free to comment below, and add to the discussion.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/embeddedform?formkey=dEY5cEpwUHQ5dmwzNC1jMFc0eV83cXc6MQ" width="620" height="1004" frameborder="0" marginheight="0" marginwidth="0">Loading...</iframe></p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-16489782.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>How the Church Has Always Been a Social Network (ThinkJump Journal #71 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Comfort</category><category>Community</category><category>Computers</category><category>Internet</category><category>Jobs</category><category>Prayer</category><category>Resources</category><category>Teaching</category><category>Technology</category><category>christianity</category><category>church</category><category>communication</category><category>community</category><category>computers</category><category>email</category><category>social media</category><category>social network</category><category>technology</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 23:57:27 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2012/5/21/how-the-church-has-always-been-a-social-network-thinkjump-jo.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:16381343</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><em>In the <a href="http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2012/5/21/social-technology-and-connection-thinkjump-journal-69-with-k.html">previous article</a>, we included a video post from a Ted talk presentation about social technology and its possible negative effects on the human psychology. In this blog entry, we want to cover a more hopeful look at social networking from the perspective of the church, based on an article we wrote in May, 2011 for Worship Leader Magazine. &nbsp;We hope you find this helpful. K. Gentes</em></p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/ichthus.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1337646697970" alt="" /></span></span>It was Monday morning. Jake Johnson had just started work. Aaron walked by, declaring his customary &ldquo;good morning&rdquo; and smile. Only this morning, the smile was gone. Aaron said quickly, &ldquo;Could you come to my office please Jake.&rdquo; Jake liked working for Aaron. He was sometimes intense, but never over-demanding and always honest. Jake stepped into Aaron&rsquo;s office.</p>
<p>Aaron closed the door behind Jake and walked around the desk. Before he sat down he had already started his sentence, &ldquo;I&rsquo;m sorry Jake, but we&rsquo;re going to have to let you go.&rdquo;</p>
<p>In an instant, Jake&rsquo;s mind washed with numbness. Somewhere in the background Aaron was talking about sales, financials and corporate cutbacks. But Jake was already moving from numbness to questions and panic. Soon he walked back to his desk, took out his cell phone and called his wife, Kara. Having relocated just 18 months before, Kara&rsquo;s heart sank as Jake told her the news.</p>
<p>Kara immediately logged on to Facebook and sent a message to her mom in another state. She also sent a text to her friend, Alyssa. Kara&rsquo;s mom, Sarah, called the rest of the family. Alyssa told the church secretary and an email quickly went out to the prayer group. Over the next 24 hours, friends and family began looking for possible job openings at their places of employment. Over the next weeks, encouragement, prayers and support helped, as Jake would eventually find a job through a contact in their small group. Thank you Lord!</p>
<p>What happened to Jake and Kara is a powerful reminder that community has an important place in our lives. It also shows us how technology can be a tool to help connect to our real social networks for communication and support. When change comes, it is often the community that provides a supportive safety net in our languishing situations. Over the last two thousand years, the church has been God&rsquo;s family on earth meant to support and encourage one another &ndash; a living, breathing example of Christ, as we love one another.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Tweets in the Early Church</strong></p>
<p>From the earliest church found in the book of Acts, social networks of care have been integral to church life, even survival. When we hear the words &ldquo;social network&rdquo; today, we often think of it as synonymous with Internet technologies and websites. However, long before LOL, BFF, Twitter or Facebook, Christians were using coded abbreviations, communications and relationships as supportive social networks to help the community of God survive and thrive.</p>
<p>We know that early persecution drove Christians to gather in secrecy in many parts of the ancient Mediterranean world, and for the first four hundred years the tight-knit bonds of faith in the church could mean the difference between life and death. During that time, the use of the word Ichthus (&Iota;&Chi;&Theta;&Upsilon;&Sigma; &ndash; which literally meant &ldquo;fish&rdquo; in Greek) was used as a code word (often times along with a symbol of a fish) to identify Christian tombs, meetings and even Christians themselves. This code word was an acrostic in the Greek language that represented the words &ldquo;Jesus Christ God&rsquo;s son Savior.&rdquo;</p>
<p>But Ichthus (also known as Ixthus and Ichthys) is only a small part of early church social networks. Networks, by definition, are associations comprised of two things: a) members and b) relationships between members. True social networks are simply associations based on human relationships, allowing for interaction and communication. Relationship and community were hallmarks of the early church.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>All the believers were together and had everything in common. They sold property and possessions to give to anyone who had need. Every day they continued to meet together in the temple courts. They broke bread in their homes and ate together with glad and sincere hearts, praising God and enjoying the favor of all the people. And the Lord added to their number daily those who were being saved.</p>
<p><em>Acts 2:44-47 (NIV)</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>For the early church, social networks were formed from the relationships of trust that bound them in faith, gathered them together, prompted them to give sacrificially to one another, and resulted not only in praise for God but attracted the attention of people seeking to live in such a community.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Blogging and the Reformation</strong></p>
<p>Over the centuries, relationships, community and communication continued to be integral components of ever changing social networks among Christians. Long before email and blogging exploded on the Internet, Martin Luther and John Calvin&rsquo;s voices of reformation were propelled into wide spread conversation by the advent of another technology- the printing press. While early versions of the printing press had been developed around 1440 by Gutenberg, it was the explosive topic of church reform that allowed Luther&rsquo;s Ninety-Five Theses (and other writings) to spread like wildfire on the wings of the new technology. This mechanical movable type made Martin Luther one of the first profoundly impacting &ldquo;bloggers.&rdquo;</p>
<p>While social media tools have changed from the printing press to online tools, clearly technology remains a powerful ally for spreading both knowledge and opinion, as we saw recently with the controversial blogging surrounding author Rob Bell&rsquo;s recent book on heaven and hell, &ldquo;Love Wins.&rdquo; Blogs, tweets and Facebook all became part of a global, interactive conversation that expressed opinions from different viewpoints.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Using Social Network Technologies Wisely</strong></p>
<p>Social networks have always been a part of the Christian community. Our networks and communication have relied on the relationships and technologies of the time to bring us together, protect us, and even create controversy and change. Today&rsquo;s online social networks are simply digital expressions of human patterns of relationship, thought, and interaction. They offer the ability to extend our engagement with one another. But like so many tools, they are amoral- providing neither good nor bad weight to the communication.</p>
<p>The danger of online social networking (as opposed to face-to-face interaction) is that Internet communications provide for anonymity and/or instant electronic distribution, which ultimately allows for relationships in which we have <em>contact without a corresponding accountability</em>. But like the Ichthus and printing press, online tools can also support the best of what social networking has to offer. For Jake and Kara these same social networking systems were important tools that allowed them to connect to the support and love of the Body of Christ. Social networks will always be part of our Christian communities. The social network technologies and our use of them remain helpful tools for us, if we choose to apply them with God&rsquo;s wisdom.</p>
<p>Use the tools &ndash; but remember that human beings were made for direct communication. Tools were made for man; not man for the tools.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>Kim Gentes is a worship leader, pastor, writer and technologist. Aside from serving as CTO of a Christian media company, he was the founder of Worshipmusic.com and WorshipTeam.com and is the author of the new book &ldquo;2011 Ultimate Worship Resource Guide: Songs &amp; Media Edition.&rdquo; He can be found online at <a href="http://www.kimgentes.com/">www.kimgentes.com</a>.</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>[<span>Copyright &copy; 2011 by Worship Leader Media. Used by permission. All rights reserved.]</span></em></p>
<p><em><span>NOTE:&nbsp;</span>Article originally published in Worship Leader Magazine, May 2011 edition. Please visit <a class="offsite-link-inline" href="http://www.worshipleader.com/" target="_blank">http://www.worshipleader.com</a> for more information or to subscribe</em></p>
<p><em><br /></em></p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-16381343.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>Why Do People Do Karaoke? (ThinkJump Journal #70 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Blog</category><category>Music</category><category>karaoke</category><category>poll</category><category>singing</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2012/5/21/why-do-people-do-karaoke-thinkjump-journal-70-with-kim-gente.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:16478291</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/karaoke-freak.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1338268239149" alt="" /></span></span>OK, time out from the seriousness of the blog for a lighter question on strange human behavior.</p>
<p>This is the question that has plagued humanity since the 70's-</p>
<p><strong>Why Do People Do Karaoke?&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>Please, help me out, and answer this! Doing so may just save the galaxy from imploding!! Well maybe not, but then again, it is one of the strangest human behaviors brought on with the advent of technology in music.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Check out the poll below. Answer the question and see the current survey results graph. Thanks all! Have FUN!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><iframe src="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/embeddedform?formkey=dEtzbGtzazVvRzZnYzYzYmxvR3Y0LWc6MQ" width="620" height="500" frameborder="0" marginheight="0" marginwidth="0">Loading...</iframe></p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-16478291.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>Social Technology And Connection (ThinkJump Journal #69 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Blog</category><category>Community</category><category>Computers</category><category>Family</category><category>Health</category><category>Internet</category><category>Interview</category><category>Leadership</category><category>TED</category><category>communication</category><category>community</category><category>connection</category><category>conversation</category><category>relationship</category><category>social media</category><category>society</category><category>technology</category><category>video</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 22:42:25 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2012/5/21/social-technology-and-connection-thinkjump-journal-69-with-k.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:16380774</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/connected.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1338969097764" alt="" /></span></span>In 1998 I was asked to present a teaching on technology and media, from a Christian perspective. From 1999 through 2003, I presented that teaching at conferences in the US and Canada. It was nothing ground breaking, but it did scratch the surface of what would later become an increasingly powerful force in our society- the role of technology in our personal lives. One of the key themes that arose from this study was a concern that we do not allow technology to supplant our real relationships for information and connection that has no accountability. &nbsp;I summarized it this way:</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">Technology and media have increasingly become tools allowing us to communicate without the demands of real relationship. We are in constant danger of allowing ourselves to connect and engage without accountability.</p>
<p>This last week, I discovered an excellent TED talk on this same subject (thanks to <a class="offsite-link-inline" href="http://vickybeeching.com/blog/" target="_blank">Vicki Beeching's</a>&nbsp;great blog!). &nbsp;Sherry Turkle's presentation is a poignant and well thought out consideration of how social technology is redefining the actual psychology of people and changing the otherwise normal development of conversation and self-reflection in the human personality. I found the points and conclusions she arrives at to be very profound. I felt that rather than bringing my points to bear on this, I would rather point to this TED talk, where Turkle does a great job of articulating the salient points.</p>
<p>From the viewpoint of this worship leader, pastor and Christian, I think she is touching some of the questions that our faith communities are meant to address (though, obviously through her perspective as a psychologist). I am not saying this presentation is from a "Christian" perspective (I don't know Turkle's influences or religious beliefs). But I am saying that she is pointing to the heart of what conversation, identity and relationship mean to the human psyche. At one point she even refers to the physical place in which we escape from technology as "sacred space"- very telling!</p>
<p><object width="526" height="374">
<param name="movie" value="http://video.ted.com/assets/player/swf/EmbedPlayer.swf"></param>
<param name="allowFullScreen" value="true" />
<param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always"/>
<param name="wmode" value="transparent"></param>
<param name="bgColor" value="#ffffff"></param>
<param name="flashvars" value="vu=http://video.ted.com/talk/stream/2012/Blank/SherryTurkle_2012-320k.mp4&su=http://images.ted.com/images/ted/tedindex/embed-posters/SherryTurkle_2012-embed.jpg&vw=512&vh=288&ap=0&ti=1409&lang=&introDuration=15330&adDuration=4000&postAdDuration=830&adKeys=talk=sherry_turkle_alone_together;year=2012;theme=media_that_matters;theme=what_s_next_in_tech;event=TED2012;tag=communication;tag=community;tag=culture;tag=technology;&preAdTag=tconf.ted/embed;tile=1;sz=512x288;" />
<embed src="http://video.ted.com/assets/player/swf/EmbedPlayer.swf" pluginspace="http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" wmode="transparent" bgColor="#ffffff" width="526" height="374" allowFullScreen="true" allowScriptAccess="always" flashvars="vu=http://video.ted.com/talk/stream/2012/Blank/SherryTurkle_2012-320k.mp4&su=http://images.ted.com/images/ted/tedindex/embed-posters/SherryTurkle_2012-embed.jpg&vw=512&vh=288&ap=0&ti=1409&lang=&introDuration=15330&adDuration=4000&postAdDuration=830&adKeys=talk=sherry_turkle_alone_together;year=2012;theme=media_that_matters;theme=what_s_next_in_tech;event=TED2012;tag=communication;tag=community;tag=culture;tag=technology;&preAdTag=tconf.ted/embed;tile=1;sz=512x288;"></embed>
</object></p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-right ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/one-connect.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1338969371948" alt="" /></span></span>I don't expect everyone will agree with me in my admiration of Turkle's thesis in this video, but I think she has found wisdom in her study and it is simply a reflection of the wisdom we already see in God's word- that some of our core human needs are companionship, community and conversation.</p>
<p>I encourage you to watch this video and give your thoughts as it relates to your own faith journey, your local communities and expressions of ministry.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>Sincerely</em></p>
<p><em>Kim Gentes</em></p>
<p><em><br /></em></p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-16380774.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>The Road Home: Learning from the Prodigal's Journey Back to the Father (ThinkJump Journal #68 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Bible</category><category>Community</category><category>Devotional</category><category>Family</category><category>Guidance</category><category>Healing</category><category>Jesus</category><category>Jesus</category><category>Love</category><category>Scripture</category><category>Teaching</category><category>Theology</category><category>contrition</category><category>drive</category><category>home</category><category>humility</category><category>journey</category><category>parable</category><category>prodigal son</category><category>reconciliation</category><category>repentance</category><category>road</category><category>the road</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 17:02:48 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2012/5/21/the-road-home-learning-from-the-prodigals-journey-back-to-th.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:16375573</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/road-image.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1338236740102" alt="" /></span></span></p>
<p>Life is often referred to analogously as a journey. This imagery has held true in great literature from "The Pilgrim's Progress" to "The Road Not Taken" (Poem by Robert Frost) to Psalm 23 ("though I walk through the valley...") and even to Jesus parable of "The Good Samaritan". The path we take in life is a marker of both the choices we will come to, and the history of choices we have made. Among all the great works of art and literature that reflect life's journey on a path, none is as rivetting and poigniant as Jesus parable we often call "The Prodigal Son".</p>
<p>In the deepest sense, this parable speaks to all people. It is God the Father's call to humanity to return to him. But in a very personal sense, this parable reminds us that the way back from any broken relationship has two primary elements - contrition and humility. Let's read the portion of the parable that deals with the road home for this prodigal.</p>
<blockquote>
<div>"That brought him to his senses. He said, 'All those farmhands working for my father sit down to three meals a day, and here I am starving to death. I'm going back to my father. I'll say to him, Father, I've sinned against God, I've sinned before you; I don't deserve to be called your son. Take me on as a hired hand.' He got right up and went home to his father.</div>
<div>&nbsp;</div>
<div></div>
<div>"When he was still a long way off, his father saw him. His heart pounding, he ran out, embraced him, and kissed him. The son started his speech: 'Father, I've sinned against God, I've sinned before you; I don't deserve to be called your son ever again.'</div>
<div>&nbsp;</div>
<div></div>
<div>"But the father wasn't listening. He was calling to the servants, 'Quick. Bring a clean set of clothes and dress him. Put the family ring on his finger and sandals on his feet. Then get a grain-fed heifer and roast it. We're going to feast! We're going to have a wonderful time! My son is here&mdash;given up for dead and now alive! Given up for lost and now found!' And they began to have a wonderful time.</div>
<div>&nbsp;</div>
<div><em>(Luke 15:17-24 - The Message)</em></div>
</blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-right ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/cropped-drive_000135.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1337623185674" alt="" /></span></span>Countless teachings have been done on this parable, but I simply want to highlight one element of the process of reconciliation that was squarely within the prodigal son's realm of responsibility. The son had to come to the point of contrition about his own lostness, his own lack, and his offense against both God and others (his father, in this case). &nbsp;On doing that, he also made a conscious decision to consider himself less than he truly was in order to find his way back to his father. This is an obvious reversal of the pride that led him away from home in the first place.</p>
<p>This teaches us two things about reconciling with others.</p>
<p><strong>Contrition </strong>- First, if we are not yet ready to admit our own error and wrong relatedness to a relationship, there is little chance of reconciliation. The son saw this and responded with admission and contrition.</p>
<p><strong>Humility </strong>- Second, we must be willing to humble ourselves if we hope to actually restore relationship. Contrition will be little more than a verbal apology if it is not followed by humility. Humility is an action that re-engages the possibility of relationship by saying "your friendship is more important than my rights".</p>
<p>Are you wondering how to start the journey to reconciliation with someone? I encourage you to consider reading the parable of the Prodigal Son. &nbsp;Ask God to reveal practical steps for you to take that you see in the parable. I pray that you will find not only revelation and encouragement from the scriptures, but guidance as you look for restoration in relationships. May God grant you his love and wisdom in all your relationships as you endeavor to find your road home.</p>
<p>In the spirit journeying, I have included a video of a scenic drive, accompanied by a musical soundscape that you may find encouraging as you think and pray about your own road home with relationships in your life. I hope you enjoy it. <em>(I encourage you to watch this in "Original" or 1080HD mode, and in full screen- or if you have a triple monitor system to watch it in 3 screen mode- 720p for each screen x 3)</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><object width="550" height="309"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/svpYssZLJ18?version=3&amp;hl=en_US&amp;rel=0"></param><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true"></param><param name="allowscriptaccess" value="always"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/svpYssZLJ18?version=3&amp;hl=en_US&amp;rel=0" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="550" height="309" allowscriptaccess="always" allowfullscreen="true"></embed></object></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>Journeying with you</em></p>
<p><em>Kim Gentes</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-16375573.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>When Authenticity Became a Fad (ThinkJump Journal #67 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Church Fathers</category><category>Commitment</category><category>Community</category><category>Creative</category><category>Devotional</category><category>Direction</category><category>Family</category><category>History</category><category>Leadership</category><category>Marketing</category><category>Music</category><category>Resources</category><category>Sunday Services</category><category>Teaching</category><category>Theology</category><category>Worship</category><category>Worship Leaders</category><category>authenticity</category><category>community</category><category>fad</category><category>leaders</category><category>music</category><category>pastors</category><category>songs</category><category>worship</category><category>writers</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 22:29:38 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2012/4/30/when-authenticity-became-a-fad-thinkjump-journal-67-with-kim.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:15738309</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/latte-coffee-cup.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1335825185046" alt="" /></span></span><em>[Join in the conversation: Be sure to post your comments or thoughts at bottom of this post!]</em></p>
<p>A few months ago, I was sitting down to have a chai tea latte at a local Starbucks. I like my hot chai with extra cream. As I sat down, I wondered how many people drink the same thing I do. I couldn't think of a single person I knew that drank the same thing I do. Something about that made me feel pretty special. Then it struck me- why was the item on the menu? Of course, not just a few people, but likely dozens, hundreds, maybe thousands of people around the world drink chai tea lattes, just like me. This was obvious simply because a huge chain like Starbucks (about 20,000 outlets worldwide) must have an economy of scale on any product in its selection in order to continue to carry it. But for a few delusional moments, I felt somehow unique in having a drink that I liked with the thought no one else was ever enjoying its great taste. I still enjoy chai tea lattes. We'll come back to this.</p>
<p>Today's worship leaders in local churches have an extraordinary amount of expectations placed on them by many congregations. This is partly because of the generational inclusion that is sometimes present in many congregations. Many churches have an age range that starts at infants and children and goes to seniors 70, 80 and older. Somehow in that range, worship leaders are expected to be attentive to all generations and styles and songs. As a worship leader, I love the challenge and try to remain current while reaching across the generations (or centuries) to borrow the best and gather them for the community I am serving in at the time.</p>
<p>Still, many churches (and senior pastors) don't recognize that we ask worship leaders to be something that no one can be. In trying to accommodate the entire community, pastors can often listen to many specific requests from the congregation (without filtering them) and then send "down" direct and indirect messages to the worship leader that they need to be all things to all people. Worship leaders end up having the unenviable job of being asked to be some perfect combination of all the icons of generations from George Beverly Shea to Don Moen to Ron Kenoly to Darlene Zschech to Kevin Prosch to Matt Redman to Marantha Praise Band to Delirious to Paul Baloche to Chris Tomlin to Kari Jobe to&nbsp;Michael Gungor to Mumford and Sons.  And the worship leader who doesn't get it 100% right each and every Sunday is then asked why they aren't being more sensitive to the slice of the congregation that isn't touched by that week's "worship". And even when the worship leader does get a sense of worship and spans the generations and styles of their congregation, they are asked why they aren't "creative" and are just playing like a cover band. Of course, when they are creative, they are asked why they don't sound like one of the aforementioned names and why the songs aren't already pre-known, or why they aren't using songs that are already being played on K-LOVE. It's a no win situation for many worship leaders.</p>
<p>Obviously, I am exaggerating to make a point here. But not by much. <span class="full-image-float-right ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/banjo-nun.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1335826796654" alt="" /></span></span>The deeper question of why we have so much affinity for hearing the sounds and songs that connect with us is what we must address. People love music, and music speaks to the heart and soul of their knowledge and emotions. It combines what they know and what they remember. Music is the ultimate vehicle of experience. &nbsp;So when you are talking about the music of worship, you are talking about the framework of the sacred space in which people experience God. It is no wonder that inside that space, you have such strong opinions. But we can't expect a single music style or experience to cover the breadth of expectations that exist across multiple generations - any more than we can expect a nun playing a banjo would cover all our bases!</p>
<p>The problem isn't with music having a place in our sacred space of worship. The problem is that we expect our time in that space to be re-iterated in a way which is genuine to our past experience. The music that framed our pivotal experiences in sacred space in the past will always be the music we deem as "best" for worship. Once we delve into talking about the things of music in sacred space, the waters become murky with theological and psychological debate. So let's take one step back.</p>
<p>What makes you love one song, style or person who writes/leads your favorite worship/sacred music? For most people, it is a sense of authenticity that the music has to their own story, life and experiences. This is, of course, what popular music purveyors have known for years. Tell people a story they know that connects to their own lives, but say it in a way which is unique- this has long been the formula of many country, pop and rock lyrics &amp; melodies. Sacred space music may be different in its use as musical framework for worship, but it certainly has no less power. Because of this, when we hear a song that connects deeply to our story in the midst of worship, we feel a genuine connection with the music and truth it contains.</p>
<p>We may hear those same songs later and reflect to the meaning once again. Each time we worship, we can have a more or less authentic connection to restating and reaffirming the truths of those sacred space songs. This is why many pastors and theologians want to make sure the songs we sing in worship are "proper" theology. That is, they want to make sure the song's theology agrees with their interpretation of the Bible, so that it reiterates their understanding of correct doctrine.</p>
<p>But lets get back to the sense of "authenticity" we find in some songs. What happens when we repeat these same songs and even try to replicate the same experience? It becomes less and less authentic. What made it authentic in the first place was not just the music and our connection to it, but the place it occurs in our story. As time moves on, we are changed. The experiences of life (even those experiences in the sacred space) change us. The next time we return to worship and music within the context of sacred space, we are different people. Our story is in a different place. But still, those songs that change us remain in our hearts and experience as powerful. They are "authentic" but now in a sense they point us to something different than they did when we first encountered them and were changed by them.</p>
<p>This is something of how we find the great songs of the church- they are songs that have become anthems for us and are sung around the globe. They join us together, beyond our local congregations and have an important place amongst our song repertoire. But we must be careful not to think that our local congregation should be defining its music of sacred space by only listening to the Christian radio top 40 or adhering to the CCLI top 25. We must look deeper.</p>
<p>Authenticity has become a catch word for much of the music industry, and a "claim" of many a worship album in their marketing blurbs. But the truth is, nothing is authentic without context. It may be authentic to the people who created the songs, and to the congregation that engaged with them as they were being birthed in their local communities. But whether they are authentic with the larger body of Christ is a matter of experience, of context and of our place in the story in which God has us.</p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/fingerprint-image.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1335826359918" alt="" /></span></span>Authenticity is, by definition, something we can't formulate. We can't "make something authentic". The moment we do, we are trying to force our sense of genuine experience on to that thing. For example, let's look at what happens for different people in a congregation on a typical Sunday. If you are the worship leader you may get various responses from people wanting to tell you about their experience related to worship. &nbsp;A few people tell you it was the most authentic, amazing worship time ever. A few others give an obligatory "good job". Some may critique, but normally that comes later in the week in the form of emails or "anonymous" letters. &nbsp;This range of response comes from the range of experience.</p>
<p>So, can we hope to be authentic? Yes, I think we can. But it must come from the unique identity, unique fingerprint of your local church, local leadership, and pastor and worship leader. Like a fingerprint, there are common features to all Christian churches (this make them all Christian) and unique features that distinguish them in local areas. &nbsp;We must take both into account.&nbsp;</p>
<p>There are obvious first steps that some churches take. The pastor and worship leader meet and talk about the real vision, the mission, the real values and the real ethos they intend for their church community/congregation. As much as possible, I encourage pastors and worship leaders doing this to answer how they are going to minister to the whole family in their church, as it relates to music /worship. The truth is healthy local churches are built on families, not just a single age group. Churches built on a single age group (normally young people) don't last, at least they don't last as is- they transform into family churches who have young children (a bit of age, marriage and life do that!).</p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-right ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/newsletter-2.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1337669138679" alt="" /></span></span>For church leaders, ask yourself how your community gatherings can be places of authentic inclusion for the entire church family. The answer some churches have come to is age-segregated services. This can be one answer, though I personally think it is less healthy as a realistic image of the "family of God". Even if you are focusing on a certain music style, certain age group for your main church core, recognize that you must find ways to let the entire family be a part of the sacred space music and experience.</p>
<p>Being authentic as a community may mean that the worship leader must be wary of relying too heavily on their proclivity to specific songs or writers. &nbsp;They must serve the community. But at the same time, pastors and congregations must recognize that at times they are asking the worship leader to be something no human being can be- an integration of all their leadership/music/songwriting styles.</p>
<p>We must stop trying to "be authentic" according to the definition of the worship music companies trying to market their latest release. We must rather be authentic to the local churches we are in, and live in community with them as a more important goal than the desire to try to be more like the heroes of the music we have enjoyed.</p>
<p>We must stop making authenticity a fad. The funny thing is, the business world has long seen this desire to falsely use "authenticity" as a guise for marketing. They, like we as Christians, understand that people who experience our attempts at "trying to be authentic" will automatically intuit the falacy in our efforts and our ultimate goals. Business Insider writer Greg Voakes archives a pithy letter from an advertising film director on this very subject (see it <a class="offsite-link-inline" href="http://read.bi/Jn8ohD" target="_blank">here</a>). If we are completely honest, many of our attempts at authenticity in church settings are little more than a marketing ploy to bring in more people. Let's stop that.</p>
<p>Again, authenticity is not the "raw" factor, the "reality TV" expos&eacute;, or the attempts at being culture current that reflect something that doesn't have integrity with our actual community in which we live and serve.&nbsp;We must simply live rightly, in our communities, inviting them in with a breadth of understanding that is an invitation and not a notice that they are entering an exclusive club. Worship leaders, congregations and pastors all have important parts to play in developing authentic communities. What it comes down to is this- what we exemplify on Sunday mornings should have a consistency that looks like us all throughout the week (Weds, Friday, etc- any day). There is a sense in which our corporate gatherings do indeed allow "iron to sharpen iron" and that we can "spur one another on" by our meetings. &nbsp;However, trying to espouse a false sense of identity by stealing someone elses definition of "authenticity" amounts to no authenticity at all. It amounts to forgery.</p>
<p>Hardly the authentic thing we said we were looking for.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>Sincerely ;)</em></p>
<p><em>Kim Gentes</em></p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-15738309.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>Worship Research: Transition from Hymnal to Modern Worship (ThinkJump Journal #66 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>CCM</category><category>Community</category><category>Computers</category><category>Creative</category><category>History</category><category>Holy Spirit</category><category>Internet</category><category>Interview</category><category>Kim Gentes</category><category>Marketing</category><category>Music</category><category>Resources</category><category>Sunday Services</category><category>Teaching</category><category>Technology</category><category>Training</category><category>Trinity</category><category>Worship</category><category>history</category><category>hymnal</category><category>hymns</category><category>modern worship</category><category>music</category><category>praise and worship</category><category>styles</category><category>thesis</category><category>transition</category><category>worship</category><category>worship wars</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 19:24:57 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2012/4/26/worship-research-transition-from-hymnal-to-modern-worship-th.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:16014309</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>There is so much content and information being generated in the "modern worship" world that we rarely see anyone placing this work and resources in the context of the historical stream of change in which it falls. &nbsp;One part of my recent thesis work related to resourcing the church dealt with an investigation into the transition of church worship from its primary source of the hymnal as its musical resource to the extensive list of digitally driven solutions we have today. This happens in the context of major changes within stylistic, musician tools, technological and marketing aspects of music. On top of those changes (which were happening in culture and impacting the church), changes inside of the church we converging for the "perfect storm". &nbsp;These forces intermingled and we have the resultant worship revolution of the last 40 years.</p>
<p>This brief video presentation is an effort to begin talking about these changes, church worship, and placing them in the historical context in which they occured. It is not meant to be a conclusion on anything, but a primer for the work I did and continue to do.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/w_2vAjmgGR0?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Kim Gentes</p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-16014309.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>The Road (ThinkJump Journal #65 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Bible</category><category>Devotional</category><category>Easter</category><category>Jesus</category><category>Jesus</category><category>Kingdom of God</category><category>Passion Week</category><category>Scripture</category><category>Suffering</category><category>Teaching</category><category>easter</category><category>hosanna</category><category>messiah</category><category>mount of olives</category><category>palm sunday</category><category>passion week</category><category>son of david</category><category>triumphal entry</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 02:46:26 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2012/4/1/the-road-thinkjump-journal-65-with-kim-gentes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:15684503</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/hopefulroad.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1333342229544" alt="" /></span></span>Less than three weeks ago, I walked through Jerusalem, going through most of the historic locations where Jesus is recorded to have traveled in his Passion week. Beginning with the Mount of Olives, I walked down the road leading to the Old City area, the likely route many scholars believe Jesus might have taken for his triumphal entry. As you walk down the road into the Kidron Valley you can see the enormity of the temple mount, on which used to sit the huge edifice of Judaism- the temple itself. &nbsp;With the people clamoring and honoring Jesus by placing the palm branches in his path, one can imagine the heady jubilation that was in the air. &nbsp;The crowds were lauding him as he was welcomed as the "Son of David", "He who comes in the name of the Lord", "<span>Peace in heaven and glory in the highest!"</span>&nbsp;and "the king of Israel".</p>
<p>One must understand the times of 1st century Palestine. One must understand that the Jews were subject to the occupation of the&nbsp;Roman "super power" that kept the Jewish hopes under the heal of the Roman&nbsp;legions. One must understand that inside this imperial stranglehold was the hidden and overt unrest that was regularly seething up, being headed by so-called "messiahs" who would rise up to lead revolts only to eventually be crushed on the power of the ruling regime. But the Jewish people still had hope- hope that a Messiah would come and free them from their oppression, just as YHWH had come in their history and freed them from oppression. &nbsp;Surely the new Messiah would do the same- free them from the oppression of military and political domination.</p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-right ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/garden-gethsemane.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1333342337944" alt="" /></span><span class="thumbnail-caption" style="width: 300px;">Modern Day Olive Groves in the area of the Garden of Gethsemane</span></span>The road would have taken Jesus by the Garden of Gethsemane, which he would later return to in his most painful hour. But he could continue for now. &nbsp;As Jesus descended the hill, on his road down to Jerusalem, one gets the sense that the Messiah the Jews were hoping for was something quite different than the king who was riding on the donkey, quite different from Jesus. &nbsp;Certainly Jesus had become known and his miraculous deeds had drawn the attention of many people, small and great. But the crowds were drawn to Jesus even more as he refuted and confounded the religious leaders, always showing compassion to the outcast, the rejected and lowly. But as they saw Jesus coming now, entering the city, they glorified the Jesus they hoped for, not the one who was truly there. &nbsp;They wanted a Jesus who would lead them as a political and perhaps military leader, freeing them from the oppression of Rome. &nbsp;But many other military revolutionaries had come and gone- and Rome eventually crushed&nbsp;them all.</p>
<p>No, the Jesus that rode the donkey into Jerusalem was coming in peace. He had in himself the hope for true peace, where every person could rest their soul. They wanted a Jesus who could come and kill the enemy. The real Jesus was there to die. &nbsp;They wanted a victorious Jesus. The real Jesus was there to surrender to seeming defeat. They wanted a Jesus who would defend and expel the rulers and authorities and establish justice against them. The real Jesus would not even open his mouth to defend himself, and allowed the cruel injustice and hatred of all evil to be placed on his head as a thorny crown of pain.</p>
<p>The road Jesus was taking looked like one of victory. &nbsp;Even the shouts from the crowd would rally any political or popular leader. &nbsp;But Jesus neither rebuked the crowds (as the Pharisees asked him to do), nor did he give their adulation a confirmation of its hidden meaning. &nbsp;With this backdrop, let us read again, the account of Luke's gospel and Jesus entry to Jerusalem.</p>
<blockquote>
<div>They brought it to Jesus, threw their cloaks on the colt and put Jesus on it. As he went along, people spread their cloaks on the road.&nbsp;When he came near the place where the road goes down the Mount of Olives, the whole crowd of disciples began joyfully to praise God in loud voices for all the miracles they had seen:</div>
<div><br />"Blessed is the king who comes in the name of the Lord!"</div>
<div>"Peace in heaven and glory in the highest!"</div>
<div></div>
<div><br />Some of the Pharisees in the crowd said to Jesus, "Teacher, rebuke your disciples!"</div>
<div>"I tell you," he replied, "if they keep quiet, the stones will cry out."</div>
<div></div>
<div><br />As he approached Jerusalem and saw the city, he wept over it and said, "If you, even you, had only known on this day what would bring you peace&mdash;but now it is hidden from your eyes. The days will come upon you when your enemies will build an embankment against you and encircle you and hem you in on every side. They will dash you to the ground, you and the children within your walls. They will not leave one stone on another, because you did not recognize the time of God&rsquo;s coming to you."</div>
<div><br /><em>(Luke 19:35-44)</em></div>
</blockquote>
<p>Notice, how Jesus responds to the real issues here. Yes, he had come to bring peace, but not the peace the nation and people of Israel hoped for. They hoped for a revolution that would free them from political oppression. Jesus wouldn't bring leadership to such a revolution. And in fact, the peace Jesus had in mind, would be rejected. The people would watch Jesus die and look for another revolutionary that they would follow in rebellion against Rome. &nbsp;Jesus was warning them here that such a leader and revolution would not bring them peace, but would eventually lead to their utter destruction. And in 70AD, this prophetic word of Jesus came to fruition, as the Roman general Titus would lay siege to Jerusalem. Titus (who would later become emperor) came to put down a revolt that had temporarily placed control of Jerusalem back in the hands of revolutionary Jews in the year 66AD. To show its imperial power, Titus would utterly wipe Jerusalem, the temple and its people into dust, demolishing everything but the temple mount foundation on which the temple stood.</p>
<p>Jesus knew political and military revolt was not the answer to the problems of the Jews, or humanity. The real revolution would indeed be about peace, but not a peace brought by power- a peace brought by surrender to the will of God. &nbsp;Jesus wouldn't explain it- it seemed that even his own disciples didn't understand. Jesus would have to show them what peace looked like. &nbsp;Jesus' peace did not mean "calm". Instead, it meant looking into the face of violence and accusation and remaining resolute to love. Jesus' peace didn't mean the absence of pain. Instead it meant enduring the worst pain, and not giving in to retribution or response in kind.</p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-right ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/dark-road.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1333342265071" alt="" /></span></span>So while the people didn't recognize what kind of peace Jesus was bringing, He brought them the real peace they couldn't have understood. And on this triumphal entry, he didn't try to make everyone understand. He didn't stop the parade and correct everyone. He didn't make sure those following him were "tracking with the plan". &nbsp;No. Jesus simply trusted that being who he was, and facing what he would face, he would incarnate in his own flesh the perfect example of peace that would speak louder than words could say. He knew his words would fall on deaf ears (remember he said "If you, even you, had only known on this day what would bring you peace&mdash;but now it is hidden from your eyes"). So Jesus just continued on the road. The road of misunderstanding. The road of jubilation. The road of joy. The road of pain. The road of peace.</p>
<p>As you take stock of your own life, what road are you on? More importantly, as you go, are you following on the road Jesus is leading you through? Are you frustrated with not being understood? Are you upset that things aren't "calm"? &nbsp;Perhaps it is time for us to accept that the peace God brings is not that of being understood. The peace God brings is instead about following our call such that the ravages of the outside world (whether they are chanting for us, or against us) do not change the direction of our lives. The peace that God brings is the keel of our ship- it doesn't change course, but it gives us a centering strength bound in God's love. The peace that God brings walks through the valley of the shadow of death and fears no evil- not because it won't come upon us, but because it won't do real harm to God's purposes even when it touches us.</p>
<p>Come, Lord Jesus. Bring us with you on your road of peace. Help us hear your voice, not that of the crowds. Help us follow your heart, not the surging passions of defending ourselves against others, or of obtaining "what we deserve". Help us follow you on the road, Lord Jesus. The road of your pain. The road of your peace.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>Travelling with you,</em></p>
<p><em>Kim Gentes</em></p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-15684503.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>Thoughts About Nationalism in Worship Contexts (ThinkJump Journal #64 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Blog</category><category>Community</category><category>Sunday Services</category><category>USA</category><category>Worship</category><category>america</category><category>citizenship</category><category>nationalism</category><category>worship</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2012 04:37:39 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2012/1/6/thoughts-about-nationalism-in-worship-contexts-thinkjump-jou.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:14476428</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/prayer-flag.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1325914107808" alt="" /></span></span>For the last year I have been working on completing filing all the paperwork and walking through the process of naturalization in the US. Born a Canadian, I've been living in the US for the last 20+ years, paying taxes, registered for the selective service, obeying the laws and trying to contribute positively to the society and communities in which I've lived.&nbsp;One thing that is clear to me is that Americans are proud of their heritage of standing for freedoms and rights, and are constantly placing the values of competing agendas in contrast to those freedoms to make sure that none are violated.</p>
<p>I am not, by nature or choice, a political person. Being a resident alien in the US has given me the opportunity to observe and contribute to the economic ecosystem of the country, while not being involved in the political or civil process. As well as not being allowed to vote, a resident&nbsp;alien cannot serve on juries or be appointed to any government leadership. In a way, this has given me an "out" when I didn't want to become embroiled in contraversial political opinions and discussions.</p>
<p>
<p>That said, one thing that always struck me as a bit odd was the interjection of nationalism in worship community activities, events or even liturgy. I certainly understand the notion that a citizen can be proud of his country and freedoms it provides and want to celebrate those.&nbsp; But is a worship service the place for that? I am not talking about political campaigning or opinion-swaying, but just nationalism in forms of honor. Things such as national anthems, pledges, and flags used in a worship community center- are these in or out of place in a building where we gather as the family of God?</p>
<p>
<p>For my part, I don't mind if people honor their country, have flags represented and honor those people who serve in civil or military service. I understand and respect that.&nbsp; The one thing that I sometimes feel uncertain about is the idea of singing national anthems or nationalistic songs in the flow and context of a worship service. This seems out of place to me, though I certainly think it is a matter of opinion, not conscience.</p>
<p>
<p>On the lighter side of this discussion, I am studying for my final test for US citizenship and I learned a number of things.&nbsp; I thought I would give a short&nbsp;8 questions that they ask in the study guide to those of you who are interested in a bit of&nbsp;historical American quiz-fun.&nbsp; Try to answer the following&nbsp;8 questions without looking at the very bottom. Then score yourself. I'd be interested to see if these are common knowledge among US citizens (the majority of the readers on my blog are US based, but please feel free to take the quiz wherever you are from).&nbsp; When you are done the quiz, for fun, post where you are from (city/state) and let us know (if you are comfortable with it) what your score was. When I took the study test myself, I only knew&nbsp;5 of the&nbsp;8 answers, but have learned them all through the study guide now.</p>
<p><ol>
<li>What is the supreme law of the land?</li>
<li>The idea of self government is in the first 3 words of the constitution. What are these words?</li>
<li>What do we call the first 10 amendments to the constitution?</li>
<li>What are the 5&nbsp;rights or freedoms from the first amendment?</li>
<li>How many amendments does the constitution have?</li>
<li>What are the three rights in the declaration of independence?</li>
<li>Who is one of your state's US Senators?</li>
<li>What are the 3 branches of government?</li>
</ol>
<p>The study guide actually includes 100 such questions, which go on to include history and details of national leaders, government and details of the laws, states and territories.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let us know how you scored! And also, be sure to post your opinion, thoughts about how, or if, nationalism is appropriate to be included in worship community contexts.</p>
<p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>blessings </em>
<p><em>Kim Gentes</em>
<p>
<p>&nbsp; 
<hr />
<p><em style="font-size: 90%;"><span style="font-size: 90%;">&nbsp;</span></em></p>
<p><em style="font-size: 90%;"><span style="font-size: 90%;">For those who took the test above, here are the answers to the questions:</span></em>&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>
<p><ol>
<li><em style="font-size: 90%;"><span style="font-size: 90%;">The constitution</span></em></li>
<li><em style="font-size: 90%;"><span style="font-size: 90%;">"We the people"</span></em></li>
<li><em style="font-size: 90%;"><span style="font-size: 90%;">The bill of rights.</span></em></li>
<li><em style="font-size: 90%;"><span style="font-size: 90%;">Speech, religion, assembly, press, petition the government.</span></em></li>
<li><em style="font-size: 90%;"><span style="font-size: 90%;">27 (twenty seven)</span></em></li>
<li><em style="font-size: 90%;"><span style="font-size: 90%;">Life, liberty, pursuit of happiness</span></em></li>
<li><em style="font-size: 90%;"><span style="font-size: 90%;">varies by state</span></em></li>
<li><em style="font-size: 90%;"><span style="font-size: 90%;">Legislative, Judicial, Executive</span></em></li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;
<p>&nbsp;</p>
</p>
</p>
</p>
</p>
</p>
</p>
</p>
</p>
</p>
</p>
</p>
</p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-14476428.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>The Gift of Worship (ThinkJump Journal #63 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Bible</category><category>Christmas</category><category>Jesus</category><category>Jesus</category><category>Scripture</category><category>Worship</category><category>bow</category><category>christmas</category><category>gifts</category><category>men</category><category>offering</category><category>season</category><category>treasure</category><category>wise</category><category>wisemen</category><category>worship</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 03:51:18 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2011/12/8/the-gift-of-worship-thinkjump-journal-63-with-kim-gentes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:14037672</guid><description><![CDATA[<blockquote style="text-align: right;"><span class="full-image-float-right ssNonEditable"><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/treasure-box.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1323754013555" alt="" /></span>On coming to the house, they saw the child with his mother Mary, and they bowed down and worshiped him. Then they opened their treasures and presented him with gifts of gold and of incense and of myrrh.&nbsp;<br /><em style="font-size: 80%;">Matthew 2:11&nbsp;</em><br /></blockquote>
<p>The Christmas season is often lost in commercialism, shopping and busyness. Even our well-intentioned family agendas can sometimes obscure the focus from the celebration that is God coming to dwell with man- Emmanuel, Christ with us. The foundation of the Christian Christmas celebration is the acknowledgement and honoring of first of all, God's gift to us in the person of His Son, Jesus. But wrapped within the story is the response of those people who left their own lives, countries and palaces to journey to see the true King. To hear of distant wisemen traveling to see Christ seems noble, but the above scripture should gather our attention.</p>
<p>The first response to being in the presence of Jesus was to bow down and to worship him. No pleasentries, no asking questions. Some of the wisest men of the ancient world could do nothing but fall down and worship in the presence of Jesus. This is the profound and honest response of the human being to the encounter person of Jesus.</p>
<p>The second response is also important- <em>"Then they opened their treasures and presented him with gifts</em>". What is your treasure right now? What do you value most? &nbsp;It is from that place of that we dare to draw forward our gifts to God.</p>
<p>As we think of worship, and of coming before Jesus, we can see that this bowing our wills and making an offering of love are both components. The token (or gift) we bring is less important than the heart from which it is offered. Still, have you considered whether or not your token of love truly represents your offering of humility and affection towards Christ?<br /><br />Perhaps a lackluster token represents correctly a lackluster attitude towards Christ and what worshipping him really means. Perhaps we need to examine our hearts and be challenged by the example of the wise men that, though meeting Jesus for the first time, gave him gifts of incredible value. Their hearts, likewise, matched those gifts. They spent 2 years (most scholars believe) traveling in search of Jesus.<br /><br />May our hearts be ready to worship Jesus with everything we have, for as long as we live!<br /><br /><em>Selah!&nbsp;<br />Kim Gentes</em></p>
<p><br /><span style="font-size: 75%;">The above scripture is Copyright &copy; 1973, 1978, 1984 by International Bible Society. All rights reserved.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-14037672.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>Twelve Tips of Christmas - 12 Tips for Men Shopping at Christmas (ThinkJump Journal #62 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Family</category><category>Giving</category><category>christmas</category><category>gifts</category><category>ideas</category><category>men</category><category>season</category><category>shopping</category><category>tips</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 07:15:26 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2011/12/3/twelve-tips-of-christmas-12-tips-for-men-shopping-at-christm.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:13954272</guid><description><![CDATA[<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/12tips.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1323108109625" alt="" /></span></span>It's the Christmas season and everyone is doing things in twelves. &nbsp;Here is a shout out to the guys shopping and some practical tips I've learned "the hard way". &nbsp;Hope they help!</p>
<p>If you have additional tips for your fellow man, feel free to post them below. I know there must be some great ideas out there others can share....&nbsp;</p>
<p>Here we go ...</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Tip #12</strong>: What is her favorite thing to do? Don't know? Find out. Pick something she loves, then gift around it.</p>
<p><strong>Tip #11</strong>: If you're completely locked up for ideas, try this- Her favorite romantic movie ever. BluRay. Amazon. Bam.</p>
<p><strong>Tip #10</strong>: Treat Christmas eve like the Apocalypse: you want to be plenty ready long before it arrives. Day of= CRAZY</p>
<p><strong>Tip #9</strong>: Gift cards are not generally considered "a thoughtful gift" when giving to your spouse. Exceptions apply.</p>
<p><strong>Tip #8</strong>: Don't press too hard when she is gone for an extra long time. She may have been shopping for you.</p>
<p><strong>Tip #7</strong>: When necessary, it's OK to offer one of your children as your replacement co-shopper while you stay home.</p>
<p><strong>Tip #6</strong>: The answer is "yes". Science tells us the ratio is: HerY = HisY * 10 where HerY=her yes, and HisY=his yes</p>
<p><strong>Tip #5</strong>: Plan to go to at least 2 extra stores beyond her promised number. Prepare for it mentally and be ready.</p>
<p><strong>Tip #4</strong>: Drink plenty of liquids. Keeps you hydrated, and a full bladder is a good excuse to leave any painful store.</p>
<p><strong>Tip #3</strong>: Malls rule. When given choice, go to malls rather than standalone stores. Malls have food &amp; sports scores.</p>
<p><strong>Tip #2</strong>: Trust her instincts! Sounds counter intuitive, but do it. Even if she's wrong, you'll save time not arguing!</p>
<p><strong>Tip #1</strong>: ABMTAE ! Which means- always be moving to an exit.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>out shopping at the moment,</em></p>
<p><em>Kim Gentes</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-13954272.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>Video Aesthetics In Worship: 7 Suggestions for Lyric Video Presentations (ThinkJump Journal #61 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Computers</category><category>Creative</category><category>Music</category><category>Nature</category><category>Resources</category><category>Sunday Services</category><category>Technology</category><category>Visual</category><category>Worship</category><category>aesthetics</category><category>backgrounds</category><category>icons</category><category>images</category><category>lyrics</category><category>presentation</category><category>software</category><category>video</category><category>visual</category><category>worship</category><category>worship leader</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 02:03:52 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2011/11/21/video-aesthetics-in-worship-7-suggestions-for-lyric-video-pr.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:13819051</guid><description><![CDATA[<div><span>I am a worship leader, pastor, artist and writer. It is from that perspective that I wanted to make some suggestions related to the use of video imagery, lyrics, fonts and colors. I seek to encourage participation, engagement, and functional utility in the use of any tools purposed in the course of our worship and gathered services. Recently, I had the pleasure of hearing seminar sessions on "<a class="offsite-link-inline" href="http://members.worshiptraining.com/courses/the-visual-worship-leader-projection/" target="_blank">the Visual Worship Leader</a>"&nbsp;from Dan Wilt and Nate Ragan. These two experts, along with VJ Stephen Proctor, have been primary influences in my practical understanding of how good aesthetics can be applied to video presentation in worship. Because of that, my comments herein are a good deal more rudimentary than a grand architecture of who, why, and what question/answers related to the topic. Instead, I wanted to give some thoughts from a worship pastor/leader who has an artistic eye, but a pastoral bent. If you want in depth training on visual worship leading, I would refer you to the aforementioned 3 gentlemen (and others they might recommend).</span><br /><br /><span><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/lukeworship.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1322547706182" alt="" /></span></span>That said, below are some points I have noted in my brain over the last several years, related to video presentation of lyrics during worship. These come in the light of an overwhelming push in modern worship settings to video presented lyrics with motion backgrounds, themed images and eye-catching marriages of lyric, music and imagery. These may stand in contexts which find themselves lost for sensibility in video lyric display. They may seem redundant to folks who already stress long and hard about making worship environments as un-distracting as possible. &nbsp;My primary goal with these points is just that- to remove the distraction that has become more commonplace with the use (and sometimes misuse) of video lyric presentation and backgrounds.</span><br /><br /><span>Again, these are just my suggestions. They will fit some contexts, some times, not all.</span><br /><br /><span><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/dwn-alpha.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1321981544402" alt="" /></span></span><strong>Use one background</strong>! Please consider utilizing the same image background for an entire worship set, Sunday or even a series of meetings. Choose a background that is subdued enough to present texture but not to draw attention too strongly away from the lyrics. Then make sure your chosen background works across a range of songs that you will use. Nothing can be more distracting that being jarred from one furious song background imagery into another. Creating a place of visual &ldquo;safety&rdquo; on the lyric presentation might be as simple as using the same background for an entire set. Using different backgrounds for each song or even segment of a song can become so distracting that people will reject looking at the video screen in hopes that they can worship by not being distracted by it- which all seems like the wrong thing to be happening if we are using visuals to help people in worship.</span><br /><br /><span><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/dwn-beta.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1321981564181" alt="" /></span></span><strong>Try using a maximum of two or three (2-3) lyric lines per screen</strong>. Using entire songs, stanzas or sections on a single screen can make the words small and unreadable. Using visual presentation technology should help people visually, not make it more difficult. Try to keep the fonts large and help everyone see the lyrics. The important thing to remember is that the <strong><em>lyrics</em></strong> are primary here, not the imagery or thematic nuances of the service. Ask yourself if the text is readable for everyone. Both font size and font type are important factors. Proper size will make the text readable. Proper font type will make it understandable. This is not the place to choose a fancy or artistic font. Stay well within common font types.</span><br /><br /><span><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/dwn-gamma.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1321981587142" alt="" /></span></span><strong>When it comes to color- Less is more! </strong>Try muted colors. Try fewer colors or shades of grey in background image/motion selections.&nbsp;Often black and white imagery is more profound and less intrusive than colored images. The rainbows and kaleidoscopic graphs may be all the rage in your fractal geometry class, but Sunday morning is probably not the place to force people to stand gaping at visions of psychedelic majesty. This is all in balance, and don't avoid color where it is perfect and well used in a themed approach. But remember- lyrics are king, not images or color. If your lyrics are served well with your use of color, you're on the right track.</span><br /><br /><span><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/dwn-delta.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1321981606766" alt="" /></span></span><strong>Less complete &ldquo;storyline&rdquo; movie loops</strong>- use more slow organic motion or even stills. It used to be inspiring to see the occasional background motion that followed the storyline of the lyrics. But after a thousand waterfalls, mountain scenes, and corny images of blue-screened people bowing at the edge digital ocean shores, we just might be at the end of needing to tell the story of the lyrics so literally with video. The important thing to remember here is that I am speaking to local churches, not conference settings and special events. On an occasional basis, engaging lyrical displays with motions and storylines can inspire, no doubt. But on a weekly basis, this becomes distracting, and ultimately takes the focus from the lyrics, which diminishes the message they contain. Subtlety is essential, humility is grace, less is more.</span><br /><br /><span><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/dwn-epsilon.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1321981728754" alt="" /></span></span><strong>Use icons well.</strong> &nbsp;I am the last one to suggest we use another tired image of a church steeple with clouds wafting above to backdrop a song lyric. But the excellent and proper use of icons continues to draw together good art, ideas, and tradition in our Christian communities. We&rsquo;ve all seen the tired backgrounds done with the equivalent of clip-art- those are out. But the powerful, fresh images of ancient icons such as crosses, candles, texts, sculptures, ancient paintings, architecture, stained glass and Eucharist elements still bring thousands of years of faith to bear in our present contexts. This is where great art can shine, but we must use it well and with elegance.</span><br /><br /><span><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/dwn-zeta.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1321981750718" alt="" /></span></span>God&rsquo;s icons - <strong>human images</strong>. After talking about icons, we can hardly ignore the icon God chose- human beings. A brief understanding of &ldquo;the imago dei&rdquo; brings us to the realization that no Biblical writer (or historical Christian leader of prominence) ignored the fact that God deals with us both in His story, and in ours. We are his image on earth. As we tell the story of His goodness and glory, our humanity is profoundly (and graciously) included, impacted as we are. All that to say- use more human images (especially black and whites stills) in our visual imagery for backgrounds. This is as authentic at describing the glory of God as images of nature and pictures. Using pictures of brokenness and grace, as seen in human lives, touches our songs in a powerful balance to other images. This is often missed.</span><br /><br /><span><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/dwn-eta.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1321981770532" alt="" /></span></span><strong>Sans background.</strong>&nbsp;Strip all the extras away. Leave just the lyric. Let it speak undistracted, and unaided. This is never a wrong way to do lyrics. Once in a while, just try this and see how refreshing it is, especially in situations where video presentation has become extensively artful. I have seen some of the most profound uses of video that are simply a nice, artful font in white, contrasted to a black background. Sounds simple. It is. And powerful.</span></div>
<div></div>
<div></div>
<div><br /><br /><span><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/dwn-theta.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1321983541355" alt="" /></span></span><strong>Sans everything</strong>! Woah. OK, so this is the 8th suggestion, but it is so revolutionary that it can't really be included in the "suggestions for lyric video presentation" list. What am I saying? Just this- shut off the lyric screen for a song. Do you really need to play the lyrics for "How Great Is Our God"? Really? Turn it off and let the congregation be free from the slavish devotion to a video screen and let them stand, sit, kneel, bow and honor their Creator without the "digital script" of the video calling them back to follow the dancing ball (please don't tell me anyone out there has a dancing ball on their lyrics). Seriously, folks, shut off the video presentation screen on occasion, and let people worship in song without the lyrics. It is surprisingly freeing.</span></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>I hope these suggestions for video lyric display are helpful as you consider good aesthetics in your own cultural/community contexts. My suggestions may not reflect your own situation, so don't feel tied to them. But perhaps they will work for some who find themselves caught in tired loops or lost in a maze of distracting "artistic" digital overload.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>Sincerely</em></p>
<p><em>Kim Gentes</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-13819051.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>Becoming The Liturgy with Ian Morgan Cron (ThinkJump Journal #60 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Church Fathers</category><category>Communion</category><category>Community</category><category>Eucharist</category><category>History</category><category>Leadership</category><category>Spiritual Disciplines</category><category>Sunday Services</category><category>Teaching</category><category>Theology</category><category>Worship</category><category>blood</category><category>bread</category><category>communion</category><category>cup</category><category>eucharist</category><category>ian cron</category><category>ian morgan cron</category><category>interview</category><category>liturgy</category><category>table</category><category>wine</category><category>worship leading</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 05:21:36 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2011/11/14/becoming-the-liturgy-with-ian-morgan-cron-thinkjump-journal.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:13727297</guid><description><![CDATA[<div><span id="internal-source-marker_0.32036894117482007"><em><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/communion.png?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1321334748787" alt="" /></span></span><strong>Is Liturgy Old, Dusty and Outdated? What is the value of a 2000 year old tradition in our modern society? Ultimately, is it relevant?</strong></em></span></div>
<div></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>For many people, the liturgy is the central constant of our devotional lives, indeed of our lives with Christ and in his church. But for those who are unsure of the present understanding of the liturgy, or the communion table, questions need to be addressed on its understanding and applicability. Instead of starting off with a deep historical and theological treatise on the subject, we will begin our discussion with a brief interview with author Ian Morgan Cron. Ian has some helpful things to say to bring our "modern church" misunderstanding into broader context regarding the liturgy.</p>
<p>Ian Morgan Cron is an author, speaker,&nbsp;Episcopal priest, and retreat facilitator is one of my favorite communicators recently, and we do well to start our discussion with hearing his unique perspective. Again, the purpose of the article is to unearth the issues and to begin talking about it. Please contribute to the discussion, post your thoughts, and get your local church leadership involved. It&rsquo;s an important issue that church leadership needs to consider.</p>
<div></div>
<div><span>Let&rsquo;s listen church, and then let&rsquo;s talk.</span></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div></div>
<div><span><strong>Becoming Liturgy - Ian Morgan Cron (Length 4min 57secs)</strong></span></div>
<div><iframe title="YouTube video player" width="550" height="342" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/OJCZwJiAA3U?rel=0&amp;hd=1" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Now, please, contribute your thoughtx below. This topic needs discussion and working out.</p>
<p>Again, many thanks to &nbsp;Ian Morgan Cron&nbsp;for spending time for these interviews. If you get a chance, I strongly encourage you to check out his books&nbsp;<a href="http://www.kimgentes.com/book-reviews/2011/4/1/chasing-francis-ian-morgan-cron-2006.html" target="_blank"><em>Chasing Francis: A Pilgrim's Tale</em></a>, and&nbsp;<em><a class="offsite-link-inline" href="http://amzn.to/scmZwC" target="_blank">Jesus, My Father, The CIA, and Me: A Memoir. . . of Sorts</a>. </em>I have read <em>Chasing Francis</em> and am now reading <em>Jesus, My Father, the CIA and Me</em>- both are excellent! A note of recognition to <a class="offsite-link-inline" href="http://www.theworkofthepeople.com" target="_blank">theworkofthepeople.com</a> who produced this video interview.</p>
<p><em>in Christ's love,</em></p>
<p><em>Kim Gentes</em></p>
<p><em><br /></em></p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-13727297.xml</wfw:commentRss></item><item><title>A Week on the Brentwood (ThinkJump Journal #59 with Kim Gentes)</title><category>Blog</category><category>Commitment</category><category>Diet</category><category>Food</category><category>Health</category><category>Nature</category><category>brentwood</category><category>celery</category><category>chicken</category><category>diet</category><category>food</category><category>health</category><category>lettuce</category><category>mushrooms</category><category>radish</category><category>salad</category><category>spinach</category><category>weight loss</category><dc:creator>Kim Gentes</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2011 02:49:48 +0000</pubDate><link>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/2011/10/7/a-week-on-the-brentwood-thinkjump-journal-59-with-kim-gentes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">157586:1471959:13118655</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>I thought I would share a recipe of a salad I made recently that I found particularly tasty, within the contraints of food choices I was making. I am not a dietician or medical professional, this recipe is simply given as an option for those who might be looking for something with this particular focus and blend of properties.</p>
<p>This last week I have been using a plan that focuses on changing eating mainly green vegetables, white chicken/fish meats, and some eggs for protein. The unique signature of this plan is that it allows for little to no consumption of salt, sugars (refined or natural), carbohydrates, fruits (which contain natural sugars), dairies or fats. This particular combination of do's and don'ts have become popularly known as the "Brentwood" diet, but it essentially is just a very healthful selection of food types to use and avoid for concentrated times to help break old habits and perhaps lose weight.</p>
<p>That list of abstained food types strikes deep into the core of our North American food habits, and for this person, it was a drastic change. &nbsp;The change didn't overwhelm me initially, since I've made changes to eating in the past over long periods of time (fasting etc). But once I began using the food regimen, I found a challenge.</p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/IMAG0720.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1318043956426" alt="" /></span></span>The first four days were mentally challenging due to the headaches from the body's reaction to the source changes in the food supply.</p>
<p>The real difficulty became not the body strain of the food change, or even my fortitude to sticking to a diet amidst temptation to eat regular tastey foods. Instead the real problem was that eating on my new regimen required me to eat 4 or 5 times a day. My plan broke down to breakfast of 3 scrambled eggs, lunch of salad, dinner with a chicken filet and more salad. This was fine, but I had to have another one or two smaller salads (of the same ingredient choices) in order to stay energized enough to continue my normal life. &nbsp;Maintaining a plentiful supply of good foods to eat is difficult. &nbsp;My solution- make a large salad and grilled chicken breasts each day, then eat off of it 2 or 3 times for the day.</p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-right ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/IMAG0711.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1318044358295" alt="" /></span></span>One of the best tasting recipes I built to fit in this plan is this healthy, tasty grilled chicken salad.</p>
<p>Start by chopping up the following:</p>
<ul>
<li>onions</li>
<li>green onions</li>
<li>radishes</li>
<li>cucumbers</li>
<li>celery</li>
<li>fresh mushrooms</li>
</ul>
<p>I took and put them in a container and placed them back into the fridge while I prepare the other items.</p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/IMAG0712.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1318044736951" alt="" /></span></span>Next, I took 3 skinless, boneless chicken breasts and chop them into bite-sized pieces. Using just a half tablespoon of extra virgin olive oil I cooked them in a non-stick skillet.</p>
<p>I am not a cook, so I have no idea how these things are normally done, but since I am not allowed to add any salt at this point, I wasn't really able to add any flavoring or other additives to it.</p>
<p>I cooked the chicken until it was almost done, basically white, but not charred or even brown.&nbsp;To add some variety, I added a bag of frozen peas to the mostly cooked chicken, and finished cooking the chicken and warming the peas together.</p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-right ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/IMAG0721.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1318045319497" alt="" /></span></span>Once finished, I used the largest salad bowl you have and add both a healthy portion of spinach greens and lettuce greens (I used romaine). Fill the bowl half way with greens, then add the previous chopped vegetables.</p>
<p>Toss the salad ingredients thus far, gently.</p>
<p>Finally, once that is ready, add the warm chicken and peas to the salad until it is a good balance/variety of the foods. You will likely have some chicken and peas remaining- keep those and add them later to the remaining salad base, and add more greens with them to make more of your already built salad base.</p>
<p><span class="full-image-float-left ssNonEditable"><span><img src="http://www.kimgentes.com/storage/IMAG0724.jpg?__SQUARESPACE_CACHEVERSION=1318045747796" alt="" /></span></span>I found this particular salad is very good tasting, especially when the chicken is still warm. I add a half teaspoon of balsamic vinegarette dressing to the salad meal on serving. This makes my meal enjoyable. &nbsp;The salad can be added to with the same ingredients and kept for a couple days. I loved it. I hope it helps you if you are using some similar techniques.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Again, this entry is simply a recipe explanation- not an endorsement of a food regimen or dietary suggestion of any kind. I hope you love it. I did!</p>
<p><em>good eating...</em></p>
<p><em>Kim Gentes</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description><wfw:commentRss>http://www.kimgentes.com/thinkjump-journal/rss-comments-entry-13118655.xml</wfw:commentRss></item></channel></rss>