<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/Sources/rss2html.xsl" version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Focus Podcast - Impact</title>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk</link>
<description>Some renowned experts help you present yourself to your 
                  colleagues, your directors, your clients, your shareholders 
                  ... and the rest of the world, discovering on the way the 
                  gentle art of business networking.</description>
<image>
<url>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/images/focusbizlogo.gif</url>
<title>Focus Podcasts</title>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk</link>
</image>
<copyright>Copyright 2006, FOCUS BUSINESS</copyright>
<language>en</language>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2006 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>

<item>
<title>Impact – Presentation and communication skills, Steve Jack</title>
<description>Steve Jack, European Marketing Director in the IT Industry. Steve believes that being able to present well is so vital to your success that it is a ‘career make-or-break’!  Luckily he really does know how to communicate and you will be delighted and grateful that you listened to him.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/steve02.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/steve02.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/steve02.mp3" length="7538323" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Voice - Enunciation and Modulation, Nuala O'Sullivan</title>
<description>30 percent plus of the impact of the presentation is via the voice. It needs variety and power for maximum impact.  Nuala O’Sullivan, from Westminster University, explains some of the top tips.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala01.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala01.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala01.mp3" length="535448" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Voice - Warming up, Nuala O'Sullivan</title>
<description>Crocky and weak voice? Not the best way to start a presentation.  Nuala O’sullivan, from Westminster University, explains exercises to help you warm up your voice.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala02.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala02.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala02.mp3" length="7542784" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Voice and Nerves, Nuala O'Sullivan</title>
<description>Nerves aren’t always a bad thing, especially if you know how to control them so they don’t get in the way of your message.  Nuala O’Sullivan, from Westminster University, has ways of helping you overcome those nerves.  You may even get to enjoy it!   Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala03.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala03.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala03.mp3" length="3844096" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>First Impressions, Nuala O'Sullivan</title>
<description>It’s those first few seconds that decide how people will respond.  Nuala O’Sullivan, from Westminster University, helps you make a really good first impression.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala04.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala04.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala04.mp3" length="4405248" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Audience rapport and interaction,Nuala O'Sullivan</title>
<description>If you can get the audience on your side, you’re more than half-way to getting your message across.  Nuala O’Sullivan, from Westminster University, has some valuable tips on how to build that rapport and interaction with your audience.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala05.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala05.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala05.mp3" length="7456768" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Sign-Posting, Nuala O'Sullivan</title>
<description>What does she mean by sign-posting?  How will it turn a boring presentation into something that people talk about for weeks?  Nuala O'Sullivan, from Westminster University, tells you all about the ways you can keep the attention of your audience. Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala06.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala06.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala06.mp3" length="7913472" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Handling Questions, Nuala O'Sullivan</title>
<description>Audience questions at the end of a presentation can be very intimidating.  Nuala O’Sullivan, from Westminster University, has some useful tips about how to handle them.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala07.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala07.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/nuala07.mp3" length="10662912" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Business Networking Tips, Mary Flavelle</title>
<description>If you’ve ever sat in your car, putting off going in to meet a bunch of strangers, then this is for you!  When you’ve heard Mary Flavelle, from The Thames Valley Chamber of Commerce, and her wonderful tips you won’t be able to wait till your first opportunity to try them out.  This will change your life!  Seriously.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.  </description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/networking01.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/networking01.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/networking01.mp3" length="8347648" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Structure, Adrian Moss</title>
<description>What’s your message?  It’s got a start, a middle and an end.   Jolly good.  Except there’s a little more to making a good presentation than that.  Let Adrian give you a few tips.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian01str.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian01str.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian01str.mp3" length="2342912" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Body Language, Adrian Moss</title>
<description>‘You can read them like a book!’  And you can probably tell how they are feeling about being there in front of an audience.  Adrian has some tips on how not to shuffle and cringe.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:20:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian02bl.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian02bl.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian02bl.mp3" length="3103744" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Verbal Language Style, Adrian Moss</title>
<description>It’s not necessarily what you say but the way that you say it.  Let Adrian give you some tips about the use of language.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:22:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian03ls.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian03ls.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian03ls.mp3" length="2798237" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Eye Contact, Adrian Moss</title>
<description>Reading an entire presentation from your notes without looking up, or reading from your slides with your back to the audience.  Either way is not the best way to make an impact.  Let Adrian give you some tips.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:24:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian04ec.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian04ec.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian04ec.mp3" length="3474072" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Jokes, Adrian Moss</title>
<description>A good joke to you may be totally tasteless to everyone else.  Besides it’s the way you tell ‘em!!  Take a tip from Adrian – telling jokes is a specialist business.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian05j.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian05j.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian05j.mp3" length="2532005" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Personal Image and Dress Sense, Adrian Moss</title>
<description>‘That tie!’ 'That blouse!'  Maybe you knew it was inappropriate and distracting, or worse still maybe you didn’t!  Adrian has some advice for the terminally inelegant. Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian06ds.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian06ds.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian06ds.mp3" length="3118389" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Using props, Adrian Moss</title>
<description>‘Never perform with children or animals!’  Maybe you should add computers … or anything else that might not work.  Take some tips from Adrian.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian07p.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian07p.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian07p.mp3" length="2882243" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Physical stance, Adrian Moss</title>
<description>You can stand there looking like a commander-in-chief … or you can look down-beat and dejected.  The choice is yours!!  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian08s.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian08s.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian08s.mp3" length="3128431" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Getting Ready, Adrian Moss</title>
<description>How do you prepare for your presentation?  They say that ‘Perfect planning prevents poor performance’ but does Adrian agree?  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian09gr.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian09gr.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian09gr.mp3" length="3712311" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>The Big Occasion, Adrian Moss</title>
<description>How do you handle the major event, the launch, the board meeting, the conference?  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian10bo.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian10bo.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian10bo.mp3" length="4009047" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Trigger words, Adrian Moss</title>
<description>Using ‘ trigger words’ effectively will make all the difference to the impact your presentation has on your audience.  Making an impact with your presentation and communication skills is vital if you want to succeed in business.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian11tw.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian11tw.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/impact/adrian11tw.mp3" length="3816377" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
