<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1252"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Insider Tips &amp; Hints: Walt Disney World, Universal Orlando and SeaWorld.</title>
    <description>Insider Tips &amp; Hints: Walt Disney World, Universal Orlando and SeaWorld is a series of podcasts covering a wide range of timely and interesting Orlando theme park topics. Where are the best places to go, the most exciting attractions to experience and when are the best times to do this without the biggest lines? Tune in, listen up and hear the latest about the attractions. The first-time Orlando visitor or the seasoned visitor will always find something new and interesting when they tune in. There will be occasional guest celebrities, lively conversations and interesting facts to make your time in Orlando the very best it can be. Subscribe to &amp;#147;Insider Tips &amp; Hints: Walt Disney World, Universal Orlando and SeaWorld&amp;#148; and don&amp;#146;t miss a single episode!</description>
    <link>http://www.floridaticketstation.com/Blog.aspx?Ad=iTunes</link>
    <copyright>Florida Ticket Station &amp;#169; 2007</copyright>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 7 May 2007 12:38:09 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 7 May 2007 12:30:18 -0400</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <generator>FeedForAll v1.0 (1.0.2.0)</generator>
    <item>
      <title>2007 Star Wars Weekends</title>
      <description>This informative and entertaining podcast is filled with great information about the Star Wars Weekends 2007. You will find descriptions of the event along with tons of general information and insider tips to make it a special experience. Also included in this podcast: interesting tidbits of information about some of the special events and notable high-points. Find information that will help you plan quality and interesting visits to this festival for your family and friends, with special tips to avoid long lines and pack more excitement into your visit.</description>
      <link>http://www.floridaticketstation.com/store/enews.aspx?id=487</link>
      <author>Lauren and Ryan</author>
      <comments>Interesting and helpful information about the annual and very popular 2007 Star Wars Weekends at Disney MGM Studios.</comments>
      <enclosure url="http://www.floridaticketstation.com/media/starwars2007.m4a" length="" type=""></enclosure>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.floridaticketstation.com/store/enews.aspx?id=487</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 7 May 2007 12:30:18 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2007 Epcot Flower and Garden Festival</title>
      <description>This informative podcast is filled with great information about the 2007 Epcot Flower and Garden Festival. You will find descriptions of the themes of each special weekend along with tons of general information. Also included in this podcast: interesting tidbits of information about some of the guest authors and speakers, special events and notable high-points. Find information that will help you plan quality and interesting visits to this festival for your family and friends, with special suggestions for Mother&apos;s Day, Memorial Day and much more. Also included is the celebrity entertainment rundown for the very popular Flower Power Concert Series.</description>
      <link>http://www.floridaticketstation.com/store/enews.aspx?id=474</link>
      <author>Lauren and Ryan</author>
      <comments>Interesting and helpful information about the annual and very popular 2007 Epcot Flower and Garden Festival that has been extended to 8 weeks this year!</comments>
      <enclosure url="http://www.floridaticketstation.com/media/EpcotFG07.m4a" length="" type=""></enclosure>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.floridaticketstation.com/store/enews.aspx?id=474</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Apr 2007 10:50:45 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Arabian Nights Dinner Theater</title>
      <description>This informative podcast is filled with great information about the Arabian Nights Dinner Theater, VIP Experience and pre-show. You will find descriptions of the Arabian Nights experience. Find information that will help you plan some quality Orlando entertainment time for your family and friends. Listen to this helpful information to get a jump-start on planning for a great night out with your family and friends</description>
      <link>http://secure.clubnavigo.com/store/c-19-bfreeb-podcasts.aspx</link>
      <enclosure url="http://www.floridaticketstation.com/media/arabiannights.m4a" length="11824996" type="audio/x-m4a"></enclosure>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://secure.clubnavigo.com/store/c-19-bfreeb-podcasts.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2007 13:46:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roller Coasters at Universal Orlando Florida and Islands of Adventure</title>
      <description>This podcast is filled with lots of insider tips and hints regarding many of the roller coasters and thrill rides at Universal Orlando. Some of this information is not generally well known but very helpful facts to know about the attractions. If you love thrill rides and coasters, this is the podcast to listen to before you plan your day at the park.</description>
      <link>http://secure.clubnavigo.com/store/c-19-bfreeb-podcasts.aspx</link>
      <enclosure url="http://secure.clubnavigo.com/images/rollercoaster%20podcast.m4a" length="5485657" type="audio/x-m4a"></enclosure>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://secure.clubnavigo.com/store/c-19-bfreeb-podcasts.aspx</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2006 13:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insider Tips &amp; Hints: Walt Disney World, Universal Orlando and SeaWorld.</title>
      <description>These podcasts will be filled with a wealth of helpful theme park information, time-saving and money-saving tips for both the Orlando visitors and residents who love Orlando&amp;#146;s world famous attractions.</description>
      <link>http:///www.floridaticketstation.com</link>
      <enclosure url="http://www.floridaticketstation.com/media/podcast.m4a" length="5420000" type="audio/x-m4a"></enclosure>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.floridaticketstation.com/media/podcast.m4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2006 13:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
