<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>The Movie Hour</title>
  <link>http://www.gungapit.com/phpBB3/</link>
  <description>Join Greg and friends in the discussion of everything about movies.  Each Wednesday they spend a hour pointing out exactly how bias they can be. No film or actor is safe from their scrutiny.  Files are about 20MB each in mp3 form.</description>
  <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 04:43:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  <generator>ListGarden Program 1.3.1</generator>
  <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
  <item>
   <title>The George Lucas That's No Moon, It's a Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/georgelucas.mp3</link>
   <description>The Gang comes together to review their Memorial weekend experiences and the latest Hollywood has to offer.  They start off with a nod to George Lucas's comments and move on to The Great Gatsby trailer.  Greg offers up the latest and greatest Parker Posey's Play Along.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/georgelucas.mp3" length="37417489" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 04:43:18 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/georgelucas.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Stephen Tobolowsky Groundhog Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/stephentobolowsky.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour world gets turned upside down this week starting with a quiz from Jeff. The master of goblins joins the Gang from out West to share his knowledge with the world and Jim brings us our latest Parker Posey's Play Along.&lt;br>Enjoy your weekend everyone!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/stephentobolowsky.mp3" length="46581058" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 15:44:33 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/stephentobolowsky.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Nothing Rhymes With Kevin Costner Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kevincostner.mp3</link>
   <description>With another week down, &quot;The Avengers&quot; continues to murder the box office. Greg addresses the numbers and Jim gives his two cents on the movie.  As usual, Jeff does everything Greg tells him to do and ventures forth to see &quot;Cabin in the Woods&quot;.  Jeff also produces the vengeful  PPPA. Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kevincostner.mp3" length="32698350" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 14:24:35 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kevincostner.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Scarlett Johansson Translation Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/scarlettjohansson.mp3</link>
   <description>After a wrecking breaking weekend, &quot;The Avengers&quot; throws itself into the show.  The Gang starts off with some box office talk and predictions for the latest Batman movie.  Greg gives us a spoil free review of &quot;The Avengers&quot; and Jeff reviews the American version of &quot;The Girl With the Dragon Tattoo&quot;.  Greg brings the PPPA, Jim brings the watermelon.  Thank you for listening!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/scarlettjohansson.mp3" length="38892726" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2012 05:04:45 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/scarlettjohansson.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Wallace Shawn's Princess Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/wallaceshawn.mp3</link>
   <description>The Gang brings you the Summer preview for 2012. Even though Hollywood is regurgitating the last twenty years on the silver screen there is still some good to be found in the wreckage. Get your calendars ready to mark what movies to watch out for in the coming months. James has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/wallaceshawn.mp3" length="62059928" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 18:19:44 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/wallaceshawn.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Vince Vaughn, Mow My Lawn Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/vincevaughn.mp3</link>
   <description>With Hollywood almost into the summer blockbuster season, the Gang starts off with the resignation of Disney's Film division. Jeff and Greg give glowing reviews of &quot;Tinker, Tailor, Soldier, Spy&quot; and &quot;The Cabin in the Woods&quot; respectively. Jeff produces the PPPA and Greg fails.  Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/vincevaughn.mp3" length="38464091" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 21:23:35 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/vincevaughn.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Emily Blunt Wild Hunt Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/emilyblunt.mp3</link>
   <description>With Jeff's return from London, the Gang talks the latest news.  Anchorman 2, Piranha 3DD, and a new Prometheus &quot;trailer&quot; all get a nod.  Jeff reviews a slew of movies including &quot;The Guard&quot; and James reviews &quot;Water for Elephants&quot;.  Greg brings us a materialistic PPPA.  Thank you for listening!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/emilyblunt.mp3" length="44244828" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 02:53:47 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/emilyblunt.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The William Hootkins Raiders of the Lost Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/williamhootkins.mp3</link>
   <description>In a break from the norm, Greg and James host the show with Mr. Josh.  They talk a little Disney World and then discuss the recent lull of Hollywood releases.  James reviews &quot;The Boy in the Stripped Pajamas&quot; and brings us a Title Mash-up Quiz.  Josh joins us late in the game for the quiz and James Parker Posey Play Along.  Thank you all for listening!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/williamhootkins.mp3" length="57142262" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 21:28:01 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/williamhootkins.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Benicio Del Toro's Neighbor Totoro Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/beniciodeltoro.mp3</link>
   <description>Greg and the Gang bring in special guests Davey and Jarv to finally put to rest the legendary IMDB Top 250 list.  Jim walks us through the highlights and pitfalls as we discuss their list and it's features.  Afterwards, Greg reviews &quot;21 Jump Street&quot; and Jim discusses &quot;Game Change&quot; and &quot;Wrath of the Titans&quot;.  Jeff brings us a memorable PPPA answered by the entire cast of the show.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/beniciodeltoro.mp3" length="64173373" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 03:53:54 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/beniciodeltoro.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>A Jennifer Connelly Beautiful Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jenniferconnelly.mp3</link>
   <description>The Gang delivers with a full spoiler-free discussion of The Hunger Games. Jeff talks about Never Let Me Go and guest host Zale comes back with a review of Take Shelter.  Greg delivers and darker fantastical PPPA for this week's podcast.  Thank you all for listening and enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jenniferconnelly.mp3" length="44917976" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 00:47:35 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jenniferconnelly.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Frank Whaley's Field of Movie Hours</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/frankwhaley.mp3</link>
   <description>The Lorax, The Hunger Games, The Boys Are Back, Zale guest stars and GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS GREG WINS. Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/frankwhaley.mp3" length="55594534" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 19:53:27 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/frankwhaley.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Bryan Cranston Haunted Mansion Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/bryancranston.mp3</link>
   <description>After a week's rest, the Gang is in full swing.  Greg brings a review of &quot;The Secret World of Arrietty&quot; and brings more warnings of clappers at the movies.  James talks about &quot;A Man For All Seasons&quot; and being one movie away from finishing his neverending-list.  Meanwhile, Jeff talks &quot;The Debt&quot; and brings us the latest and greatest Parker Posey's Play Along.  Josh guest stars.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/bryancranston.mp3" length="39671298" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 04:58:29 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/bryancranston.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Jack Palance Number One Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jackpalance.mp3</link>
   <description>Hopefully everyone survived the Oscar weekend and is ready to discus more random movie happenings.  The full Gang is back with a positive review of broadcast. Greg throws a shout out to Studio Ghibli once again and reviews &quot;Wanderlust&quot;.  James reviews the original &quot;Slueth&quot; while Jeff has another Campari. Greg has our Oscar inspired PPPA. Enjoy your weekend!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jackpalance.mp3" length="45493663" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 02:27:32 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jackpalance.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Ronny Cox Robo-Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ronnycox.mp3</link>
   <description>No one is safe in this week's episode.  Greg is having a bad day and decides to bring everyone down to his level.  The Gang is sans a Jeff and avec a Josh for their discussion of the Oscars, &quot;Grace is Gone&quot;, and this week's quiz.  After some last minute advice for the Academy, the show is wrapped up with a James PPPA.  Enjoy the Oscars everyone!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ronnycox.mp3" length="46205002" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 19:59:23 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ronnycox.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Jeff Goldblum Face Your Doom Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jeffgoldblum.mp3</link>
   <description>The latest and greatest in the Movie Hour Saga comes with some extra Detroit excitement.  The Gang discusses a little Red Wings, Ghost Rider and Star Wars during the HHHH. Greg talks about &quot;Safe House&quot; and Ryan Reynolds. Meanwhile, James reviews &quot;Ondine&quot; and Jeff mopes in the corner.  The Parker Posey Play Along is Jeff's for the week.  Let's hope he treats her with the respect she deserves.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jeffgoldblum.mp3" length="34634472" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 03:24:25 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jeffgoldblum.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Phoebe Cates 2: The New Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/phoebecates.mp3</link>
   <description>A big, totally sweet, happy birthday to brother James this episode!  The Gang hashes out the past few days and talks film Superbowl ads. They review Oscar nominated &quot;Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close&quot; and Greg tries his hand at a quiz concerning this less spoken for Hollywood screenwriter.  Greg then pops off a PPPA that will be heard around the world.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/phoebecates.mp3" length="62250213" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 21:31:22 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/phoebecates.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Robert Davi Die Hard Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/robertdavi.mp3</link>
   <description>The gang returns for it's latest installment of quizzes and reviews. Greg talk about &quot;The Descendants&quot; and it's Oscar chances. James brings back the movie quote quiz and Jeff brings back his A game. James has this weeks PPPA. Good luck to &quot;Bewildered in Boulder&quot;</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/robertdavi.mp3" length="45670396" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 19:08:30 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/robertdavi.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Timothy Olyphant What Do You Want Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/timothyolyphant.mp3</link>
   <description>Since the world is abuzz with Oscar talk, The Movie Hour team decides to take it seriously.  After all jokes are in Greg reviews &quot;Underworld: Awakenings&quot;, Jim talks &quot;MicMacs&quot; and Jeff dissects &quot;Another Earth&quot;.  Jeff brings us our latest Parker Posey Play Along!  Thank you for listening.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/timothyolyphant.mp3" length="37454945" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 06:09:04 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/timothyolyphant.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Angus MacFayden I Don't Want To Lose Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/angusmacfayden.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour brings up the latest in the Holly Hunter's Hollywood Hoopla and review a slew of movies in this week's episode.  Jeff talks &quot;Limitless&quot; and &quot;Superheroes&quot; while James and Greg discuss &quot;Micmacs&quot; and &quot;We Bought a Zoo&quot; respectively. Josh guest stars and is the ultimate cool. Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/angusmacfayden.mp3" length="51575603" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 20:06:55 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/angusmacfayden.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The James Tolkan Masters of the Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jamestolkan.mp3</link>
   <description>Moving past the Lions loss, Greg assembles the Movie Hour team for another round of film discussion.  James sponsors the episode with a quiz, a review of The French Connection, and a quiz.  Jeff is mysteriously absent until a last minute phone call to enter the quiz competition.  Josh guest stars.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jamestolkan.mp3" length="31939750" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 00:44:33 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jamestolkan.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Jude Law Win, Lose, or Draw Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judelaw.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour team comes in big in 2012.  With a slew of New Year's stories to get through, Greg explains the celebration and James and Jeff bring the movie reviews.  They discuss Mission Impossible : Ghost Protocol, The Artist, Winnebago Man, and Dear Zachary: A Letter To A Son About His Father.  Jeff then reveals he finally watched a classic movie!  He then brings in the first PPPA of 2012.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judelaw.mp3" length="41368328" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 06:53:48 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judelaw.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Rick Moranis Honey I Shrunk The Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rickmoranis.mp3</link>
   <description>Happy New Year's everyone!  The Movie Hour wraps up 2011 with a series of movie reviews including Sherlock Holmes: A Game of Shadows, Midnight in Paris, and Carnage.  Guest host Michelle makes an appearance with a Greg Maloney PPPA.  Thank you everyone for listening this past year and beyond.  It has been a pleasure helping you pass the time and hopefully learn a thing or two in the process.  Enjoy 2012!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rickmoranis.mp3" length="36873879" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 02:42:28 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rickmoranis.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Richard Dawson's Family Feud Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson3.mp3</link>
   <description>It's the time of year to come together and challenge our movie wits with The Movie Hour's version of Family Feud!  The Ewing family(led by Greg) and the Huxtable family(led by Jeff) go head-to-head in this year's showdown. Quizmaster James lines up the trivia for our ten-person show.  It's been a fantastic year and all of us here at the Gunga Pit studios wishes you and your family a very merry Christmas. Enjoy the Feud!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson3.mp3" length="49096800" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 01:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson3.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Lee Marvin's The Dirty Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/leemarvin.mp3</link>
   <description>Tis' almost the season! The Movie Hour team show their high spirits while they relish in the latest news on &quot;Indiana 5&quot;.  Jim brings up his thoughts on Moneyball and Jeff reviews Unknown. Greg, Jeff, and guest host Josh go head-to-head in Jim's latest quiz. One last reminder, join us for our Family Feud episode on December 18th, 4PM EST.  Also, a special happy birthday to Teddy!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/leemarvin.mp3" length="60975984" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 00:38:49 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/leemarvin.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Shia Labeouf Raise the Roof Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/shialabeouf.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang rolls up their sleeves and wrap up a series of reviews.  The Muppet Gods please James and Greg and Hugo comes in a close second.  Jeff recalls his viewing of 30 Minutes or Less with less fondness.  Jeff brings us a Holiday themes PPPA and Josh joins us from out west.  A podcast to be remembered for years to come. Don't forget to join us for The Family Feud episode on December 18th! Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/shialabeouf.mp3" length="55927968" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:37:02 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/shialabeouf.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Peter Stormare Nihilistic Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/peterstormare.mp3</link>
   <description>After Thanksgiving rolls by, the Movie Hour meets to discuss matters of our pop culture.  Greg fulfills an old promise to watch Fargo and talks Coen brothers. Jeff and James review Crazy, Stupid, Love and In Time respectively. The Parker Posey Play Along is provided by Greg and guest host Josh shows up late from the West Coast. Coming up: reviews of Hugo and The Muppets.  Our Family Feud episode will be recorded on December 18th, see the gungapit.com for details!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/peterstormare.mp3" length="52114893" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 01:46:33 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/peterstormare.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The James Dean Rebel Without A Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jamesdean.mp3</link>
   <description>With a plethora of live listeners, the Movie Hour Gang gets serious. After a brief revisit to Netflix, they discuss some Twilight: Breaking Dawn and Black Friday Blu-ray sales. James and Greg review Ides of March and The Cove respectively while Jeff rehashes Gran Torino. James brings a quiz that results in one of the closest races to date and then provides the PPPA. Josh joins us from the West Coast. Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jamesdean.mp3" length="57627743" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 23:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jamesdean.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Mena Suvari, I'm So Sorry Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/menasuvari.mp3</link>
   <description>This week's episode shows Greg as his usual upset self.  The Gang talks about the recent state of affairs with the latest Twilight and Jeff's Oscar host prediction.  Things turn ugly for Greg when Jeff brings this weeks PPPA. Enjoy the show and thanks for listening!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/menasuvari.mp3" length="30386562" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 00:53:27 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/menasuvari.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Seymour Cassel Christmas Time Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/seymourcassel.mp3</link>
   <description>The Gang is back in studios to bring you their latest opinions on the Oscar host juggling and the general state of affairs.  Jeff gives a friendly review of Bridesmaids and Greg brings up the latest weekly question the Parker Posey Play Along.  Come for the laughs, stay for the laughs.  Enjoy your day!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/seymourcassel.mp3" length="26457580" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 01:41:55 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/seymourcassel.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Bela Lugosi's Plan 9 From the Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/belalugosi.mp3</link>
   <description>Still recovering from Halloween festivities, The Movie Hour crew returns to talk about their Trick 'r Treat experiences.  Greg talks about his celebrity experience while James reviews Solitary Man and then follows up with another amazing Title Mash-Up quiz.  Gust host Josh joins the team for another epic episode of The Movie Hour.  Thanks for listening.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/belalugosi.mp3" length="49481881" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 18:47:09 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/belalugosi.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Amanda Peet Trick 'r Treat Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/amandapeet.mp3</link>
   <description>There aren't enough words in the dictionary to explain the awesomeness that lies within this episode.  You'll hear reviews of Land of the Dead and Paul W.S. Anderson's Three Musketeers.  Guest host Karyn brings a spooky tagline quiz to the table and Jeff presents the Holiday themed quiz.  Enjoy your Halloween everyone and thank you for listening to the Movie Hour!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/amandapeet.mp3" length="56396776" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 02:33:09 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/amandapeet.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Michael Biehn Silver Screen Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelbiehn.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang's hate for Netflix is spreading.  Jeff regales us with his experience of the Book of Eli and special guest Josh joins in just in time for a Halloween themed PPPA.  Prepare thyself for next week with featuring another one of our favorite guest hosts Karyn.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelbiehn.mp3" length="35751115" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 07:37:04 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelbiehn.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Burt Lancaster's From Here to The Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/burtlancaster.mp3</link>
   <description>It has been a fantastic ride here at The Movie Hour and we thank you all for your support over the years.  During this monumental episode we discuss Netflix's terrible apology letter and Lion King in 3-D.  Greg reviews the German film North Face and Jeff brings in the hate with Wall Street 2.  James invents a new quiz that will have you shouting answers.&lt;br>Josh guest stars.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/burtlancaster.mp3" length="56361269" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 03:58:08 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/burtlancaster.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Meryl Streep You're a Creep Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/merylstreep.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang comes together to talk about friends of the show and the continuing lack of movie fun.  Greg apologizes for all his mistakes and then makes another one.  The torment will not end for our hero host.  Enjoy your week and have a happy Movie Hour.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/merylstreep.mp3" length="34843609" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2011 20:09:42 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/merylstreep.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Meryl Streep You're a Creep Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/merylstreep.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang comes together to talk about friends of the show and the continuing lack of movie fun.  Greg apologizes for all his mistakes and then makes another one.  The torment will not end for our hero host.  Enjoy your week and have a happy Movie Hour.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/merylstreep.mp3" length="" type="" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2011 20:09:33 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/merylstreep.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Tim Roth's Honey Bunny Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/timroth.mp3</link>
   <description>With Jeff's recent quiz success getting to his head, he leaves Greg and James to billboard the rest of the year's movies.  They call  Mr. Josh and Josh in for reinforcements.  You'll hear movie reviews on Scott Pilgrim vs The World and Panic.  Then they spell out the highlights, or lack there of, for the rest of the movie year.  Enjoy your day!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/timroth.mp3" length="64990461" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 02:27:11 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/timroth.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Liz Taylor's Who's Afraid of the Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/liztaylor.mp3</link>
   <description>After surviving hurricane Irene, Jeff goes head to head with Greg over James' latest quiz.  Not before reviews of Our Idiot Brother and Red come into the picture.  You won't like what Greg has to say.  James has a PPPA that the whole family will enjoy.  More info on James quiz at gungapit.com.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/liztaylor.mp3" length="62326879" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 04:57:24 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/liztaylor.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Hugo Weaving, Now I'm Leaving Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/hugoweaving.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour break their usual mold with James pulling out a Pop Quiz while Greg waxes philosophically about the film Coraline.  Still standing in disgust of Hollywood's lack of effort, Jeff releases the latest PPPA.  Enjoy your movie-filled day and take a minute to visit gungapit.com</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/hugoweaving.mp3" length="34127196" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 15:31:19 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/hugoweaving.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>John Goodman's Arachnophobic Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johngoodman.mp3</link>
   <description>After a brief expedition at a four star resort, the Movie Hour Gang returns two weeks later with shocking news.  Hollywood has produced absolutely nothing in the last few weeks and Greg has a sad.  Take a listen this week since James may succumb to his wounds by next week.  Enjoy!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johngoodman.mp3" length="29381074" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 19:49:11 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johngoodman.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Walter Matthau's Grumpy Old Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/waltermatthau.mp3</link>
   <description>This week's podcast features an erudite review of Cowboys and Aliens, another comprehensive look at box office wonder Captain America, and a look into last year's Cedar Rapids. Quizmaster James pitches another great quiz, and Parker Posey's Play Along is strong as ever.  &lt;br>&lt;br>Download now and we'll throw in free shipping!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/waltermatthau.mp3" length="57546595" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 23:52:52 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/waltermatthau.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Dan Hedaya I Am Not a Crook Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/danhedaya.mp3</link>
   <description>After a long weekend, The Movie Hour comes back more sober than ever.  This afternoon recording featured Jeff's review of Captain America: The First Avenger and James discusses The Sweet Hereafter.  Next Week: drunken talk of Cowboys &amp;amp; Aliens.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/danhedaya.mp3" length="44538911" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 19:08:31 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/danhedaya.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Kelly MacDonald Is My Favorite Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kellymacdonald.mp3</link>
   <description>The Gang fights over Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows : Part 2.  Harry Potter Harry Potter Harry Potter Harry Potter Harry Potter Harry Potter Harry Potter Harry Potter Harry Potter Harry Potter Harry Potter Harry Potter Harry Potter and a PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kellymacdonald.mp3" length="54634100" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 21:12:23 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kellymacdonald.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Alec Guinness' Movie Hour on the River Kwai</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/alecguinness.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour gets pissed.  The Gang drops their Netflix sponsorship, talk Oldboy remakes, and rip on Harry Potter wannabes.  James reviews Horrible Bosses and Jeff* talks The Adjustment Bureau.  After a quiz and the PPPA, will Greg cheer up?  </description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/alecguinness.mp3" length="60544047" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 14:29:21 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/alecguinness.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The James Spader Now or Later Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jamesspader.mp3</link>
   <description>The Gang reunites with Jeff and creates a podcast that will go down in history.  They start off with recognizing the sovereign country of Canada and continue to the movie reviews.  Knight &amp;amp; Day, Barney's Version, and Bowling for Columbine.  Jeff brings his first PPPA in weeks and there may have been some G.R.R. martin talk.  Thank you for listening!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jamesspader.mp3" length="49597080" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 05:54:30 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jamesspader.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Michael Bay's Giant American Flag Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelbay.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang slowly recovers from a week of adventure.   Jeff is missing in the Canadian North but Josh comes to the rescue. They talk Comic Con's, Lord of the Rings, Pixar, and of course, Michael Bay.  After short reviews of Black Death, Mega Mind, and the Wicker Man, Greg brings us a depressing PPPA.  Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelbay.mp3" length="47343907" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 16:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelbay.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Gregory Peck's To Kill A Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/gregorypeck.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang launches into the summer with remakes and sequels.  They dissect the recent Muppets trailer and take a look at the latest madness that they call &quot;Footloose&quot;.  The Gang then talks Green Lantern and whether 200 million dollars is worth seeing.  This episode features Mr. Josh and his first PPPA.  Thanks for listening.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/gregorypeck.mp3" length="59612533" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 19:57:53 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/gregorypeck.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Diane Lane Choo-Choo Train Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/dianelane.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang talk the latest Hoopla including Risk and the Academy's new rules for Best Picture.  Jeff finally discovers Time Bandits and James reviews the latest Super 8.  Greg brings us the real deal PPPA.  Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/dianelane.mp3" length="31154530" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 02:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/dianelane.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Sean Bean Seldom Seen Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/seanbean.mp3</link>
   <description>After a week hiatus, the Movie Hour rallies the troops. The Gang brings in Josh and discuss Broken Lizard and the death of physical media. They then review X-Men: First Class and Fair Game. The Parker Posey Play Along falls to Josh for the first time. Enjoy the show and KIT!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/seanbean.mp3" length="40539977" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2011 02:36:08 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/seanbean.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Gene Kelly's Singin' in the Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/genekelly.mp3</link>
   <description>As the Gunga Pit is in a state of mourning over the loss of the Macho Man himself, the Gang still finds a way to bring the laughs.  With another special guest Mr. Josh, they talk Pirates 4, Appaloosa, and Oscar bait.  This episode also features a 3-way race to the top of Jim's Movie Trivia Mountain.  There can only be one...enjoy the show.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/genekelly.mp3" length="66172414" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 04:29:25 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/genekelly.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Michael Madsen Madhouse Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelmadsen.mp3</link>
   <description>Bring in the ladies!  The Movie Hour recruits extra opinions while Jeff is away.  Josh calls in from the West coast and we welcome for the first time Madame Karyn.  The Gang then reviews Thor in detail, then comment on The Road and the bizarre Fantastic Planet.  Karyn brings up a fresh PPPA that almost stumped the show.  Thanks for listening! Tip your waiter.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelmadsen.mp3" length="55711506" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 00:23:38 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelmadsen.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Woody Allen’s Analyst Says Listen to the Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/woodyallen.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour goes through the Hollywood ramblings of the week.  You'd be surprised who leads box office numbers for the year and what movie Jim target's with his review.  Kudos to the Red Wings and the Avatar series for making Jim's week.  There's a lot of Jim in this episode.  Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/woodyallen.mp3" length="35139474" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 18:08:43 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/woodyallen.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Audrey Hepburn's Breakfast at the Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/audreyhepburn.mp3</link>
   <description>After lamenting about the Red Wings, The Movie Hour Gang discusses a slew of movies.  Jim reviews the Indie film Rubber while Jeff talks Cyrus.  They revisit a couple other movies before tackling Jim's new quiz.  Anything can happen with Greg, Jeff, and newcomer Josh fighting for the number one spot.  It's another crazy day inside the Gunga Pit Studios.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/audreyhepburn.mp3" length="51649362" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 01:22:03 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/audreyhepburn.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Donald Sutherland Loves Us All Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/donaldsutherland.mp3</link>
   <description>With summer blockbusters quickly approaching, the gang comes together to spell out which ones are worth their salt.  Jeff talks Tribeca will James and Greg review Breaking and Entering and Ghost in the Shell respectively.  Special guests include Josh and 10,000 Maniacs.  Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/donaldsutherland.mp3" length="59466191" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 03:11:22 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/donaldsutherland.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Hayden Christensen Stole My Innocence Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/haydenchristensen.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour gang reunites with Jeff for a flurry of film-talk.  We talk reviews and the PPPA and even bring Josh back to talk spring break.  Go Red Wings and enjoy the podcast of the week!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/haydenchristensen.mp3" length="36524038" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 02:29:36 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/haydenchristensen.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Jimmy Stewart's It's A Wonderful Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jimmystewart.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour breaks yet another record with two guests on the show to talk tinsel town. Greg and James walk Jim P and Josh through the HHHH and a new quiz. We review a spectrum of movies with Source Code, Grave of the Fireflies, and The Human Centipede. Jim P get's the honor of asking the PPPA this week. Thank you all for playing along and making the show what it is, a gauntlet of success.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jimmystewart.mp3" length="61475178" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2011 18:54:53 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jimmystewart.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Honorable Judge Reinhold Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judgereinhold2.mp3</link>
   <description>It's the Movie Hour like you've never seen it before.  The Gang adds a friend to the film discussion.  They check in with the Sci-Fi March Madness bracket and go through a slew of reviews, including Rango, Waiting for Superman, and The Lottery.  It's Spring Break in Michigan.  Look out for Jeff exposure.  Thanks for listening.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judgereinhold2.mp3" length="45807730" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 04:20:17 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judgereinhold2.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Nicholas Cage Coke-Fueled Rage Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nickcage.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Team revisits the Sci-Fi March Madness bracket before they talk a little Wes Anderson.  James leaps into the past with a review of Fellini's 8 1/2.  Greg gives a thorough handling on Sucker Punch just before Jeff's PPPA.  It's another beautiful day in the Movie Hour.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nickcage.mp3" length="46441098" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 15:52:02 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nickcage.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Karl Malden's Street Car Named The Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/karlmalden.mp3</link>
   <description>Too many things to discuss in such little time.  The Movie hour revisits this so called &quot;sci-fi movie bracket&quot;.  Jeff and Greg explain the documentary 'Why We Fight' and Jim follows in Greg's footsteps with a review of 'Ponyo'.  We have one of the longest quizzes to date and the PPPA.  Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/karlmalden.mp3" length="69753570" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 17:34:51 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/karlmalden.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Michael Gambon's Irish Poem Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelgambon.mp3</link>
   <description>Happy St. Patrick's Day everyone! The Movie Hour team is in full spirits and take some time to share their thoughts on the recent hoopla.  Reviews fall on Withnail and I, and Dirty Pretty Things.  Things start turning green with a limerick poetry slam.  Drinks are on us, enjoy!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelgambon.mp3" length="41186620" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 18:34:57 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelgambon.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Robert Deniro You're My Hero Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/robertdeniro.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang wastes no time with idle threats.  After Nerd in a Show references we talk movie reviews.  Helvetica and My Neighbor Totoro share the spotlight while Jim plays with Bridget Jones's Diary.  We draw comparisons between Disney and Hayao Miyazaki and wrap up with a fitting PPPA.  You are all the best! Thank you for listening.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/robertdeniro.mp3" length="39923057" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 02:18:48 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/robertdeniro.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Natalie Wood's West Side Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nataliewood.mp3</link>
   <description>The Oscars have passed but not without final inspection by yours truly.  We provide insight, intrigue, and much needed class to the awards show and quickly move on to greater things.  James provides a new quiz.  Jeff and Greg discover they need to become temporary allies in this war against trivia.  Let's hope no one gets hurt.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nataliewood.mp3" length="60533743" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 17:35:19 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nataliewood.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Alan Ruck Has Run Amok Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/alanruck.mp3</link>
   <description>Jeff returns in time to dispense justice.  He weighs in on movies from last week and catches up with movie reviews In The Loop, Death at a Funeral(2007), and How to Train Your Dragon.  Then we attack the Oscars and follow up with a special Oscars Parker Posey's Play Along.  </description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/alanruck.mp3" length="32389936" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 23:38:17 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/alanruck.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Teri Hatcher Atom Smasher Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/terihatcher.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour gang is one short.  Jeff spontaneously combusted and left the serious business of film podcasting to the Maloney Brothers.  They chime in on the noteworthy movies on the way from Hollywood.  James reviews 'The Great Buck Howard' while Greg almost closes the chapter on his Hayao Miyazaki saga.  Jeff sends in his PPPA from the afterlife. Happy Birthday Jim P.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/terihatcher.mp3" length="39118514" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 02:08:12 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/terihatcher.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Jack Lemmon Likes It Hot Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jacklemmon.mp3</link>
   <description>During tonight's episode we observe the birthday of Quiz Master James.  Then we have the reviews of Green Hornet, Inside Man, Blue Valentine, and The Secret In Their Eyes.  Greg apologizes for failing on yet another quiz while Jeff continues his tyrannical reign.  Happy birthday shout-outs to everyone and enjoy the show.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jacklemmon.mp3" length="58055385" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:56:25 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jacklemmon.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Gary Busey and the Order of the Phoenix Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/garybusey.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour has attracted a long history of key Hollywood players, probably none as important as Friend of the Show Gary Busey.  We honor his name with reviews of Tron, The Fighter, and The Good, The Bad, and the Ugly.  The PPPA and HHHH all make appearances in this episode of The Movie Hour series.  Stay warm.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/garybusey.mp3" length="45031280" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 04:20:06 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/garybusey.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Liam Neeson One Good Reason Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/liamneeson.mp3</link>
   <description>It's another special day in the world of movies.  The Movie Hour discusses the Oscar hype and chime in on more of the weekly news.  We review Exit Through the Gift Shop and Rescue Dawn.  Then join us for Parker Posey's Play Along. Thank you for listening!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/liamneeson.mp3" length="40016591" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 06:51:52 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/carygrant.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Cary Grant All-Star Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/carygrant.mp3</link>
   <description>After the Gang talks Golden Globes, we move to important issues like Expendables 2 and the Governator.  After a month off, Quiz-master James put Greg and Jeff through the gauntlet with a quiz.  James launches the next PPPA and reveals who the true genius is.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/carygrant.mp3" length="17772171" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 06:16:32 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/carygrant.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Nick Nolte's Happy Birthday Jeff Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nicknolte.mp3</link>
   <description>Today we celebrate many things, one of which is our illustrious co-host's birthday.  We talk Ghosbusters 3, movie reviews, and a completely awesome PPPA.  Celebrate with us with a few laughs, a couple of drinks, and many happy returns.  Enjoy the show.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nicknolte.mp3" length="15255642" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:56:44 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nicknolte.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Catherine Zeta Jonestown Massacre Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/catherinezetajones.mp3</link>
   <description>The Gunga Pit Studios have opened up for 2011 business.  The Gang talks tough, then the discussion goes serious with Black Swan and True Grit reviews.  We also talk IMAX, how does that work? Happy 2011 all and welcome back to the podcast.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/catherinezetajones.mp3" length="18783209" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 07:09:13 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/catherinezetajones.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Richard Dawson's Back From the Dead Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson2.mp3</link>
   <description>One of the many traditions we didn't chose to ignore this year.  We have returned with the Christmas Feud episode.  Family's led by Jeff and James go head-to-head.  This leaves Greg to burn the place down with the most intense questions to hit Feud to date.  Merry Christmas everyone! Thank you so much for the excellent year.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson2.mp3" length="29227880" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 06:07:04 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson2.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Natalie Portman Yuletide Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/natalieportman.mp3</link>
   <description>As we head toward the New Year, the Movie Hour Gang continues to shine.  We talk Tron vs True Grit, more Hayao Miyazaki, and The Damned United. This is all following drunken holiday talk and a slew of top-notch jokes.  James has a Quiz and the PPPA.  Happy Holidays everybody!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/natalieportman.mp3" length="37314366" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 19:53:46 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/natalieportman.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Rob Lowe Furlough Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/roblowe.mp3</link>
   <description>The Gang is split up once again.  The Movie Hour broadcasts from Florida and Michigan and the greatest simulcast of the century.  James comes to us from an assisted living resort while Greg and Jeff broadcast in the cold of Detroit.  Let there be no mistake, we're here for the women.  Enjoy!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/roblowe.mp3" length="18651799" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 23:02:25 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/roblowe.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Morgan Freeman Wikileaks Prosecution Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/morganfreeman.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang gathers in a memorial for friend-of-the-show Leslie Nielson.  We reflect on the laughs we shared thanks to his genius and wish his friends and family the best.  We then review Morning Glory and Harry Potter in full.  Look for upcoming news on the Family Feud Episode.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/morganfreeman.mp3" length="21365525" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2010 19:08:30 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/morganfreeman.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Ally Sheedy Don't Be Greedy Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/allysheedy.mp3</link>
   <description>The Holidays have pretty much arrived.  We lose Jeff to family affair but the Movie Hour gang moves on.  A special guest from the West coast joins us and ends up going head-to-head with Greg in one of the most devastating quizzes to date.  Greg talks more Hayao Miyazaki with Princess Mononoke and hints about the latest Harry Potter.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/allysheedy.mp3" length="31477624" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 02:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/allysheedy.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Michael Ironside's Blatant Blindsides Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelironside.mp3</link>
   <description>After 108 episodes, Jeff feels like it's time for him to write a quiz.  Greg and Jim face off for only the second time in Movie Hour history. Between the jokes you'll find a review of Due Date, a final look at the Mad Max trilogy, and a whole lot of Muppet discussion.  Stay cool!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelironside.mp3" length="26259078" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 00:46:56 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelironside.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Topher Grace Blue in the Face Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/tophergrace.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang does your dirty work for you.  We make fun of movies straight to TV before theaters, we joke about the movie Devil, and we poke fun at Mel Gibson.  All of this for the first time in 128 kbr dynamic surround sound.  Don't hold back your laughter.  People probably already think you're weird.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/tophergrace.mp3" length="33218538" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 04:21:03 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/tophergrace.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Christopher Lee All Hallow's Eve Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/christopherlee.mp3</link>
   <description>Another Halloween is upon us!  The Movie Hour Gang talk festivities and then move on to reviews.  Greg and Jeff sat in on a viewing of Wes Craven's latest while James takes a gentler approach.  We discuss costumes and then move on to a Scary themed PPPA!  We reveal our costumes of 2010 before it's all over.  Have a happy Halloween!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/christopherlee.mp3" length="22440566" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 03:39:35 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/christopherlee.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Oliver Platt Baby Fat Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/oliverplatt.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour delivers late but comes with some special surprises.  We talk more remakes during the Hollywood Hoopla.  Jeff reviews the Social Network while the rest of us have to listen.  More reviews and more PPPA follow on this episode of It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/oliverplatt.mp3" length="19292472" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 04:41:26 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/oliverplatt.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Carla Gugnio Mine Shaft Rescue Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/carlagugino.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Triforce is back in the studio for another episode of the latest and greatest.  After discussing MSU being the best team in the WORLD, we move on to the classic features that make this podcast great.  Greg reviews yet another Hayao Miyazaki movie and James produces another DVD chapter quiz.  There can only be one king of the castle, let's hope it's Greg.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/carlagugino.mp3" length="23917659" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 03:19:52 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/carlagugino.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>James Woods Long Live the New Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jameswoods.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang is up late!  With that, comes drunkenness and possibly some vulgar language.  We discuss the latest from Hollywood and the sad path that lies ahead.  Greg brings up a stellar PPPA on this episode James Woods himself couldn't stay away from!  Keep truckin.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jameswoods.mp3" length="20326778" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 05:04:44 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jameswoods.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Wesley Snipes On the Lam Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/wesleysnipes.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour continues to dominate the interwaves with film nonsense.  Lucas rewrites the Saga, Greg invents new words, and Jeff has the PPPA.  You've just been Hobbit-struck!  Enjoy the show.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/wesleysnipes.mp3" length="24564324" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 04:41:55 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/wesleysnipes.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Sophia Loren's Bingo Hall Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/sophialoren.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour Gang kicks off the next hundred with a return to the classic features.  The HHHH, the PPPA, the BSDM?  We review The Town and James serves up a quiz.  Someone is about to get stomped and he doesn't even know it yet.  Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/sophialoren.mp3" length="19697370" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 03:15:23 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/sophialoren.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Bill Cosby Keepin It Clean Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billcosby.mp3</link>
   <description>Holy Mother of God.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billcosby.mp3" length="32842917" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 17:19:43 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billcosby.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Evan Rachel Wood If I Could Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/evanrachel.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour celebrates it's unification.  Jeff is back in studio and we can barely contain the awesome.  Come for the Hoopla, stay for the Parker Posey.  We love you all and thanks for listening!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/evanrachel.mp3" length="16697325" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 17:19:09 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/evanrachel.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Will Arnett Forget-Me-Not Movie Hour </title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/willarnett.mp3</link>
   <description>Team Greg and James continue to dominate the Movie Hour waves.  We take down serious Hoopla topics before James reviews friend of the show Joaquin Phoenix.  James presses Greg to do a solo quiz, can you beat my score of Awesome?  I didn't think so.  Have a great Labor Day everyone and thanks for listening!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/willarnett.mp3" length="24574044" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 15:35:51 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/willarnett.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Elizabeth Shue's All That Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/elizabethshue.mp3</link>
   <description>We have returned from celebrity paradise to perform once again for our fervent fans.  We are a unit once again sans a Jeff.  James and Greg talk Tim Burton and this weekends numbers.  Then goes The Expendables review with a special reading.  Eat, Pray, Love also gets put under our microscope.  It's good to be back!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/elizabethshue.mp3" length="23549536" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 04:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/elizabethshue.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The David Cross All is Lost Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/davidcross.mp3</link>
   <description>Like clockwork, Jeff comes crawling back to the Movie Hour studio this episode.  The Gang reunites to discus who will be this weekend's box office winner.  Jeff and Greg saw The Other Guys this week and one of them swore they wouldn't.  Who could it have been?! All answers are revealed within.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/davidcross.mp3" length="21044485" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2010 03:25:18 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/davidcross.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Ray Liotta Birthday Bonanza Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rayliotta.mp3</link>
   <description>The Gang has created one of the finest episodes to grace the internet. The Movie Hour celebrates Greg's birthday with a special guest Michelle! Jeff calls in and has appeared to have fallen of the horse again. We talk Dinner for Schmucks and Michelle throws out a devastating PPPA. HAPPY BIRTHDAY ME!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rayliotta.mp3" length="24885147" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 04:18:56 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rayliotta.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Elizabeth Berkley's Pole Dancing Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/elizabethberkley.mp3</link>
   <description>The stars have aligned! The Movie Hour Gang invites Jim P. back to the studio to replace MIA Jeff.  We dissect Inception and talk comics. Jim P. and Greg go head-to-head for the first time during the quiz.  Greg continues the comic talk with the latest PPPA.  Enjoy one of the longest Movie Hour's to date!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/elizabethberkley.mp3" length="30553281" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/elizabethberkley.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Michael Moore Working Poor Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelmoore.mp3</link>
   <description>After recovering from a drunken haze, Greg pieces together a Movie Hour for the history books.  We talk Predators, Despicable Me, and touch on Inception.  Jeff asks the latest Parker Posey.  Thank you all for the support.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelmoore.mp3" length="17920003" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 20:34:57 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaelmoore.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Sir Patrick Stewart Muffin Top Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/patrickstewart.mp3</link>
   <description>Add another Stewart to the list, the Sir Patrick Stewart episode brings you the latest in the tinsel town news with Greg getting serious about anime.  Prepare for groundbreaking insight and massive name calling.  Jim has the PPPA.Someone turn on the AC. Stay gold!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/patrickstewart.mp3" length="21349936" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 20:59:52 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/patrickstewart.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Kristen Stewart Potluck Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kristenstewart.mp3</link>
   <description>After a weekend of BBQ and beers, The Movie Hour gang returns to talk about the news of the week with the Hollywood Hoopla.  Greg reviews The Last Airbender and Quiz master Jim creates a new quiz.  Who could possibly win between mortal enemies Greg and Jeff?  I'll give you a hint.  The Dutch.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kristenstewart.mp3" length="28359496" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 23:12:02 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kristenstewart.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Paul Hogan Croc-o-Maniac Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/paulhogan.mp3</link>
   <description>Another week without the Jeff! The Movie Hour treks on nonetheless with discussions about the World Cup and Sandler's latest movie Grown Ups.  We do our best to ignore Twilight and move on to discover Martin Scorsese's favorite Harry Potter character.  I'll give you a hint, it's not Filius Flitwick.  Happy Fourth of July everyone!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/paulhogan.mp3" length="20229104" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 17:41:42 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/paulhogan.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Frances McDormand's Appendicitis Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/francesmcdormand.mp3</link>
   <description>While the Movie Hour Gang revels in World Cup madness they try to stay on the path of the movie reviews.  We talk Toy Story 3, A-Team, A Serious Man, and Frozen River.  If that's not enough we touch on the latest news and the best feature to hit the interwebs, Parker Posey's Play Along.  I'm not sure I can contain my excitement. Okay, I can't. See you soon!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/francesmcdormand.mp3" length="28822863" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 21:52:28 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/francesmcdormand.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Robert Stack Unsolved Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/robertstack.mp3</link>
   <description>We are whole once again!  The Holy Trinity of Greg, James, and Jeff are together again to bring you the latest on everything movie related.  We discuss the news, dissect Killers, and then move on to another Chapter quiz from James.  Come for the eye candy, stay for the elephants ears.  This is the Movie Hour.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/robertstack.mp3" length="22910355" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 00:21:21 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/robertstack.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Devon Sawa Eiffel Tower Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/devonsawa.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour lost a jeff!  He joins us intermittently while we discuss Get Him to the Greek and our famous Hollywood Hoopla.  Prepare yourself for the World Cup and Jeff being stranded somewhere in Pennsylvania.  Greg has yet another PPPA!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/devonsawa.mp3" length="19158036" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 23:18:39 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/devonsawa.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Nia Long Sunday Crossword Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nialong.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour gang brings you reviews on Prince of Persia and Moon.  We hit the high notes with the Hollywood Hoopla and bring smiles to orphans everywhere.  Come listen to biggest geniuses this side of the oil-free Mississippi.  Happy post Memorial Day!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nialong.mp3" length="23987813" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2010 02:46:05 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/nialong.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Eli Roth's Battle of Hoth Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/eliroth.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour goes quiz crazy.  Jeff's quiz left everyone wanting more so Jim delivers!  Greg swears revenge and things turn ugly.  Like Mrs. Doubtfire ugly.  Another feature filled Movie Hour is here for the enjoyment of the sheeple.  Thank you for listening!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/eliroth.mp3" length="31215846" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 03:43:01 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/eliroth.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Jon Cryer Warehouse Fire Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/joncryer.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour team talks Robinhood amongst other things during beautiful weather in the mitten.  Enjoy the show while sipping on a Majito out in the sun!  Jeff brings the most controversial PPPA to date but makes up for it with a stellar quiz.  &lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/joncryer.mp3" length="25466776" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 15:49:28 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/joncryer.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Judy Greer, Have No Fear Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judygreer.mp3</link>
   <description>Another installment of movie magic hits the airwaves with reviews on Iron Man and The Losers.  The Movie Hour gang stops to mock babies and tell Zombie John Hughes to stop writing material.  Enjoy the funny! PPPA is Greg's this week.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judygreer.mp3" length="20554434" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 19:30:21 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judygreer.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Val Kilmer Top Secret! Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/valkilmer.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour gang goes back to basics.  We touch on the happenings of Tinsel Town with Holly Hunters Hollywood Hooplah, then move on to review the new Nightmare on Elm Street, Tropic Thunder, and Manufacturing Consent.  We top it off with our home grown Parker Posey's Play Along brought to you this week by James.  Archer=Funny.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/valkilmer.mp3" length="31717034" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 15:04:47 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/valkilmer.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Kurt Russell's Saggy Muscles Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kurtrussell.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour leaves summer movies behind to get back to it's roots.  The Quiz has been put off for too long and enough is enough!  Jim delivers while Greg and Jeff duel to the death.  Who will come out on top?  You'll just need one guess.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kurtrussell.mp3" length="21177301" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 18:26:46 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kurtrussell.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Catherine Keener Tea Party Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/matthewbroderick.mp3</link>
   <description>Summer Previews Part 2  hits the The Movie Hour with full force.  We look a little deeper into our imaginary movie categories for this summer's movies.  We discuss the stand out plots, movies by Apatow's spawn, and celebrities trying to keep their careers afloat.  Jeff chimes in from New York City.  All this and more in this week's Movie Hour.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/catherinekeener.mp3" length="26031167" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 20:45:15 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/matthewbroderick.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Matthew Broderick's Broadyway Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/matthewbroderick.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour gives you a first look at summer movies. We sell you predictions on #1 box office and movie flops while reminiscing over the 80's remakes on their way to the theater. Everything before July 31st is fair game. The summer movies will get another shake next week. Go wings! Go Taxes! Go Banana!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/matthewbroderick.mp3" length="32305302" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 04:36:15 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/matthewbroderick.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Martin Sheen Fresh and Clean Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/martinsheen.mp3</link>
   <description>We take the Movie Hour on tour! Greg finds himself in the Rockies while Jeff recently returns from New York.  We talk about the fantasy genre and what has always seem just beyond the bizarre.  Will there we chaos without the host in town?  Tune in for another hour of greatness.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/martinsheen.mp3" length="26846141" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 05:52:11 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/martinsheen.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Laura Linney Breakfast in Bed Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/lauralinney.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour goes back to its roots!  We bring in the long awaited quiz and debate the tenants of Scientology.  Greg talks about his plans to go cross country while Jeff dies from typhoid.  Come for the quiz, stay for the lawls.  Thank you live listeners and go State!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/lauralinney.mp3" length="28380618" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2010 15:58:16 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/lauralinney.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Roger Moore Final Four Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rogermoore.mp3</link>
   <description>It's official, we will never have a longer episode than this one.  We reveal our true feelings on the March Madness Movie Match-Up Month as it comes to a dramatic end.  This weeks topic is Best Epic Death Scene and it is a deep field.  Greg finally sees &quot;2012&quot; and Jim apologizes to &quot;The Room&quot;.  All this wrapped up in a shiny ninety minute long webisode.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rogermoore.mp3" length="42520709" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 16:57:23 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rogermoore.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Sean William Scott Ready or Not Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/seanwilliamscott.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour team rallys back for another March Madness episode.  Within this hour of movie info you'll hear arguments for our favorite Father Figures, an R.I.P. to some big actors, and our usual All-star features.  Another happy St. Patrick's Day to all and merry Christmas.&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/seanwilliamscott.mp3" length="27787330" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 22:07:25 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/seanwilliamscott.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Olivia Wilde's Bake Sale Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/oliviawilde.mp3</link>
   <description>March Madness Movie Match-Up Month continues.  We get together to watch -Actors famous for one role- fight for the title in the longest podcast to ever hit the internet.  James takes time to enlighten us about this &quot;Oscar&quot; stuff and we Greg delivers our PPPA.  The saga continues...</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/oliviawilde.mp3" length="39567227" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 04:15:58 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/oliviawilde.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Don Cheadle is Too Cool to Use Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/doncheadle.mp3</link>
   <description>The gang strikes back with a show of epic proportions.  We bring our sports minds into the March with a seasonal feature called &quot;March Madness Movie Match-up Month&quot;.  Movies get pitted against each other for the top spot of this week's theme Unintentional Comedies.  Who will take down the crown?  Let's hope to god it won't be Duke.  Thank you all for listening!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/doncheadle.mp3" length="35078463" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 16:39:22 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/doncheadle.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Billy Crudup Sit Down, Shut Up Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billycrudup.mp3</link>
   <description>This week's opus:  Jeff is back from his stint in India, the gang catches up on movie reviews, and Jim puts on a world class quiz with an Olympic theme.  Will Greg review a movie that isn't from the 80's?  Go Michelle, Go!  Don't miss our latest return to the internet.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billycrudup.mp3" length="32936512" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2010 23:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billycrudup.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Mel Gibson Push'Em in the Oven Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/melgibson1.mp3</link>
   <description>The secret is out!  Jeff is safe in rehab and The Movie Hour needs to replace him.  We bring in consultant Jim P to wade through the potential employees.  Where's our numbers guy when you need him!?  Get well soon Jeff.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/melgibson1.mp3" length="24540145" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 11:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/melgibson1.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Ione Skye Awkward Silence Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ioneskye.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour tackles the tough issues surrounding the newly released Oscar nominations.  Rip Torn creates some Hollywood Hoopla.  And Jeff prepares himself for the dangers of international travel.  Enjoy the show!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ioneskye.mp3" length="28956858" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 14:29:07 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ioneskye.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Slim Pickens' Pastry Shop Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/slimpickens.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour gang gets on board with the useless award season.  Who will take home the first annual coveted Gungy awards?  We also celebrate the christening of our newly named Hollywood Rundown and a brand new quiz from James.  Enjoy the longest Movie Hour to date!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/slimpickens.mp3" length="34609216" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 05:14:01 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/slimpickens.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Hank Azaria Hazard Area Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/hankazaria.mp3</link>
   <description>In honor of Martin Luther King we discuss leaders of the movie world.  Who are the greatest fictional leaders of cinema?  If you are are thinking Mumbles from Happy Feet is Jeff's answer you may be right.  Another fantastic late night recording in the Movie Hour history.  Jeff has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/hankazaria.mp3" length="28764736" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 06:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/hankazaria.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Kirstie Alley's Low-Fat Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kirstiealley.mp3</link>
   <description>&quot;Episode 67 is another late night broadcast from the Movie Hour studios.  Greg's whimsical talent alongside the knowledge of Jim and Jeff is truly a pleasure to listen to.  Their insight on the winter movies to come will surely have you ready to make an informed adult decision when you go to your local cinema.  Their the best there is.&quot; - Obama</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kirstiealley.mp3" length="28700992" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 04:41:15 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kirstiealley.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Judge Reinhold The Phone Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judgereinhold.mp3</link>
   <description>We celebrate the 2010 arrival with a slew of extended features.  We have two weeks of mock news to cover for the Hollywood Rundown and Jim has seen a dozen movies.  We come back armed with a quiz to put Jeff and Greg to the test...and this time it's personal.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judgereinhold.mp3" length="31769344" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 03:09:45 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/judgereinhold.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Richard Dawson's Wheel of Death Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson1.mp3</link>
   <description>The calendar has come full circle and it's time again for another clash of movie knowledge.  Greg and Jeff face off with their teams to form our second installment of the Family Feud.  Come follow the mayhem as the Dorito family face off against the Masters Of Karate And Friendship For Everyone family.  Only one will be left standing after the dust settles.&lt;br>Happy 2010!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson1.mp3" length="27872192" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 21:23:33 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson1.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Dina Meyer's Coup De Grace Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/dinameyer.mp3</link>
   <description>Happy Holidays everyone! We celebrate the New Year by reviewing everyone's favorite new film Avatar.  It's also time for New Year's resolutions and the Feats of Strength.  The show doesn't end until you solve answer my Parker Posey's Play Along! What's a Baldwin?</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/dinameyer.mp3" length="24765008" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 21:52:48 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/dinameyer.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The George Takei Lambda Lambda Lambda Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/georgetakei.mp3</link>
   <description>Take a voyage through 2009 with The Movie Hour crew as they pick out the highlights.  Caution; James and Jeff are extra goofy today.  Episode bonus: Greg hearts Alice in Wonderland.  James has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/georgetakei.mp3" length="30330304" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 07:55:18 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/georgetakei.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Mel Gibson's Merry-go-round Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/melgibson.mp3</link>
   <description>Greg, James, and Jeff come together to talk about our movie predictions from the past.  Who was right about Transformers making the most money thus far?  We point fingers at movies that made predictions of their own and what we have in store for the future if they were right.  It's snowing!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/melgibson.mp3" length="29846272" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 21:51:07 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/melgibson.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Mel Gibson's Merry-go-round Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/melgibson.mp3</link>
   <description>Greg, James, and Jeff come together to talk about our movie predictions from the past.  Who was right about Transformers making the most money thus far?  We point fingers at movies that made predictions of their own and what we have in store for the future if they were right.  It's snowing!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/melgibson.mp3" length="32445952" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 03:27:22 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/melgibson.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Lucy Liu Cage Match Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/lucyliu.mp3</link>
   <description>As the Movie Hour strolls into December we address some of the upcoming releases.  The Broken Lizards and the Jason Reitmans of Hollywood face our scrutiny.  Will they survive?  We also wrap up Jim's impossible quiz.  Family Feud episode to come!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/lucyliu.mp3" length="29527744" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 05:19:43 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/lucyliu.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ron Perlman's Dodecahedron's Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ronperlman.mp3</link>
   <description>After a short hiatus, Greg returns to the Movie Hour with exotic stories from Detroit.  Jeff laughs himself to death and James brings a quiz that stumps his moronic co-hosts.  The Movie Hour touches on all the important elements with it's humor, intelligence, and justice...oh so much justice.  Thanks for listening.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ronperlman.mp3" length="30643541" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2009 03:27:22 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ronperlman.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Dolph Lundgren's Macho Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/dolphlundgren.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour returns and asks the tough questions...Who's #1 in the box office?  Can you film in space?  And where's Greg?!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/dolphlundgren.mp3" length="16006656" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2009 15:23:47 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/dolphlundgren.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Matthew Perry Super Scary Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/matthewperry.mp3</link>
   <description>Happy Halloweeeeeeeen!  It's been a busy week full of fun and shenanigans.  We top it off with the first Movie Hour with a special horror guest.  Our good friend and horror connoisseur Jim P.  We discuss the latest in Hollywood, the plight of horror movies, and a little special quiz for the horror laymen amongst us.  Remember to put your costume on for the podcast!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/matthewperry.mp3" length="32985728" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 03:21:13 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/matthewperry.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Carrie Fisher Surprise Party Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/carriefisher.mp3</link>
   <description>Takin' it easy at The Movie Hour this week.  Lay back and relax while we do a round table discussion of the weekly events.  Halloween creeps closer and Greg invites the world to the microphone.  The Tag Line quiz makes a return and Greg has the PPPA.  Go see Astroboy!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/carriefisher.mp3" length="25606528" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 06:41:28 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/carriefisher.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Sylvester Stallone's Socialized Medicine Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/sylvesterstallone.mp3</link>
   <description>As Halloween nears, The Movie Hour finds a place in its heart for the bad guy.  The antagonists of our favorite films get bad reputations from their ulterior motives and maniacal plotting.  We show you the sunnier side of this supposed world of crime so you can see your favorite &quot;evil&quot; characters in a different light. Jim has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/sylvesterstallone.mp3" length="22566848" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 05:38:52 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/sylvesterstallone.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Ellen Page Uncomfortable Eye Contact Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ellenpage.mp3</link>
   <description>The Boys are back in town!  Now that the Movie Hour team is a whole, we concentrate all our efforts on actors.  More specifically, we celebrate those who have made the leap to the director's chair.  Accompanied with your usual Parker Poseys and Hollywood updates, you'll have your weekly dose of pop culture know how.  Yippee Arrested Development!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ellenpage.mp3" length="23230016" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 04:25:23 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ellenpage.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Roman Polanski's Daycare Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/romanpolanski.mp3</link>
   <description>After weeks with his Nieces, Greg starts thinking like a child. We quickly address the remastering of Wizard of Oz before turning toward more nostalgic favorites. We discuss the differences between your old childhood movies and the blockbuster animations of today. Every third episode we have quizmaster James test us on our movie knowledge and today is no different. Will Greg finally redeem himself? Join us for lots of laughs and maybe a few tears.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/romanpolanski.mp3" length="31736576" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2009 06:17:59 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/romanpolanski.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Jessica Biel's Plate Tectonics Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jessicabiel.mp3</link>
   <description>Autumn is here! We discuss what Hollywood has laid out for us for our fall films.  Some of them simply catch our curiosity while others will have us lined up for tickets.  We have some recommendations for you as well as a Parker Posey's Play Along.  Greg says hi from Cali! R.I.P. Swayze.  </description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jessicabiel.mp3" length="24891904" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 03:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jessicabiel.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Daniel Craig Fantasy Football Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/danielcraig.mp3</link>
   <description>Marvel is on our minds.  Before Greg and Jeff leave town it's time we discussed the Disney take over of comic masters Marvel Entertainment.  We look at Marvel's past productions and pitch some ideas to the Disney execs on what may be their next big movie.  Greg has a surprise quiz while Jeff has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/danielcraig.mp3" length="30662848" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 00:51:52 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/danielcraig.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Bruce Willis Back to School Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/brucewillis.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour gets back in the saddle with a deep look at the movie 9.  Greg and Jeff turn to Sesame Street for some inspiration while Jim hands out a new species of Quiz.  This episode is brought to you by the letters A, U, and the number 9.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/brucewillis.mp3" length="27147328" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 03:07:45 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/brucewillis.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Brangelina's Waffle House Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/brangelina.mp3</link>
   <description>It's time for celebration!  The Movie Hour team comes together for their fiftieth episode on the shows one year anniversary.  Come listen to a weekly does of reviews, movie updates, and our Parker Posey's Play Along.  The team spends their time reveling in the jokes that made the show fun and acknowledging the fans that made it great.  Thank you all for listening and raise a glass in hopes of more to come.  Cheers!&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/brangelina.mp3" length="31137728" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2009 02:17:35 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/brangelina.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Ashton Kutcher Movie Butcher Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ashtonkutcher.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour team is back on schedule!  We bring with us a full allotment of movie reviews and Parker Posey Play Along answers.  Inglourious Basterds gets the coveted Gunga Pit Seal of Approval.  We also wrap up our Aliens in August segment with a in depth analysis of District 9 and our personal hopes for our cinematic aliens' futures. Jeff has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ashtonkutcher.mp3" length="28888448" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 02:43:32 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ashtonkutcher.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Anthony Michael Hall Pass Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/anthonyhall.mp3</link>
   <description>Our Aliens in August sequel kicks off with a broad look at the evil aliens Hollywood could create.  Aside from scary killers, is there any hope for a plot in these movies?  We pick some of our personal favorites and end with a vote for most the meanest monster.  Jim has the PPPA.  This episode was recorded much earlier than it's release date to match up with busy scheduling.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/anthonyhall.mp3" length="21609152" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 04:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/anthonyhall.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Rutger Hauer Puppy Power Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rutgerhauer.mp3</link>
   <description>Aliens in August has arrived!  Greg acts like Carl Sagan while Jeff and James line up our discussion of friendly alien lifeforms.  We take on everything from Star Trek to E.T.  When will the next good alien flick come out and how sociable can aliens really be, all here at the ridiculously named Movie Hour episode.  Jeff has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rutgerhauer.mp3" length="22892032" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 04:39:06 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/rutgerhauer.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>John Woo's Gunfu Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johnwoo.mp3</link>
   <description>Things are getting busy.  The Movie hour team reminisce about their Drunken Olympics weekend and family weddings.  We bring up our favorite reunion movies and films that give you that fuzzy warm feeling.  Wait, what?&lt;br>Listen for the Ultra Cute sound bytes.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johnwoo.mp3" length="21650176" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 21:26:41 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johnwoo.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Geena Davis Story Time Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/geenadavis.mp3</link>
   <description>Jeff's alcoholism has lead to a expensive gambling habit.  He brings us stories of his trip to Vegas while we address movies concerning casinos and the degenerates that populate them.  Jim brings us another themed quiz for another showdown between Greg and Jeff.  Listeners, I know you know I won this time.  Jim has the Parker Posey's Play Along.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/geenadavis.mp3" length="29967488" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 05:14:29 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/geenadavis.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Fraternal Order of Shatner Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/shatner.mp3</link>
   <description>Science!  We put on our thinking caps to discuss technology in film.  Artificial intelligence, the mystery of human nature, and the search for the ultimate weapon are all on the table.  We can thank science for a lot of terrible movies.  Jeff has the PPPA.  P.S. Thank you Mr. Science for Slurpees.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/shatner.mp3" length="24585856" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 04:39:03 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/shatner.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Megan Fox's Thumb Wrestling Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/meganfox.mp3</link>
   <description>Magic is in the Air.  Harry Potter's 6th installment is near release and the Move Hour team is up late to discuss it's novelties.  Can kids really act, and if so, are they getting worse as they age? Greg has this weeks Parker Posey's Play Along and it's not all about vanilla ice cream this time.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/meganfox.mp3" length="21420928" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 06:35:21 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/meganfox.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Michael Jackson Was Murdered Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaeljackson.mp3</link>
   <description>Transformers makes billions at the box office.  Greg explains the mysterious plot while the team analyzes what makes such terrible movies so profitable.  Jim introduces a new quiz to the shows line-up as well as a top notch Parker Posey's Play Along.  Join the laughs at gungapit.com.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaeljackson.mp3" length="28875904" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 03:55:32 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/michaeljackson.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Martin Short HGH Scandal Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/martinshort.mp3</link>
   <description>Happy Father's Day men.  We celebrate your heroism with a discussion of some of our favorite dad characters.  We elaborate on their relationships with their sons and take a moment to reflect on what makes a summer movie to us.  Jeff has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/martinshort.mp3" length="24373013" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2009 06:26:30 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/martinshort.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Chuck Sheen's Accidental Orgy Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/chucksheen.mp3</link>
   <description>The team comes together to discuss voice actors and what makes them completely awesome.  We also add in narration and a whole slew of well spoken people.  Mel Blanc didn't sign the liability waiver so we left him at home.  Have some of the Movie Hour. Now with more laughs!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/chucksheen.mp3" length="22039360" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 04:34:21 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/chucksheen.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Lloyd Bridges Automatons Attack Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/lloydbridges.mp3</link>
   <description>As summer movies continue the Movie Hour team lays out a road map to flawless movie viewing.  We make all the hard decisions for you on this month's movie releases.  &quot;The Morten&quot; has our latest quiz.  Did Jeff finally retake his crown? James asks potentially the best Parker Posey's Play Along to date.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/lloydbridges.mp3" length="25774720" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 04:31:15 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/lloydbridges.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Harold Ramis Hari-kari Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/haroldramis.mp3</link>
   <description>The trinity is whole once again!  Jeff wastes no time settling back in and addresses what he would have said during Music in May.  He also brings up what movies helped him through his recovery.  The team then moves through the weeks events in movies and playoff hockey.  Welcome back Jeff. Go Wings!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/haroldramis.mp3" length="20501632" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2009 03:36:06 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/haroldramis.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Martha Plimpton Speed Dating Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/marthaplimpton.mp3</link>
   <description>Greg and James are one man short of a team!  Jeff recovers from swine flu while the brothers wrap up the Music in May series.  Pop music in movies needs to be put to rest and they're just the two to do it.  Directors with an ear for music, movies that kick ass, and bands that benefit are all on the agenda.  Get well soon Jeff.  As for you other folk, enjoy the rest of the series!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/marthaplimpton.mp3" length="21110336" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2009 03:16:51 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/marthaplimpton.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Fred Astaire Bow-tie Pasta Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/fredastaire.mp3</link>
   <description>Music is in the air! Join the episode where Jeff and Greg team up to discover a relic known as the 'Musical'. Jim shakes his head at our shenanigans. Also, Star Trek is laid to rest, Terminator Lame-ation is addressed, and a Pop quiz that hints to our final Music in May episode.  Listen for the Easter Egg! Our third episode in our music series.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/fredastaire.mp3" length="25568384" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 01:09:08 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/fredastaire.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Barbra Streisand's Rhinoplasty Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/barbrastreisand.mp3</link>
   <description>Segment two of our Music in May series has arrived.  We express our love for some of our favorite movie composers and their musical scores.  Classical music and it's use in modern day film also gets some time in the limelight.  Tune in for the Williams, stay for the Strauss. Jeff has the Parker Posey's Play Along!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/barbrastreisand.mp3" length="23773696" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 06:27:44 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/barbrastreisand.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The John Williams Carbon Dating Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johnwilliams.mp3</link>
   <description>Music in May has arrived!  We introduce you to the first episode of our saga on sound.  We go through some of the movies we fell in love with thanks to their focus on musicians and music.  We try to grasp what makes them great and why Jeff likes terrible movies.  Greg has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johnwilliams.mp3" length="28622272" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 08:20:58 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johnwilliams.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Wil Wheaton's Star Trek: The Movie Hour </title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/wilwheaton.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour goes Warp 9!  The new Star Trek dynasty begins May 8th.  Will Abrams and his no name crew cut it? Greg reveals his inner nerd and James brings the Parker Posey's Play Along.  Set course to completely awesome.  Engage!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/wilwheaton.mp3" length="24576008" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 04:29:07 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/wilwheaton.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Jason Biggs Experimental Physics Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jasonbiggs.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour team count dollars as we note the terrible films making a killing in the box office.  We show our respect for Earth Day and spell out what movies have inspired us and the rest of the world alike.  Who knew that Jeff liked porn so much?  He also has our PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jasonbiggs.mp3" length="26143343" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 02:48:15 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jasonbiggs.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Steve Guttenberg Going Out of Business Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/steveguttenberg.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour classifieds hit the streets.  Looking for enthusiastic people to listen, 1 hour/week.  Offering witty banter and  comfy living area.  Comes furnished.  Greg has the PPPA. </description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/steveguttenberg.mp3" length="23403436" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 03:47:23 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/steveguttenberg.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Craig T. Nelson's Forehead Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/craigtnelson.mp3</link>
   <description>Basketball and snow invade Detroit,  Fast &amp;amp; Furious makes too much money, and we can't stop talking about memorable movie cars.  These are tonight's headlines.  Also, another great quiz and PPPA by James.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/craigtnelson.mp3" length="24920033" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 02:59:36 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/craigtnelson.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The John Candy I'm Dead Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johncandy.mp3</link>
   <description>Parodies exposed! After discussing our drinking problems we enlighten the world of the parody. Zucker Bros, Mel Brooks, and the Monty Python crew are discussed. Will Jeff's PPPA be an April Fools?</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johncandy.mp3" length="28006996" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 05:41:47 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/johncandy.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Ryan Reynolds Telethon Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ryanreynolds.mp3</link>
   <description>We wrap up March with a closer look at animation and the new movie Monsters Vs Aliens.  Will 3-D movies ever die and will Pixar take over the world?  We also take a look at the weekly releases.  Greg has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ryanreynolds.mp3" length="25138918" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 05:29:44 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ryanreynolds.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Patrick Duffy Poetry Slam Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/patrickduffy.mp3</link>
   <description>Kiss us, we're Irish! We litter the podcast with movie limericks and update everyone on the latest releases.  Try not to cry as our poetic prowess takes over.  James has the PPPA. Happy St. Patrick's Day!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/patrickduffy.mp3" length="25591648" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 04:27:29 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/patrickduffy.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Patrick Swayze's Bar Crawl Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/patrickswayze.mp3</link>
   <description>The Watchmen is put under the microscope. We spend time categorizing the actors, music, and plot of the mighty organism. Beware the Ides of March! The terrible movies on the way with the age of the athlete turned actor. We don our swords and sandals and answer Jeff's PPPA. Back off man. I'm a scientist.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/patrickswayze.mp3" length="27251589" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 04:36:26 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/patrickswayze.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Richard Gere's Adopt-A-Pet Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richardgere.mp3</link>
   <description>We felt exceptionally superior today so we weighed in on the biggest box office movies of the season.  Can any movie make more money than Megan Fox?  Joaquin misses another show and Greg has our PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richardgere.mp3" length="25463769" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 05:18:11 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richardgere.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The Jean-Claude Van Damme it all to Hell Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jeanclaude.mp3</link>
   <description>Oscars exposed! Where is the love for The Wrestler crew? Winslet loves a quiz and Bat boy endorses James PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jeanclaude.mp3" length="24180365" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 04:43:32 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/jeanclaude.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marlon Brando's Massage Parlor Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/marlonbrando.mp3</link>
   <description>Hollywood gives us Che part 2 while we give you Killer Klowns from Outer Space.  What other biopics are out there worth seeing?  This weeks PPPA is brought to you by Jeff.&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/marlonbrando.mp3" length="22012480" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 15:29:06 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/marlonbrando.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Christian Bale's Anger Management Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/christianbale.mp3</link>
   <description>The team shows the world they have a heart.  You'll hear suggestions on how girls and guys can both enjoy romantic movies this Valentine's Day. Greg likes to drink and run, he also has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/christianbale.mp3" length="28852877" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 04:52:27 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/christianbale.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Fran Drescher's Bot Mitzvah Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/frandrescher.mp3</link>
   <description>Jeff returns from Arizona.  James has a birthday and Greg proposes a tagline quiz for the masses.  James has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/frandrescher.mp3" length="23274479" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2009 05:38:13 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/frandrescher.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Kevin Pollak's Crab Shack Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kevinpollak.mp3</link>
   <description>The longest Movie Hour to date!  We continue our planning for your 2009 movies and mock the Oscar nominations.  Greg finally discovers 2001: A Space Odyssey.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kevinpollak.mp3" length="29222656" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 05:52:46 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/kevinpollak.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>David Duchovny's Rehab Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/davidduchovny.mp3</link>
   <description>Our crew analyzes your future for 2009 movies.  What should you see five times and what you should avoid?  Also a humble salute to Ricardo Montalban.   Greg has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/davidduchovny.mp3" length="25097953" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 05:06:47 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/davidduchovny.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Emma Watson's Training Bra Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/emmawatson.mp3</link>
   <description>Can a movie about a mall cop on a Segway played by Kevin James be funny? The obvious answer lies within these walls complete with a sharp look at straight comedies and a quiz to boot! James has the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/emmawatson.mp3" length="27330754" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 05:20:16 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/emmawatson.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Susan Sarandon's Slaughterhouse Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/susansarandon.mp3</link>
   <description>We break loose in 2009. Greg joins Netflix. Jeff returns to Philadelphia, and James acts unimpressed. The council addresses Benjamin Button and AFI's Ten top Ten. I love this town!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/susansarandon.mp3" length="26639733" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 11:38:13 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/susansarandon.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Richard Dawson's Game Show to the Death Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson.mp3</link>
   <description>Happy holidays everyone! A special thanks to everyone that took part in our Feud episode and thank you to everyone we supports this podcast daily.  We had a face off of Team Jeff vs Team Greg with an epic last minute win.  Who came out on top?  Included is a special Parker Posey just for listeners.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson.mp3" length="23638336" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 11:36:10 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/richarddawson.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ron Howard's Halfway House Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ronhoward.mp3</link>
   <description>Our Christmas Episode is vastly approaching.  The Movie Hour fellas give a taste of whats to come and mock some soon-to-be blockbusters.  Try to prepare yourself for the rush of nostalgia in the Christmas movie discussion.  James brings the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ronhoward.mp3" length="21025216" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 15:41:46 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/ronhoward.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>The David Schwimmer Liberation Front Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/davidschwimmer.mp3</link>
   <description>Family Feud Christmas episode explained. David Fincher and Nazis attack the holiday while your hosts cover the commentary. Could this episode beat the one gig of bandwidth from last week?</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/davidschwimmer.mp3" length="20107840" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2008 12:50:33 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/davidschwimmer.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Bill Duke's Show and Tell Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billduke.mp3</link>
   <description>The crew promotes the upcoming Christmas Episode! They then shine their divine light on the sea of movies redone. The most information on movie remakes ever in a podcast under 40 minutes. Greg brings you the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billduke.mp3" length="18846208" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 12:38:44 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billduke.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Leslie Nielson's Tornado Watch Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/leslienielson.mp3</link>
   <description>Gungacast members say goodbye to Joaquin.  They dissect terrible movie lists and Hancock's change of strategy.  Bring popcorn.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/leslienielson.mp3" length="19511297" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 13:37:31 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/leslienielson.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Dean Cain's Blue Light Special Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/deancain.mp3</link>
   <description>The longest Gungacast to date!  The panel attacks upcoming Thanksgiving movies and actors that can't say no.  James offers a quiz to shed light on Greg's ineptitude.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/deancain.mp3" length="25666048" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 12:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/deancain.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Chuck Heston's Sing Along Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/chuckheston.mp3</link>
   <description>Live listeners galore! Michael Crichton gets a nod from the team for his scientific blockbusters.  Can Seth Rogen and Judd Apatow be stopped? Greg exclaims the PPPA.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/chuckheston.mp3" length="21234880" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 14:17:57 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/chuckheston.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Tom Selleck's Mustache's Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/tomselleck.mp3</link>
   <description>The council brings up a slew of questions.  Who cares about the new Bond movie? What actor would play Barack Obama in a film? Jim addresses the new PP(Parker Posey).</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/tomselleck.mp3" length="20680768" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 13:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/tomselleck.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Helen Hunt's Haunted House Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/helenhunt.mp3</link>
   <description>The Movie Hour has its first live listener!  Meanwhile, Greg denies any possible movie representing the Halloween Holiday.  After a long look at Horror films Jeff launches the new Parker Posey.  Will he succeed where Greg failed?</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/helenhunt.mp3" length="19531868" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 10:06:44 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/helenhunt.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Pauly Shore's Pizza Party Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/paulyshore.mp3</link>
   <description>Our geniuses meet up to rant on about presidential movies in a homage to the presidential election.  We then disect Halloween costumes, both past and future.  Greg proposes the greatest Parker Posey to date.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/paulyshore.mp3" length="23168482" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 11:51:38 GMT</pubDate>
   <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/paulyshore.mp3</guid>
   <author>gungapit@gmail.com (www.gungapit.com/phpBB3)</author>
<image>
   <url>http://img518.imageshack.us/img518/7126/pauly20shorejy3.jpg</url>
   <title>Mr. Shore</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com</link>
   <width>300</width>
   <height>376</height>
</image> 
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Corey Feldman's Big Top Circus Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/coreyfeldman.mp3</link>
   <description>The crew address the fans directly.  We touch on the latest theatrical releases and the baseball playoffs get a mention.  After lacing into baseball Jim provides the new Play Along. </description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/coreyfeldman.mp3" length="17259756" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 11:55:17 GMT</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/coreyfeldman.mp3</guid>
<author>gungapit@gmail.com (www.gungapit.com/phpBB3)</author>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Bruce Campbell's Broom Closet Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/brucecampbell.mp3</link>
   <description>Forum responses get brought to light, DVD features get explained then attacked, and movie sequels don't meet the hype.  Parker Posey makes her second appearance. </description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/brucecampbell.mp3" length="20370880" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 7 Oct 2008 11:50:43 GMT</pubDate>
<author>gungapit@gmail.com (www.gungapit.com/phpBB3)</author>
<guid>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/brucecampbell.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Billy Baldwin's Bathtime Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billybaldwin.mp3</link>
   <description>Greg, James, and Jeff honor Paul Newman with a panel discussion on his movies.  We then rant on about video games brought to the silver screen.  The birth of the Parker Posey's Plan Along takes place with sexy results.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billybaldwin.mp3" length="22058757" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 11:40:45 GMT</pubDate>
<author>gungapit@gmail.com (www.gungapit.com/phpBB3)</author>
<guid>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/billybaldwin.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Frank Stallone's Icecream Social Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/frankstallone.mp3</link>
   <description>The Gungacast team returns to discuss the new Coen Bros film Burn After Reading.  We also describe in detail the rest of the Coen Bro's films and cap it off with Greg quizzing James and Jeff on movie tag lines.  This time it's personal.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/frankstallone.mp3" length="21627779" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 08:40:45 GMT</pubDate>
<author>gungapit@gmail.com (www.gungapit.com/phpBB3)</author>
<guid>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/frankstallone.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Gary Sinise Fan Club Movie Hour</title>
   <link>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/garysinise.mp3</link>
   <description>The birth of the Movie Hour saga.  Greg, James, and Jeff attack Memorial Weekend movies.  We touch on out hope for the new Choke movie and a possible future for Arrested Development.  Can Movies spawn useful TV shows?</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/garysinise.mp3" length="19954491" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 16:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
<author>gungapit@gmail.com (www.gungapit.com/phpBB3)</author>
<guid>http://www.gungapit.com/podcasts/garysinise.mp3</guid>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
