<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Music Calgary Podcast</title>
		<link>http://www.musiccalgary.com/site/podcast.php</link>
		<description>We produce a high quality weekly podcast dedicated to promoting Canadian musicians and music industry people. Our show features music, interviews, giveaways, industry news, song reviews, and much more. And each week we take a guest into the listening room to review a few new songs. The audio quality of our podcast is very good.</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>Copyright 2006 Corey Milner</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2006 05:05:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<generator>Corey Milner</generator>		<webMaster>musiccalgary@email.com</webMaster>
		<ttl>1</ttl>
		<item>
			<title>Music Calgary Podcast #4</title>
			<description>This week I interview Jimmy Payne. Master drummer, creative genius, and all around good guy. Jimmy is one of the artists who helped establish the blues scene in Canada. Amongst many others, he's played drums for R &amp; B legends King Curtis, Little Milton, Pinetop Perkins, John Hammond, and Otis Rush. And after all these years in such a lowdown, cutthroat, dog-eat-dog business, he's still genuinely optimistic about the creative process.<a href='http://odeo.com/claim/feed/c5e2c29123e6e1dd'>My Odeo Channel</a> (odeo/c5e2c29123e6e1dd)</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2006 05:12:12 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://ia310138.us.archive.org/1/items/Music_Calgary_4/15-04-06.mp3" length="40306688" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://ia310138.us.archive.org/1/items/Music_Calgary_4/15-04-06.mp3</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Music Calgary Podcast #3</title>
			<description>In this third episode we interview local R &amp; B and Motown music mainstay Gary Martin. We discuss the early days of R &amp; B, the halcyon days of the Toronto music scene, and the new Funk Brothers Jr. music program. We also review a few cool tunes. If you are in the Calgary area check out Gary Martin and The Heavenly Blues every Saturday and Sunday at The Bowness Hotel and every Sunday evening at Kitt's on 16th.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 8 Apr 2006 03:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Music_Calgary_3/08-04-06.mp3" length="36071424" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.archive.org/download/Music_Calgary_3/08-04-06.mp3</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Music Calgary Podcast #2</title>
			<description>In this second episode we interview the winner of the Ceili's Icon singing contest, Narda. We discuss rock and roll, her secret fondness for Simon Cowell, and creative ways for bands with no money to get their demos recorded. We also review a few cool new tunes.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 1 Apr 2006 05:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://ia310109.us.archive.org/3/items/Music_Calgary_2/04-01-06.mp3" length="31508608" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://ia310109.us.archive.org/3/items/Music_Calgary_2/04-01-06.mp3</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Music Calgary Podcast #1</title>
			<description>In this premiere episode we interview Rock/Blues saxophone phenom Marvin Yakoweshen about such topics as the double sax trick, touring with Dr. Hook during the heyday, and the infamous "Danceland" tavern.</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2006 05:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://ia310130.us.archive.org/2/items/Music_Calgary/Music_Calgary_03-25-06.mp3" length="35400000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://ia310130.us.archive.org/2/items/Music_Calgary/Music_Calgary_03-25-06.mp3</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Music Calgary Podcast #1 Reviews</title>
			<description>We take Blues/Rock saxophonist Marvin Yakoweshen into the listening room to review 3 new songs. We start with a jazz tune, then review a funk tune and a blues tune. Marvin shares some insights about music and a couple entertaining asides in this recording.</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2006 05:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://ia310130.us.archive.org/2/items/Music_Calgary/Music_Calgary_03-25-06-bonus.mp3" length="16600000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://ia310130.us.archive.org/2/items/Music_Calgary/Music_Calgary_03-25-06-bonus.mp3</guid>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>MP3 sampler: Gary Martin and The Heavenly Blues</title>
			<description>Here's an MP3 sampler of Marvin Yakoweshen playing a variety of popular hits live in Calgary with Gary Martin and the Heavenly Blues band. Enjoy!</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2006 05:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.albertadesign.com/music-calgary/mp3/sampler.mp3" length="4830000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.albertadesign.com/music-calgary/mp3/sampler.mp3</guid>
			</item>
		</channel>
	</rss>