<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
  <title>UnBreak Your Health with Alan Smith, author of the award-winning book UnBreak Your Health (Loving Healing Press).</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com</link> 
  <description>Alan Smith, the author of How To UnBreak Your Health, interviews leaders in the field of complementary and alternative health on his podcast radio health program.</description> 
  <image>     
	<url> http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/images/2edicover.jpg
	</url>
   <title>UnBreak Your Health with Alan Smith</title>      
	<link> http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts.htm
    </link>
  </image>
  <itunes:category text="Health"/> 
  <language>en-us</language> 
  <copyright>2008. All rights reserved.</copyright> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 16 July 2008 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 July 2008 09:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate> 
  <managingEditor>alan@unbreakyourhealth.com(Alan Smith)</managingEditor> 
  <webMaster>Alan Smith</webMaster> 
  <itunes:owner>
  <itunes:name>Alan Smith</itunes:name> 
  <itunes:email>alan@unbreakyourhealth.com</itunes:email> 
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Introduction to UnBreak Your Health Program</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Introduction.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Welcome to the podcast program UnBreak Your Health.  Alan Smith is your host and in each 20-minute program he interviews a leading authority about a different type of healing therapy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 06 February 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Welcome to the podcast program UnBreak Your Health.  Alan Smith is your host and in each 20-minute program he interviews a leading authority about a different type of healing therapy.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:01:45</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Introduction.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Osteopathy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Osteopathy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>June 17, 2008 interview on Osteopathy with Dr. Philip Slocum, Dean of the Kirksville College of Osteopathic Medicine at A. T. Still University discussing the features and benefits of osteopathy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 16 July 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Our first podcast interview was with Dr. Philip Slocum, Dean of the Kirksville College of Osteopathic Medicine, on July 17, 2008.  Dr. Slocum graduated from KCOM in 1976 and then completed his residency, training in internal medicine and critical care medicine at the Maine Medicine Center in Portland, Maine.  He chaired the Department of Medicine at the University of New England College of Osteopathic Medicine and was Chief of Pulmonary/Critical Care Medicine at the University of North Texas Health Sciences in Fort Worth, Texas before becoming Dean at KCOM.  His is a Fellow in several major medical colleges and has done leading research on tuberculosis.  His interests now revolve around medical education reform.  Our conversation was on the uniquely American medical system of Osteopathy and the benefits it offers patients today.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Philip Slocum, osteopathy</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:22:27</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/osteopathy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Chiropractic</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Chiropractic.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>July 22, 2008 interview on Chiropractic with Dr. Kurt Wood, Executive Dean for Clinic Affairs at Palmer College of Chiropractic explaining what chiropractic care is and its benefits.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 23 July 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Our second podcast interview was with  Dr. Kurt Wood, Executive Dean – Clinic Affairs, Palmer College of Chiropractic in Davenport, Iowa.  He came to Palmer from Northwestern Health Sciences University where he was Associate Dean – Clinical Services.  At Northwestern he also served as Associate Dean and earlier as Chair and Professor at the College of Chiropractic.  In addition he has written several articles for professional journals.  He received his B.S.-Biology and B.S. Chemistry from Upper Iowa University in 1976 and his Doctor of Chiropractic (D.C.) from Palmer College of Chiropractic in 1979.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, chiropractic, Dr. Kurt Wood, Palmer College</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:26</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/chiropractic.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Massage</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Massage.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>August 1, 2008 interview on Massage with Dr. Leena Guptha, immediate Past President of the American Massage Therapy Association discussing the health benefits of massage therapy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 01 August 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Leena S. Guptha is a doctor of osteopathy and is the immediate Past President of the American Massage Therapy Association.  She is also Dean of the Massage Therapy program at Lehigh Valley College.  Dr. Gupthat received both her N.D. and D.O. from the British College of Naturopathy and Osteopathy and received her degree in acupuncture and traditional Chinese medicine from the British College of Acupuncture in London.  She ws born and raised in the U.K. and currently practices in Bethelhem, PA.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Massage, Dr. Leena Guptha</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:43</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/massage.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Reiki</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Reiki.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>August 7, 2008 interview on Reiki with William Lee Rand, the founder of The International Center for Reiki Training, a Master Teacher of Usui and Karuna Reiki and author of several books on Reiki.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 07 August 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Our guest for Reiki is William Lee Rand, the founder of The International Center for Reiki Training, a Master Teacher of Usui and Karuna Reiki and author of several books on Reiki.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Reiki, William Lee Rand</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:36</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Reiki.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Humor Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HumorTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>August 14, 2008 interview on Laughter or Humor Therapy with Lenny Dave, President of the Association for Applied and Therapeutic Humor.  Chuckle along with this interview!</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 07 August 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Laughter or Humor Therapy is one of mankind's oldest health treatments. Listen as Lenny Dave, President of the Association for Applied and Therapeutic Humor, talks about this wonderful therapy.  He may not be a doctor but he has been known to perform successful surgery on the human spirit!</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, humor, laughter, Lenny Dave, AATH</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:28</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HumorTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Yoga</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Yoga.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>August 21, 2008 interview with Elizabeth Winter, Assistant Editor of Yoga Journal magazine, about the features and benefits of yoga.  September is National Yoga Month.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thurs, Aug. 22, 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>August 21, 2008 interview with Elizabeth Winter, Assistant Editor of Yoga Journal magazine, on the features and benefits of yoga.  This is one of the most popular therapies/exercises in America today with nearly 16 million participants.  September is National Yoga Month.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Elizabeth Winter, Yoga Journal, yoga</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:06</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Yoga.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Healing Touch Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HealingTouch.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>August 28, 2008 interview with Lisa Anselme and Diane Wardell of Healing Touch International about this new therapy and their upcoming annual conference.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 28 August 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Discover one of the newer types of complementary therapy, Healing Touch, in our discussion with Lisa Anselme, Executive Director at Healing Touch International and Diane Wind Wardell, Research Director at Healing Touch.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Healing Touch, Healing Touch International, Lisa Anselme, Diane Wind Wardell</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:03</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HealingTouch.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Crystal Bowl Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/CrystalBowlTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Imara about the ancient therapy using Crystal Bowls for healing with sound.  Also called Singing Bowl Therapy when used with brass or other materials.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 21 August 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Imara about the ancient therapy using Crystal Bowls for healing with sound.  Also called Singing Bowl Therapy when used with brass or other materials.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Imara, Crystal Bowls, Singing Bowl Therapy</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:23:51</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/CrystalBowlTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Touch For Health</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TouchForHealth.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Matthew Thie on September 4, 2008 about Touch For Health.  Matthew is the son of the creator of the Touch For Health therapy, Dr. John F. Thie.  He is an advanced Touch For Health instructor.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 4 September 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Matthew Thie on September 4, 2008 about Touch For Health.  Matthew is the son of the creator of the Touch For Health therapy, Dr. John F. Thie.  He is an advanced Touch For Health instructor.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Touch For Health, Matthew Thie, John F. Thie</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:22:21</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TouchForHealth.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
   <item>
  <title>Psych-K</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Psych-K.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Robert Williams, the creator of the Psych-K process, on September 11, 2008 discussing the features and benefits on this relatively new therapy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 18 September 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Robert Williams, the creator of the Psych-K process, on September 11, 2008 discussing the features and benefits on this relatively new therapy.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Psych-K, Rob Williams</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:47</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Psych-K.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
   <item>
  <title>Traumatic Incident Reduction</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TIR.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Marian Volkman, President of the Traumatic Incident Reduction Association, on September 25, 2008.  She is also a TIR trainer and practitioner along with being an author on the subject.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 25 September 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Marian Volkman, President of the Traumatic Incident Reduction Association, on September 25, 2008.  She is also a TIR trainer and practitioner along with being an author on the subject.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Traumatic Incident Reduction, TIR, Marion Volkman</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:46</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TIR.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Homeopathy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Homeopathy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Manfred Mueller, President of the North American Society of Homeopaths or NASH on October 6, 2008 discussing homeopathy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 06 October 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Manfred Mueller, President of the North American Society of Homeopaths or NASH on October 6, 2008 discussing homeopathy.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, homeopathy, NASH, Manfred Mueller</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:11</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Homeopathy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Gem Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/GemTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Dr. Ada Gonzalez, a Gemstone Energy Medicine Educator in Portland, Oregon.  Dr. Ada is a licensed naturopathic physician who received her undergraduate degree from Cornell University, her masters from Yale and her medical degree from the National College of Naturopathic Medicine.  Enjoy learning about the ancient and worldwide healing arts using gems and crystals.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 17 October 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Dr. Ada Gonzalez, a Gemstone Energy Medicine Educator in Portland, Oregon.  Dr. Ada is a licensed naturopathic physician who received her undergraduate degree from Cornell University, her masters from Yale and her medical degree from the National College of Naturopathic Medicine.  Enjoy learning about the ancient and worldwide healing arts using gems and crystals.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, gem therapy, crystal therapy, Gemisphere, Dr. Ada Gonzalez, gemstone medicine, gemstone energy medicine</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:19:24</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/GemTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Feldenkrais Method</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Feldenkrais.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with MaryBeth Smith, Director of the Feldenkrais Center of Houston and a Certified Feldenkrais Practitioner talking about the healing therapy developed by Dr. Moshe Feldenkrais.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 23 October 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with MaryBeth Smith, Director of the Feldenkrais Center of Houston and a Certified Feldenkrais Practitioner talking about the healing therapy developed by Dr. Moshe Feldenkrais.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, MaryBeth Smith, Feldenkrais Method, Feldenkrais, Moshe Feldenkrais</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:57</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Feldenkrais.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Rolf Structural Integration</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/RolfSI.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Susan Melchoir, School Director for the Rolf Guild in Boulder, Colorado discussing the therapy created by Ida Rolf.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 30 October 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Susan Melchoir, School Director for the Rolf Guild in Boulder, Colorado discussing the therapy created by Ida Rolf.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Susan Melchoir, Rolf Guild, Rolf Guild of Structural Integration, Rolfing, Ida Rolf</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:19:03</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/RolfSI.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Health Freedom</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HealthFreedom.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with attorney Diane Miller, Board Member and spokesman for the National Health Freedom Coalition, about the efforts to protect American's rights to choose complementary and alternative medicine.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 06 November 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with attorney Diane Miller, Board Member and spokesman for the National Health Freedom Coalition, about the efforts to protect American's rights to choose complementary and alternative medicine.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, National Health Freedom Coalition, health freedom, freedom to choose, Diane Miller</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:19:55</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HealthFreedom.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Alexander Technique</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AlexanderTechnique.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on November 13, 2008 with Robert Rickover, author of Fitness Without Stress - A Guide To The Alexander Technique, and an Alexander Technique teacher for 28 years.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 14 November 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on November 13, 2008 with Robert Rickover, author of Fitness Without Stress - A Guide To The Alexander Technique, and an Alexander Technique teacher for 28 years.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Alexander Technique, F. M. Alexander, Robert Rickover, A.T.</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:29</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AlexanderTechnique.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Bruce Lipton</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BruceLipton.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on November 20, 2008 with Bruce Lipton, Ph.D., author of The Biology of Belief.  Dr. Lipton is a cellular biologist whose discoveries led to the new science of Epigenetics.  Today he is an international authority of bridging science and spirit.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 21 November 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on November 20, 2008 with Bruce Lipton, Ph.D., author of The Biology of Belief.  Dr. Lipton is a cellular biologist whose discoveries led to the new science of Epigenetics.  Today he is an international authority of bridging science and spirit.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Bruce Lipton, New Biology, Epigenetics, Biology of Belief</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:53</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BruceLipton.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Reflexology</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Reflexology.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on December 4, 2008 with Cynthia Hill, spokesperson for the Reflexology Association of America and President of the North Carolina Reflexology Association.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 December 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on December 4, 2008 with Cynthia Hill, spokesperson for the Reflexology Association of America and President of the North Carolina Reflexology Association.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Cynthia Hill, reflexology</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:36</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Reflexology.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Berard AIT</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AIT.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on December 18, 2008 with Sally Brockett, President of the Berard Auditory Intervention Training International Society and Director of the IDEA Training Center.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 December 2008 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on December 18, 2008 with Sally Brockett, President of the Berard Auditory Intervention Training International Society and Director of the IDEA Training Center.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Sally Brockett, Berard AIT, auditory intervention training, AIT</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:16</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AIT.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Hypnosis</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Hypnosis.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Dr. Mark Weisberg, Vice President of the American Society of Clinical Hypnosis and past President of the Minnesota Society of Clinical Hypnosis, on the health uses of hypnosis.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 02 January 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Dr. Mark Weisberg, Vice President of the American Society of Clinical Hypnosis and past President of the Minnesota Society of Clinical Hypnosis, on the health uses of hypnosis.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Mark Weisberg, hypnosis, clinical hypnosis</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:37</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Hypnosis.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>TTouch For You</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TTouch.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Linda Tellington-Jones, creator of TTouch For You, and Founder/President of TTouch Training.  Linda has been inducted into the Massage Hall of Fame and the Western States Horse Expo Hall of Fame.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 11 January 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Linda Tellington-Jones, creator of TTouch For You, and Founder/President of TTouch Training.  Linda has been inducted into the Massage Hall of Fame and the Western States Horse Expo Hall of Fame.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Linda Tellington-Jones, TTouch, TTouch For You</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:20</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TTouch.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>The Sedona Method</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/SedonaMethod.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Hale Dwoskin, co-founder and CEO of Sedona Training Associates and author of the New York Times best seller The Sedona Method: Your Key To Lasting Happiness, Success, Peace and Emotional Well-Being.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 23 January 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Hale Dwoskin, co-founder and CEO of Sedona Training Associates and author of the New York Times best seller The Sedona Method: Your Key To Lasting Happiness, Success, Peace and Emotional Well-Being.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Hale Dwoskin, Sedona Method, The Secret</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:22:00</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/SedonaMethod.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>The Relox Procedure</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Relox.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Dr. Bruce Rind, creator of the Relox Procedure for healing stroke and other brain injuries.  Dr. Rind's unique combination of training in anesthesiology, nutrition and osteopathy combined to meet the needs of his patients in an effective new procedure to treat stroke and other brain injuries.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thurs, 29 January 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Dr. Bruce Rind, creator of the Relox Procedure for healing stroke and other brain injuries.  Dr. Rind's unique combination of training in anesthesiology, nutrition and osteopathy combined to meet the needs of his patients in an effective new procedure to treat stroke and other brain injuries.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Dr. Bruce Rind, Relox, Relox Procedure</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:28</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Relox.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Transcendental Meditation</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TranscendentalMeditation.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Linda Lasseter, Ph.D., the Director of the Dallas/Ft. Worth Transcendental Meditation Program.  She was trained by the originator of TM, Maharishi Mahesh Yogi, to become a Certified TM teacher and has been teaching the technique for decades.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thurs, 12 February 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Linda Lasseter, Ph.D., the Director of the Dallas/Ft. Worth Transcendental Meditation Program.  She was trained by the originator of TM, Maharishi Mahesh Yogi, to become a Certified TM teacher and has been teaching the technique for decades.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Transcendental Meditation, TM, Linda Lasseter, meditation</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:32</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TranscendentalMeditation.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Acupuncture</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Acupuncture.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on February 16, 2009 with Mr. Bill Reddy, Vice President of the American Association of Acupuncture and Oriental Medicine about this ancient healing therapy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 February 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on February 16, 2009 with Mr. Bill Reddy, Vice President of the American Association of Acupuncture and Oriental Medicine about this ancient healing therapy.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Acupuncture, Oriental Medicine, Traditional Chinese Medicine, TCM, Bill Reddy</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:30</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Acupuncture.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Cognitive Behavior Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/CognitiveBehaviorTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on February 19, 2009 with Dr. David D. Burns, Adjunct Clinical Professor of Psychiatry Emeritus at Stanford University School of Medicine and author of several books on CBT and now CIT.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 February 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on February 19, 2009 with Dr. David D. Burns, Adjunct Clinical Professor of Psychiatry Emeritus at Stanford University School of Medicine and author of several books on CBT and now CIT.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Cognitive Behavior Therapy, CBT, Cognitive Interpersonal Therapy, CIT, Dr. David Burns, Dr. Burns, Feeling Good, Feeling Good Together, When Panic Attacks</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:02</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/CognitiveBehaviorTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>NLP</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/NLP.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on March 4, 2009 with Richard Bandler, father and co-creator of Neuro-Linguistic Programming or NLP.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 07 March 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on March 4, 2009 with Richard Bandler, father and co-creator of Neuro-Linguistic Programming or NLP.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Neuro-Linguistic Programming, NLP, Richard Bandler</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:40</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/NLP.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Naturopathy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Naturopathy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on March 9, 2009 with Dr. Lise Alshuler, President of the American Association of Naturopathic Physicians an Board certified naturopathic physician specializing in oncology.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 14 March 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on March 9, 2009 with Dr. Lise Alshuler, President of the American Association of Naturopathic Physicians an Board certified naturopathic physician specializing in oncology.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Naturopathy, naturopathic medicine, Dr. Lise Alshuler, AANP</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:40</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Naturopathy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Aromatherapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Aromatherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Kelly Holland Azzaro, Vice President of the National Association for Holistic Aromatherapy, a Registered Aromatherapist, a Certified Clinical Aromatherapy Practitioner and Certified Bach Flower Practitioner about Aromatherapy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 22 March 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Kelly Holland Azzaro, Vice President of the National Association for Holistic Aromatherapy, a Registered Aromatherapist, a Certified Clinical Aromatherapy Practitioner and Certified Bach Flower Practitioner about Aromatherapy.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, NAHA, Kelly Holland Azzaro, aromatherapy, essential oil, smell</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:08</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Aromatherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Animal Assisted Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AnimalAssistedTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with JoAnn Turnbull, the Director of Marketing for the Delta Society.  Founded in 1977 the organization now has 10,000 members in the U.S. and in seveeral foreign countries.  Learn more about the health benefits of our furry and feathered friends.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 April 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with JoAnn Turnbull, the Director of Marketing for the Delta Society.  Founded in 1977 the organization now has 10,000 members in the U.S. and in seveeral foreign countries.  Learn more about the health benefits of our furry and feathered friends.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Animal Assisted Therapy, Animal Assisted Activities, Delta Society, service animals, therapy animals, JoAnn Turnbull</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:35</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AnimalAssistedTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>The Silva Method</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/SilvaMethod.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on April 6, 2009 with Laura Silva Quesada, President of Silva International and daughter of the process creator, Jose Silva.  Laura has presented the Silva Method for 30 years, is the author of For Parents Only and authro/producer of the Silva Life System.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 April 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on April 6, 2009 with Laura Silva Quesada, President of Silva International and daughter of the process creator, Jose Silva.  Laura has presented the Silva Method for 30 years, is the author of For Parents Only and authro/producer of the Silva Life System..</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Silva Method, Silva Mind Control, Jose Silva, Laura Silva Quesada</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:25</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/SilvaMethod.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Feng Shui</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/FengShui.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on April 14, 2009 with Rosalie Prinzivalli, Board Chair of the International Feng Shui Guild, and Laurie Bornstein, CEO of the Guild discussing the health aspects of this ancient practice.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 15 April 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on April 14, 2009 with Rosalie Prinzivalli, Board Chair of the International Feng Shui Guild, and Laurie Bornstein, CEO of the Guild discussing the health aspects of this ancient practice.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, feng shui, International Feng Shui Guild, Rosalie Prinzivalli, Laurie Bornstein</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:19:59</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/FengShui.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Environmental Medicine</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/EnvironmentalMedicine.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on April 27, 2009 with Dr. Amy Dean, Board Member of the American Academy of Environmental Medicine and Chairman of the Public Relations Committee.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 30 April 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on April 27, 2009 with Dr. Amy Dean, Board Member of the American Academy of Environmental Medicine and Chairman of the Public Relations Committee.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, environmental medicine, American Academy of Environmental Medicine, Dr. Amy Dean</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:42</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/EnvironmentalMedicine.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Quantum Techniques</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/QuantumTechnqiues.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on May 22, 2009 with Dr. Stephen Daniel and Beth Daniel about this EFT "cousin" technique for healing.  Dr. Daniel created the process after 22 years as a psychotherapist and psychologist.</description> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on May 22, 2009 with Dr. Stephen Daniel and Beth Daniel about this EFT "cousin" technique for healing.  Dr. Daniel created the process after 22 years as a psychotherapist and psychologist.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Quantum Techniques, Dr. Stephen Daniel, Beth Daniel, EFT cousin</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:03</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/QuantumTechniques.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Bonnie Prudden Myotherapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BonniePruddenMyotherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on June 5, 2009 with Bonnie Prudden, America's First Lady of Fitness.  The 2007 recipient of the President's Council Lifetime Achievement Award Bonnie wrote the first book on physical fitness, followed by 18 more.  In 1980 she created a new type of mythoerapy to relieve 95% of muscle pain.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 June 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on June 5, 2009 with Bonnie Prudden, America's First Lady of Fitness.  The 2007 recipient of the President's Council Lifetime Achievement Award Bonnie wrote the first book on physical fitness, followed by 18 more.  In 1980 she created a new type of mythoerapy to relieve 95% of muscle pain.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Bonnie Prudden, Myotherapy, Bonnie Prudden Myotherapy</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:35</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BonniePruddenMyotherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Medical Intuition</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/MedicalIntuition.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on June 8, 2009 with Francesca McCartney, PhD in Energy Medicine and Intuition Medicine, Founder/President of the Academy of Intuition Medicine and the Energy Medicine University.</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 June 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on June 8, 2009 with Francesca McCartney, PhD in Energy Medicine and Intuition Medicine, Founder/President of the Academy of Intuition Medicine and the Energy Medicine University.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, medical intuition, medical intuitive, psychic, intuitive, Francesca McCartney, Academy of Intuition Medicine, Energy Medicine University</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:16</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/MedicalIntuition.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Trager Approach</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TragerApproach.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on June 11, 2009 with Roger Tolle, spokesman for the United States Trager Association and an instructor and practitioner for 20 years.</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 June 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on June 11, 2009 with Roger Tolle, spokesman for the United States Trager Association and an instructor and practitioner for 20 years.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Roger Tolle, Trager Approach, Dr. Milton Trager, United States Trager Association</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:19</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TragerApproach.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Qigong</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Qigong.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on June 18, 2009 with Dean Johnson, spokesman for the Qigong Association of America, Qigong practitioner and instructor.</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 June 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on June 18, 2009 with Dean Johnson, spokesman for the Qigong Association of America, Qigong practitioner and instructor.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Qigong, American Qigong Association, Dean Johnson, Whole Health Clinic</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:19:41</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Qigong.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Biofeedback</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Biofeedback.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on July 9, 2009 with Dr. John G. Arena, President of the Association for Applied PsychoPhysiology and Biofeedback on Biofeedback therapy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 14 July 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on July 9, 2009 with Dr. John G. Arena, President of the Association for Applied PsychoPhysiology and Biofeedback on Biofeedback therapy.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, biofeedback, psychophysiology, Dr. John Arena, John Arena, Ph.D., AAPB</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:15</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Biofeedback.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Pranic Healing</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/PranicHealing.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on July 15, 2009 with Master Stephen Co, senior disciple and personal student of Grandmaster Choa Kok Sui, United States Master Pranic Healer and Senior Qualified Instructor.</description> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 21 July 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on July 15, 2009 with Master Stephen Co, senior disciple and personal student of Grandmaster Choa Kok Sui, United States Master Pranic Healer and Senior Qualified Instructor.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Pranic Healing, Master Stephen Co, Grandmaster Choa Kok Sui, energy medicine, Dr. Eric Robins</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:11</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/PranicHealing.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Naprapathy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Naprapathy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on July 16, 2009 with Dr. Wayne Cichowicz, Academic Dean at the National College of Naprapathic Medicine in Chicago and President of the American College of Physical Medicine.</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 03, Aug 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on July 16, 2009 with Dr. Wayne Cichowicz, Academic Dean at the National College of Naprapathic Medicine in Chicago and President of the American College of Physical Medicine.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Naprapathy, National College of Naprapathic Medicine, Dr. Wayne Cichowicz, naprapathic medicine</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:33</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Naprapathy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>AIM Energetic Balacing</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AIM.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on August 13, 2009 with Stephen Lewis, creator of the AIM Energetic Balancing program and co-author of Santuary: The Path to Consciousness.</description> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 18, Aug 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on August 13, 2009 with Stephen Lewis, creator of the AIM Energetic Balancing program and co-author of Santuary: The Path to Consciousness.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, AIM, AIM Energetic Balancing, EMC2, Stephen Lewis, Santuary: The Path to Consciousness, energy healing</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:19:49</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AIM.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Radical Forgiveness</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/RadicalForgiveness.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on August 27, 2009 with Colin Tipping, creator of the Radical Forgiveness Process and author of the 1997 book Radical Forgiveness: Making Room For The Miracle.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 28, Aug 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on August 27, 2009 with Colin Tipping, creator of the Radical Forgiveness Process and author of the 1997 book Radical Forgiveness: Making Room For The Miracle.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Colin Tipping, Radical Forgiveness, Radical Forgiveness: Making Room for the Miracle</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:17</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/RadicalForgiveness.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>BodyTalk System</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BodyTalkSystem.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on September 3, 2009 with Dr. John Veltheim, creator of the BodyTalk System therapy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 09, Sept 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on September 3, 2009 with Dr. John Veltheim, creator of the BodyTalk System therapy.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Dr. John Veltheim, John Veltheim, BodyTalk, BodyTalk System</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:08</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BodyTalkSystem.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>CranioSacral Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/CranioSacralTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview on September 30, 2009 with Dr. Lisa Upledger, wife of the creator of CranioSacral Therapy Dr. John Upledger, and a practioner for 28 years.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 03, Oct 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview on September 30, 2009 with Dr. Lisa Upledger, wife of the creator of CranioSacral Therapy Dr. John Upledger, and a practioner for 28 years.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Dr. Lisa Upledger, Dr. Upledger, CranioSacral Therapy, CST, SomatoEmotional Therapy, craniosacral therapy</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:18</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/CranioSacralTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>SKENAR and Biomodulator</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/SKENAR-Biomodulator.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Dr. Jerry Tennant, creator of the Biomodulator Plus device based on the concepts of the Russian SKENAR technology.</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 12, Oct 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Dr. Jerry Tennant, creator of the Biomodulator Plus device based on the concepts of the Russian SKENAR technology.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Dr. Jerry Tennant, Tennant Institute, SKENAR, Biomodulator, Biomodulator Plus</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:54</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/SKENAR-Biomodulator.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Bioenergetic Analysis</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BioenergeticAnalysis.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Rick Spletter, President of the Dallas Society for Bioenergetic Analysis.  Rick has been using Bioenergetic Analysis with clients for 30 years and has presented many workshops and trainings on the therapy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 18, Oct 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Rick Spletter, President of the Dallas Society for Bioenergetic Analysis.  Rick has been using Bioenergetic Analysis with clients for 30 years and has presented many workshops and trainings on the therapy.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Rick Spletter, Dallas Society for Bioenergetic Analysis, Bioenergetic Analysis, Dr. Alexander Lowen</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:29</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BioenergeticAnalysis.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Hellerwork Structural Integration</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HellerworkSI.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>The 49th program features an interview with Joseph Heller, creator of Hellerwork Structural Integration, talking about his unique therapy built on a foundation of Rolfing.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 30, Oct 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>The 49th program features an interview with Joseph Heller, creator of Hellerwork Structural Integration, talking about his unique therapy built on a foundation of Rolfing.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Hellerwork, Hellerwork Structural Integration, Joseph Heller, bodywork, structural integration</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:48</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HellerworkSI.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Bach Flower Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BachFlowerTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>The 50th program featured Stefan Ball of the Bach Flower Centre in England talking about the unique system of herbal essences developed by Dr. Edward Bach nearly 70 years ago.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 08, Nov 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>The 50th program featured Stefan Ball of the Bach Flower Centre in England talking about the unique system of herbal essences developed by Dr. Edward Bach nearly 70 years ago.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Bach Flower Essences, Bach Flower Therapy, Bach Flower, Dr. Edward Bach, Stefan Ball, Bach Centre</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:10</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BachFlowerTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Electrotherapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Electrotherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith interviews George O'Clock, Ph.D. former president of IABC on the work of Dr. Bjorn Nordenstrom and the new world of electrotherapy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 20, Nov 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith interviews George O'Clock, Ph.D. former president of IABC on the work of Dr. Bjorn Nordenstrom and the new world of electrotherapy.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Dr. Bjorn Nordenstrom, IABC, Biologically Closed Electric Circuits, Dr. George O'Clock</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:05</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Electrotherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Edgar Cayce's Radiac</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/EdgarCayceRadiac.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith interviews Thomas Dewey about Edgar Cayce's Radiac, also called Radio Active or Radial Appliance.  Tom is the spokesman for the Association for Research and Enlightenment and has experience building the device.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 03, Dec 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith interviews Thomas Dewey about Edgar Cayce's Radiac, also called Radio Active or Radial Appliance.  Tom is the spokesman for the Association for Research and Enlightenment and has experience building the device.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Edgar Cayce, Association for Research and Enlightenment, Radiac, Radial Appliance, Radioactive, energy medicine device</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:52</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/EdgarCayceRadiac.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Polarity Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/PolarityTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith interviews Mary Jo Ruggieri, PhD, RPP, spokesperson for the American Polarity Therapy Association and Director of the Columbus Polarity Center for Integrative Health and Wellness about the therapy developed by Dr. Randolf Stone in Chicago.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 11, Dec 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith interviews Mary Jo Ruggieri, PhD, RPP, spokesperson for the American Polarity Therapy Association and Director of the Columbus Polarity Center for Integrative Health and Wellness about the therapy developed by Dr. Randolf Stone in Chicago.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Polarity Therapy, Mary Jo Ruggieri, American Polarity Therapy Association</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:14</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/PolarityTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Therapeutic Touch</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TherapeuticTouch.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith interviews Diane May, president of of the Therapeutic Touch International Association and author of several books on Therapeutic Touch about this American innovation.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 18, Dec 2009 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith interviews Diane May, president of of the Therapeutic Touch International Association and author of several books on Therapeutic Touch about this American innovation.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Therapeutic Touch, TT, Diane May, Therapeutic Touch International Association</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:00</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TherapeuticTouch.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Secrets of New Science and Old Medicine</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Secrets of New Science and Old Medicine.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith presents his most popular speech introducing the world of complementary and alternative medicine.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 01, Jan 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith presents his most popular speech introducing the world of complementary and alternative medicine.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, speaker</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:18:42</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Secrets of New Science and Old Medicine.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^ 
  <item>
  <title>Art Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/ArtTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith talks with Dr. Patricia Isis, spokesperson for the American Art Therapy Association and art therapy practitioner for 30 years about Art Therapy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 14, Jan 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith talks with Dr. Patricia Isis, spokesperson for the American Art Therapy Association and art therapy practitioner for 30 years about Art Therapy.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Art Therapy, Dr. Patricia Isis, American Art Therapy Association</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:37</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/ArtTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
   <item>
  <title>Integrative Medicine</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/IntegrativeMedicine.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith talks with Dr. Eleanor D. Hynote, President and CEO of the American College for Advancement in Medicine and Founder/Director of Phoenix Well Care in Napa, California about the trend towards Integrative Medicine.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 14, Jan 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith talks with Dr. Eleanor D. Hynote, President and CEO of the American College for Advancement in Medicine and Founder/Director of Phoenix Well Care in Napa, California about the trend towards Integrative Medicine.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Integrative Medicine, Phoenix Well Care, Dr. Elenor Hynote, ACAM, American College for Advancement in Medicine</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:45</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/IntegrativeMedicine.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Doula</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Doula.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith talks with Susan Toffolon, President of DONA International, about Doulas and their part in the birth process.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 11, Feb 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith talks with Susan Toffolon, President of DONA International, about Doulas and their part in the birth process.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, doula, Doulas, DONA International, Susan Toffolon, childbirth, birth</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:34</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Doula.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Bowen Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BowenTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith spoke with Deni Larimore Albrecht, Administrative Director of Bowen Therapy International.  She and her late husband Milton sponsored the first Bowen seminar outside of the South Pacific in 1989 and began Bowen Therapy International.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 24, Feb 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith spoke with Deni Larimore Albrecht, Administrative Director of Bowen Therapy International.  She and her late husband Milton sponsored the first Bowen seminar outside of the South Pacific in 1989 and began Bowen Therapy International.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Bowen Therapy, Bowen Therapy International, Deni Larimore Albrecht, Milton Albrecht, Tom Bowen</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:18:39</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BowenTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Bee Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BeeTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith spoke with Frederique Keller, President of the American Apitherapy Society about Bee Venom Therapy (BVT) and other bee treatments.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 18, March 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith spoke with Frederique Keller, President of the American Apitherapy Society about Bee Venom Therapy (BVT) and other bee treatments.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Bee Venom Therapy, BVT, honey, American Apitherapy Society, bees</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:34</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BeeTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>NAET</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/NAET.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith spoke with Dr. Devi Nambudripad about how her own quest for better health led to the development of Nambudripad Allergy Elimination Technique or NAET in 1983.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 18, June 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith spoke with Dr. Devi Nambudripad about how her own quest for better health led to the development of Nambudripad Allergy Elimination Technique or NAET in 1983.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, NAET, Dr. Devi Nambudripad, Nambudripad Allergy Elimination Technique</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:28</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/NAET.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Pilates</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Pilates.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith spoke with Trent McEntire, President of the Board for the Pilates Method Alliance about Joseph Pilates and the history of his unique therapy and exercise program.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 25, June 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith spoke with Trent McEntire, President of the Board for the Pilates Method Alliance about Joseph Pilates and the history of his unique therapy and exercise program.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Pilates, Joseph Pilates, Pilates Method, Pilates Method Alliance, Trent McEntire, McEntire Pilates</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:21</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Pilates.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Hyperbaric Oxygen Therapy (HBOT)</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HBOT.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith spoke with Shannon Kenitz, Executive Director of the International Hyperbarics Association, about the health benefits of oxygen and pressure.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 11, July 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith spoke with Shannon Kenitz, Executive Director of the International Hyperbarics Association, about the health benefits of oxygen and pressure.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, HBOT, Hyperbaric Oxygen Therapy, International Hyperbarics Association, Shannon Kinetz</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:44</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HBOT.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
   <item>
  <title>Ayurveda</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Ayurveda.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith spoke Dr. Bhaswati Bhattacharya about the ancient medical system of Ayurveda and its growing popularity in America</description> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 17, July 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith spoke Dr. Bhaswati Bhattacharya about the ancient medical system of Ayurveda and its growing popularity in America.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, complementary and alternative medicine, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Bowen Therapy, Bowen Therapy International, Deni Larimore Albrecht, Milton Albrecht, Tom Bowen</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:24:22</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Ayurveda.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Tapas Acupressure Technique</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TAT.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith spoke with Tapas Fleming, the creator of the Tapas Acupressure Technique or TAT, about her unique form of energy healing.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 22, July 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith spoke with Tapas Fleming, the creator of the Tapas Acupressure Technique or TAT, about her unique form of energy healing.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Tapas Fleming, TAT, Tapas Acupressure Technique</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:12</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/TAT.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Mindfulness</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Mindfulness.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith spoke with Dr. Karen Sherman, a New York psychologist with 20 years of experience, about Mindfulness and her book Mindfulness and the Art of Choice.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 12, Aug 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith spoke with Dr. Karen Sherman, a New York psychologist with 20 years of experience, about Mindfulness and her book Mindfulness and the Art of Choice.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Mindfulness, Jon kabat-Zinn, Dr. Karen Sherman, Mindfulness and the Art of Choice</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:21</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Mindfulness.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Watsu</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Watsu.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Alan Smith spoke with Harold Dull, the creator of Watsu, a unique warm-water therapeutic bodywork process.  This therapy is all about relaxation which is why it's so popular at spas and health centers.</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 30, Aug 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Alan Smith spoke with Harold Dull, the creator of Watsu, a unique warm-water therapeutic bodywork process.  This therapy is all about relaxation which is why it's so popular at spas and health centers.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Watsu, Tantsu, Harold Dull, water therapy, Zen Shiatsu</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:19:01</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/Watsu.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Healing from the Body Level Up</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HBLU.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Judith Swack, creator of Healing from the Body Level Up, about her journey from scientist to healer and the therapy she built from other treatments.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 01 October 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Judith Swack, creator of Healing from the Body Level Up, about her journey from scientist to healer and the therapy she built from other treatments.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Judith Swack, Healing from the Body Level Up, HBLU</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:59</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/HBLU.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Ayurveda and NAMA</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AyurvedaNAMA.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Devi Mueller, Clinical Ayurvedic Specialist and President of the National Ayurvedic Medical Association about the organization's efforts to promote Ayurveda.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 15 October 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Devi Mueller, Clinical Ayurvedic Specialist and President of the National Ayurvedic Medical Association about the organization's efforts to promote Ayurveda.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Ayurveda, NAMA, ayurveda, Devi Mueller, National Ayurvedic Medical Association</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:02</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AyurvedaNAMA.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Jin Shin Jyutsu</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/JinShinJyutsu.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with David Burmeister, President of JSJ, Inc. and son of Mary Burmeister, who brought JSJ to America from Japan more than 50 years ago..</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 November 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with David Burmeister, President of JSJ, Inc. and son of Mary Burmeister, who brought JSJ to America from Japan more than 50 years ago.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, David Burmeister, Mary Burmeister, Jin Shin Jyutsu, JSJ</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:38</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/JinShinJyutsu.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>IBMT</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/IBMT.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Dr. Yi-Yuan Tang, creator of Integrated Body-Mind Training (IBMT), from the ancient wisdom of Traditional Chinese Medicine.  This is one of the newest but most researched types of CAM.</description> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Dr. Yi-Yuan Tang, creator of Integrated Body-Mind Training (IBMT), from the ancient wisdom of Traditional Chinese Medicine.  This is one of the newest but most researched types of CAM.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Dr. Yi-Yuan Tang, Integrated Body-Mind Training, IBMT, University of Oregon, Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:15</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/IBMT.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Dr. Roy Martina</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/RoyMartina.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Dr. Roy Martina about his new book coming out in America on March 15, 2011 called EMOTIONAL BALANCE.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 03 Feb 2011 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Dr. Roy Martina about his new book coming out in America on March 15, 2011 called EMOTIONAL BALANCE.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Dr. Yi-Yuan Tang, Integrated Body-Mind Training, IBMT, University of Oregon, Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:19</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/RoyMartina.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Biomagnetic Therapy</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BiomagneticTherapy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Suzy Balliett, Dean of the Biomagnetic Institute,about the history and use of Biomagnetic Therapy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thur, 17 February 2011 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Suzy Balliett, Dean of the Biomagnetic Institute,about the history and use of Biomagnetic Therapy.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Biomagnetic Therapy, Biomagnetic Institute, Suzy Balliett, biomagnetics</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:13</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/BiomagneticTherapy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>The China Study</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/ChinaStudy.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with the co-author of The China Study, T. Colin Campbell, PhD. about the relationship of diet to our health.  Even President Clinton credits The China Study for his weight loss and improved health.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 13 March, 2011 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with the co-author of The China Study, T. Colin Campbell, PhD. about the relationship of diet to our health.  Even President Clinton credits The China Study for his weight loss and improved health.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, The China Study, T. Colin Campbell, Dr. T. Colin Campbell, T. Colin Campbell PhD, diet, nutrition</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:22:44</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/ChinaStudy.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>An Alphabet of Good Health</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AlphabetofHealth.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Dr. Martha Grout discussing her award-winning book An Alphabet of Good Health in a Sick World.  Dr. Grout is Vice President of the Arizona Board of Homeopathic and Integrated Medicine Examiners.</description> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Dr. Martha Grout discussing her award-winning book An Alphabet of Good Health in a Sick World.  Dr. Grout is Vice President of the Arizona Board of Homeopathic and Integrated Medicine Examiners.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, An Alphabet of Good Health, Dr. Martha Grout, Mary Budinger</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:19:49</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/AlphabetofHealth.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>EFT</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/EFT.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Tina Craig, daughter of EFT creator Gary Craig, about the status and future of one of the world's most popular therapies.</description> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Tina Craig, daughter of EFT creator Gary Craig, about the status and future of one of the world's most popular therapies.</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, EFT, Emotional Freedom Technique, Gary Craig, Tina Craig, tapping</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:20:09</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/EFT.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  <item>
  <title>Iyengar Yoga</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/IyengarYoga.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Interview with Dr. Rajvi Mehta, editor of Yoga Rahasya, teacher at the Iyengar Yoga institute in Mumbai and a student for over 30 years.</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 August 2011 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Interview with Dr. Rajvi Mehta, editor of Yoga Rahasya, teacher at the Iyengar Yoga institute in Mumbai and a student for over 30 years.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, Iyengar Yoga, BKS Iyengar, yoga, Rajvi Mehta</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:17:44</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/IyengarYoga.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
   <item>
  <title>Intro to EFT</title> 
  <link>http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/EFTIntro.mp3</link> 
  <itunes:author>Alan Smith</itunes:author> 
  <dc:creator>Alan Smith</dc:creator> 
  <description>Introduction to Emotional Freedom Technique or EFT with Tina Craig, daughter of EFT creator Gary Craig, one of the most popular therapies in the world.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thurs, 08 September 2011 GMT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:summary>Introduction to Emotional Freedom Technique or EFT with Tina Craig, daughter of EFT creator Gary Craig, one of the most popular therapies in the world.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:keywords>health, wellness, CAM, complementary and alternative, alternative, UnBreak Your Health, Alan Smith, EFT, Emotional Freedom Technique, Tina Craig, Gary Craig</itunes:keywords> 
  <itunes:duration>0:21:02</itunes:duration> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.unbreakyourhealth.com/podcasts/EFTIntro.mp3" length="15204352" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
  </item>
  ^
  </channel>
  ^
  </rss>
