<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Say Boo to the Flu</title>
        <description>Learn about the CDC's recommendation for all healthy children 6 months to 5 years old get vaccinated against the flu.</description>
        <link>http://www.sayboototheflu.com</link>
        <copyright>2006 Say Boo to the Flu</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 4 Oct 2006 11:42:14 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>mail@citycastmedia.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Wed, 4 Oct 2006 11:40:14 -0400</pubDate>
        <generator>CityCast Media http://www.citycastmedia.com</generator>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.citycastonline.com/boototheflu/flu.gif</url>
            <title>Say Boo to the Flu</title>
            <link>http://www.sayboototheflu.com</link>
            <width>86</width>
            <height>60</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>Say Boo to the Flu</title>
            <description>This flu season, for the first time, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) recommends all healthy children 6 months to 5 years old get vaccinated against the flu.  However, a recent survey found that only 16 percent of parents were aware of these new, expanded recommendations. That is why, Families Fighting Flu, a group of families who experienced the loss of a child to the flu, many Visiting Nurse Associations and The Clorox Company joined forces to say Boo to the flu with a national campaign to raise awareness of the importance of flu vaccinations for children. At Say Boo to the Flu events, local Visiting Nurse Association nurses will administer flu vaccines and distribute prevention tips to teach children and parents how to scare away the flu virus this season. Families can visit www.sayboototheflu.com to find the nearest Say Boo to the Flu event or other flu vaccination events in their area, and learn more information about the seriousness of the flu. In this Podcast, members Gary and Doris Stein from Families Fighting Flu (FFF) and B.K. Morris from the Visiting Nurse Association (VNA) discuss the importance of vaccinating children against the flu virus and other ways to help prevent the spread of the flu virus.</description>
            <link>http://sayboototheflu.com</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.citycastonline.com/boototheflu/sayboototheflupodcast.mp3" length="1854271" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.citycastonline.com/boototheflu/sayboototheflupodcast.mp3</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 4 Oct 2006 11:23:36 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
