<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
  <itunes:new-feed-url>http://joankenley.com/podcast/TheJoanKenleyShow.xml</itunes:new-feed-url>
    <title>Dr. Joan Kenley's Conversations on Wellness, Love, Relationships, Politics, Health, Green living, and Transformation</title>
    <link>http://www.joankenley.com</link>
    <description>Dr. Joan Kenley\'s Conversations on Wellness, Love, Relationships, Politics, Health, Green living, and Transformation</description>
    <generator>Feeder 1.4 http://reinventedsoftware.com/feeder/</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <language>en</language>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 16:56:07 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 5:40:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
    <itunes:subtitle>Conversations on Wellness, Love, Relationships, Politics, Health, Green living, and Transformation</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>The Joan Kenley Show - branded as Conversation Radio - is dedicated to
conversations that matter: healthy living, green relationships,
progressive politics, and sustainability at every level. We inspire listeners with
new thinking and action ideas, ranging from the personal to the global.</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:keywords>wellness, love, relationships, health, green, living, natural, healthy, spirit, alternative</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.joankenley.com/images/JoanKenley_3-1.jpg" />
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Joan Kenley</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>joan@joankenley.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
    <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
        <itunes:category text="Philosophy" />
        <itunes:category text="Personal Journals" />
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:category text="Health"/>
<!-- Podcast Alley - A Directory -->
<item>
      <title>Feed Claim</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.podcastalley.com/"> My Podcast Alley feed!</a> {pca-a445f622a1036601f47e7d0599d453a2}]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 16:48:12 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">feed-claim</guid>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
 </item>
<!-- Joan Kenley Shows start here -->
<!-- Use Archive.org URLs for MP3 files -->
<!-- Enter New Show Just Below This Comment - Most Recent to Least Recent -->
<!-- make last build date one day AFTER show date -->

<!-- The Media: What's True, What's Not | Repeat 8-5-11 - NEW SHOW 4-11-09 -->
<item>
      <title>The Media: What's True, What's Not</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20120505.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>We're delighted to post new updates about our impressive guests, as we re-visit this important program. Our 24/7 media cycle is dominated by opinionated news pundits and an onslaught of celebrity or person-of-the-moment headlines. Do we create a false reality from false information? How do our reactions impact our lives – personally and collectively – from politics to war to the economy to and to our planet's very survival? Not afraid to challenge media spin with their own brand of truth-telling, Peter and Norman share their wisdom on how to best navigate through all the noise.  You'll hear:
</p><p>
    * how headlines are shaped by the media, government, and corporations<br />
    * the ways we are influenced by "dis-info-tainment"<br />  
    * inside stories that may challenge your opinions<br />     
    * reliable sources you can reference for accurate reporting</p>
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Norman Solomon is running for the House of Representatives in California’s new 2nd Congressional District, has authored a dozen books - including, "War Made Easy: How Presidents and Pundits keep Spinning Us to Death" and "Made Love, Got War: Close Encounters With America's Warfare State." A nationally syndicated columnist on media and politics since 1992 - he's been featured in the NY Times, Washington Post, USA Today, and LA Times, and is frequently published on truthout.org. A recipient of the esteemed George Orwell award, Solomon founded the Institute for Public Accuracy in 1998 and serves as executive director. www.SolomonForCongress.com
</p>
<p>Peter B. Collins is a well-known broadcaster, entrepreneur, and media consultant based in San Francisco. He is one of the owners of KRXA/540, the progressive talk station serving Monterey, Salinas and Santa Cruz. From 2005 to March 2009, he hosted the Peter B. Collins Show - a daily, syndicated radio commentary and call-in program. In his late teens, during the Watergate years, he was a nightly on-air personality and talk show host at Chicago's ABC FM affiliate, and at that intense time in history - his broadcast was rated number one. He's also known as a media consultant. You can find his many podcasts at www.peterbcollins.com
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 18:00:12 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/TheMediaWhatIsTrueWhatIsNot/media-what-is-true.mp3" length="32503160" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">media-what-is-true-what-is-not-2012</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>32:19</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Pet Info: The Latest, The Best "New Media" Version | Formerly Your Pets: Best Love, Best Care KKGN 960 2008 Repeat show with edits -->
<item>
      <title>Pet Info for Pet Smart Care</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20120413.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>It's been said, "Until one has loved an animal, a part of one's soul remains unawakened." Our show includes how pet owners can offer the best kind of love and care - all of which will help pets live longer and healthier. Hear the latest veterinary trends and treatments. And we’ll tell you how dogs, cats, bunnies, and birds are so much smarter than you may imagine! We'll talk about:
</p><p>
    * why the holistic approach to pet care is so important<br />
    * the dual benefits of children reading to dogs<br /> 
    * preventive health care for your animals<br />  
    * what you should consider about pet insurance<br />     
    * how good dental care can keep your pet living longer and better</p>
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Dr. Gary Richter has been a veterinarian in the Bay Area since 1988, and his interests include emergency medicine, general practice, and traditional Chinese veterinary medicine. Gary is the 2009 winner of Bay Area Best Vet Award from Beast of the Bay. He is one
of the founders of the Montclair Pet and Wildlife Fund, a non-profit dedicated to wildlife rescue and orphaned pets. Dr. Richter also helps organize the disaster relief program for animals in Alameda County and sponsors "Pet Mayor for the Day" in Montclair Village. 
http://www.montclairvethospital.com  510-339-8600
</p>
<p>Dr. Bonnie Bergin originated the concept of using service dogs to assist people with mobility impairments over thirty years ago. In 1991, she founded the Assistance Dog Institute – now known as the Bergen University of Canine Studies – in Santa Rosa. It is
the only college in the country offering degrees in Human Canine Life Sciences and Assistance Dog Education, along with the College of Scent Detection – for research and training – as part of the curriculum. Bonnie's numerous awards include Oprah Winfrey's "Use Your Life Award" and the "Presidential Points of Light Award". http://www.assistancedog.org  707-545-3647
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-Pets/Pets_Whole_64kb.mp3" length="23446174" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">pet-info-for-pet-smart-care</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Choosing Happiness repeated 3-22-12 as is and Oct 3 2011 Nov 22 2008 NEW SHOW -->
<item>
      <title>Choosing Happiness</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20120322.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Happiness can be a day-to-day choice -- when you are filled with joy or when times are not so good. Our conversation brings forgiveness, gratitude, and love into the concept of experiencing a happier life. Re-focusing your daily intention and attention about your attitude and behavior can be full of rewards. You'll hear:
</p><p>
    * why inspiration from others can add to your happiness commitment<br />
 * how giving up blame and resentments can soften and open your heart<br />
* about three ways you can process forgiveness<br />
* what it means to live gratitude and the "golden bottom line"<br />
* that happiness and health are true partners for a more joyful life<br />
<p><b>Featured Guest</b><br />
Dr. John Demartini is an international speaker, philosopher, consultant, and author of forty books. He is the founder of the Demartini Human Research and Education Institute, which includes the Studies of Wisdom research and the Concourse of Wisdom. John is the creator of The Breakthrough Experience seminar and originator of The Demartini Method and The Great Discovery www.drdemartini.com</p>
<p><b>Co-host </b><br />Dr. Brenda Wade is a San Francisco-based psychologist, author, television host, and producer. She is also a monthly host on Black Renaissance on the CW Network. Brenda's most recent book is Power Choices: Seven Signposts on Your Journey to Wholeness, Love, Joy and Peace. www.powerchoicestv.com www.docwade.com
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-ChoosingHappiness/ChoosingHappinessFinal_64kb.mp3" length="27579999" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">choosing-happiness-2012</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>57:28</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- The Dream - Reaching the Tipping Point - REPEAT BUT RE-WORKED - 7-28-07 Circle Gatherings: Changing Lives -->
<item>
      <title>Creating Circles Worldwide</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20120303.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>We celebrate that Circles were supported at the recent United Nations 2012 Commission on the Status of Women, where Millionth Circle Convener,
Ann Smith - circleconnections.com - held a dynamic circle session. This podcast shares the dream to raise consciousness everywhere with the creation of a million circles around the globe. The idea is to manifest positive change for our planet through Women's Circles, Men's Circles, Men & Women Circles, Couples Circles, and Intergenerational Circles that are involved in personal, social, cultural, and psycho/spiritual transformation. You will hear about
</p>
* why global circles can create a morphic field for positive change<br />
* what time-honored guidelines add value to circle gatherings<br />
* how various circles have personally affected our lives<br />
* the Millionth Circle Initiative and its Conveners<br />
* circles that are connecting and influencing many cultures<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Jean Shinoda Bolen, MD is an internationally-known author of eleven books, including Goddesses in Everywoman, The Millionth Circle, Urgent Message From Mother - Gather the Women, Save the World, and most recently: Like a Tree. Jean's powerful writing supports peaceful planetary consciousness by encouraging more inclusion of the feminine genius everywhere. Dr. Bolen is a Jungian analyst, activist, speaker, and recently - clinical professor of psychiatry at the University of California, San Francisco. www.jeanbolen.com
</p>
<p>Justine Willis Toms is the acclaimed co-founder of New Dimensions Radio - hosting and producing worldwide broadcasts. Justine's inspiring interviews always include uplifting conversations for her listeners. Her guests have included Riane Eisler, Jane Goodhall, Gloria Steinem, and Alice Walker. Her latest book is Small Pleasures - Finding Grace in a Chaotic World, 50 uplifting and engaging essays on friendships, rituals, animals, nature, circles, and much more. www.newdimensions.org  www.justinewillistoms.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.joankenley.com/podcast/CreatingCirclesWorldwide.mp3" length="49478973" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">creating-circles-worldwide</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>51:31</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- What's Love Got to Do with It - Now Beyond Valentine Love 2011 KKGN 960 2008 Repeat show -->
<item>
      <title>Beyond Valentine Love</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20120218.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Let's go beyond what's possibly seen as a commercial view of Valentine love and remember Tina Turner's award-winning song - "What's Love Got To Do With It?" The lyrics proclaim: "Love is not a second-hand emotion". So, what does it take to keep love alive and have a relationship not only last, but flourish? We'll delve into the challenges of love and offer ways to promote relationship richness and rewards. You'll hear:
</p><p>
    * that difficult times can be transformed into deeper love <br />
    * how men and women do indeed communicate differently<br />   
    * well-tested ideas for singles who want to find the right relationship<br />     
    * why past experiences impact how we perceive our partner<br />  
    * the reason commitment is so integral to relationship<br />
	* what emotional infidelity is and isn't – and why it's important to know the difference<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Brenda Wade, PhD regularly appears on CNN and NBC's Today Show as a psychology expert. Featured on shows such as Oprah and Good Morning America, she hosted both the nationally syndicated Can This Marriage Be Saved? and the national PBS Pledge Special Power Choices. She is the author of four books: Power Choices, Love Lessons, What Mama Couldn't Tell Us About Love, and 99 Things You Wish You Knew Before Falling In Love, and is founder of the International Love, Money & Seva Summit. www.loveandmoneysummit.com www.docwade.com</p>
<p>Ed McClune, MFT works as a licensed Marriage and Family Therapist specializing in couples counseling. He also works as a supervising process teacher for the esteemed Hoffman Institute, where he facilitates transformational workshops throughout the US and Europe. McClune is formerly a San Francisco broadcast host for KBLX, and he currently views his professional work, primarily, as helping couples to restore the faith in their lives and their relationships. www.hoffmaninstitute.org
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-WhatsLoveGotToDoWithIt/TJKS_08_08_Whole.mp3" length="71916772" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">beyond-valentine-love-2012</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:57</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Beyond Valentine Love Repeat show edited for podcast repeated feb 2011, repeated 2-6-12 -->
<item>
      <title>Valentine Love</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20120206.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>More than poems, cards, candy, or flowers, Valentine's Day comes around each year to remind us of both romance and enduring love. Yet we know that relationships involve so much more than the heady passion of the "falling in love" phase: authenticity, loyalty, deep friendship, respect, and so very much more.
</p><p>It's been said, "Where there's love, there's life." We explore the wonders of love and offer some helpful ideas to promote intimacy and handle rough patches. You'll hear:</p>
<p>
    * what dynamics are involved when two people fall in love<br />   
    * stories that describe why love changes over time <br />     
    * the importance of honoring the various stages of loving<br />  
    * why commitment is both sexy and freeing<br />
	* how to create the vital mature phase of a relationship<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Brenda Wade, PhD regularly appears on CNN and NBC's Today Show as a psychology expert. Featured on shows such as Oprah and Good Morning America, she hosted both the nationally syndicated Can This Marriage Be Saved? and the national PBS Pledge Special Power Choices. She is the author of four books: Power Choices, Love Lessons, What Mama Couldn't Tell Us About Love, and 99 Things You Wish You Knew Before Falling In Love, and is founder of the International Love, Money & Seva Summit. www.loveandmoneysummit.com www.docwade.com</p>
<p>Ed McClune, MFT works as a licensed Marriage and Family Therapist specializing in couples counseling. He also works as a supervising process teacher for the esteemed Hoffman Institute, where he facilitates transformational workshops throughout the US and Europe. McClune is formerly a San Francisco broadcast host for KBLX, and he currently views his professional work, primarily, as helping couples to restore the faith in their lives and their relationships. www.hoffmaninstitute.org
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 18:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-BeyondValentineLove/ValentineLove09_64kb.mp3" length="22470030" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">valentine-love-2012</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>46:47</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Choose a Healthy New Year KKGN 960 2007 repeat show -->
<item>
      <title>Choose a Healthy New Year</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20120118.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Can positive choices make you healthier and happier? Is change really possible? It's never too late to learn new ways to truly take care of yourself. English playwright John Dryden once said, "We first make our habits, and then our habits make us." Because everyone can benefit from committing to healthier choices, our conversation explores:
</p><p>
    * what role the mind plays in the habits we have<br />
    * reactions you may experience when you make healthy lifestyle changes<br />   
    * the ways we sabotage ourselves when committing to something new<br />     
    * what happens physiologically when you exercise, eat well, and reduce stress<br />  
    * how cultural norms and the media affect our attitude about ourselves and others<br />
    * why having a spiritual focus can influence a healthier consciousness<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Joyce Gidel is a licensed Marriage Family Therapist and head of the family therapy program at Merritt Peralta Institute, part of Alta Bates-Summit Medical Center. Joyce has a private practice in Oakland and is in the process of writing a book on codependency and spirituality. 510-559-7775, gidelj@sutterhealth.org
</p>
<p>Patty Torza is a certified Personal Fitness Trainer, Post-Rehab Conditioning Specialist, and holistic Nutrition Consultant. She has worked in the fitness profession as an athlete, teacher, administrator, coach, and lecturer. Patty's approach to fitness is goal-oriented, motivating, and fun-filled. 510-835-2745, HealthWorks5@aol.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-HealthyHabits/HealthWhole.mp3" length="71812074" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">choose-a-healthy-new-year-2012</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Authoring Your Life repeated for 2012 - show edited 2008 for podcast -->
<item>
      <title>Authoring Your Life</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20111231.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Authoring your life path for 2012 and beyond is a meaningful choice, and there is always something to learn about how to live more effectively and more heartfully. Our expert panel brings inspiration and suggestions to make this authorship fresh. You'll hear about:
</p><p>
    * the value of setting clear intentions<br />
    * reasons to include grace, gratitude, reflection and forgiveness every day<br />   
    * why anger is such a burden<br />     
    * how important it is to set aside time to listen to inner guidance<br />  
    * when expectations can become an issue<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Gwen Mazer, style consultant, speaker and workshop leader, brings a new dimension to growing in age in the 21st century with her book: Wise Talk, Wild Women, a collection of conversations with prominent luminaries. A former fashion editor and columnist for Harpers Bazaar, she has been a boutique owner in New York and San Francisco. Her workshops and Wild Women Sunday Salons are forums for women exploring their life path. Ms. Mazer's company is Total Image Management. www.gwenmazer.com
</p>
<p>George Schofield, PhD is the author of After 50 It's Up to Us. As a researcher, personal coach, author, speaker, and consultant to employers, he focuses his interest on the skills needed for living well after mid-life and is an expert in human and organizational development, professional career management, and the art of balancing an intelligent life plan. Dr. Schofield is also a founding principle of The Clarity Group, located in San Francisco. www.georgeschofield.com
</p>
<p>Brenda Wade, PhD shares vivid stories and guidelines in her book Power Choices about inner discoveries that are essential for key life transitions. She has earned numerous awards as a psychologist, author, television host, keynote speaker, and seminar leader. Brenda appears weekly on The Today Show and is host of Black Renaissance on the CW Network. Dr. Wade's other books are Love Lessons and What Mama Couldn't Tell Us About Love. www.docwade.com
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-AuthoringYourLife/Tjks7_42_Whole_64kb.mp3" length="23392466" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">authoring-life-2012</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:51</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- RETITLED 2x - Holidays from Thanksgiving - A Time for Gratitude The Gratitude Miracle - A Time for Giving Thanks KKGN 960 2008 Repeat show renamed  -->
<item>
      <title>Holidays Full of Gratefulness and Gratitude</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20111118.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gratefulness and gratitude are intrinsic human qualities that can bring our personal lives more joy, peace, meaning, and ease. Learn about unlocking the fullness of life - turning what we already have into abundance. Paying attention to ourselves with a fierce commitment to deep-felt appreciation can work miracles. You'll hear about:
</p><p>
    * the important work of A Network for Grateful Living (ANG*L)<br />
    * how to cultivate daily gratefulness, acts of kindness, and sustainable activism<br />   
    * music and poetry's positive influence on growing your "attitude of gratitude"<br />     
    * the wild and wonderful "Poetry of Gratefulness" benefit at the Herbst Theatre<br />  
    * some of the best online resources with practices and tools for grateful living<br />
	* the many offerings on www.gratefulness.org – (61/2 million visitors last year!)<br />
	* why gratefulness has the power to unite all religions and beliefs<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Dale Biron is a speaker, poet and integrative coaching specialist to leaders and organizational teams. He is interested in the practical, no nonsense use of poetry in our everyday personal and business lives. Dale is co-founder of Core Action Associates, Inc., an organizational coaching company based in Marin. He serves as a board member and Poetry Editor At Large for ANG*L. www.core-action.com www.dalebiron.com</p> 
<p>Linda Larsson is on the board of ANG*L and is a member of the Board Development Committee. She has been an English Instructor at a community college; an Analyst and Designer for administrative and engineering configuration management systems; and a Sales Administrator and Analyst for a technology company. Linda has also developed and managed residential property. lmlarsson@yahoo.com
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 17:00:01 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-Gratitude/GratitudeWhole_64kb.mp3" length="23953994" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">holidays-gratefulness-and-gratitude</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:52</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Visioning What Can Change edited to Personal Journeys for Global Change 2011 - was KKGN 960 2007 version -->
<item>
      <title>Personal Journeys for Global Change</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20111024.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>When thinking about how personal journeys can affect change, it's interesting to reflect that "the world we are experiencing today is the result of our collective consciousness . . . and if we want a new world, each of us must start taking responsibility for helping to create it." You'll hear an inspiring conversation with two visionary leaders who have devoted their lives to personal transformation and social change. Some of the topics we'll explore include:
</p>
<p>- the journeys that led O'Dea and Jones to the important work they're doing now
</p>
<p>- what steps guarantee an economic win-win for creating "green collar jobs"
</p>
<p>- why personal consciousness and social healing are necessary for true global change
</p>
<p>- how the IONS Shift-in Action program reaches many to encourage societal transformation
</p>
<p>- Van's role in Nancy Pelosi's initiative to create a Clean Energy Jobs Bill and Green Technology Job Centers
</p>
<p>James O'Dea is former President and Extended Faculty of the Institute of Noetic Sciences (IONS), located in Northern California, dedicated to research and education into the frontiers of human consciousness. His recently published book, Creative Stress, focuses on transforming negative stress into positive action. Additionally, James leads the Peace Ambassador Training program, which is our preeminent virtual training with the world's top peacebuilders. O'Dea previously served as the Executive Director for the SEVA Foundation, and Director of the Washington DC office of Amnesty International, where he testified before Congress and served as a representative to the State Department, the White House, and the World Conference on Human Rights. JamesOdea.com TheShiftNetwork.com
</p>
<p>Van Jones is a co-founder of three successful nonprofit organizations: the Ella Baker Center for Human Rights, Color of Change, and Green For All. He is now a leader in the The American Dream Movement. He is also an eco-visionary, civil rights attorney, and public speaker. Van is working to integrate solutions to America's two biggest problems: social inequality and environmental destruction. He serves on the Board of many leading-edge organizations involved in improving community health and promoting responsible business. Jones envisions a national initiative that will create a green pathway out of poverty and diversify the coalitions fighting global warming - reflected in his best-selling book The Green Collar Economy. VanJones.net RebuildTheDream.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/VisioningWhatCanChange/james_odea_van_jones.mp3" length="118495619" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">personal-journeys-for-global-change-2011</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:47</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Repeat Edited Peace Day Show - 2010 with Year change to 2011 -->
<item>
      <title>International Peace Day - 2011</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20110913.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>September 21st is the annual International Day of Peace, when millions of people, worldwide, come together to celebrate and hold Peace Day events - such as concerts, workshops, vigils, and school projects. Based on last year's reports, it is estimated that there will be over 10,000 events, sponsored by thousands of organizations. Over 200 million people will participate in hundreds of countries. Our informative program is dedicated to the people and organizations that contribute to the urgent premise that now is the time for building a peaceful and sustainable planet. This inspiring conversation includes call-ins from eminent Peace Leaders:
</p>
<p>- Joanie Misrack Ciardelli – Pathways to Peace</p>
<p>- Louise Diamond – Global Systems Initiatives</p>
<p>- Sharon Franquemont – Annual Prayer Vigil for the Earth</p>
<p>- Barbara Gaughen-Muller – Pax 2100</p>
<p>- Dot Maver – Department of Peace Initiative; Peace Partnership Int'l</p>
<p>- Sharon Mehdi – Author, "The Great Silent Grandmother Gathering"</p>
<p>- Patricia Smith Melton – Peace X Peace</p>
 <p>- Robert Muller – Univ. of Peace; Former UN Assist. Secretary General</p>
<p>– Featuring music by composer and performing artist Gary Malkin –</p>
<p>Peace is a raging river! It plunges over a cliff to become a waterfall, sparkling and roaring in the sunlight. It is power. It is generative, nourishing, and irresistible. It calls me to new places where I will change. – David Spangler
</p>
<p>www.internationaldayofpeace.org | www.cultureofpeace.org<br>

              Our Program is a Special Project of Pathways to Peace<br>
                              www.pathwaystopeace.org</p>

<p>Avon Mattison  is Co-Founder and President of Pathways to Peace, an international peace-building educational and consulting organization. Avon is a forerunner in the field of peace-building, and has been involved with The International Day of Peace since it's inauguration. Pathways to Peace serves as international coordinator of the Culture of Peace Initiative, which has been granted UN Peace Messenger status.
</p>
<p>Charles Gibbs  is the founding Executive Director of the United Religions Initiative, a global interfaith network for world peace that is active in 60 countries. Charles has traveled worldwide as a featured speaker and collaborator with religious, spiritual, and community leaders. He co-authored Birth of a Global Community  about the birth of the United Religions Initiative.</p>
<p>Masankho Banda  is an international performer and educator dedicated to building peace through music and storytelling. Masankho has brought his work into schools, organizations, corporations and communities around the world. He is the founder of UCanDanc' African Healing Arts  and the Co-Founder and Co-Director of The Institute for Peacebuilding. He also serves on the Board of Directors for Pathways to Peace.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-DayOfPeace2010/PeaceDay2010.mp3" length="23202167" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">international-peaceday-2011</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:20</itunes:duration>
    </item>

<!-- Coping With Recession Blues original was Nov 8 2008 NEW SHOW -->
<item>
      <title>Coping With Recession Blues</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20110707.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Americans are faced with mortgage problems, job insecurities, and healthcare worries. Problems in the economy are creating fear and doubt about the future. Feeling hopeful can be learned, even when stress and fear seem to be everywhere. During this program, you'll hear our experts address:
</p><p>
    * how to find strength in the center of emotional storms<br />
 * the importance of relationships with family and community in hard times<br />
* that forgiveness is the gift that brings possibility for renewal<br />
* action steps for transformative thinking and living with inner richness<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Reverend Andriette Earl  – Reverend Andriette Earl is acclaimed as "The Freedom Coach" and is Assistant Minister of the East Bay Church of Religious Science in Oakland. She is well-known as a transformational specialist, inspirational speaker, and life coach. Her informative book is Embracing Wholeness: Living in Spiritual Congruence. www.ebcrs.org
</p>
<p>Satyen Raja  – combines the strength of the Warrior and the wisdom of the Sage to inspire audiences worldwide with his work and seminars — blending both power and heartfulness. He is a Kung-Fu Master and a trainer of the renowned Illumination Intensive. Satyen's most recent book is Living Ecstasy. www.warriorsage.com</p>
<p><b>Co-host </b><br />Dr. Brenda Wade – is a San Francisco-based psychologist, author, television host, and producer. She is also a monthly host on Black Renaissance on the CW Network. Brenda's most recent book is Power Choices: Seven Signposts on Your Journey to Wholeness, Love, Joy and Peace. www.powerchoicestv.com www.docwade.com
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-RecessionBlues/RecessionBluesFinalWhole_64kb.mp3" length="26732587" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">coping-with-recession-blues-2011</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>55:42</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Skin Care for All Seasons - WAS Skin Care: The Latest, The Best - EDITED REPEAT SHOW -->
<item>
      <title>Skin Care for All Seasons</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20110622.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Save the Skin You're In! Learn the facts from renowned dermatologist, Dr. Vic Narurkar. Know that prevention is the major key. Also, recovery from certain skin damage is more possible than ever. We cover the latest skin treatments and the growing caution about advertised skin regimens. Injectable fillers can enhance shallow contours, soften facial wrinkles, or improve the appearance of recessed scars. Other subjects include rosacea, hair removal, skin cancer, and more. You'll hear about:
</p>
    * the dangers of overexposure to the sun<br />
    * advances the Fraxel Laser brings to laser treatments<br />
    * customizing the use of botox and facial fillers<br />   
    * effectiveness of Starlux PhotoFacials<br />     
    * how to choose safe tattoo removal<br />  
    * post-radiation procedures to heal skin damage<br />
    * whether medispas are safe<br />
<p><b>Featured Guest</b><br />
Dr. Vic Narurkar founded the acclaimed the Bay Area Laser Institute and has a full dermatology practice in San Francisco. He has pioneered treatments for acne scars, wrinkles, and skin rejuvenation, and offers a unique brand of aesthetic combination therapies - using botox and facial fillers with appropriate laser procedures. Dr. Narurkar recently served as president of the American Society of Cosmetic Dermatology and Aesthetic Surgery. www.bayarealaserdr.com; www.fraxel.com
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-HealthySkin/HealthySkinWhole.mp3" length="22801971" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">skin-care-for-all-seasons</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>47:30</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Repeat of New Show July 2010 - Avatar: The Meaning & The Message -->
<item>
      <title>Exploring Avatar - The Meaning and The Message</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20110527.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>We'll talk in depth about the futuristic film Avatar. It takes place in the year 2154 on the moon called Pandora. The story has so many implications for our world right now. Beyond the issues of right and wrong, good and evil, and choices of all kinds - there are also aspects about what the deep connection to nature, plants, animals, and one another can mean for mankind. This visually impressive masterpiece is written and directed by James Cameron - a true visionary genius. You'll hear
</p>
    * that without significant inner, personal change for loving one another with compassion and kindness - the outer world cannot survive<br />
    * about Steve Robertson's insights, founder of project-peaceonearth.org<br />   
    * the profound meaning of the three words that are at the heart of the film:
"I See You"<br /> 
    * how Jake, the injured Earth soldier, has his heart and soul transformed because of his loving relationship with the Navi heroine Neytiri<br />
    * why it's a good idea to join the Avatar Home Tree Initiative to plant one million trees - go to www.avatarmovie.com to register</p>
<p><b>Featured Guest</b><br />
Jaison Starkes lectures, presents seminars on spiritual growth and personal development, and serves as an Intuitive Consultant - giving personal readings for individuals and businesses worldwide. His passion is to inspire people to find the best within themselves and to realize their true life potential. Starkes currently lives in California and presents his work worldwide. Along with teaching "personal mastery", he is a film and television writer. Jaison's new book, "Quotes from the Soul" is co-authored with Claudia Chittim. When published, it will be available from Amazon. www.personalmasteryusa.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-Avatar/AvatarWholeFinal.mp3" length="53479574" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">exploring-avatar-the-meaning-and-the-message</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>51:58</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- REPEAT w EDITS - Mothers Standing for Peace on-demand repeat show, but re-worked to reflect 2011 -->
<item>
      <title>A Mother's Day Gift - Standing for Peace</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20110426.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Celebrating Mother's Day can be a gift for all.  Hear how The Standing Women Initiative - www.standingwomen.org - invites people of all ages around the world to gather silently for peace on May 8th at 1PM for five minutes local time - with a special focus on a better world for our children and future generations.</p>

<p>In this unique program, Brenda, Carol, and Joan read the powerful, lyrical story, "The Great Silent Grandmother Gathering", a book that has created exciting global attention. The conversation will also share the impact "foremothers", mentors, and mothers have for 21st Century change. On this stirring program, you'll hear about:
</p><p>
    * Julia Ward Howe's 1870 original Mother's Day proclamation calling for peace<br />
    * Jean Bolen's "Urgent Message from Mother - Gather the Women, Save the World"<br /> 
    * ways to actively participate and "Stand for Peace" on Mother's Day</p>
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Dr. Brenda Wade  is a psychologist, author, television host, and producer. National audiences know Brenda from her syndicated TV program, Can this Marriage be Saved, her PBS shows, and her recent guest appearances on the Today Show. She is also a regular host on the Bay Area TV show, Black Renaissance, and is the co-author of several books, including What Mama Couldn't Tell Us About Love. www.docwade.com
</p>
<p>Carol Adrienne is an intuitive counselor and author of books on life purpose, numerology, and change, which have been translated into over fifteen languages. Oprah has praised her best-selling book, The Purpose of Your Life: Finding Your Place in the World Using Synchronicity, Intuition, and Uncommon Sense. Carol develops and co-leads seminars and is in demand as a keynote speaker. www.caroladrienne.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-MothersDay09/Mothersday09.mp3" length="33614433" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">mothers-day-gift-standing-for-peace-2011</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>31:01</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- renamed - was Greening Your Health 2007 Repeat Now - Greening Your Health - Greens the Planet-->
<item>
      <title>Greening Your Health - Greens the Planet</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20110329.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Healthcare must start at home - and it can only be done one person at a time. We know that "Greening Your Health" is imperative for "Greening Our Planet". Yes, We are the World - as, indeed, the lyrics of the song propose. We have the choice to save our own lives - from how we choose to eat, to what we wear, to how we live. Our guests - two amazing Bay Area health experts - offer terrific down-to-earth, evolutionary ideas about green healthcare and green living. You'll hear about:
</p><p>
    * why learning about "green choices" is so vital to your health and well-being <br />
    * the food labeling fiasco, facts about genetic modification, and what not to trust<br />   
    * kudos for the film: Food, Inc. - as well as all Michael Pollan books<br />     
    * how to follow your food's journey from the farm to your table<br />  
    * some surprising information from Brian Wansink, author of Mindless Eating<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Dr. Joel Kreisberg is the Founder & Executive Director of the Teleosis Institute – an institution dedicated to reducing healthcare's footprint, while broadening its ecological vision. He is an adjunct professor at the School of Holistic Studies at John F. Kennedy University in Pleasant Hill, and is the author of The Homeopathic Treatment of Poison Ivy and Poison Oak, and An Integral Ecology of Sudden Oak Death. Dr. Kreisberg continues to teach worldwide and maintains a private practice in Homeopathy and Integrative Healthcare in Berkeley, CA. www.joelkreisberg.com www.teleosis.org</p>
<p>Ed Bauman is the Director of Bauman College, a cutting edge school that focuses on Holistic Nutrition and Culinary Arts. His "Eating for Health" model serves as the foundation of the Bauman College curriculum, as well as the nutrition studies in the Masters programs at both JFK University and New College of California. For more than 30 years, he has been a leader in his field, and his dream is for holistic nutrition, culinary arts and gardening to become a part of public school and public health programs throughout California. www.baumancollege.org www.baumanclinic.com
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/GreeningYourHealth-GreensThePlanet/TheJoanKenleyShow-GreeningYourHealth-GreensThePlanet10.mp3" length="24454709" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">greening-your-health-greens-the-planet-2011</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>

<!-- Green Money - EDITED REPEAT SHOW last repeat was may 23 2009 -->
<item>
      <title>Greening Your Money</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20110307.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Green banking blends with money and emotions in this informative program. We offer conversation about the leading-edge advantages of a "green bank" and about the power of focusing on healthy personal attitudes about money matters. Embracing financial health and social awareness is dynamically explored with two well-known innovators. You'll hear about:
</p>
    * what's involved in creating a "green" bank<br />
    * why money is a such a loaded subject within families and relationships<br />   
    * how culture and family attitudes affect children and their lifelong ideas about money<br />     
    * why investing "green" is profitable and a vote for the future<br />  
    * the surprising advantages of shifting financial attitudes with trained consultants<br />
    * how green bankers can offer helpful guidelines for "going green"<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Peter Liu  is the founder and vice chairman of San Francisco's New Resource Bank – a commercial bank whose primary mission is to serve the needs of green entrepreneurs and sustainable business. Peter was featured as a "Global Warming Big Thinker" in the April 9th, 2007 issue of Time Magazine. He has worked in the banking and energy industries for nearly two decades – as a top executive for Credit Suisse First Boston and Chase Manhattan Bank, and as a private investor and strategic advisor to several clean energy technology companies. www.newresourcebank.com
</p>
<p>Bari Tessleris the founder of Conscious Bookkeeping – a team of financial therapists, coaches, and bookkeepers who serve those who want to transform their relationship with money. The company focuses on the practical, psychological, and spiritual aspects of handling finances. Bari has a Masters in Somatic Psychology from Naropa University and works as a teacher, therapist, and speaker. She is also a featured author in the recently published anthology, Einstein's Business. www.consciousbookkeeping.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-GreeningYourMoney/GreeningMoneyWhole_64kb.mp3" length="23882732" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">green-your-money-4</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>53:32</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- What's Love Got to Do with It - Now Beyond Valentine Love 2011 KKGN 960 2008 Repeat show -->
<!-- Beyond Valentine Love Repeat show edited for podcast repeated feb 2011 -->
<!-- Conscious Giving repeat show edited 2009 for podcast -->
<item>
      <title>Conscious Buying - Thoughtful Giving</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20101712.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Maya Angelou said, "I have found that giving liberates the soul of the giver." And we agree! Giving can mean selecting a gift as an expression of your personal consciousness or philosophy. Because our show is a Special Project of Pathways to Peace, we wanted everyone to know that the Directors' Council just acknowledged Justin Bieber as an outstanding Peacebuilder for 2010 - for his music and for all he gives back to his worldwide community. Giving frees us from the familiar territory of our own needs by opening our hearts and awareness to the needs of others. In this program, you'll hear about:
</p><p>
    * environmentally responsible gifts and where to get them<br />
    * charitable giving to help those in need<br />
    * websites you need to know about<br />  
    * how customers can find fair trade products<br />
    * what it means to vote with your gift dollars all year<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Tex Dworkin is Director of Social Media for Global Exchange, as well as founder and consultant for DoGoodBiz.com. She actively participates in the Fair Trade movement, promoting the philosophy that shopping can change the world. Tex believes in the power of business enterprise as a tool for social change, meeting and speaking with artisans, students, vendors and producers from around the world. www.globalexchange.org
</p>
<p>Priya Haji is the CEO and co-founder of World of Good, Inc. - offering ethically sourced gifts, housewares and accessories. She built the concept while completing her MBA at UC Berkeley, leading the company to its current success with e-Bay and focusing on using the engine of enterprise to create social impact. Priya also serves as the Board Chair for their non-profit sister entity, the World of Good Development Organization. worldofgood.com www.worldofgoodinc.com
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-ConsciousGiving2010/ConsciousGiving2010Whole.mp3" length="64542466" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">conscious-buying-giving</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:51</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- The Gratitude Miracle - A Time for Giving Thanks KKGN 960 2008 Repeat show renamed  -->
<!-- Edited Peace Day Show - 2010 -->
<!-- Coaching for Personal Change on-demand repeat show, but re-worked to reflect 2008 - repeated in june 2010 -->
<item>
      <title>Personal Coaching: Reap the Rewards</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20100612.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>People from all walks of life are now hiring coaches to assist them in achieving a variety of career and personal goals. Certified, professional coaching has grown exponentially over the last decade – helping clients learn to expand their awareness and enhance their quality of life. Is coaching something you may want to explore? In this informative conversation with Joan and Pamela, you'll hear:
</p>
    * the ways coaching differs from therapy<br />
    * various techniques to help you achieve your goals<br />   
    * that unconscious resistance can handicap your aspirations<br />     
    * how coaches focus on action and results<br />
    * why it is important to work with a certified licensed coach</p>
<p><b>Featured Guest</b><br />
Pamela Weiss is the founder of An Appropriate Response. She is a Buddhist meditation teacher, executive coach and trainer of coaches. Pamela has been a pioneer in integrating the principles and practices of mindfulness meditation into coaching and leadership development programs inside organizations. She recently served as a senior course leader with New Ventures West, a coach training organization based in San Francisco. www.appropriateresponse.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-CoachingForChange/CoachingShowWhole.mp3" length="110715297" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">personal-coaching-reaping-the-rewards</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>51:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!--  Everything Music -->
<item>
      <title>Everything Music</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20100514.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Music is a universal influence on the physical, emotional, and spiritual facets of our lives. Particular compositions, tones, and rhythms can strengthen the mind, unlock the creative spirit, and heal the body and soul: Inspiring words about music fill our program: "Music is the poetry of the air." "Without music, life would be a mistake." "Music is what feelings sound like." "Music is the wine that fills the cup of silence." In this hour we'll be exploring:
</p>
    * the value of bringing music more centrally into our daily lives<br />
    * how various types of music and rhythm affect our moods and emotions<br />   
    * important influences of music on healing, individually and globally<br />     
    * why music is an important part of life transitions and celebrations<br />  
    * some of the ways drumming can enhance relationships in the workplace<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Gary Malkin is an award-winning composer, producer, arts activist, and founder of Wisdom of the World, a life-enhancing media production company. His most recent work, Graceful Passages: A Companion for Living and Dying, is used throughout the world as a support tool for life transitions. Gary is dedicated to making a difference in the world by creating music, media, and events that inspire the heart and catalyze social healing. www.wisdomoftheworld.com
</p>
<p>Marian Hubler is a concert producer for Bread & Roses where she organizes free, live, entertainment for those living in San Francisco Bay Area institutions. For more than a decade, she has promoted the Bread & Roses' mission of bringing the healing power of music to people living in isolation. Marian is also a singer and a writer and has over 25 years experience in cultural programming, public relations and special event management. www.breadandroses.com
</p>
<p>Shari Berger is a musician and music educator. She is the founder of Kulanu Productions, an environmentally and socially responsible company specializing in audio, web and event production. Shari has taught drumming to individuals of all ages, believing that rhythm plays a key role in developing our sense of self and connection to others. She also has an MBA in Sustainable Business from New College of California.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/EverythingMusical/TJKS_07.03_Webmix.mp3" length="51772669" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">everything-music-may</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>


<!-- renamed - was Greening Your Health 2007 Repeat Now - Greening Your Health - Greens the Planet-->

<!-- Authoring Your Life repeat show edited 2008 for podcast -->
<!-- The Dream - Reaching the Tipping Point - REPEAT BUT RE-WORKED - 7-28-07 Circle Gatherings: Changing Lives -->
<!-- Loving Green-Sustaining Relationships - REPEAT - Was NEW SHOW 6-28-08 -->
<item>
      <title>Loving Green-Sustaining Relationships</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20090620.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>"Loving Green" involves nurturing relationships to stay "evergreen" – with spouses, life partners, siblings, children, parents, friends, and co-workers. Paying attention to positive basic principles can green your relationships at every level. Learn about the importance and the rewards of the physical, mental, emotional, and spiritual aspects of growing and sustaining love. You'll hear about:
</p>
    * John and Mary's commitment to greening their marriage<br />
    * what happens during the "un-greening" of relationships<br />   
    * the power of making a sincere apology<br />     
    * how a healthier relationship can positively affect your health<br />  
    * ways to argue peacefully and put disappointments aside<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Dr. Brenda Wade  is a San Francisco-based psychologist, author, television host, and producer. National audiences know Brenda from her frequent appearances as a relationship expert on The Today Show. She is also a monthly host on Black Renaissance on the CW Network. Brenda has authored Love Lessons, What Mama Couldn't Tell Us About Love and Power Choices: Seven Signposts on Your Journey to Wholeness, Love, Joy and Peace. www.docwade.com  and www.powerchoicestv.com
</p>
<p>Dr. Joan Kenley – author, psychologist, and media personality – hosts The Joan Kenley Show, branded as Conversation Radio™. She has appeared on high profile television programs: ABC's 20/20, CNN, Dateline, The Oprah Winfrey Show, and Good Morning America, as well as countless radio shows. Joan has been featured in: The New York Sunday Times Magazine, Reader's Digest, Health, Allure, Cosmo, Wired, and Fortune, and authored two notable books: Voice Power and Whose Body Is It Anyway?</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-LovingGreen/LovingGreenWhole_64kb.mp3" length="25698138" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">loving-green-relationships</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>53:32</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Green Money - EDITED REPEAT SHOW -->
<!-- Political Straight Talk | NEW SHOW 4-25-09 -->
<item>
      <title>Political Straight Talk</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20090425.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Eager to hear more political straight talk? Can you recognize when commentators and news sources are committed to the truth? Are you aware of the media manipulation about what's happening in our world? Journalist, author and media critic, Norman Solomon and eminent broadcaster, Peter B. Collins – in Part Two of our conversation – will reveal how to think more consciously about what you see, hear, and read. Remember – if history doesn't repeat itself, it certainly rhymes a lot. You'll hear:
</p><p>
    * how presidents and leaders use rhetoric to make war seem necessary<br />
    * what intentional selectivity affects media messages<br /> 
    * about the hidden, astronomical costs of the Iraq war<br />  
    * reliable sources you can reference for accurate reporting<br />     
    * Congresswoman Barbara Lee's speech to Congress against the Iraq war</p>
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Norman Solomon has authored a dozen books – including, "War Made Easy: How Presidents and Pundits keep Spinning Us to Death" and "Made Love, Got War: Close Encounters With America's Warfare State." A nationally syndicated columnist on media and politics since 1992 – he's been featured in the NY Times, Washington Post, USA Today, and LA Times, and is frequently published on truthout.org. A recipient of the esteemed George Orwell award, Solomon founded the Institute for Public Accuracy in 1998 and serves as executive director. www.normansolomon.com
</p>
<p>Peter B. Collins is a well-known broadcaster, entrepreneur, and media consultant based in San Francisco. He is one of the owners of KRXA/540, the progressive talk station serving Monterey, Salinas and Santa Cruz. From 2005 to March 2009, he hosted the Peter B. Collins Show – a daily, syndicated radio commentary and call-in program. In his late teens, during the Watergate years, he was a nightly on-air personality and talk show host at Chicago's ABC FM affiliate, and at that intense time in history – his ground-breaking broadcast was rated number one. www.peterbcollins.com
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2009 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-PoliticalStraightTalk/PoliticalStraightTalk.mp3" length="38141776" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">political-straight-talk</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>39:44</itunes:duration>
    </item>

<!-- Stories: Powerful, Healing, Inspiring - FORMERLY: Why Stories Are Needed KKGN 960 2007 rpt show (Storytelling for All Seasons) re-titled -->
<item>
      <title>Stories: Powerful, Healing, Inspiring</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20090228.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>We explore why stories matter in our lives — why we love them — and how they help us communicate. Since the most primitive campfires and throughout history, stories have helped teach, influence, and bind people together. They encourage the understanding — of self, of others, and of life — which is vital for sustaining cultures. You'll hear:
</p>
<p>- what's involved in telling a captivating story
</p>
<p>- the difference between a fairy tale, a myth and a fable
</p>
<p>- Gay's story about being a guest on Mr. Rogers' Neighborhood
</p>
<p>- how stories can enhance education and bring hope to young people
</p>
<p>- why children can benefit from story hours at local libraries
</p>
<p>Gay Ducey is a children's librarian, free-lance storyteller, and storytelling educator. She has appeared on Mr. Rogers' Neighborhood and performs regularly throughout North America. She was commissioned by the Smithsonian's Museum of American History to present stories in "Union Maid: Stories from America's Women at Work." Gay is also co-author of Spilt Milk: Traditional Tales of Mother and Motherhood, scheduled for publication in 2007. mducey@earthlink.net
</p>
<p>Sandra Noman is a teacher, writer, grandmother and lively teller of tales. She is currently directing a program serving the needs of homeless middle school children in San Francisco. Born in East Africa to medical missionaries, she has lived in many lands, gathering stories everywhere. She recently was the director of the Dominican University Storytelling Program. sandra@homeaway.org</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-StoriesPowerfulHealingInspiring/StoriesPowerfulHealing_64kb.mp3" length="22901155" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">stories-powerful-healing-inspiring</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- What's Love Got to Do with It 2008 Repeat show edited for podcast -->
<!-- Beyond Valentine Love Repeat show edited for podcast repeated jan 27 2010-->
<!-- Choosing Happiness Nov 22 2008 NEW SHOW -->
<!-- The Election Imperative: Every Vote Must Count Oct 2008 NEW SHOW -->
<item>
      <title>The Election Imperative: Every Vote Must Count</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20081025.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Can Americans expect to fairly elect the president of their choice this year – having had two questionable elections in 2000 and 2004? Dorothy Fadiman has just launched the free-to-play and download Internet version of her explosive film STEALING AMERICA: Vote by Vote – stealingamericathemovie.org.  In this conversation, you'll hear:
</p><p>
    * how Dorothy made this in-depth exploration of the last two elections<br />
 * facts about the mortgage crisis, corporate taxes, nuclear power, off-shore drilling<br />
* Colin Powell's endorsement of Barack Obama<br />
* the tough challenges facing America's next president<br />
* action steps to take for fair voting in 2008<br />
<p><b>Featured Guest</b><br />
Dorothy Fadiman - In addition to STEALING AMERICA: Vote by Vote, Dorothy has been producing documentaries with a focus on social justice and human rights for thirty years. Winner of more than 50 major awards, she is Producer/Director of twenty films, including RADIANCE: The Experience of Light; FROM THE BACK ALLEYS to the SUPREME COURT & BEYOND; WHY DO THESE KIDS LOVE SCHOOL? Her new book is Producing with Passion: Making Films that Change the World. www.concentric.org
</p>
<p><b>Co-host </b><br />Barry Kendall - Executive Director of the Commonweal Institute, Barry is an expert in the use of drama and narrative to bring people to a new understanding of themselves and the world. Through Commonweal, he applies these skills to build support for the kinds of values and ideas that will create a better society. Kendall has a Masters degree in religion from Yale, and a PhD in drama from Stanford. www.commonwealinstitute.org
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2008 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-TheElectionImparative/TheElectionImperative128_64kb.mp3" length="28107882" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">every-vote-must-count</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>58:33</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Practical Intuition for Today new media 2008 Edited REPEAT show -->
<item>
      <title>Practical Intuition For Today</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20081018.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Intuition – from A to Z – is an important capacity to use in everyday life and especially in hard times. Hear about Sharon's 30 years of expertise in the field, and how she and her daughter Megan use intuition in their own lives. You'll hear:
</p><p>
    * whether intuition is something you can learn or a talent you have at birth<br />
 * how intuition can affect your relationships, work life, and self-knowing<br />
* Sharon's four simple steps for developing your intuitive capabilities<br />
* the way Megan uses body/mind clues to make important life choices<br />
* how intuition is defined in other countries and societies<br />
* why developing intuition is essential to our evolution and global harmony<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Sharon Franquemont is the Education Director for the Life Science Foundation and is an international speaker, trainer, and coach on intuition and innovation. She is the author of three books, including You Already Know What To Do, and is working on an online learning module for the University of Minnesota's Center for Spirituality and Healing, called Intuition's Role in Your Health and Wellbeing. Sharon is also a co-founder of the annual interfaith Prayer Vigil for the Earth in Washington, DC. www.intuitionworks.com  www.lifesciencefoundation.org www.oneprayer.org.
</p>
<p>Megan Doherty Sharon's daughter, recently changed careers from her role as a highly successful retail manager to a specialist in Corporate Community Outreach. In 2000, she worked as a Representative for Youth at the Wittenberg Center for Alternative Resources - an NGO at the United Nations. Megan also serves as a key role for the annual Prayer Vigil for the Earth. Intuition has been a constant influence in her life. She says, "A balance of intuition, heart, and intellect guide most of the major decisions I make in my life." www.oneprayer.org.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2008 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-PracticalIntuitionGuidanceforHardTimes/PracticalIntuitionGuidanceforHardTimes_64kb.mp3" length="23015757" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">practical-intuition-for-today</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>47:57</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- REPEATED Oct 30 2009 - What On Earth Are We Eating? new media 2008 Edited REPEAT show -->
<!-- The Urgency of Now: Peace Day - 2008 - EDITED REPEAT SHOW -->
<!-- Choosing Wellness - REPEAT SHOW -->
<item>
      <title>Choosing Wellness</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20080906.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>What does it mean to be truly healthy? As diagnostics improve, better healing ideas and possibilities emerge. Guidelines for achieving good health and staying well are easier to find than ever. Information about how to focus on a better qualityof life at every age is important. Integrated healthcare – which addresses all aspects of wellness – is a fast-growing, positive trend. In this informative conversation you'll hear about:
</p>
<p>    * naturopathic medicine, botanicals, and homeopathic remedies<br />
    * why new information about vitamin D is making it the "Vitamin of the Year"<br />   
    * how important it is to know the latest news about hormone replacement<br />     
    * Phoenix WellCare's approach to diagnostics, treatments, and therapies<br />  
    * often over-looked silent diseases Ð how finding them early is life-saving<br />
    * the importance of working with the immune system<br />
    * treating allergies, acid reflux, and inflammation with complementary methods<br /></p>
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Eleanor Hynote, MD, is the Director of Phoenix WellCare in Napa, California – an integrative health care practice, combining conventional and complementary medicine. She is a board certified internist and was in one of Dr. Andrew Weil's first training groups in Botanical Medicine at Columbia University. She serves as Vice-President of the American College for Advancement in Medicine. Dr. Hynote mentors physicians interested in integrative medicine practice by providing on-site training and ongoing consultation.</p>
<p>Moses David Goldberg, ND  is a practitioner at Phoenix WellCare, where he is a Doctor of Naturopathic Medicine, using western diagnostic skills for treatments, as well as a variety of natural modalities – including botanical medicine, hydrotherapy, homeopathy, nutritional supplements, and natural hormones. Dr. Goldberg specializes in chronic fatigue, fibromyalgia, menopause, stress, gastro-intestinal disorders, cancer support, food sensitivity, allergies, hormonal imbalances, ADHD, and detoxification.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/The_Wellness_Approach/The_Wellness_Approach_webmix_64kb.mp3" length="23993700" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">choosing-wellness</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Poets on Fire - EDITED REPEAT SHOW -->
<item>
      <title>Poets on Fire</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20080816.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Poetry from the ridiculous to the sublime – from laughter to tears to healing is so informing. It can evoke emotional and profound responses within our souls. Thomas Gray said that poems are "thoughts that breathe, and words that burn". You'll hear:
</p>
    * compelling life experiences that brought our guests into the world of poetry<br />
    * the many ways poetic  verse has the power to evoke profound responses<br />   
    * a lively in-studio poetry slam with Drew & Barbara<br />     
    * about some of the poets we know and love<br />  
    * how to ignite and cultivate your inner muse<br />
    * information about the activist-driven collective – Poets for Global Justice<br />
    * some of the best places to hear and perform poetry<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Drew Dellinger is a poet, teacher, activist and the founder of Poets for Global Justice. He has performed at events across the United States and the UK, speaking on justice, cosmology, ecology, and democracy. His collection, love letter to the milky way, has inspired readers on four continents. Drew has been called "a national treasure" by Joanna Macy and "a deep, courageous poet" by Alice Walker.  www.drewdellinger.com</p>
<p>Barbara Lyon has been writing poetry for more than a quarter century. Born in Chicago and raised in New York, she moved to the San Francisco and raised five children with her husband of 63 years. Her book of selected poems is titled Memories & Mysteries. At age 87, she paints, teaches yoga, and practices tai chi. At 60, Barbara received her Masters in Human Values at the SF Theological Seminary. 510-797-8971</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-PoetsOnFire/PoetsOnFireWhole_64kb.mp3" length="23454115" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">poets-on-fire</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>42:58</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- The Power of Loving Intention - EDITED REPEAT SHOW -->
<item>
      <title>The Power of Loving Intention</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20080802.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Loving intention can play an extraordinary role in your life. Our guests are two wonderfully successful women who credit their achievements to using conscious intention – in many ways – throughout their lives. The stories you'll hear from Brenda, Marcia and Joan will inspire you, motivate you, and touch your mind, body, heart, and soul. You'll hear about:
</p>
    * creating more ways to live with intention<br />
    * what may be blocking the choices you dream of<br />   
    * heartful ways to use intention for positive change<br />     
    * what intention and spirituality have in common<br />  
    * how to embrace Ð without fear – what may feel like a risk<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Dr. Brenda Wade is a San Francisco-based psychologist, author, television host, and producer. National audiences know Brenda from her frequent appearances as a relationship expert on The Today Show. She is also a monthly host on Black Renaissance on the CW Network. Brenda has authored Love Lessons, What Mama Couldn't Tell Us About Love and Power Choices: Seven Signposts on Your Journey to Wholeness, Love, Joy and Peace. www.docwade.com www.powerchoicestv.com
</p>
<p>Marcia Jaffe is an entrepreneur and visionary - founding the Quest for Global Healing Conference series in Bali. She is President of the Bali Institute for Global Renewal in Ubud – a hub for transformative changes through dialogue and leadership training. She has been creating and producing conferences and events for more than 30 years, bringing countless people together around cutting edge topics of national and international concern. www.questforglobalhealing.org www.baliinstitute.org</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-LovingIntention/LovingIntentionWhole1_64kb.mp3" length="19812936" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">the-power-of-loving-intention</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>41:17</itunes:duration>
    </item>

<!-- Why Conversations Matter - NEW SHOW -->
<item>
      <title>Why Conversations Matter</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20080719.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Conversations do matter to you and to the future of our planet. Some of the basic principles involve the importance of deep, respectful listening, avoiding blame and judgment, and staying true to yourself and your values – even in difficult circumstances. Hear useful ways to engage, heal, and inspire! We'll talk about:
</p>
    * how all situations can benefit from conscious, intentional conversation<br />
    * conversation guidelines to enhance relationships and family life<br />   
    * what fragmented attention can do to sabotage a conversation<br />     
    * the importance of asking good questions and managing expectations<br />  
    * whether you feel prepared to initiate and explore sensitive subjects<br />
    * why learning to have "conversations that matter" has rich rewards<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Juanita Brown - early in her career, was a noted community organizer with César Chávez. She then became a thinking/design partner to major organizations, and her work involves leaders from around the globe. Juanita co-founded The World Café movement with David Isaacs, who co-authored - along with the World Café Community - the best selling book, "The World Café: Shaping Our Futures Through Conversations That Matter" – now translated into many languages worldwide. www.theworldcafe.com
</p>
<p>Tom Hurley is currently guiding the global evolution of the World Café and serves as a senior advisor and executive coach for leaders seeking innovative approaches to key strategic issues and large-scale systems change. Tom was co-founder of the Chaordic Commons, a nonprofit consulting organization and served as a member of the senior management team with the Institute of Noetic Sciences. He is a board member of the World Café Community Foundation and the Berkana Institute. tom@tjhassociates.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-Conversations/ConversationWhole.mp3" length="23154229" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">why-conversations-matter</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:14</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Green Money - deleted - repeated above - no edits - originally an EDITED REPEAT SHOW -->
<!-- Loving Green-Sustaining Relationships - NEW SHOW June 28, 2008 -->
<!-- Healthy Choices For Your Horses, Bunnies, Cats & Dogs was KKRX but new show now On Demand -->
<item>
      <title>Healthy Choices For Your Horses, Bunnies, Cats and Dogs</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20080614.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Our conversation will cover standard care, as well as alternative treatments such as chiropractic, acupuncture, and homeopathy — all to benefit your pet's well being. From allergies to serious illnesses, we'll be talking about the best care for your animals. You'll hear about:
</p>
    * choices to keep your pets even healthier and happier<br />
    * the importance of expert advice to manage your pet's needs<br />   
    * why dog parks are so important for you and your dog<br />     
    * what massage can offer for both healing and performance<br />  
    * the reasons dental care is so critical for your dog, cat, or horse<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Jenny Taylor, DVM has a broad background, as well as advanced training, in her career as a veterinarian. She founded Creature Comfort Holistic Veterinary Center in Oakland, California — the first complementary veterinary clinic in the Bay Area. Dr. Taylor and her staff offer Chinese and Western herbal therapies, acupuncture, homeopathy, and chiropractic — in addition to traditional Western veterinary medicine. www.creaturecomfort.com
</p>
<p>Emily Rosenberg is a long time social activist and animal advocate. Her special interest is helping people benefit from the companionship of animals. She helped launch San Francisco's "Pets Are Wonderful Support" — also known as PAWS — the first organization helping AIDS patients keep their pets throughout their illness. Emily also works locally to create dog parks and to actively support Smiley Dog Rescue in Oakland. www.dogparkinfo.com
</p>
<p>Rebecca Thomas, EBW  is a certified equine body worker in the Bay Area. Her practice includes backyard pets, trail horses, endurance racers, and high-end show horses. Working with vets and individual owners, she handles injury recovery, physical therapy, arthritis, and general maintenance for horses, dogs, cats, and birds. Her massage is an adjunct to veterinary care for healing and optimal performance. www.equinebodywork.net</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-PetsHour1Part1/PetsHr1.1Whole.mp3" length="114936684" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">activism-for-change-08</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Activism for Change was KKGN 960 2007 new show now On Demand -->
<item>
      <title>Activism for Change</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20080531.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>This program focuses on how to speak the language of peace and spread the word! People everywhere need to know that "applied peace building" is a new and powerful science. What are the politics of peace? Have you heard about the Student Peace Alliance? It's important to put more action into activism by learning which programs you can get behind. From grassroots to government, there are organizations in countless cultures around the globe that are taking on the challenges that could stimulate major global change. You'll hear about:
</p>
    * Robert Redford's film Lions for Lambs – a call to question what's true<br />
    * The Peace Alliance, its mission, and its presence in all 50 states<br />   
    * what it could mean to our country to have a Department of Peace<br />     
    * why thinking of peace as technicolor and vital makes it more powerful<br />  
    * how to get involved in the "Summer of Peace" Initiative for 2009<br />
    * the way Walter Cronkite describes peace as "an inside job"<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Dorothy Maver, a resident of Vermont, is one of the founders of The Peace Alliance, an organization that empowers civic activism for a culture of peace while also advocating for a US Department of Peace. Dot was the National Campaign Manager for Kucinich for President 2004, is a co-founder of the Vermont Peace Academy, and is active in community organizing. She co-authored the book Conscious Education: The Bridge to Freedom. The Peace Alliance – www.thepeacealliance.org – 202.296.1187
</p>
<p>Matthew Albrecht is a long-time ecological, social justice activist, and a founding member of The Peace Alliance, which was started three years ago. Matt is currently involved in the Greater Bay Area "Summer of Peace" initiative for 2009 that will harness the efforts of dozens of groups and cutting-edge programs to drastically reduce violence as well as helping to create new models for collaboration that can be replicated in cities across the US and in other countries worldwide. The Peace Alliance – www.thepeacealliance.org – 202.296.1187
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenelyShow-ActivismForChange/ActivismWhole_vbr.mp3" length="50889264" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">activism-for-change-08</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>

<!-- REMOVED Mothers Standing for Peace on-demand repeat show, but re-worked to reflect 2008 -->
    <!-- Can Do Politics on-demand new show -->
<item>
      <title>Can Do Politics</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20080503.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hear from Supervisor Nate Miley and co-host, Barry Kendall – Executive Director of the Commonweal Institute – about lively issues during this "Can Do" political conversation. Our position is that a positive attitude with aggressive political strategies can influence solutions for the economy, housing foreclosures, oil prices, healthcare, and greening the environment. We'll be addressing these subjects and more. You'll hear about:
</p>
    * the key role Supervisors play in serving their communities<br />
    * basic central values that drive pro-active political leaders<br />   
    * whether we can hope for fair elections in the future<br />     
    * how the media shapes and influences the political scene<br />  
    * getting involved in green consciousness</p>
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Supervisor Nate Miley was first elected to the Alameda County Board of Supervisors in 2000, was re-elected in 2004, and is now looking forward to serving a third term. He is currently chair of the Board's Transportation and Planning Committee and Public Protection Committee. In fact, Nate has been involved in community service his entire adult life, serving his constituents with energy and innovation. www.natemiley.com
</p>
<p>Barry Kendall, the Executive Director of the Commonweal Institute, is an expert in the use of drama and narrative to bring people to a new understanding of themselves and the world. Through Commonweal, he applies these skills to build support for the kinds of values and ideas that will create a better society. Kendall has a Masters degree in religion from Yale, and a PhD in drama from Stanford. www.commonwealinstitute.org</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-PoliticsWithNateMiley/Politics_WholeShow.mp3" length="124316733" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">can-do-politics</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>51:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Authoring Your Life KKGN 960 2007 new show deleted and updated for jan 1 2010 -->


<!-- Expert Choices KKGN 960 2007 version repeated -->
<item>
      <title>Expert Choices For Looking Better</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20080329.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cosmetic/reconstructive surgery and dermatology treatments are becoming more common in today's culture. Our well-known guests share many of the options available, in addition to what motivates people to have various procedures — from professors with frown lines to those who want their outer appearance to reflect their inner vitality and identity. You'll hear about:
</p>
<p>- the psychological and spiritual aspects of plastic surgery
</p>
<p>- how facial fillers can be combined and customized
</p>
<p>- why life transitions or illness may lead to cosmetic and reconstructive choices
</p>
<p>- some unexpected benefits of botox and the latest in aesthetic lasers
</p>
<p>- what makes sunscreens and skincare products effective
</p>
<p>- recommended procedures versus harmful trends
</p>
<p>Dr. Loren Eskenazi is the founder of Women's Plastic Surgery in San Francisco – the only plastic surgery practice in the United States headed by three women. She has appeared on CNN, Dr. Dean Edell, and the Discovery Channel, to name a few – and has been voted "Top Woman Doctor" in her field for many years. Dr. Eskenazi is a formally trained artist and singer as well as a surgeon. Her most recent book, "More than Skin Deep", offers a unique psycho/spiritual approach to physical transformation through surgery. www.transformationalsurgery.com and www.womensplasticsurgery.com
</p>
<p>Dr. Christine Brozowski has been a Cosmetic Physician in the Bay Area for ten years. Formerly, she was a Medical Director for the City of Berkeley Public Health Clinic. Although her expertise is in dermatology and women's health, she provides full-spectrum care for her patients and has appeared on local talk radio and television programs as a medical expert. Dr. Brozowski emphasizes a natural approach to beauty and aging and uses state-of-the-art techniques to give the best aesthetic results possible. In her spare time she is an artist and painter. www.doctoragogo.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-ExpertChoices/TJKS_07_40_webmix.mp3" length="47895613" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">experts-choices-for-looking-better</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:53</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Election Fever & Progressive Values KKGN 960 2008 new show -->
<item>
      <title>Election Fever and Progressive Values</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20080315.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Democrats are fired up about this history-making presidential election like never before. The media and pundits are having a feast about what they choose to report and how they frame the message. The direction of our country is at a critical crossroads, with the choice of Commander in Chief more crucial than ever. You'll hear about:
</p>
<p>- how the Commonweal Institute supports the modern progressive movement
</p>
<p>- the use of "liberal" and "progressive" changing over the years
</p>
<p>- ways the campaigns are evolving and what the influences are
</p>
<p>- recognizing that the "center" of politics shifts slowly and in cycles
</p>
<p>- the Democracy Alliance and Rob Stein's important contributions
</p>
<p>- Commonweal's ideas and programs to help you get involved
</p>
<p>- the Progressive Roundtable – its role in building a progressive infrastructure
</p>
<p>Dr. Katherine Forrest is the president and co-founder of the Commonweal Institute, an action-oriented, advocacy, progressive think tank based in the San Francisco Bay area. She specializes in idea-marketing and political strategy, and is the creator of the Institute's popular seminar, Talking Politics with People Unlike Ourselves. Dr. Forrest has medical and public health degrees from Harvard University.
</p>
<p>Barry Kendall, the Executive Director of the Commonweal Institute, is an expert in the use of drama and narrative to bring people to a new understanding of themselves and the world. Through Commonweal, he applies these skills to build support for the kinds of values and ideas that will create a better society. Mr. Kendall has a Masters degree in religion from Yale, and a Ph.D. in drama from Stanford.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-ElectionFever/TJKS_08_11_Whole_vbr.mp3" length="47692076" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">election-fever-and-progressive-values</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:51</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Why Everything About Your Teeth Matters KKGN 960 2007 version repeated -->
<item>
      <title>Why Everything About Your Teeth Matters</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20080308.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>From A to Z — your teeth affect the rest of your body, mind and wellbeing. Our guests are two dentists who give their patients a lot to smile about. Dentistry has come a long way since the time when people thought tooth decay was caused by little animals called tooth worms. In this jam-packed hour, we're going to share the exciting 21st century approach to your mouth, tongue, teeth, and gums, as well as many other things you need to know about dental health. You'll hear about:
</p>
<p>- various reasons for restoring your smile—veneers, bonding, braces, etc.
</p>
<p>- silver versus composite fillings
</p>
<p>- causes for bad breath
</p>
<p>- which kind of teeth respond to whitening
</p>
<p>- why your dentist can forecast other health concerns
</p>
<p>- what dentists look for during pregnancy and menopause
</p>
<p>- those who are good candidates for implants
</p>
<p>- the emerging dental spas
</p>
<p>Dr. Robert Watkins is a prosthodontist who practices general, aesthetic and restorative dentistry in Berkeley. He's been an assistant professor at U.C.S.F School of Dentistry in San Francisco for many years and currently teaches part-time in the post-graduate prosthodontic program. 510-845-1505
</p>
<p>Dr. Dorothy Slattery is a restorative and general dentist in Mill Valley. She has 30 years experience in the field as well as 10 years of training at the Seattle Institute of Advanced Dental Education. In her practice, she restores smiles with veneers, implants and cosmetic restorations — with an emphasis on patient comfort.
415-388-6006</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TeethMatters/TJKS_07_39_webmix.mp3" length="47850474" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">why-everything-about-your-teeth-matters-08</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:51</itunes:duration>
    </item>

<!-- Valentine Love KKGN 960 2008 Repeat show deleted -->
<!-- Practical Intuition KKGN 960 2008 Repeat show deleted - repeated 10-17-08 -->
<!-- Poetry Power KKGN 960 2008 new show deleted - repeated 8-16-08 -->
<!-- Your Pets: Best Love, Best Care KKGN 960 2008 Repeat show with edits -->
    <!-- YOUR HOME: The Art of Buying, Designing and Selling KKGN 960 2007 repeat show -->
<item>
      <title>YOUR HOME: The Art of Buying, Designing and Selling</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20080105.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Buying, designing, and selling a home includes many aspects – mental, emotional, physical, and financial. The savvy Glass-Sabine Team joins our conversation with expert advice. They have distinguished themselves by making their own brand of home-staging a marketing specialty. It's been said, "Home is where the heart is." Taking that idea one step further: Why not put your heart into your home? You can hear about:
</p><p>
    * how to make buying a home an even smarter investment<br />
    * the many advantages of considering design psychology & Feng Shui<br />   
    * ways a cluttered home or work space can negatively impact your life<br />     
    * why "green" building and environmental re-modeling are so important<br />  
    * tips and suggestions that make homes more attractive for buyers<br />
    * why sellers who stage their homes have a big advantage in the marketplace<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Judith Glass has an impressive history in design and sales. Her MBA is in marketing, and she is a member of the Berkeley Architectural Heritage Association. Judith was the owner and founder of The Fashion Connection – an image consulting firm in Ann Arbor, Michigan, and The New Moon – a specialty clothing store in Oakland, California.
</p>
<p>Sheila Sabine has extensive experience in property management, renovation, design, building and residential sales, and serves as an Interior Design Trainer for new agents. Sheila has published numerous articles in the San Francisco Chronicle, Northern California Homes and Gardens, and San Francisco Magazine.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2008 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-InvestingInYourHome/TJKS_08_01_Whole_vbr.mp3" length="50193325" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">your-home-the-art-of-buying-designing-and-selling</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Choose a Healthy New Year KKGN 960 2007 repeat show -->
<!-- The Wonders of Tea KKGN 960 2007 repeat show -->
<item>
      <title>The Wonders of Tea</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20071222.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>For thousands of years, tea has been an important part of our human culture. It is the second most consumed beverage in the world after water. Tea experts Trinity Ava and Anna Wasserman expand our relationship to the wonders of tea. You'll hear about:
</p><p>
    * how drinking tea and herbal beverages offers a broad range of health benefits<br />
    * the exquisite rituals and ceremonies surrounding tea<br />   
    * why quality and grade are important in making tea choices<br />     
    * the source of white tea and why it's being proclaimed as the new "green"<br />  
    * what Numi and Traditional Medicinals are doing to support sustainability<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Trinity Ava was formerly an herbal education specialist for Traditional Medicinals, a socially and environmentally conscious tea company in Sebastopol, CA. She designs and teaches innovative educational programs and has led seminars on herbal medicine throughout the United States. Trinity has worked with farmers worldwide to support organic, fair-trade and sustainable farming methods. She has also taught aromatic botanical medicine at the California School of Herbal Studies. Trinity is currently with Organix-South – herbal body care products and supplements. www.organixsouth.com
</p>
<p>Anna Wasserman is the Public Relations Manager for Numi Organic tea, an organic & fair trade tea company based in Oakland, CA. She is a certified nutritionist who promotes naturopathic philosophy, natural medicines, and environmental sustainability. Anna spent six years in Australia studying natural medicine, and is a graduate of New College of California's Culture, Ecology, and Sustainable community program. Anna believes in educating people on the benefits of a healthy life through food, lifestyle, herbalism, and clinical nutrition. www.numitea.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-TheMagicOfTea/TeaWhole.mp3" length="71813328" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">the-wonders-of-tea</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Awaken Your Soul Purpose KKGN 960 2007 repeat show -->
<item>
      <title>Awaken Your Soul Purpose</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20071215.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>More and more – conversations, books, and films are exploring the subject of the soul. We know that personal experiences of soul are not the same, but on this program you hear about the kind of moments that call to everyone. What are the challenges of living with soul purpose? Are there ways to know whether you're on your soul path? During this rich conversation we talk about:
</p><p>
    * what ignites your soul<br />
    * various ways your soul journey can become blocked<br />   
    * the many kinds of stories that can awaken your soul purpose<br />     
    * why Jonathan uses myth, books, and movies to reveal soul recognition<br />  
    * how Brenda's book "Power Choices" can guide explorations of the soul<br />
    * the importance of sages and mentors in finding your soul path<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Dr. Brenda Wade is a San Francisco-based psychologist, author, television host, and producer. National Television audiences know Brenda from her regular appearances on The Today Show and her syndicated program, Can this Marriage be Saved. Locally, she hosts the Bay Area community affairs television series, Black Renaissance. Her newest book is Power Choices: Signposts on Your Journey to Wholeness, Love, Joy and Peace. www.powerchoices.net www.docwade.com
</p>
<p>Dr. Jonathan Young is a psychologist and founder of The Center for Story and Symbol in Santa Barbara. He and his partner Ann Bach offer continuing education seminars on the psychology of fairy tales, mythic stories, creativity and more. He was the Founding Curator of the Joseph Campbell Archives and Library and worked for several years assisting Campbell. Jonathan created and chaired the Mythological Studies Department at the Pacifica Graduate Institute. www.folkstory.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-YourSoulPurpose/SoulWhole_vbr.mp3" length="50590170" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">awaken-your-soul-purpose</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Edwards Bold Solutions KKGN 960 2007 new show -->
<item>
      <title>Edwards Bold Solutions</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20071208.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Senator Edwards' bid for the Presidency is the topic of this energized conversation. Despite the significant attention given to the front-running Democrats, Edwards has managed to capture substantial voter support and keen interest. In this program, we take an in-depth look at this electable contender's conviction and sincere passion to reclaim our government and the promise of America for the future. We hear about:
</p><p>
    * Edwards' proposal for comprehensive, universal health coverage for all US citizens<br />
    * how the Senator addresses the struggling middle class and the poor<br />   
    * concrete plans for solutions to the national security crisis facing our country<br />     
    * the Senator's hands-on approach to foreign policy: a new paradigm of diplomacy<br />  
    * ending the violence in Iraq and creating lasting stability in the whole region<br />
    * ways for the US to capitalize on a "Green Energy Economy"<br />
    * utilizing American ingenuity to end global warming and restore our environment<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Nina Horne is a City Commissioner for the Oakland Fund for Children and Youth and is a co-founder of the Win the White House in '08 initiative - a regional group of community and business leaders convened to alter the split between fundraising and campaign organizing. Nina is currently pursuing her masters in public policy at the Goldman School of Public Policy at University of CA-Berkeley. www.wwh08.com
</p>
<p>Senator Leland Yee - after serving four years in the California State Assembly - was elected to the State Senate in 2006 with over 78 percent of the vote, the largest percentage ever for any Democrat with a Republican challenger. He represents District 8, which includes San Francisco and San Mateo County and is also a member of the Senate Democratic Leadership as the Assistant President pro tem. www.senate.ca.gov/yee
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2007 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow_EdwardsSolution/TJKS_07_49_whole_vbr.mp3" length="52044529" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edwards-bold-solutions</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:51</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Supporting Causes That Matter KKGN 960 2007 new show -->
<item>
      <title>Supporting Causes That Matter</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20071201.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Recognizing that "You can't cross the sea merely by standing and staring at the water." - our guests share how they work with causes that matter. We talk about issues that are important to so many of us - in this country and cultures everywhere. In this program you'll hear about:
</p><p>
    * WIN and CAWA's beginnings and their visionary platforms for action<br />
    * the needs you don't hear about – ranging from civil issues to the war in Iraq<br />   
    * creating joy for others, sharing what we have for the betterment of person-kind<br />     
    * bringing hope to the lost and love to the lonely<br />  
    * Rose Aguilar's radio show Your Call, her journalistic endeavors and causes<br />
    * Marilyn Fowler's path to activism and her profound journeys around the globe<br />
    * whether there will be a 5th Women's World Conference<br />
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Rose Aguilar hosts Your Call - a daily public affairs radio show on KALW 91.7 FM - San Francisco's local NPR-affiliate. The show focuses on politics, social issues, the environment, and the arts. She is on the board of the Women's Intercultural Network and contributes articles to AlterNet.org. Rose is currently writing a book detailing her 2005 experiences through the "red states", a project she chose to ask people why they vote the way they do. WIN/CAWA - www.win-cawa.org/cawa - 415.221.4841
</p>
<p>Marilyn Fowler, is Founder and President of the Women's Intercultural Network. She has been connecting women across cultures for collective action for 30 years throughout the US, as well as villages in Afghanistan, Uganda, Japan and beyond. Marilyn also currently coordinates CAWA - The California Women's Agenda that is the million women network follow-up to the 4th World Conference on Women that took place in Beijing in 1995. WIN/CAWA - www.win-cawa.org/cawa - 415.221.4841
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-CausesThatMatter/TJKS_07_48_whole_vbr.mp3" length="51727689" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">supporting-causes-that-matter</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:51</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Volunteer Power: The Green Challenge KKGN 960 2007 repeat of Red, White and Green with Edits show -->
<item>
      <title>Volunteer Power: The Green Challenge</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20071103.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>This lively conversation focuses on how California, America, and the planet can benefit from Volunteer Power. There is an ever-growing imperative to understand and get involved with the needs of our neighborhoods and communities. November 17th is National Family Volunteer Day – meant to celebrate and promote volunteer commitments. Learn about the vital, on-going programs at the Volunteer Center of Silicon Valley. You'll want to hear about:
</p>
    * how to take part in the three-year VCSV Green Challenge Program<br />
    * "We‘ve Got the Power!" celebration at Santa Clara University November 17th<br />   
    * signing up for the 7 Step, Live Earth Pledge at www.liveearthpledge.org<br />     
    * great ways families can join together for socially responsible causes<br />  
    * important reasons for knowing when to call 211 in stead of 911<br />
    * big pay-offs for individuals, corporations & governments working together
<p><b>Featured Guests</b><br />
Judy Levin is in her second year as President of the Volunteer Center of Silicon Valley, known as VCSV, which is celebrating its 20th year. She has been active in community volunteer efforts for over two decades, primarily in Silicon Valley, and has served on the Board of Trustees of KTEH Public TV, the Yavneh Day School, and was President of the Jewish Federation of Silicon Valley. Most recently, Judy chaired a 25 million dollar capital campaign to build the Levy Jewish Family Campus in Los Gatos.
</p>
<p>Stephen T. Quigley, Jr. – known by his middle name Tim – is a civic entrepreneur and the Executive Director of VCSV. His professional forty-year career has encompassed both public and community service - from the arts to international business to childhood development. His senior executive positions have included President of the Silicon Valley Defense/Space Consortium, Executive Director/CEO of the Silicon Valley Global Trading Center, and Commanding Officer at Moffett Field Naval Air Station.
</p>
<p>Volunteer Center of Silicon Valley, www.vcsv.us, 408-247-1126</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-VolunteerPower/TJKS_7_44_Whole.mp3" length="71770069" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volunteer-power-the-green-challenge</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>

<!-- Coffee: Grounds for Health KKGN 960 2007 version -->
<item>
      <title>Healthy Grounds for Coffee</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20071020.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>During this jazzy java conversation, you'll hear fascinating information and inside stories about what brings coffee to all of us from coffee experts Orrel Lanter and Andi Trindle. From the fields to fair trade, we'll cover:
</p>
<p>- new reports about the health benefits of coffee
</p>
<p>- what kind of coffee offers the most anti-oxidants
</p>
<p>- how Orrel equates cupping with wine tasting
</p>
<p>- the best ways to store and keep coffee fresh
</p>
<p>- Andi's info about the coffee industry's benefits for women
</p>
<p>- the lowdown on decaf
</p>
<p>Orrel Lanter is founder and Director of Business Development for Uncommon Grounds Coffee. She is an entrepreneurial business executive with a long track record of leadership in community-based organizations. In 1984 she co-founded Uncommon Grounds Coffee, based on a "sustainable" global model. Orrel organized the first Sustainable Business Conference in Berkeley, California and was a panelist with Fortune Magazine's "Women In Leadership Conference". www.uncommongrounds.net
</p>
<p>Andi Trindle is a consultant for VOLCAFE Specialty Coffee and Boot Coffee Consulting. She is Vice President of the International Women's Coffee Alliance and serves on the board for the E-Café Foundation, an organization dedicated to Transparency, Sustainability and Quality for the specialty coffee industry. Andi lectures on various aspects of specialty coffees and has taught numerous espresso and cupping workshops nationally and internationally. www.volcafe.com and www.bootcoffee.com</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-CoffeeGroundsForHealth/Tjks.07.41whole.mp3" length="47992682" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">healthy-grounds-for-coffee</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:00</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Your Pets: Best Love, Best Care KKGN 960 2007 version DELETED and replaced with a slightly updated version 1-19-08 -->
<!-- Peace Day – 2007 KKGN 960 2007 version -->
<item>
      <title>Peace Day – 2007</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20070915.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The annual International Day of Peace (Peace Day) is celebrated on September 21st when millions of people—worldwide—come together in the name of Peace. In 2006, more than 3500 Peace Day events – such as concerts, workshops, vigils, and school projects, took place in 200 countries. Our program is dedicated to the people and organizations around the world that are, each day, doing their part to contribute to a peaceful and sustainable planet. The show includes call-ins from inspiring Peace Leaders:
</p>
<p>- Robert Muller – Univ. of Peace; Former UN Assist. Secretary General
</p>
<p>- Patricia Smith Melton – Peace X Peace
</p>
<p>- Sharon Mehdi – Author, "The Great Silent Grandmother Gathering"
</p>
<p>- Joanie Misrack – Pathways to Peace
</p>
<p>- Louise Diamond –The Peace Company
</p>
<p>- Sharon Franquemont – Annual Prayer Vigil for the Earth
</p>
<p>- Barbara Gaughen-Muller – Pax 2100
</p>
<p>- Dot Maver – The Peace Alliance; Department of Peace Initiative
</p>
<p>We are pleased to feature the music of Gary Malkin, an award-winning composer, producer and performer dedicated to making a difference in the world.
</p>
<p>Peace is a raging river! It plunges over a cliff to become a waterfall, sparkling and roaring in the sunlight. It is power. It is generative, nourishing, and irresistible. It calls me to new places where I will change. – David Spangler
</p>
<p>Avon Mattison  is Co-Founder and President of Pathways to Peace, an international peace-building educational and consulting organization. Avon is a forerunner in the field of peace-building, and has been involved with The International Day of Peace since it's inauguration. Pathways to Peace serves as international coordinator of the Culture of Peace Initiative, which has been granted UN Peace Messenger status.
</p>
<p>Charles Gibbs  is the founding Executive Director of the United Religions Initiative, a global interfaith network for world peace that is active in 60 countries. Charles has traveled worldwide as a featured speaker and collaborator with religious, spiritual, and community leaders. He co-authored Birth of a Global Community  about the birth of the United Religions Initiative.</p>
<p>Masankho Banda  is an international performer and educator dedicated to building peace through music and storytelling. Masankho has brought his work into schools, organizations, corporations and communities around the world. He is the founder of UCanDanc' African Healing Arts  and the Co-Founder and Co-Director of The Institute for Peacebuilding. He also serves on the Board of Directors for Pathways to Peace.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TheJoanKenleyShow-Peace/PeaceDay_Webmix.mp3" length="46878719" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">peace-day-2007</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:50</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Visioning What Can Change KKGN 960 2007 version -->
<!-- Healthy Habits Updated to Use KKGN 960 2007 version -->
<!-- Changed the pubDate -->
<!-- Appears out of order because it had been uploaded earlier -->
    <item>
      <title>Healthy Habits Year Round</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20070804.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Can positive habits make you healthier and happier? Is change really possible? It's never too late to begin new habits to truly take care of yourself. English playwright John Dryden once said, "We first make our habits, and then our habits make us."
</p>
<p>Because everyone can benefit from creating better habits, our conversation explores:
</p>
<p>- what role the mind plays in the habits we have
</p>
<p>- how people may react when you make healthy changes in your life
</p>
<p>- the ways we sabotage ourselves when we commit to new habits
</p>
<p>- what happens physiologically when you exercise, eat well, and reduce stress
</p>
<p>- how cultural norms and the media affect our attitude about ourselves and others
</p>
<p>- why having a spiritual focus can influence a healthier consciousness
</p>
<p>Joyce Gidel  is a licensed Marriage Family Therapist and head of the family therapy program at Merritt Peralta Institute, part of Alta Bates-Summit Medical Center. Joyce has a private practice in Oakland and is in the process of writing a book on codependency and spirituality.
</p>
<p>Patty Torza is a certified Personal Fitness Trainer, Post-Rehab Conditioning Specialist, and holistic Nutrition Consultant. She has worked in the fitness profession as an athlete, teacher, administrator, coach, and lecturer. Patty's approach to fitness is goal-oriented, motivating, and fun-filled.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 4 Aug 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/TJKS_19_Healthy_Habits_Webmix/TJKS_19_Healthy_Habits_Webmix.mp3" length="24024706" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">healthy-habits-year-round</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>50:02</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Welcome Show Quake 960 2006 9_16 version -->
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Joan Kenley Show</title>
      <link>http://www.joankenley.com/20060916.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Veteran talk show host, Peter B. Collins – a mentor and senior member of the production team – interviews Joan with humor, interest, and sensitivity. They have a lively exchange about launching The Joan Kenley Show and branding the format as ‘Conversation Radio'.</p>

<p>You'll hear why Joan was invited into in the San Francisco market – and how The Joan Kenley Show is new and different for radio listeners.</p>

<p>This introductory show contains excerpts from three of her programs over the last six months:</p>

<p><b>-Alternative Pet Care -</b><br />
Jenny Taylor, DVM has a wealth of background and advanced training in her career as a veterinarian. She founded Creature Comfort Holistic Veterinary Center in Oakland, California — the first complementary veterinary clinic in the Bay Area. Her clinic offers Chinese and Western herbal therapies, acupuncture, homeopathy, and chiropractic — in addition to traditional Western veterinary medicine. She was the featured veterinarian and host of the DVD version of "Dogs for Dummies". Contact information is Creature Comforts at 510-530-1373 or www.creaturecomfort.com
</p>
<p>Rebecca Thomas, EBW is a certified equine body worker in the Bay Area. Her practice includes backyard pets, trail horses, endurance racers and high-end show horses. Working with vets and individual owners, she handles injury recovery, physical therapy, arthritis, and general maintenance for the equine/canine performers, dogs, cats and birds. Massage is never a replacement for veterinarian care, but an important adjunct for healing and performance. To reach Rebecca, go to www.equinebodywork.net, rebecca@equinebodywork.net or call 510-304-1890.
</p>
<p>Heidi Kistler was inspired by her love of animals to start her pet sitting business nine years ago, The Pawsitively Pampered Pet.  Within the first two years she was awarded Pet Sitter of the Year by the Pet Sitting International organization.  With the success of her business, and with the help of her clients, she has recently planned and presented charity events that raise money for needy mothers and children.  For more information go to www.yourpamperedpets.com
</p>
<p><b>- The Art of Storytelling -</b><br /> 
Gay Ducey is a children's librarian, free-lance storyteller, storytelling educator and organizer. She has appeared on Mr. Rogers' Neighborhood and performs regularly throughout North America. She was commissioned by the Smithsonian's Museum of American History to present stories in "Union Maid: Stories from America's Women at Work." Gay is also co-author of Spilt Milk: Traditional Tales of Mother and Motherhood, scheduled for publication in 2007. mducey@earthlink.net
</p>
<p>Sandra Noman is a teacher, writer, grandmother and lively teller of tales. She is currently directing a program serving the needs of homeless middle school children in San Francisco. Born in East Africa to medical missionaries, she has lived in many lands, gathering stories everywhere. She recently was the director of the Dominican University Storytelling Program. sandra@homeaway.org
</p>
<p><b>-The Power of Intention -</b><br />
Dr. Brenda Wade is a psychologist, author, television host and producer. Power Choices is the name of her new book and her PBS pledge special. Dr. Wade helps viewers turn stumbling blocks into stepping stones and is best known for her love-centered approach to transformation. Power Choices will be aired on KQED in the Bay Area on June 5th and 15th. Contact PBS for air times in other areas. www.docwade.com; www.powerchoices.net; 888-362-9233.
</p>
<p>Marcia Jaffe is a conference entrepreneur and the visionary behind the Quest for Global Healing Conference series in Bali. She has been creating and producing conferences and events for more than 30 years, bringing together up to 400,000 people around cutting edge topics of national and global concern. Early this May, Marcia completed her second event in Bali with Desmond Tutu and more than 650 delegates from over 35 countries. www.questforglobalhealing.com; 800-577-2254.
</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2006 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.joankenley.com/podcast/WelcomeShow_09_16_06.mp3" length="115646181" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">welcome-to-the-joan-kenley-show</guid>
      <itunes:author>joan@joankenley.com (Joan Kenley)</itunes:author>
      <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:11</itunes:duration>
    </item>
<!-- Enter all ITEMS above this comment -->
  </channel>
</rss>