<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/podcast.xml" />
		<lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 11:05:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
		<title>Streaming Cafe</title>
		<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
		<link>http://streamingcafe.net</link>
		<generator>Podcast Maker v1.4.1 - http://www.lemonzdream.com/podcastmaker</generator>
		<description><![CDATA[A weekly video podcast that features music and insights from indie artists that have performed at the Streaming Cafe.

We are a listening room inspired to discover, connect, and promote independent artists and offer a unique platform for performers to interact directly with indie music-lovers. Every Saturday night we showcase live performances by established and up & coming talent from Canada and beyond. These weekly shows are streamed free live online, where viewers anywhere in the world can enjoy direct and personal interaction with the artists via the live chat.]]></description>
		<itunes:subtitle>Live indie music on your computer at streamingcafe.net - Bringing Music to the World!</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>A weekly video podcast that features music and insights from indie artists that have performed at the Streaming Cafe.

We are a listening room inspired to discover, connect, and promote independent artists and offer a unique platform for performers to interact directly with indie music-lovers. Every Saturday night we showcase live performances by established and up &amp; coming talent from Canada and beyond. These weekly shows are streamed free live online, where viewers anywhere in the world can enjoy direct and personal interaction with the artists via the live chat.</itunes:summary>
		<language>en</language>
		<copyright>Streaming Cafe</copyright>
		<itunes:owner>
			<itunes:name>Streaming Cafe</itunes:name>
			<itunes:email>martin@streamingcafe.net</itunes:email>
		</itunes:owner>
		<image>
			<url>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/SCpodcast_image_144.jpg</url>
			<title>Streaming Cafe</title>
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net</link>
			<width>144</width>
			<height>139</height>
		</image>
		<itunes:image href="http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/SCpodcast_image.jpg" />
		<category>Music</category>
		<itunes:category text="Music" />
		<category>Podcasting</category>
		<itunes:category text="Technology">
			<itunes:category text="Podcasting" />
		</itunes:category>
		<category>Performing Arts</category>
		<itunes:category text="Arts">
			<itunes:category text="Performing Arts" />
		</itunes:category>
		<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
		<item>
			<title>Steve Gates</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Poetic lyrics written from a sincere and humble heart with delicate finger-picking that warms the room, there are few musicians that are so accurately represented in their music as Steve Gates. In this podcast he plays the song "Five White Tigers" from his 2012 album "A Bee In Her Mouth". Steve talks about his time in the Yukon and helping an elementary school with music for its Christmas concert.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Poetic lyrics written from a sincere and humble heart with delicate finger-picking that warms the room. Steve Gates plays the song &quot;Five White Tigers&quot; from his 2012 album &quot;A Bee In Her Mouth&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Poetic lyrics written from a sincere and humble heart with delicate finger-picking that warms the room, there are few musicians that are so accurately represented in their music as Steve Gates. In this podcast he plays the song &quot;Five White Tigers&quot; from his 2012 album &quot;A Bee In Her Mouth&quot;. Steve talks about his time in the Yukon and helping an elementary school with music for its Christmas concert.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120606%20SteveGates.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="52479476" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120606%20SteveGates.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 10:29:15 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:14</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cara Luft</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[As a founding member of Juno award winning group the Wailin' Jennys, Cara Luft is no stranger to the Canadian folk/roots community. Her latest self-produced solo album titled 'Darlingford' 2012 was recorded across Canada in old churches, living rooms and home studios. Cara played an engaging solo set along side Jordan Klassen, James Lamb and Andy Shauf during the One Night Music Fest at the Streaming Cafe. An artist true to her craft she knows her songs inside and out, the inspiration behind them and the stories that forged them. In this podcast Cara plays the tune "Black Water Side" gives a bit of a background for the song and makes a shout out to the Led Zeppelin fans in the audience.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>As a founding member of Juno award winning group the Wailin&apos; Jennys, Cara Luft is no stranger to the Canadian folk/roots community. In this podcast she plays the tune &quot;Black Water Side&quot; and makes a shout out to the Led Zeppelin fans in the audience.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>As a founding member of Juno award winning group the Wailin&apos; Jennys, Cara Luft is no stranger to the Canadian folk/roots community. Her latest self-produced solo album titled &apos;Darlingford&apos; 2012 was recorded across Canada in old churches, living rooms and home studios. Cara played an engaging solo set along side Jordan Klassen, James Lamb and Andy Shauf during the One Night Music Fest at the Streaming Cafe. An artist true to her craft she knows her songs inside and out, the inspiration behind them and the stories that forged them. In this podcast Cara plays the tune &quot;Black Water Side&quot; gives a bit of a background for the song and makes a shout out to the Led Zeppelin fans in the audience.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120529%20Cara%20Luft.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="43069363" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120529%20Cara%20Luft.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 11:21:48 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:32</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Samantha Savage Smith</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Calgarian Samantha Savage Smith (apparently also known as "Savage", "Triple S" or "Triple S Threat") put on quite the show with her honest and engaging lyrics backed by a voice so distinct and powerful it can't be mistaken for anyone else. Savage's time spent in the underground indie scene was short lived after being discovered by Lorrie Matheson in 2009 who recorded her in 2010 and released the album "Tough Cookie" in 2011 which was distributed by Arts & Crafts. This podcast features the tune "You Always Come To Mind".]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Calgarian Samantha Savage Smith put on quite the show with her honest and engaging lyrics backed by a voice so distinct and powerful it can&apos;t be mistaken for anyone else. This podcast features the tune &quot;You Always Come To Mind&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Calgarian Samantha Savage Smith (apparently also known as &quot;Savage&quot;, &quot;Triple S&quot; or &quot;Triple S Threat&quot;) put on quite the show with her honest and engaging lyrics backed by a voice so distinct and powerful it can&apos;t be mistaken for anyone else. Savage&apos;s time spent in the underground indie scene was short lived after being discovered by Lorrie Matheson in 2009 who recorded her in 2010 and released the album &quot;Tough Cookie&quot; in 2011 which was distributed by Arts &amp; Crafts. This podcast features the tune &quot;You Always Come To Mind&quot;.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120523%20Samantha%20Savage%20Smith.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="49626310" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120523%20Samantha%20Savage%20Smith.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 13:19:45 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:12</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mike Edel</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Mike Edel has been a Cafe favourite ever since his solo show back in 2011. This year Mike brought four of his friends and treated us to the full "Mike Edel" experience. This podcast features the song "West Mont" and Mike tells us the story that served as inspiration for the tune.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>This podcast features the song &quot;West Mont&quot; and Mike tells us the story that served as inspiration for the tune.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Mike Edel has been a Cafe favourite ever since his solo show back in 2011. This year Mike brought four of his friends and treated us to the full &quot;Mike Edel&quot; experience. This podcast features the song &quot;West Mont&quot; and Mike tells us the story that served as inspiration for the tune.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120511%20Mike%20Edel.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="64317048" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120511%20Mike%20Edel.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2012 16:55:18 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:05:23</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Keith Price Trio</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Hailing from Winnipeg, Manitoba The Keith Price Trio is doing their part to make Jazz accessible to the masses. They start by taking indie Rock/Pop songs by artists like Nirvana, Neil Young, Grizzly Bear and St. Vincent and then recomposing them into instrumental jazz works of art. Their 2011 album "Gaia/Goya" features these cover songs along with originals. In this podcast we feature an excerpt from the "Gaia/Goya Suite" and Keith retells how he crafts an instrumental 6-piece song based on how choice/fate/the universe can result in magic! ...and the difference between Jazz and Elevator music.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In this podcast we feature an excerpt from the &quot;Gaia/Goya Suite&quot; as Keith retells how he crafts an instrumental 6-piece song based on how choice/fate/universe can result in magic! ...and the difference between Jazz and Elevator music.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Hailing from Winnipeg, Manitoba The Keith Price Trio is doing their part to make Jazz accessible to the masses. They start by taking indie Rock/Pop songs by artists like Nirvana, Neil Young, Grizzly Bear and St. Vincent and then recomposing them into instrumental jazz works of art. Their 2011 album &quot;Gaia/Goya&quot; features these cover songs along with originals. In this podcast we feature an excerpt from the &quot;Gaia/Goya Suite&quot; and Keith retells how he crafts an instrumental 6-piece song based on how choice/fate/the universe can result in magic! ...and the difference between Jazz and Elevator music.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120426%20KeithPriceTrio.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="67361985" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120426%20KeithPriceTrio.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 10:53:01 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:05:45</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music, Keith Price Trio, Gaia/Goya, Nirvana, Neil Young, St Vincent, Grizzly Bear</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>In Medias Res</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[In Medias Res is a Vancouver indie-rock group that has earned veteran status for it's 12 year career. Their most recent album "It Was Warm and Sunny When We First Set Out" (2011) showcases the band's diversity and range as it sweeps from slow-burning crescendos to sweetly melodic lulls.

In this podcast they perform a real crowd pleaser - an unplugged acoustic version of "Untitled New Track" (We called Andrew from In Medias Res to confirm the actual title for this track...But this was it.)  While playing this song the band needed to enforce one simple rule…You must be at the very least on your feet if not actually STANDING on something.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In Medias Res is a Vancouver indie-rock group that has earned veteran status for it&apos;s 12 year career. In this podcast they perform a real crowd pleaser - an unplugged acoustic version of &quot;Untitled New Track&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>In Medias Res is a Vancouver indie-rock group that has earned veteran status for it&apos;s 12 year career. Their most recent album &quot;It Was Warm and Sunny When We First Set Out&quot; (2011) showcases the band&apos;s diversity and range as it sweeps from slow-burning crescendos to sweetly melodic lulls.

In this podcast they perform a real crowd pleaser - an unplugged acoustic version of &quot;Untitled New Track&quot; (We called Andrew from In Medias Res to confirm the actual title for this track...But this was it.)  While playing this song the band needed to enforce one simple rule…You must be at the very least on your feet if not actually STANDING on something.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120417%20In%20Medias%20Res.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="40617668" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120417%20In%20Medias%20Res.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 10:45:49 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:16</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sheree Plett</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Sheree Plett is a singer/songwriter based out of Vancouver, BC. Her most recent release is an album of dreamy, original lullabies titled "Hello Night". The record was created by drawing inspiration from moments shared with her first born and results in a collection of songs that can be enjoyed not only by young ones, but by their mothers and anyone else who enjoys a whimsical contemporary-folk album!

Sheree plays the title track "Hello Moon" and dedicates the album to her son, Henry. She jokes about what to give to her child on the way, how about a book? http://shereeplett.com/timestwo]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Sheree plays the title track &quot;Hello Moon&quot; and dedicates the album to her son, Henry. She jokes about what to give to her child on the way, how about a book?</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Sheree Plett is a singer/songwriter based out of Vancouver, BC. Her most recent release is an album of dreamy, original lullabies titled &quot;Hello Night&quot;. The record was created by drawing inspiration from moments shared with her first born and results in a collection of songs that can be enjoyed not only by young ones, but by their mothers and anyone else who enjoys a whimsical contemporary-folk album!

Sheree plays the title track &quot;Hello Moon&quot; and dedicates the album to her son, Henry. She jokes about what to give to her child on the way, how about a book? http://shereeplett.com/timestwo</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120411%20Sheree%20Plett.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="40411687" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120411%20Sheree%20Plett.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 12:30:54 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:11</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Craig Cardiff</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Its always a great feeling to see our friends recieve recognition for their work, Craig Cardiff's album "Floods & Fires" earned a 2012 Juno nomination for Roots & Traditional Album Of The Year: Solo. Craig played an all folked up and edgy double-bill back in January and left his audience with something great to talk about.

In this week's podcast Craig plays the song "Dance Me Outside" from his 2010 album "Songs For Lucy", he tells the story of driving through town with his grandmother giving directions from memory and asking how tall the trees are.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Craig Cardiff&apos;s album &quot;Floods &amp; Fires&quot; earned a 2012 Juno nomination for Roots &amp; Traditional Album Of The Year: Solo. In this week&apos;s podcast Craig plays the song &quot;Dance Me Outside&quot; from his 2010 album &quot;Songs For Lucy&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Its always a great feeling to see our friends recieve recognition for their work, Craig Cardiff&apos;s album &quot;Floods &amp; Fires&quot; earned a 2012 Juno nomination for Roots &amp; Traditional Album Of The Year: Solo. Craig played an all folked up and edgy double-bill back in January and left his audience with something great to talk about.

In this week&apos;s podcast Craig plays the song &quot;Dance Me Outside&quot; from his 2010 album &quot;Songs For Lucy&quot;, he tells the story of driving through town with his grandmother giving directions from memory and asking how tall the trees are.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120404%20Craig%20Cardiff.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="59786613" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120404%20Craig%20Cardiff.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 14:24:07 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:53</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ma Petite</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Australia born Indiana Avent turned her focus to her own music after years of backing artists like Bon Iver, Gotye and Dan Mangan. Her solo project, Ma Petite, put out an EP in 2010 and is schedule to release it's first full length album titled "The Road That Led Me To Fall" in early 2012.

In this week's podcast Indiana plays the song "Lonesome" that will be on her soon to be released album. She goes on to tell of her inspiration for the song, but gets somewhat side tracked with a little piece of Australia/Canada culture shock.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In this week&apos;s podcast Ma Petite plays the song &quot;Lonesome&quot; that will be on her soon to be released album. She goes on to tell of her inspiration for the song, but gets somewhat side tracked with a little piece of Australia/Canada culture shock.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Australia born Indiana Avent turned her focus to her own music after years of backing artists like Bon Iver, Gotye and Dan Mangan. Her solo project, Ma Petite, put out an EP in 2010 and is schedule to release it&apos;s first full length album titled &quot;The Road That Led Me To Fall&quot; in early 2012.

In this week&apos;s podcast Indiana plays the song &quot;Lonesome&quot; that will be on her soon to be released album. She goes on to tell of her inspiration for the song, but gets somewhat side tracked with a little piece of Australia/Canada culture shock.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120328%20Ma%20Petite.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="51040915" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120328%20Ma%20Petite.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 13:34:42 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:02</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Fish &amp; Bird</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[The Victoria formed 2-piece turned 5-piece group Fish & Bird have made quite a splash with their flight into the Canadian folk/indie scene (all puns intended). Their 2011 album "Every Whisper is a Shout Across the Void" exhibits tight musicianship, spot on vocals and songs that present the fragility of our humanly interactions.

In this podcast Fish & Bird play the song "Burst Into Flower" off of their 2009 album "Left Brain Blues" and talk about how prior to the show, Taylor and Ryan were musing about who might be teaching who in an unforeseeable future.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In this podcast Fish &amp; Bird play the song &quot;Burst Into Flower&quot; off of their 2009 album &quot;Left Brain Blues&quot; and talk about how prior to the show, Taylor and Ryan were musing about who might be teaching who in an unforeseeable future.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The Victoria formed 2-piece turned 5-piece group Fish &amp; Bird have made quite a splash with their flight into the Canadian folk/indie scene (all puns intended). Their 2011 album &quot;Every Whisper is a Shout Across the Void&quot; exhibits tight musicianship, spot on vocals and songs that present the fragility of our humanly interactions.

In this podcast Fish &amp; Bird play the song &quot;Burst Into Flower&quot; off of their 2009 album &quot;Left Brain Blues&quot; and talk about how prior to the show, Taylor and Ryan were musing about who might be teaching who in an unforeseeable future.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120322%20Fish%20%26%20Bird.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="42132828" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120322%20Fish%20%26%20Bird.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 11:17:03 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:26</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Reuben Bullock</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Described as 'a singer/songwriter. A citizen. An understudy of all things misunderstood.' Reuben's simple melodies and rich lyrics produce powerful, evoking yet calming tunes that articulate the feelings that stir deep within their creator. Reuben started 2012 off with a bang at the Streaming Cafe as he performs the tune "Marionette" and talks about how his musical tastes do or do not affect his own song writing.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Reuben started 2012 off with a bang at the Streaming Cafe as he performs the tune &quot;Marionette&quot; and talks about how his musical tastes do or do not affect his own song writing.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Described as &apos;a singer/songwriter. A citizen. An understudy of all things misunderstood.&apos; Reuben&apos;s simple melodies and rich lyrics produce powerful, evoking yet calming tunes that articulate the feelings that stir deep within their creator. Reuben started 2012 off with a bang at the Streaming Cafe as he performs the tune &quot;Marionette&quot; and talks about how his musical tastes do or do not affect his own song writing.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120314%20Reuben%20Bullock%202.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="46913405" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120314%20Reuben%20Bullock%202.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 15:53:52 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:42</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Windmills</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Windmills is Cory Myraas.

In this week's podcast Cory generously gives his audience a crash course in looping while playing the tune "Corona". With a curriculum consisting of Reverse Double-Times, Half-Times and One Man Harmonies - be sure to pay attention because there might be a pop quiz afterwards…Eyes on your own work.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Windmills is Cory Myraas.

In this week&apos;s podcast Cory generously gives his audience a crash course in looping while playing the tune &quot;Corona&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Windmills is Cory Myraas.

In this week&apos;s podcast Cory generously gives his audience a crash course in looping while playing the tune &quot;Corona&quot;. With a curriculum consisting of Reverse Double-Times, Half-Times and One Man Harmonies - be sure to pay attention because there might be a pop quiz afterwards…Eyes on your own work.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120307%20Windmills2.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="63010254" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120307%20Windmills2.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 10:53:07 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:05:06</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Brent Tyler</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Brent Tyler is in fact the World's Tallest Guitarist.* In this podcast Brent plays the title track from his record "In Rhythm" and talks about the temporary handicap that put him in the mindset that in life, at any one second everything could be taken away from you.

* Streaming Cafe has no authority in awarding Brent with the actual title of World's Tallest Guitarist, but we truly believe he is pretty dang close…and is a very nice man.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In this podcast Brent plays the title track from his record &quot;In Rhythm&quot; and talks about the temporary handicap that put him in the mindset that in life, at any one second everything could be taken away from you.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Brent Tyler is in fact the World&apos;s Tallest Guitarist.* In this podcast Brent plays the title track from his record &quot;In Rhythm&quot; and talks about the temporary handicap that put him in the mindset that in life, at any one second everything could be taken away from you.

* Streaming Cafe has no authority in awarding Brent with the actual title of World&apos;s Tallest Guitarist, but we truly believe he is pretty dang close…and is a very nice man.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120301%20BrentTylerPodcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="64146938" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120301%20BrentTylerPodcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 14:10:31 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:05:07</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steph Machperson</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[This week our podcast features artist Steph Macpherson who played for us in September of 2011. Steph plays the song "Bells and Whistles" that she wrote when competing in Vancouver's Peak Performance Contest. Steph gives a stellar performance and shares the story that is written into her song.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>This week our podcast features artist Steph Macpherson who played for us in September of 2011. Steph plays the song &quot;Bells and Whistles&quot; that she wrote when competing in Vancouver&apos;s Peak Performance Contest.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>This week our podcast features artist Steph Macpherson who played for us in September of 2011. Steph plays the song &quot;Bells and Whistles&quot; that she wrote when competing in Vancouver&apos;s Peak Performance Contest. Steph gives a stellar performance and shares the story that is written into her song.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120224%20Steph%20Machperson.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="52578249" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120224%20Steph%20Machperson.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 08:33:37 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:17</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sarah Brendel</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Germany native Sarah Brendel returned to the Cafe a year after her first performance and played an electrifying double bill with Daniel Moir. In true artistic and experimental fashion, Michael Fraser (aka DJ Redworm) who was the violinist with Daniel Moir joined in with Sarah's performance for unrehearsed musical bliss. This podcast features the song "Poets" off of Sarah's 2011 album "Before The Mountains". Sarah talks about the inspiration for her song coming from the encouragement she received from her father during her early songwriting career.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Germany native Sarah Brendel returned to the Cafe a year after her first performance and played an electrifying double bill with Daniel Moir. This podcast features the song &quot;Poets&quot; off of Sarah&apos;s 2011 album &quot;Before The Mountains&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Germany native Sarah Brendel returned to the Cafe a year after her first performance and played an electrifying double bill with Daniel Moir. In true artistic and experimental fashion, Michael Fraser (aka DJ Redworm) who was the violinist with Daniel Moir joined in with Sarah&apos;s performance for unrehearsed musical bliss. This podcast features the song &quot;Poets&quot; off of Sarah&apos;s 2011 album &quot;Before The Mountains&quot;. Sarah talks about the inspiration for her song coming from the encouragement she received from her father during her early songwriting career.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120217%20Sarah%20Brendel.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="45721386" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120217%20Sarah%20Brendel.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 10:37:54 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:54</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>100th Podcast with Portage and Main</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Well, it finally happened - we've reached 100 Podcasts! For all those who watch our live shows over the internet and don't get a chance to see the wood wall in person (it's real cherry wood, by the way...) we wanted to give you a peak at what its like to be front row at the Streaming Cafe. Featuring the tune "Carolina" by Portage And Main and an inside look at how we transform our coffee shop into a high-tech live music venue.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Well, it finally happened - we&apos;ve reached 100 Podcasts! Featuring the tune &quot;Carolina&quot; by Portage And Main and an inside look at how we transform our coffee shop into a high-tech live music venue.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Well, it finally happened - we&apos;ve reached 100 Podcasts! For all those who watch our live shows over the internet and don&apos;t get a chance to see the wood wall in person (it&apos;s real cherry wood, by the way...) we wanted to give you a peak at what its like to be front row at the Streaming Cafe. Featuring the tune &quot;Carolina&quot; by Portage And Main and an inside look at how we transform our coffee shop into a high-tech live music venue.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120204%20100th%20Podcast%20v2.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="41019360" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120204%20100th%20Podcast%20v2.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 08:53:51 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:12</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Dominique Fricot</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Dominique Fricot played solo for the first time at the Streaming Cafe back in December 2011 (He first played back in November 2009 with a three piece called "The Painted Birds"). Bursting at the seams with charm and charisma, Dominique gave a high energy and captivating performance. In this podcast he plays the song "Burn And Start Over" and with the help of a mysterious bus rider in a cowboy hat, draws the correlation between music and cheese. …You learn something every day!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Dominique Fricot played the Streaming Cafe back in December 2011. In this podcast he plays the song &quot;Burn And Start Over&quot; and draws the correlation between music and cheese. …You learn something every day!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Dominique Fricot played solo for the first time at the Streaming Cafe back in December 2011 (He first played back in November 2009 with a three piece called &quot;The Painted Birds&quot;). Bursting at the seams with charm and charisma, Dominique gave a high energy and captivating performance. In this podcast he plays the song &quot;Burn And Start Over&quot; and with the help of a mysterious bus rider in a cowboy hat, draws the correlation between music and cheese. …You learn something every day!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120131%20Dominique%20Fricot.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="44127513" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120131%20Dominique%20Fricot.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 10:42:34 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:28</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ryan McAllister</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Ryan McAllister performs with buddies Daniel Huscroft and JJ Shiplett to a packed house at the Streaming Cafe. They play the song "Mystery White Boy" written about the late great Jeff Buckley.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Ryan McAllister performs with buddies Daniel Huscroft and JJ Shiplett to a packed house at the Streaming Cafe. They play the song &quot;Mystery White Boy&quot; written about the late great Jeff Buckley.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Ryan McAllister performs with buddies Daniel Huscroft and JJ Shiplett to a packed house at the Streaming Cafe. They play the song &quot;Mystery White Boy&quot; written about the late great Jeff Buckley.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120124%20RyanMcAllister.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="72994231" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120124%20RyanMcAllister.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 14:51:33 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:05:57</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>William Fitzsimmons Pt. 3 &quot;Beautiful Girl&quot;</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[William plays the song "Beautiful Girl" off his 2011 album "Gold In The Shadows". Having previously worked in the Mental Health field, William finds inspiration for his songs from observations of the human nature, the good and the bad (but admitting to focus more so on the bad). He says song writing doesn't always come easy, but those Writer's Blocks are part of the process and should be embraced.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>William plays the song &quot;Beautiful Girl&quot; off his 2011 album &quot;Gold In The Shadows&quot;. In this podcast, William talks about his source of inspiration and how he deals with Writer&apos;s Block.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>William plays the song &quot;Beautiful Girl&quot; off his 2011 album &quot;Gold In The Shadows&quot;. Having previously worked in the Mental Health field, William finds inspiration for his songs from observations of the human nature, the good and the bad (but admitting to focus more so on the bad). He says song writing doesn&apos;t always come easy, but those Writer&apos;s Blocks are part of the process and should be embraced.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120112%20William%20Fitzsimmons%20Podcast%203%20Beautiful%20Girl.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="30528475" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120112%20William%20Fitzsimmons%20Podcast%203%20Beautiful%20Girl.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 14:13:54 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:31</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>William Fitzsimmons Pt. 2 &quot;I Don&apos;t Feel It Anymore&quot;</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[In Part 2 of our William Fitzsimmons Podcast Series, William performs the song "I Don't Feel It Anymore (Song of the Sparrow)" off his 2009 album "The Sparrow And The Crow". He reflects on his dedication to performance and how he wont perform a song that he cannot emotionally connect to at that time, and he admits that the greatest compliment he could receives is when someone can connect with his music and find comfort or aid in it.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In Pt. 2, William performs the song &quot;I Don&apos;t Feel It Anymore (Song of the Sparrow)&quot;. He reflects on his dedication to performance and admits that the greatest compliment he could receives is when someone can connect with his music.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>In Part 2 of our William Fitzsimmons Podcast Series, William performs the song &quot;I Don&apos;t Feel It Anymore (Song of the Sparrow)&quot; off his 2009 album &quot;The Sparrow And The Crow&quot;. He reflects on his dedication to performance and how he wont perform a song that he cannot emotionally connect to at that time, and he admits that the greatest compliment he could receives is when someone can connect with his music and find comfort or aid in it.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120105%20William%20Fitzsimmons%20Podcast%202%20I%20Don%27t%20Feel%20It%20Anymore.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="50401343" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/120105%20William%20Fitzsimmons%20Podcast%202%20I%20Don%27t%20Feel%20It%20Anymore.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 12:31:45 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:09</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>William Fitzsimmons Pt. 1 &quot;Blood And Bones&quot;</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[We are starting off the new year with a 3 part Podcast series featuring our most viewed show of 2011, US troubadour William Fitzsimmons.

William Fitzsimmons is an indie troubadour from Jacksonville, IL who performed a sold out show at the Cafe on May 14, 2011. He treated his audience to a mix of old and new songs and even an off-the-cuff serenade for young couple who would be playing his music at their wedding. This podcast features the song "Blood And Bones" off his 2011 release "Gold In The Shadows". William talks about the background of the tune and fields a online question regarding the mythical existence of  "True Love".]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>We are starting off the new year with a 3 part Podcast series featuring our most viewed show of 2011, US troubadour William Fitzsimmons.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>We are starting off the new year with a 3 part Podcast series featuring our most viewed show of 2011, US troubadour William Fitzsimmons.

William Fitzsimmons is an indie troubadour from Jacksonville, IL who performed a sold out show at the Cafe on May 14, 2011. He treated his audience to a mix of old and new songs and even an off-the-cuff serenade for young couple who would be playing his music at their wedding. This podcast features the song &quot;Blood And Bones&quot; off his 2011 release &quot;Gold In The Shadows&quot;. William talks about the background of the tune and fields a online question regarding the mythical existence of  &quot;True Love&quot;.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111229%20William%20Fitzsimmons%20Podcast%201%20Blood%20And%20Bones.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="34915321" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111229%20William%20Fitzsimmons%20Podcast%201%20Blood%20And%20Bones.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 12:49:09 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:56</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>William Fitzsimmons, Blood And Bones, streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Greg Sczebel</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Podcast veteran Greg Sczebel (Greg was the very first Streaming Cafe artist featured on the SC Podcast back on December 19, 2009) returns with Christmas cheer! Greg performed back to back sold out shows full of Christmas spirit at the Cafe. This podcast features the chart topping Christmas tune "Perfect (Merry Little Christmas)" and Greg tells of the roller coast ride to the top of iTunes.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Podcast veteran Greg Sczebel returns with Christmas cheer! This podcast features the chart topping Christmas tune &quot;Perfect (Merry Little Christmas)&quot; and Greg tells of the roller coast ride to the top of iTunes.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Podcast veteran Greg Sczebel (Greg was the very first Streaming Cafe artist featured on the SC Podcast back on December 19, 2009) returns with Christmas cheer! Greg performed back to back sold out shows full of Christmas spirit at the Cafe. This podcast features the chart topping Christmas tune &quot;Perfect (Merry Little Christmas)&quot; and Greg tells of the roller coast ride to the top of iTunes.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111220%20Greg%20Sczebel.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="41070771" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111220%20Greg%20Sczebel.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 16:41:39 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:14</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>My Dearest Friends</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Self described as 'naprock,' My Dearest Friends are making music which undeniably needs to be heard. Frontman Luke Nielsen played a solo show (My Dearest Luke?) at the Cafe and performs the tune "From Dust We Came".]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Self described as &apos;naprock,&apos; My Dearest Friends are making music which undeniably needs to be heard. Frontman Luke Nielsen played a solo show (My Dearest Luke?) at the Cafe and performs the tune &quot;From Dust We Came&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Self described as &apos;naprock,&apos; My Dearest Friends are making music which undeniably needs to be heard. Frontman Luke Nielsen played a solo show (My Dearest Luke?) at the Cafe and performs the tune &quot;From Dust We Came&quot;.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111216%20My%20Dearest%20Friends.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="51917960" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111216%20My%20Dearest%20Friends.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 14:45:44 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:06</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Crooked Brothers</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[The Crooked Brothers shook the timber back in early October. A trio of multi-instrumentalist songwriters who's songs move from sorrow to joy and back with an ageless grace. This podcast features the gritty tune "17 Horses" that is essentially inspired by a pile of dead horses - I have yet to decide if it is a literal or metaphorical pile of dead horses.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>The Crooked Brothers shook the timber back in early October. This podcast features the gritty tune &quot;17 Horses&quot; that is essentially inspired by a pile of dead horses - I have yet to decide if it is a literal or metaphorical pile of dead horses.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The Crooked Brothers shook the timber back in early October. A trio of multi-instrumentalist songwriters who&apos;s songs move from sorrow to joy and back with an ageless grace. This podcast features the gritty tune &quot;17 Horses&quot; that is essentially inspired by a pile of dead horses - I have yet to decide if it is a literal or metaphorical pile of dead horses.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111209%20The%20Crooked%20Brothers.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="44473768" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111209%20The%20Crooked%20Brothers.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 11:37:06 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:37</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Charlotte Cornfield</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Toronto-native Charlotte Cornfield has been named “The next it-girl of folk-rock.” A rock poet with lyrics reminiscent of Joni Mitchell, Bob Dylan or Neil Young and an upbeat energy of Late-70's New York rock and roll. Charlotte shared a lovely summers evening with us, and in this podcast she plays the song "Construction in the Street" off her debut full-length album "Two Horses". She talks about her schooling at McGill University where she studied Jazz Drumming and how drumming is universally applicable to all aspects of music.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Toronto-native Charlotte Cornfield has been named “The next it-girl of folk-rock.” Playing the song &quot;Construction in the Street&quot;  she talks about how drumming is universally applicable to all aspects of music.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Toronto-native Charlotte Cornfield has been named “The next it-girl of folk-rock.” A rock poet with lyrics reminiscent of Joni Mitchell, Bob Dylan or Neil Young and an upbeat energy of Late-70&apos;s New York rock and roll. Charlotte shared a lovely summers evening with us, and in this podcast she plays the song &quot;Construction in the Street&quot; off her debut full-length album &quot;Two Horses&quot;. She talks about her schooling at McGill University where she studied Jazz Drumming and how drumming is universally applicable to all aspects of music.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111202%20Charlotte%20Cornfield.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="41212934" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111202%20Charlotte%20Cornfield.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 10:15:28 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:18</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>Charlotte Cornfield, streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Michael Bernard Fitzgerald</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Michael Bernard Fitzgerald returned to the Cafe for a live CD release after previously playing as part of Break Out West. Michael plays the tune "Suzie (I Love You)" and enlightens his audience on what a "Heavy Chevy Tour" is and why you want to catch the next one.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Michael Bernard Fitzgerald played a show at the Cafe as part of his live CD release party. Michael plays the tune &quot;Suzie (I Love You)&quot; and enlightens his audience on what a &quot;Heavy Chevy Tour&quot; is and why you want to catch the next one.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Michael Bernard Fitzgerald returned to the Cafe for a live CD release after previously playing as part of Break Out West. Michael plays the tune &quot;Suzie (I Love You)&quot; and enlightens his audience on what a &quot;Heavy Chevy Tour&quot; is and why you want to catch the next one.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111125%20Michael%20Bernard%20Fitzgerald.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="35972656" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111125%20Michael%20Bernard%20Fitzgerald.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 09:56:46 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:55</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music, Michael Bernard Fitzgerald</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Paper Beat Scissors</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Relocated Brit Tim Crabtree began Paper Beat Scissors in 2008 following a move to Halifax, Nova Scotia. Live, Tim's music translates to intimate solo finger-picked laments, paired with live loops and a haunting voice that slips seamlessly in and out of the music. This podcast features the song "Flicker" and Tim gives insight to some of his musical influences.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>The live performance of Paper Beat Scissors&apos; Tim Crabtree translates to intimate solo finger-picked laments, paired with live loops and a haunting voice. This podcast features the song &quot;Flicker&quot; and Tim gives insight to some to his musical influences.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Relocated Brit Tim Crabtree began Paper Beat Scissors in 2008 following a move to Halifax, Nova Scotia. Live, Tim&apos;s music translates to intimate solo finger-picked laments, paired with live loops and a haunting voice that slips seamlessly in and out of the music. This podcast features the song &quot;Flicker&quot; and Tim gives insight to some of his musical influences.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111122%20Paper%20Beat%20Scissors.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="63486792" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111122%20Paper%20Beat%20Scissors.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 17:06:25 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:05:07</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Snailhouse</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Feuerstack/Snailhouse’s album Lies on the Prize was nominated for a 2009 Polaris prize, he also plays guitar in the band Wooden Stars, which won a Juno with Julie Doiron for their alternative album Julie Doiron and the Wooden Stars. In this podcast Mike Feuerstack takes requests, gives a "Snailhouse Award" for 'Best Vocal Performance Put to Tape' and says "Lumpy Dumpus" live on the internet (which is definitely a first for the Streaming Cafe). This track features the smooth tune "Clean Water".]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In this podcast Snailhouse takes requests, gives a &quot;Snailhouse Award&quot; for &apos;Best Vocal Performance Put to Tape&apos; and says &quot;Lumpy Dumpus&quot; live on the internet (which is definitely a first for the Streaming Cafe).</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Feuerstack/Snailhouse’s album Lies on the Prize was nominated for a 2009 Polaris prize, he also plays guitar in the band Wooden Stars, which won a Juno with Julie Doiron for their alternative album Julie Doiron and the Wooden Stars. In this podcast Mike Feuerstack takes requests, gives a &quot;Snailhouse Award&quot; for &apos;Best Vocal Performance Put to Tape&apos; and says &quot;Lumpy Dumpus&quot; live on the internet (which is definitely a first for the Streaming Cafe). This track features the smooth tune &quot;Clean Water&quot;.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111111%20Snailhouse.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="47155391" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111111%20Snailhouse.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 15:59:33 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:48</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cécile Doo-Kingué</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Considered one of Montreal’s most electrifying guitarists by local press and groove aficionados, Cécile Doo-Kingué's bewitching and incomparable fretwork as well as her deep and suave voice are no longer secret to Montreal’s night-owls. Cécile masterfully demonstrates her impeccable abilities while getting her Cafe audience tapping their feet in a type of 'afro-folk funk fantasy' that only she can conjure up from the neck of a guitar. Playing the tune "Pure Entertainment," Cécile jokes about the memory of the worst gig she's ever played.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Considered one of Montreal’s most electrifying guitarists, Cécile Doo-Kingué gets her audience tapping their feet in an afro-folk funk fantasy. Playing the tune &quot;Pure Entertainment,&quot; she jokes about the worst gig she&apos;s ever played.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Considered one of Montreal’s most electrifying guitarists by local press and groove aficionados, Cécile Doo-Kingué&apos;s bewitching and incomparable fretwork as well as her deep and suave voice are no longer secret to Montreal’s night-owls. Cécile masterfully demonstrates her impeccable abilities while getting her Cafe audience tapping their feet in a type of &apos;afro-folk funk fantasy&apos; that only she can conjure up from the neck of a guitar. Playing the tune &quot;Pure Entertainment,&quot; Cécile jokes about the memory of the worst gig she&apos;s ever played.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111104%20Ce%CC%81cile%20Doo-Kingue%CC%81.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="101702127" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111104%20Ce%CC%81cile%20Doo-Kingue%CC%81.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 13:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:08:17</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>Cécile Doo-Kingué, streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Matt Beckler</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Currently residing in Nashville, Matt Beckler made his Streaming Cafe debut a memorable one. He proved that with the right charisma a guy with a guitar can take a song that was originally intended for a full band and create a new and equally exhilarating experience.
Matt plays the song "Lately" which he describes as being written, not necessarily out of a state of depression, but as a result of life among the snowdrifts. He also recalls his attempts at deciphering the foreign language of Music Theory and how sometimes you don't need to know what your playing, but simply play what you know.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Matt Beckler made his Streaming Cafe debut a memorable one. Playing the song &quot;Lately&quot; Matt confesses that you don&apos;t need to know what your playing, but simply play what you know.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Currently residing in Nashville, Matt Beckler made his Streaming Cafe debut a memorable one. He proved that with the right charisma a guy with a guitar can take a song that was originally intended for a full band and create a new and equally exhilarating experience.
Matt plays the song &quot;Lately&quot; which he describes as being written, not necessarily out of a state of depression, but as a result of life among the snowdrifts. He also recalls his attempts at deciphering the foreign language of Music Theory and how sometimes you don&apos;t need to know what your playing, but simply play what you know.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111028%20Matt%20Beckler.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="51343845" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111028%20Matt%20Beckler.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 10:19:26 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:10</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music, Matt Beckler</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jasper Sloan Yip</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Jasper Sloan Yipp and his band stopped by during their double bill tour with Behind Sapphire. Jasper played an energetic set, one that would be expected from a 2011 Peak Performance Top 20 finalist. In this Podcast Jasper plays "Shell".]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Jasper Sloan Yipp and his band stopped by during their double bill tour with Behind Sapphire. Jasper played an energetic set, one that would be expected from a 2011 Peak Performance Top 20 finalist. In this Podcast Jasper plays &quot;Shell&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Jasper Sloan Yipp and his band stopped by during their double bill tour with Behind Sapphire. Jasper played an energetic set, one that would be expected from a 2011 Peak Performance Top 20 finalist. In this Podcast Jasper plays &quot;Shell&quot;.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111018%20JasperSloanYip.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="59876817" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111018%20JasperSloanYip.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 15:29:44 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:57</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Daniel Moir</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Daniel Moir is a twice celebrated Streaming Cafe Artist. Having been described as a real up and comer with a very bright future, Daniel has a refreshing and youthful approach to the classic folk singer/songwriter genre. This podcast is taken from Daniel's second appearance and features his song "Penticton" which he admits, looses a bit of it's whimsical mystery if you've actually been to Penticton. Daniel also describes his gradual transition from being a visual artist and painting portraits of his favourite musicians, to audible artist playing songs like…well, Penticton!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>This podcast is taken from Daniel&apos;s second appearance at the Cafe and features his song &quot;Penticton.&quot; Daniel describes his gradual transition from being a visual artist to an audible artist!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Daniel Moir is a twice celebrated Streaming Cafe Artist. Having been described as a real up and comer with a very bright future, Daniel has a refreshing and youthful approach to the classic folk singer/songwriter genre. This podcast is taken from Daniel&apos;s second appearance and features his song &quot;Penticton&quot; which he admits, looses a bit of it&apos;s whimsical mystery if you&apos;ve actually been to Penticton. Daniel also describes his gradual transition from being a visual artist and painting portraits of his favourite musicians, to audible artist playing songs like…well, Penticton!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111011%20Daniel%20Moir.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="36268299" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111011%20Daniel%20Moir.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 09:28:22 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:59</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Grey Kingdom</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Grey Kingdom performed an amazing double bill in June of 2011 with fellow touring musician Young Wife. Grey Kingdom's soft, soothing tunes washed around the room like a warm tropical tide pool and were book-ended by Spencer Burton's unique and often dry comedic takes on life and love. Spencer has a mid-song conversation with his audience and fields a few internet comments, all the while never missing a beat and maybe even learning a little something about himself. This podcast features the song "Quiet King City" off of the album "Eulogy of Her, and Her, and Her."]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In this Podcast Grey Kingdom&apos;s Spencer Burton has a mid-song conversation with his audience and fields a few internet comments. This podcast features the song &quot;Quiet King City.&quot;</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Grey Kingdom performed an amazing double bill in June of 2011 with fellow touring musician Young Wife. Grey Kingdom&apos;s soft, soothing tunes washed around the room like a warm tropical tide pool and were book-ended by Spencer Burton&apos;s unique and often dry comedic takes on life and love. Spencer has a mid-song conversation with his audience and fields a few internet comments, all the while never missing a beat and maybe even learning a little something about himself. This podcast features the song &quot;Quiet King City&quot; off of the album &quot;Eulogy of Her, and Her, and Her.&quot;</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111004%20Grey%20Kingdom.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="60417291" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/111004%20Grey%20Kingdom.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 13:01:10 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:54</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Stevies</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[With their refreshing harmonies and lilting Southern-Hemisphere accents, Australia's The Little Stevies graced Streaming Cafe with their presence as part of a cross-country tour in July of 2011. This was their thrid trip to North America. The Little Stevies had recorded an album in Los Angeles on their last visit, and on this trip to the continent they wanted to focus on Canada, so they set up a tour and hit the road to be with us all. It was a great show, with comments coming in online from folks Down Under as well as in LA and across Canada.

In this podcast, one of The Little Stevies shares about her favourite song, and all three of them give us a lesson in cross-cultural understanding regarding a particular Australian expression. Oh, and they play one of their songs, too...]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>With their refreshing harmonies and lilting Southern-Hemisphere accents, Australia&apos;s The Little Stevies graced Streaming Cafe with their presence as part of their cross-country tour in July of 2011.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>With their refreshing harmonies and lilting Southern-Hemisphere accents, Australia&apos;s The Little Stevies graced Streaming Cafe with their presence as part of a cross-country tour in July of 2011. This was their thrid trip to North America. The Little Stevies had recorded an album in Los Angeles on their last visit, and on this trip to the continent they wanted to focus on Canada, so they set up a tour and hit the road to be with us all. It was a great show, with comments coming in online from folks Down Under as well as in LA and across Canada.

In this podcast, one of The Little Stevies shares about her favourite song, and all three of them give us a lesson in cross-cultural understanding regarding a particular Australian expression. Oh, and they play one of their songs, too...</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110924%20Little%20Stevies.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="66461891" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net/performances/show/179/The-Little-Stevies</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110924%20Little%20Stevies.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 22:00:18 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:05:39</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Zaac Pick redux</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[The buzz around Zaac Pick has been on a steady incline since the release of his debut solo EP Fierce Wind. You might recognize Zaac Pick's 'Maybelline' as the opening tune for our Streaming Cafe shows; this podcast, however, features another one of Zaac's tunes, titled 'My Century', which was the first-place winner of Vancouver's Shore 104.3FM Summer Song Search. In this podcast Zaac tells us what this song means to him.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>The buzz around Zaac Pick has been on a steady incline since the release of his debut solo EP Fierce Wind. You might recognize Zaac Pick&apos;s &apos;Maybelline&apos; as the opening tune for our Streaming Cafe shows...</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The buzz around Zaac Pick has been on a steady incline since the release of his debut solo EP Fierce Wind. You might recognize Zaac Pick&apos;s &apos;Maybelline&apos; as the opening tune for our Streaming Cafe shows; this podcast, however, features another one of Zaac&apos;s tunes, titled &apos;My Century&apos;, which was the first-place winner of Vancouver&apos;s Shore 104.3FM Summer Song Search. In this podcast Zaac tells us what this song means to him.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110914%20Zaac%20Pick.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="56173236" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110914%20Zaac%20Pick.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 16:08:58 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:33</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>James Lamb visits again</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[James Lamb first played at our Cafe 2 years ago back in 2009 - which in Cafe years seems a lot longer! In those two short years James has grown and sharpened his craft to give us a show that we won't soon forget. James plays the song "Ten To One" that was inspired by arguably one of the most influential country musicians of all time, Hank Williams. He also tells the story of his struggle to avoid all things musical in his early years.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>James Lamb first played at our Cafe 2 years ago back in 2009 - which in Cafe years seems a lot longer! In those two short years James has grown and sharpened his craft to give us a show that we won&apos;t soon forget.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>James Lamb first played at our Cafe 2 years ago back in 2009 - which in Cafe years seems a lot longer! In those two short years James has grown and sharpened his craft to give us a show that we won&apos;t soon forget. James plays the song &quot;Ten To One&quot; that was inspired by arguably one of the most influential country musicians of all time, Hank Williams. He also tells the story of his struggle to avoid all things musical in his early years.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110909%20James%20Lamb.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="48535244" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net/artists/show/17/James-Lamb</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110909%20James%20Lamb.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 12:42:19 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:58</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Raleigh</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[After a quick drive from the coast, Raleigh managed to deliver a 100% amazing performance even though they were only able to perform with 66% of their band (their drummer wasn't able to make it). However, they were able to showcase how live and interactive our Streaming Cafe shows are as they had some dialogue with online listeners and even took a request to play 'Murderer.']]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Raleigh managed to deliver a 100% amazing performance even though they were only able to perform with 66% of their band (their drummer wasn&apos;t able to make it).</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>After a quick drive from the coast, Raleigh managed to deliver a 100% amazing performance even though they were only able to perform with 66% of their band (their drummer wasn&apos;t able to make it). However, they were able to showcase how live and interactive our Streaming Cafe shows are as they had some dialogue with online listeners and even took a request to play &apos;Murderer.&apos;</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110831%20Raleigh%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="42993791" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net/artists/show/23/Raleigh</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110831%20Raleigh%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 11:04:43 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:36</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ambre McLean</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Ambre McLean came through the cafe with Gabrielle Papillon for a great double feature night, though I guess it could be a triple feature if you counted Ambre's pregnant belly! In this podcast Ambre not only entertains the audience but also gives them a valuable lesson on white lies, morality and that in the end, the truth will set you free!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Ambre McLean came through the cafe with Gabrielle Papillon for a great double feature night. In this podcast Ambre gives a valuable lesson on white lies, morality and that in the end, the truth will set you free!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Ambre McLean came through the cafe with Gabrielle Papillon for a great double feature night, though I guess it could be a triple feature if you counted Ambre&apos;s pregnant belly! In this podcast Ambre not only entertains the audience but also gives them a valuable lesson on white lies, morality and that in the end, the truth will set you free!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110824%20Ambre%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="37740107" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110824%20Ambre%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 11:26:22 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:07</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jon Bryant</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Jon Bryant has been a good friend and supporter of the Streaming Cafe for as long as we can remember. This podcast is taken from a performance he did back in January 2011. Jon plays a new tune titled "Take Me If You Must", he confesses that from time to time his mind wonders to the subject of death and how life is a precious gift that can be taken in the blink of an eye. Jon also tell us what his biggest show related Pet Peeve is, and how during one fateful show in Edmonton, Alberta he turned that exact aggravation into a celebration!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>This podcast is from a show Jon did back in January 2011. Playing &quot;Take Me If You Must&quot; he confesses that often his mind wonders to the subject of death and how precious life is. He also tells us the biggest Pet Peeve he has while performing!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Jon Bryant has been a good friend and supporter of the Streaming Cafe for as long as we can remember. This podcast is taken from a performance he did back in January 2011. Jon plays a new tune titled &quot;Take Me If You Must&quot;, he confesses that from time to time his mind wonders to the subject of death and how life is a precious gift that can be taken in the blink of an eye. Jon also tell us what his biggest show related Pet Peeve is, and how during one fateful show in Edmonton, Alberta he turned that exact aggravation into a celebration!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110816%20Jon%20Bryant.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="64314242" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110816%20Jon%20Bryant.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 13:51:52 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:05:20</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jess Hill</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Vancouver based singer-songwriter Jess Hill made quite the impression on her audience when she came through our Cafe in May of 2011. In this podcast she performs the song "From Above" that has not only earned her play on national television, but the nickname "The Crow Girl" when she was younger. Jess talks about the footnotes she gets from her father after a live performance and explains what it means to write "Murder Ballads".]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Singer-songwriter Jess Hill came through our Cafe in May of 2011. In this podcast Jess performs the song &quot;From Above&quot; that has not only earned her play on national television, but the nickname &quot;The Crow Girl&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Vancouver based singer-songwriter Jess Hill made quite the impression on her audience when she came through our Cafe in May of 2011. In this podcast she performs the song &quot;From Above&quot; that has not only earned her play on national television, but the nickname &quot;The Crow Girl&quot; when she was younger. Jess talks about the footnotes she gets from her father after a live performance and explains what it means to write &quot;Murder Ballads&quot;.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110810%20Jess%20Hill.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="76662355" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110810%20Jess%20Hill.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 10:25:27 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:06:02</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Erica Mah</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Vancouver based songwriter Erica Mah is a classically trained and extremely talented multi-instrumentalist. With two indepently released full-length albums, Erica's most recent release The Harbor Commission (2009) builds beautifully magical soundscapes that swim from delicate and articulate instrumentals to thundering folk-pop and back again. Erica not only played a beautiful show at the Cafe, but also informed us that there are other instruments in the world besides acoustic guitars and keyboards! In this podcast she pulls out her Guzheng, a 21-stringed Zither that originates from China, to perfrom the song "The Deep" off of her newest album.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Vancouver based songwriter Erica Mah is a classically trained and extremely talented multi-instrumentalist. In this podcast she pulls out her Guzheng, a 21-stringed Zither that originates from China, to perfrom the song &quot;The Deep&quot; off of her newest album.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Vancouver based songwriter Erica Mah is a classically trained and extremely talented multi-instrumentalist. With two indepently released full-length albums, Erica&apos;s most recent release The Harbor Commission (2009) builds beautifully magical soundscapes that swim from delicate and articulate instrumentals to thundering folk-pop and back again. Erica not only played a beautiful show at the Cafe, but also informed us that there are other instruments in the world besides acoustic guitars and keyboards! In this podcast she pulls out her Guzheng, a 21-stringed Zither that originates from China, to perfrom the song &quot;The Deep&quot; off of her newest album.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110802%20Erica%20Mah.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="46641372" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110802%20Erica%20Mah.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 08:28:06 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:49</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Treelines</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Treelines has been a big favourite of the Cafe with their high energy, party-good-time rock antics and dashing good looks. Coming through the Cafe for round three, they decided to take a stripped down acoustic approach for a more intimate night with their fans. Frontman Matt made sure to apologize to die-hard fans for the lack of high leg kicks - but no one was disappointed! In this podcast they play the song "Canadian Airlines" to which CBC Radio 3 chimes in with “says more about [Canada] in three mere minutes than a three-hour Throne Speech could.” With rambling guitars, wilderness imagery you can lose yourself in, and hints of harmonica filling in the scenes it’s tough to describe the record as anything but Canadian, and for the band, anything but honest.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Treelines has been a big favourite of the Cafe with their high energy, party-good-time rock antics and dashing good looks. In this podcast they play a stripped down acoustic version of the song &quot;Canadian Airlines&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Treelines has been a big favourite of the Cafe with their high energy, party-good-time rock antics and dashing good looks. Coming through the Cafe for round three, they decided to take a stripped down acoustic approach for a more intimate night with their fans. Frontman Matt made sure to apologize to die-hard fans for the lack of high leg kicks - but no one was disappointed! In this podcast they play the song &quot;Canadian Airlines&quot; to which CBC Radio 3 chimes in with “says more about [Canada] in three mere minutes than a three-hour Throne Speech could.” With rambling guitars, wilderness imagery you can lose yourself in, and hints of harmonica filling in the scenes it’s tough to describe the record as anything but Canadian, and for the band, anything but honest.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110727%20Treelines.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="40696229" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110727%20Treelines.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 11:18:46 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:23</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Dominique Fraissard</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[It it said that there is timelessness to Dominique Fraissard's music. That his guitar and a potent pen sing with an earthy lilt and an urban edge. With four albums under his belt dating from 1998 to 2010, Dominique has been building quite the reputation among folk lovers as a fierce songwriter/musician. His music reflects his views on modern times, it deciphers between truth and lies - but at no point does it ever misrepresent its maker. In this podcast Dominique plays "Time On Tick" off of his most recent album Humble In The Moment - a song that he explains was mysteriously lived out by a friend only after she heard it.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>It it said that there is timelessness to Dominique Fraissard&apos;s music. In this podcast Dominique plays &quot;Time On Tick&quot; a song that he explains was mysteriously lived out by a friend only after she heard it.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>It it said that there is timelessness to Dominique Fraissard&apos;s music. That his guitar and a potent pen sing with an earthy lilt and an urban edge. With four albums under his belt dating from 1998 to 2010, Dominique has been building quite the reputation among folk lovers as a fierce songwriter/musician. His music reflects his views on modern times, it deciphers between truth and lies - but at no point does it ever misrepresent its maker. In this podcast Dominique plays &quot;Time On Tick&quot; off of his most recent album Humble In The Moment - a song that he explains was mysteriously lived out by a friend only after she heard it.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110719%20DominiqueFraissard.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="92383731" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110719%20DominiqueFraissard.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 15:05:26 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:07:47</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jen Lane</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Jen Lane is another artist that came through our cafe with the Western Canadian Music Awards and played a rocking set with her full band. Jen had played the cafe previously but with a more stripped down acoustic set, so it was a exciting to host her again and see a whole new side to the songs and personalities that we had enjoyed some much already!

In this podcast Jen plays the title track off her WCMA nominated album "For The Night". She reminisces on the inspiration for the song and dedicates it with love to her mother-in-law who was laid to rest back in Saskatchewan.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Jen Lane is another artist that came through our cafe with the Western Canadian Music Awards. Jen plays &quot;For The Night&quot; and reminisces on the inspiration for the song.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Jen Lane is another artist that came through our cafe with the Western Canadian Music Awards and played a rocking set with her full band. Jen had played the cafe previously but with a more stripped down acoustic set, so it was a exciting to host her again and see a whole new side to the songs and personalities that we had enjoyed some much already!

In this podcast Jen plays the title track off her WCMA nominated album &quot;For The Night&quot;. She reminisces on the inspiration for the song and dedicates it with love to her mother-in-law who was laid to rest back in Saskatchewan.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110712%20Jen%20Lane.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="56249174" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110712%20Jen%20Lane.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 15:46:02 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:34</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Del Barber</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Del Barber came through our Cafe as part of the festivities surrounding the Western Canadian Music Awards. On one of the busiest nights in the Cafe's history Del still managed to stand out and demand attention with his polished finger-style guitar, quick wit and intoxicating personality.

This podcast features the song "62 Richmond" off of Del Barbers 2010 Juno nominated album "Love Songs For The Last Twenty" which is up for two WCMA including Roots Solo Recording Of The Year and Independent Album Of The Year. Del retells the story of when he met the Muse for a song about the darkest bars and tallest tales!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Del Barber came through our Cafe as part of the festivities surrounding the Western Canadian Music Awards. This podcast features the song &quot;62 Richmond&quot; and Del retells the story of when he met the Muse for a song about the darkest bars and tallest tales!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Del Barber came through our Cafe as part of the festivities surrounding the Western Canadian Music Awards. On one of the busiest nights in the Cafe&apos;s history Del still managed to stand out and demand attention with his polished finger-style guitar, quick wit and intoxicating personality.

This podcast features the song &quot;62 Richmond&quot; off of Del Barbers 2010 Juno nominated album &quot;Love Songs For The Last Twenty&quot; which is up for two WCMA including Roots Solo Recording Of The Year and Independent Album Of The Year. Del retells the story of when he met the Muse for a song about the darkest bars and tallest tales!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110705%20Del%20Barber.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="76155608" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110705%20Del%20Barber.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 13:45:12 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:06:15</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Andy Shauf</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Andy Shauf has been a good friend of the Streaming Cafe since he first played in November of 2009. This podcast was created as a tribute to his song writing prowess, skilled-beyond-his-years guitar abilities and the fact that he is a genuinely great guy. We took one excellent song of his that was performed on three separate occasions and compiled this little montage for your viewing pleasure!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Andy Shauf has been a good friend of the Streaming Cafe since he first played in November of 2009. We took one excellent song of his that was performed on three separate occasions and compiled this little montage for your viewing pleasure!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Andy Shauf has been a good friend of the Streaming Cafe since he first played in November of 2009. This podcast was created as a tribute to his song writing prowess, skilled-beyond-his-years guitar abilities and the fact that he is a genuinely great guy. We took one excellent song of his that was performed on three separate occasions and compiled this little montage for your viewing pleasure!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110629%20Andy%20Shauf.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="30538286" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110629%20Andy%20Shauf.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 12:41:29 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:23</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Old Mare</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[With a sound described as "a story your grandfather told you once and you forgot until now" and "gambling, booze and cigarettes, long stares into horizons soaked in memories" you shouldn't be caught off-guard when Old Mare starts playing and conjures up visions of tough times and victories, regrets and celebrations or parties and inward reflection. A raw, untamed and soul ladened sound gives Old Mare frontman Chris Janzen a hard-hitting, head-turning effect on listeners. In this Podcast Chris retells a story that helped form what is now know as Old Mare.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>A raw, untamed and soul ladened sound gives Old Mare frontman Chris Janzen a hard-hitting, head-turning effect on listeners. In this Podcast Chris retells a story that helped form what is now know as Old Mare.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>With a sound described as &quot;a story your grandfather told you once and you forgot until now&quot; and &quot;gambling, booze and cigarettes, long stares into horizons soaked in memories&quot; you shouldn&apos;t be caught off-guard when Old Mare starts playing and conjures up visions of tough times and victories, regrets and celebrations or parties and inward reflection. A raw, untamed and soul ladened sound gives Old Mare frontman Chris Janzen a hard-hitting, head-turning effect on listeners. In this Podcast Chris retells a story that helped form what is now know as Old Mare.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110622%20Old%20Mare.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="72971776" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110622%20Old%20Mare.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 11:24:07 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:05:48</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>JJ Shiplett</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[JJ Shiplett jetted in from his home in Toronto to 'wow' his audience in our Cafe. He gave a performance that got listeners tapping their feet and hootin' and hollerin' for one song and inwardly reflecting on their emotions for the next. In this podcast JJ performs a more romantic number (while still maintaining a Whiskey theme) and encourages his audience to cuddle-up close with their significant other or get up for a two-step slowdance.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>JJ Shiplett jetted in Toronto to &apos;wow&apos; our Cafe. In this podcast JJ performs a more romantic number (while still maintaining a Whiskey theme) and encourages his audience to cuddle-up close with their significant other or get up for a two-step slowdance.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>JJ Shiplett jetted in from his home in Toronto to &apos;wow&apos; his audience in our Cafe. He gave a performance that got listeners tapping their feet and hootin&apos; and hollerin&apos; for one song and inwardly reflecting on their emotions for the next. In this podcast JJ performs a more romantic number (while still maintaining a Whiskey theme) and encourages his audience to cuddle-up close with their significant other or get up for a two-step slowdance.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110615%20JJ%20Shiplett.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="36043756" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110615%20JJ%20Shiplett.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 11:37:02 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:01</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Miss Emily Brown</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[When Miss Emily Brown came through our Cafe she performed songs that were written with experts from her Grandmothers diary kept during World War II. In this podcast Miss Emily Brown duets with an old music box in "To Make Love Stay", giving a dream-like and whimsical performance that enchants her audience.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In this podcast Miss Emily Brown duets with an old music box in &quot;To Make Love Stay&quot;, giving a dream-like and whimsical performance that enchants her audience.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>When Miss Emily Brown came through our Cafe she performed songs that were written with experts from her Grandmothers diary kept during World War II. In this podcast Miss Emily Brown duets with an old music box in &quot;To Make Love Stay&quot;, giving a dream-like and whimsical performance that enchants her audience.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110608%20Miss%20Emily%20Brown.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="40505193" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110608%20Miss%20Emily%20Brown.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 13:53:34 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:17</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mark Irving</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Mark Irving Tromsness opened for Mike Edel back in February 2011. He gave us a passionate show with his raw vocals and lyrical finesse that all together made it a very memorable night. Mark's song "Fool For You" was written as a contest entry and proved fruitful by resulting in not only a literal victory, but as a personal accomplishment of writing a truly beautiful love long.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Mark Irving Tromsness opened for Mike Edel back in February 2011. He gave us a passionate show with his raw vocals and lyrical finesse that all together made it a very memorable night.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Mark Irving Tromsness opened for Mike Edel back in February 2011. He gave us a passionate show with his raw vocals and lyrical finesse that all together made it a very memorable night. Mark&apos;s song &quot;Fool For You&quot; was written as a contest entry and proved fruitful by resulting in not only a literal victory, but as a personal accomplishment of writing a truly beautiful love long.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110531%20Mark%20Irving.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="51208127" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110531%20Mark%20Irving.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 14:01:08 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:22</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Mountains And The Trees</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Describing himself as Folk-Pop or Folk-N-Roll, Jon Janes is the brains behind The Mountains & The Trees. He has comfortably placed himself away from the structure of plain jane "Folk" and "Rock" as he plays with too many guitar pedals and effects to be considered purely just "Folk" and yields the Banjo too many times to be accepted as "Rock". In this podcast Jon strays from his usual style of sombre and reflective songs and leans to a melody that was written in a moment of physical darkness but emotional light-heartedness!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Describing himself as Folk-Pop or Folk-N-Roll, Jon Janes is the The Mountains &amp; The Trees. In this podcast Jon plays a song that strays from his more sombre and reflective songs to one that is light-hearted, even though it was written in darkness!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Describing himself as Folk-Pop or Folk-N-Roll, Jon Janes is the brains behind The Mountains &amp; The Trees. He has comfortably placed himself away from the structure of plain jane &quot;Folk&quot; and &quot;Rock&quot; as he plays with too many guitar pedals and effects to be considered purely just &quot;Folk&quot; and yields the Banjo too many times to be accepted as &quot;Rock&quot;. In this podcast Jon strays from his usual style of sombre and reflective songs and leans to a melody that was written in a moment of physical darkness but emotional light-heartedness!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110525TheMountainsAndTheTrees.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="29197776" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110525TheMountainsAndTheTrees.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 14:27:25 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:20</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Kid on the Pavement</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Chris Lloyd is Kid On The Pavement - a namesake derived from youthful games back in his homeland of the United Kingdom. His songs consist of warm and articulate finger-picked guitar and poetic lyrics that are laden with meaning and convey sometimes ominous stories and observations. In this podcast Chris gives a back story to one of his songs that was influenced by childhood folklore.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Chris Lloyd is Kid On The Pavement. In this podcast Chris gives a back story to one of his songs that was influenced by childhood folklore.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Chris Lloyd is Kid On The Pavement - a namesake derived from youthful games back in his homeland of the United Kingdom. His songs consist of warm and articulate finger-picked guitar and poetic lyrics that are laden with meaning and convey sometimes ominous stories and observations. In this podcast Chris gives a back story to one of his songs that was influenced by childhood folklore.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110518%20Kid%20on%20the%20Pavement.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="60811691" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110518%20Kid%20on%20the%20Pavement.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 18:05:28 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:56</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Geese</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[The Geese are a coalition of talented songwriters and instrumentalists intent on making the best of each other's songs, helping them meet their full potential. Formed while attending St. Stephen's University in New Brunswick and now currently residing in Vancouver, BC, The Geese are no stranger to coast to coast tours. Fulfilling a request sent to us by The Geese fans from St. Stephen's University, this podcast features the song "Omnibot" that explores the existence and purpose of (robotic) poets and their craft in a futuristic society, as well The Geese shed some light on how their namesake was a result of their multi-instrumental and collective approach to their music.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>The Geese are a coalition of songwriters and instrumentalists intent on making the best of each other&apos;s songs. In response to a request from The Geese fans in St. Stephen&apos;s University, this is the song &quot;Omnibot&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The Geese are a coalition of talented songwriters and instrumentalists intent on making the best of each other&apos;s songs, helping them meet their full potential. Formed while attending St. Stephen&apos;s University in New Brunswick and now currently residing in Vancouver, BC, The Geese are no stranger to coast to coast tours. Fulfilling a request sent to us by The Geese fans from St. Stephen&apos;s University, this podcast features the song &quot;Omnibot&quot; that explores the existence and purpose of (robotic) poets and their craft in a futuristic society, as well The Geese shed some light on how their namesake was a result of their multi-instrumental and collective approach to their music.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110510%20The%20Geese.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="59974667" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110510%20The%20Geese.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 11:54:05 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:50</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mike Edel</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Mike Edel brought his swagger and bounce to our cafe not too long ago. Playing songs off his debut album "The Last Of Our Mountains" Mike showcases his ability as a writer and entertainer.

In this podcast Mike talks about his childhood home and the musical inspiration that those memories bring him. Mike gives an energetic and inspirational performance despite breaking a string near the very end!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In this podcast Mike talks about his childhood home and the musical inspiration that those memories bring him. Mike gives an energetic and inspirational performance despite breaking a string near the very end!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Mike Edel brought his swagger and bounce to our cafe not too long ago. Playing songs off his debut album &quot;The Last Of Our Mountains&quot; Mike showcases his ability as a writer and entertainer.

In this podcast Mike talks about his childhood home and the musical inspiration that those memories bring him. Mike gives an energetic and inspirational performance despite breaking a string near the very end!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110427%20MikeEdel.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="56840489" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110427%20MikeEdel.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 13:41:59 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:32</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jonathan Inc.</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[With a genre described as beard core, dream folk and sleep pop Jonathan Inc. is a sound architect. Using a wide array of instruments and effects, much like a painter blends darks and lights, Jonathan Anderson creates a visual and mood that renders his audience defenceless to addicting rhythms and airy vocals. Jonathan talks about his childhood dreams resulting in fresh new songs.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Jonathan Inc. is a sound architect. Jonathan Anderson creates a visual and mood that renders his audience defenceless to addicting rhythms and airy vocals. Jonathan talks about his childhood dreams resulting in fresh new songs.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>With a genre described as beard core, dream folk and sleep pop Jonathan Inc. is a sound architect. Using a wide array of instruments and effects, much like a painter blends darks and lights, Jonathan Anderson creates a visual and mood that renders his audience defenceless to addicting rhythms and airy vocals. Jonathan talks about his childhood dreams resulting in fresh new songs.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110420%20Jonathan%20Inc..m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="47004055" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110420%20Jonathan%20Inc..m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 11:40:48 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:47</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Pat LePoidevin</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Pat LePoidevin returns to the cafe with an encore performance bringing with him a bag of fresh songs, melodic guitars and contagious loops off of his new album "Highway Houses". Pat gave a very memorable performance to a packed house that left the audience buzzing (one customer was quoted saying it was the best live performance she's ever seen!) As the follow up to his acclaimed album "Moonwolves" (2010), in "Highway Houses" Pat boasts his dynamic range of layered vocals, acoustic guitar and ukelele while the new songs show his growth as musician and writer. In this podcast Pat lays out the back story to a new song about the world's northern-most green-grassed golf course!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Pat LePoidevin returns to the cafe with an encore performance bringing with him a bag of fresh songs off of his new album &quot;Highway Houses&quot;. Pat lays out the back story to a new song about the world&apos;s northern-most green-grassed golf course!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Pat LePoidevin returns to the cafe with an encore performance bringing with him a bag of fresh songs, melodic guitars and contagious loops off of his new album &quot;Highway Houses&quot;. Pat gave a very memorable performance to a packed house that left the audience buzzing (one customer was quoted saying it was the best live performance she&apos;s ever seen!) As the follow up to his acclaimed album &quot;Moonwolves&quot; (2010), in &quot;Highway Houses&quot; Pat boasts his dynamic range of layered vocals, acoustic guitar and ukelele while the new songs show his growth as musician and writer. In this podcast Pat lays out the back story to a new song about the world&apos;s northern-most green-grassed golf course!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110406%20PatLePoidevin.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="64333646" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110406%20PatLePoidevin.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 11:55:44 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:05:07</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Colin Easthope</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[BC native, Colin Easthope has mastered a sound of his own. With a blend of the past with the present, Colin's sound is infused with a unique perspective on the classic blues and folk scenes. In this podcast Colin plays a new tune that was written with the aid of Text Messaging and talks about the namesake of his album, "Of Myself and Others."]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Colin plays a new tune that was written with the aid of Text Messaging and talks about the namesake of his album, &quot;Of Myself and Others.&quot;</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>BC native, Colin Easthope has mastered a sound of his own. With a blend of the past with the present, Colin&apos;s sound is infused with a unique perspective on the classic blues and folk scenes. In this podcast Colin plays a new tune that was written with the aid of Text Messaging and talks about the namesake of his album, &quot;Of Myself and Others.&quot;</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110330%20ColinEasthope.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="48306081" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110330%20ColinEasthope.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 12:22:07 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:04</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Joshua Hyslop</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Joshua Hyslop talks about his adventures backpacking in India and how it's allowed him to write songs that relay strong messages and meaningful ideas rather than simply catchy verses and rhyming hooks!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Joshua Hyslop talks about his adventures backpacking in India and how it&apos;s allowed him to write songs that relay strong messages and meaningful ideas rather than simply catchy verses and rhyming hooks!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Joshua Hyslop talks about his adventures backpacking in India and how it&apos;s allowed him to write songs that relay strong messages and meaningful ideas rather than simply catchy verses and rhyming hooks!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110317%20JoshuaHyslop.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="42751796" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110317%20JoshuaHyslop.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 15:43:40 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:34</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Carey Ott</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Carey Ott jetted out from his home in Nashville for a special show at our Cafe. His performance demonstrated his finely tuned song-craft that has earned him several plays on popular TV shows. Carey's lyrics have the ability to convey a message that adapts and speaks to each listener in a unique way - almost like every song is written to each individual member in his audience. This podcact Carey gives some back story to one of his popular songs "Save My Life".]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Carey Ott jetted out from his home in Nashville just to play our Cafe. His performance demonstrated his finely tuned song-craft that has earned him plays on popular TV shows. In this podcact Carey give a back story to his popular song &quot;Save My Life&quot;.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Carey Ott jetted out from his home in Nashville for a special show at our Cafe. His performance demonstrated his finely tuned song-craft that has earned him several plays on popular TV shows. Carey&apos;s lyrics have the ability to convey a message that adapts and speaks to each listener in a unique way - almost like every song is written to each individual member in his audience. This podcact Carey gives some back story to one of his popular songs &quot;Save My Life&quot;.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110308%20Carey%20Ott%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="41882385" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110308%20Carey%20Ott%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 09:37:08 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:27</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ben Sigston</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Four months after playing a short set during the Peak Performance Project and Breakout West Music Festival, Ben Sigston returns to the Cafe to headline his own show. While giving a fantastic performance the ex-Canadian National Team cyclist recalls his initial trade from bike to mic and what motivated him to start writing his own music.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Four months after playing at the Peak Performance Project and Breakout West Music Festival, Ben Sigston returns to the Cafe to headline. Ex-Canadian National Team cyclist recalls his trade from bike to mic and what motivated him to write his own music.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Four months after playing a short set during the Peak Performance Project and Breakout West Music Festival, Ben Sigston returns to the Cafe to headline his own show. While giving a fantastic performance the ex-Canadian National Team cyclist recalls his initial trade from bike to mic and what motivated him to start writing his own music.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110301%20Ben%20Sigston%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="54358611" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110301%20Ben%20Sigston%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 15:08:41 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:19</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Brandon Wolfe Scott</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[British Columbia's Brandon Wolfe Scott's incredible and sparse, but lavishly folk compositions create a landscape in the mind - one whose structures are emotional and alive. Brandon typically tours as part of Canadian band YUKON BLONDE but his solo endeavours have won him the CBC Radio songwriting contest prize and opening spots for Matthew Barber, Ken Hamm and Dan Mangan. In this week's podcast Brandon talks about playing in a rock group with your friends versus having a solo project.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Brandon typically tours as part of Canadian band YUKON BLONDE but his solo endeavours have won him the CBC Radio songwriting contest prize. In this podcast Brandon talks about playing in a rock group with your friends versus having a solo project.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>British Columbia&apos;s Brandon Wolfe Scott&apos;s incredible and sparse, but lavishly folk compositions create a landscape in the mind - one whose structures are emotional and alive. Brandon typically tours as part of Canadian band YUKON BLONDE but his solo endeavours have won him the CBC Radio songwriting contest prize and opening spots for Matthew Barber, Ken Hamm and Dan Mangan. In this week&apos;s podcast Brandon talks about playing in a rock group with your friends versus having a solo project.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110224%20Brandon%20Wolfe%20Scott.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="44151274" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110224%20Brandon%20Wolfe%20Scott.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 11:34:21 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:29</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Loren</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Hailing from Northern New South Wales, Australia, popular folk roots troubadour Loren set out on his first Canadian tour, stopping by the Streaming Cafe. This was almost two years ago, but Loren's performance was so memorable that we decided to give it a bit of attention in this week's podcast. Loren plays us a very unique song, on quite an unconventional instrument, and shares a hilarious back-story of the whole experience!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Hailing from Northern New South Wales, Australia, popular folk roots troubadour Loren set out on his first Canadian tour. Loren plays us a very unique song, on quite an unconventional instrument, and shares a hilarious back-story of the whole experience!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Hailing from Northern New South Wales, Australia, popular folk roots troubadour Loren set out on his first Canadian tour, stopping by the Streaming Cafe. This was almost two years ago, but Loren&apos;s performance was so memorable that we decided to give it a bit of attention in this week&apos;s podcast. Loren plays us a very unique song, on quite an unconventional instrument, and shares a hilarious back-story of the whole experience!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110216%20Loren%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="46716633" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/110216%20Loren%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 09:52:57 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:49</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jon Rae Fletcher</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Jon Rae Fletcher has been known to move around like a free flowing river, to wash you away in a flurry of artfully crafted lyrics that light up his performances with raw passion...It only makes sense that he is known to many as Jon Rae and The River. In this podcast Jon shares a comedic moment about singing in his crib as well as the different emotions an artist will go through playing a different venue.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Jon Rae Fletcher has been known to move like a river, wash you away in a flurry of artfully crafted lyrics that light up his performance with passion. Jon shares a funny moment and talks about emotions an artist will experience playing different venue.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Jon Rae Fletcher has been known to move around like a free flowing river, to wash you away in a flurry of artfully crafted lyrics that light up his performances with raw passion...It only makes sense that he is known to many as Jon Rae and The River. In this podcast Jon shares a comedic moment about singing in his crib as well as the different emotions an artist will go through playing a different venue.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0209%20Jon%20Rae%20Fletcher.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="47679719" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0209%20Jon%20Rae%20Fletcher.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 14:10:40 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:54</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Daniel Huscroft</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Daniel Huscroft is a prime example of person being not only true to their music, but writing music that is true to their personalities. Huscroft's list of accomplishments include producer,  award-winning songwriter, guitarist in rock bands, accompaniment to singer-songwriters and doing session work for dozens of independent projects. His debut album "Here Is Just For Now" maintains a raw, honest sense of musical integrity that reflects Daniel's own musical journey. In this podcast Daniel talks about his writing influences and plays a track of his new album "From The Hills."]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Daniel Huscroft is a prime example of person being not only true to their music, but writing music that is true to their personalities. In this podcast Daniel talks about his writing influences and plays a track of his new album &quot;From The Hills.&quot;</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Daniel Huscroft is a prime example of person being not only true to their music, but writing music that is true to their personalities. Huscroft&apos;s list of accomplishments include producer,  award-winning songwriter, guitarist in rock bands, accompaniment to singer-songwriters and doing session work for dozens of independent projects. His debut album &quot;Here Is Just For Now&quot; maintains a raw, honest sense of musical integrity that reflects Daniel&apos;s own musical journey. In this podcast Daniel talks about his writing influences and plays a track of his new album &quot;From The Hills.&quot;</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0201%20Daniel%20Huscroft.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="51075588" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0201%20Daniel%20Huscroft.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 09:17:37 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:16</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jen Lane</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Jen's most recent album "For The Night" was recorded and produced by Steven Drake in Vancouver. A classic mix of indie folk and roots, showcases the storytelling and beautiful voice of this young singer-songwriter from Saskatoon. During her visit to the Cafe Jen and her husband (who plays in a group called "Smoke Killers") sit down and talk about backing each other's musical endeavours and also tell the story of how Steve Drake first took interest in producing Jen's next album.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Jen&apos;s album &quot;For The Night&quot; is described as a classic mix of indie folk and roots. During her visit Jen and her husband (who is also a musician) talk about backing each other&apos;s music and tell how Steve Drake first decided to produce Jen&apos;s next album.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Jen&apos;s most recent album &quot;For The Night&quot; was recorded and produced by Steven Drake in Vancouver. A classic mix of indie folk and roots, showcases the storytelling and beautiful voice of this young singer-songwriter from Saskatoon. During her visit to the Cafe Jen and her husband (who plays in a group called &quot;Smoke Killers&quot;) sit down and talk about backing each other&apos;s musical endeavours and also tell the story of how Steve Drake first took interest in producing Jen&apos;s next album.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0126%20jenlane%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="52170571" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0126%20jenlane%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 13:40:04 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:03</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hilary Grist</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Cabaret torch singer, thoughtful folk songwriter and accomplished pianist; Hilary Grist pens playful pop-folk music that is infectious and personal. Sung with a voice that is captivating and strong, but soft around the edges, her songs have been called 'old fashioned gems'. Hilary wears it all on her sleeve with unselfconscious warmth. She talks to us about her musical origins and how she grew into the artist she is today.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Cabaret torch singer, thoughtful folk songwriter and accomplished pianist; Hilary Grist pens playful pop-folk music that is infectious and personal. She talks to us about her musical origins and how she grew into the artist she is today.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Cabaret torch singer, thoughtful folk songwriter and accomplished pianist; Hilary Grist pens playful pop-folk music that is infectious and personal. Sung with a voice that is captivating and strong, but soft around the edges, her songs have been called &apos;old fashioned gems&apos;. Hilary wears it all on her sleeve with unselfconscious warmth. She talks to us about her musical origins and how she grew into the artist she is today.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0118%20HilaryGrist.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="52813935" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0118%20HilaryGrist.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 14:33:24 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:20</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sheree Plett</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Sheree Plett's new album The Road to my Family is an album in the truest sense. Rather than simply a collection of songs, this record likes to be played in full. Like the arc of a story, one tune informs the next giving us a chance to identify with Sheree’s journey and sense of real life. Sheree talks about a new stage of her life bringing her 5 month old son on tours with the band, as well as shares some advice to aspiring artists and songwriters.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Sheree Plett&apos;s new album &quot;The Road to my Family&quot; gives us a chance to identify with her journey and sense of real life. She talks about a new stage of life bringing her 5 month old on tour with the band and shares some advice to aspiring songwriters.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Sheree Plett&apos;s new album The Road to my Family is an album in the truest sense. Rather than simply a collection of songs, this record likes to be played in full. Like the arc of a story, one tune informs the next giving us a chance to identify with Sheree’s journey and sense of real life. Sheree talks about a new stage of her life bringing her 5 month old son on tours with the band, as well as shares some advice to aspiring artists and songwriters.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0111%20Sheree%20Plett.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="36594697" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0111%20Sheree%20Plett.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 15:02:25 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:04</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>MJ Cyr</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Toronto has been fertile ground for MJ, having completed two EPs ('The Bottom Line' & 'Ladders'), music videos, and more than a few live shows around the city. MJ has toured extensively in support of 'The Bottom Line', across Canada, The United States, and New Zealand. Its messages, and themes proved universal, and captured the attention of college radio; and it wasn't long before MJ quickly gained a new audience through word of mouth on her stirring live shows. The follow up to the ‘The Bottom Line’ is her new EP ‘Ladders’; another exhibition of MJ’s soaring, yet sensitive vocals - and nuanced writing. Most of the material was written immediately before, and after shows, or while traveling to new places to perform, something less intentional than it was a sign of where she had found new inspiration. MJ reveals the early origins of her terrific harmonies as well as a rare opportunity for her to sing with music innovator Imogen Heap.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Toronto has been fertile ground for MJ, having completed two EPs, music videos, and more than a few live shows around the city. MJ reveals the early origins of her harmonies as well as a rare opportunity for her to sing with music innovator Imogen Heap.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Toronto has been fertile ground for MJ, having completed two EPs (&apos;The Bottom Line&apos; &amp; &apos;Ladders&apos;), music videos, and more than a few live shows around the city. MJ has toured extensively in support of &apos;The Bottom Line&apos;, across Canada, The United States, and New Zealand. Its messages, and themes proved universal, and captured the attention of college radio; and it wasn&apos;t long before MJ quickly gained a new audience through word of mouth on her stirring live shows. The follow up to the ‘The Bottom Line’ is her new EP ‘Ladders’; another exhibition of MJ’s soaring, yet sensitive vocals - and nuanced writing. Most of the material was written immediately before, and after shows, or while traveling to new places to perform, something less intentional than it was a sign of where she had found new inspiration. MJ reveals the early origins of her terrific harmonies as well as a rare opportunity for her to sing with music innovator Imogen Heap.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0104%20MJ%20Cyr.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="53198178" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0104%20MJ%20Cyr.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 15:20:10 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:20</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Kevin Kane</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Kevin Kane’s songs, voice, and guitar playing are very familiar to any Canadian to have turned on a radio or TV between the mid-80s and early 90s, for at the time his band The Grapes of Wrath were one of the country’s biggest, with hit singles, videos, albums and sold out concerts from coast to coast. In this Podcast Kevin tell the tale behind the title of his song "Last To Know" as well as an old fashioned ghost story.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Kevin Kane’s songs, voice, and guitar playing are very familiar to any Canadian thanks to his band The Grapes of Wrath. In this podcast Kevin tells the tale behind the title of his song &quot;Last To Know&quot; as well as an old fashioned ghost story.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Kevin Kane’s songs, voice, and guitar playing are very familiar to any Canadian to have turned on a radio or TV between the mid-80s and early 90s, for at the time his band The Grapes of Wrath were one of the country’s biggest, with hit singles, videos, albums and sold out concerts from coast to coast. In this Podcast Kevin tell the tale behind the title of his song &quot;Last To Know&quot; as well as an old fashioned ghost story.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1214%20Kevin%20Kane%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="52782229" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1214%20Kevin%20Kane%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 13:18:17 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:17</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sister Speak</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Whether performing as a duo, or backed by their astounding rhythm section, Sister Speak (Samatha Cathart & Sherri-Anne) takes the talents of each musician to another level, combining mesmerizing vocals with elements of "Acoustic-Rock, Blues & World." The two artists met in the Chicago music scene shortly after completing their own debut albums. They have since toured the continent, playing at some of Vancouver's and Chicago's top music clubs and all over California. Canada's global TV interviewed the duo last summer and they were featured at the NAMM 2010 in January. Extensive touring throughout North America and a new album in is in the works for Sister Speak! The ladies of Sister Speak talk about some of their motives behind joining musical forces and describe some of the success they've experienced.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>The ladies of Sister Speak, Samantha Cathart and Sherri-Anne talk about some of their motives behind joining musical forces and describe some of the success they&apos;ve experienced.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Whether performing as a duo, or backed by their astounding rhythm section, Sister Speak (Samatha Cathart &amp; Sherri-Anne) takes the talents of each musician to another level, combining mesmerizing vocals with elements of &quot;Acoustic-Rock, Blues &amp; World.&quot; The two artists met in the Chicago music scene shortly after completing their own debut albums. They have since toured the continent, playing at some of Vancouver&apos;s and Chicago&apos;s top music clubs and all over California. Canada&apos;s global TV interviewed the duo last summer and they were featured at the NAMM 2010 in January. Extensive touring throughout North America and a new album in is in the works for Sister Speak! The ladies of Sister Speak talk about some of their motives behind joining musical forces and describe some of the success they&apos;ve experienced.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1207%20Sisterspeak%20Podcast%202.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="48737024" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1207%20Sisterspeak%20Podcast%202.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 09:47:55 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:00</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jordan Klassen</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Jordan Klassen's marriage of delicate acoustic guitar, melodic whistling, rhythmic toy drums, soulful fiddle and singing wine glasses have been creating a buzz in the independent music scene since his debut solo album was released in May of 2009. Jordan takes a moment to explain his album's name, St. Brigid.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Jordan Klassen&apos;s marriage of delicate acoustic guitar, melodic whistling, rhythmic toy drums, soulful fiddle and singing wine glasses have been creating a buzz in the independent music scene. Jordan takes a moment to explain his album&apos;s name, St. Brigid.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Jordan Klassen&apos;s marriage of delicate acoustic guitar, melodic whistling, rhythmic toy drums, soulful fiddle and singing wine glasses have been creating a buzz in the independent music scene since his debut solo album was released in May of 2009. Jordan takes a moment to explain his album&apos;s name, St. Brigid.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1130%20Jordan%20Klassen.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="54647537" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1130%20Jordan%20Klassen.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 09:57:40 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:23</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>My Lovely Son</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Hailing from Victoria, BC is a hidden gem in the singer/songwriter scene by the name of Satnam Minhas, but know to most as My Lovely Son. A clandestine musician by nature, Minhas has developed a style of songwriting that attempts to wrench at the listeners heartstrings while painting a melodic picture with his warm, reposeful voice.
Satnam talks about the family based inspiration behind his song "My Youth" as well as how he came across the unique pseudonym used for his recordings.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Hailing from Victoria, BC is a hidden gem in the singer/songwriter scene by the name of Satnam Minhas. Satnam talks about the family based inspiration behind his song &quot;My Youth&quot; as well as how he came across the unique pseudonym used for his recordings.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Hailing from Victoria, BC is a hidden gem in the singer/songwriter scene by the name of Satnam Minhas, but know to most as My Lovely Son. A clandestine musician by nature, Minhas has developed a style of songwriting that attempts to wrench at the listeners heartstrings while painting a melodic picture with his warm, reposeful voice.
Satnam talks about the family based inspiration behind his song &quot;My Youth&quot; as well as how he came across the unique pseudonym used for his recordings.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1123%20My%20Lovely%20Son.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="45316514" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1123%20My%20Lovely%20Son.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 13:07:29 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:43</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Andrew Allen</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Andrew Allen is a singer/songwriter from British Columbia. Hitting the road with a full tank of finely tuned pop songs, an incredibly entertaining live show and what seems like limitless energy, Andrew has proved time and time again that his songwriting style - sandwiched uniquely between the styles of Jason Mraz, John Mayer and Maroon 5 - mixed with his quirky personality, are the right ingredients for success. Playing an early rendition of his new hit sing "Loving You Tonight" Andrew talks about the inspiration behind one of his songs as well as how he mentors newly emerging and upcoming musicians on writing music as an avenue of personal expression.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Playing an early rendition of his new hit sing &quot;Loving You Tonight&quot; Andrew talks about the inspiration behind one of his songs as well as how he mentors newly emerging and upcoming musicians on writing music as an avenue of personal expression.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Andrew Allen is a singer/songwriter from British Columbia. Hitting the road with a full tank of finely tuned pop songs, an incredibly entertaining live show and what seems like limitless energy, Andrew has proved time and time again that his songwriting style - sandwiched uniquely between the styles of Jason Mraz, John Mayer and Maroon 5 - mixed with his quirky personality, are the right ingredients for success. Playing an early rendition of his new hit sing &quot;Loving You Tonight&quot; Andrew talks about the inspiration behind one of his songs as well as how he mentors newly emerging and upcoming musicians on writing music as an avenue of personal expression.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1116%20Andrew%20Allen.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="41644882" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1116%20Andrew%20Allen.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 13:49:18 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:21</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Olympic Symphonium</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[The Olympic Symphonium is a unique collaboration between three accomplished Maritime musicians. With the hopes of forming a quiet escape from their accustomed high-energy rock/pop projects, the idea of this group was to focus more on the subtle, gentler side of music. They are winners of the Group Recording Award and Anglophone Album Award in the 2010 Music New Brunswick Awards. They stopped by our cafe along with Catherine Maclellan and played "Settle Down" from their future album "The City Won't Have Time To Fight" (due out January 25, 2011). During our interview they commented on their instrument switching between songs and on their strong and beautiful use of harmonies in their songs.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>The Olympic Symphonium is a unique collaboration between three accomplished Maritime musicians. During our interview they commented on their instrument switching between songs and on their strong and beautiful use of harmonies in their songs.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The Olympic Symphonium is a unique collaboration between three accomplished Maritime musicians. With the hopes of forming a quiet escape from their accustomed high-energy rock/pop projects, the idea of this group was to focus more on the subtle, gentler side of music. They are winners of the Group Recording Award and Anglophone Album Award in the 2010 Music New Brunswick Awards. They stopped by our cafe along with Catherine Maclellan and played &quot;Settle Down&quot; from their future album &quot;The City Won&apos;t Have Time To Fight&quot; (due out January 25, 2011). During our interview they commented on their instrument switching between songs and on their strong and beautiful use of harmonies in their songs.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1109%20Olympic%20Symphonium%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="48366646" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1109%20Olympic%20Symphonium%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 10:41:31 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:54</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Christina Maria</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[After extensive European tours, Christina Maria gave us a tight knit and highly refined performance. In this week's podcast Christina talks about recording her newest album with the help of several producers, as well as letting us in on her secret of guitar accessorizing. She plays "Carolina" which is the lead track from the freshly released "Straight Lines"]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>After her European tours, Christina Maria gave us a tight knit and highly refined performance. In this week&apos;s podcast Christina talks about recording her newest album, as well as letting us in on her secret of guitar accessorizing.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>After extensive European tours, Christina Maria gave us a tight knit and highly refined performance. In this week&apos;s podcast Christina talks about recording her newest album with the help of several producers, as well as letting us in on her secret of guitar accessorizing. She plays &quot;Carolina&quot; which is the lead track from the freshly released &quot;Straight Lines&quot;</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1102%20Christina%20Maria%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="36065305" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1102%20Christina%20Maria%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 13:32:06 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:51</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Gabrielle Papillon</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Gabrielle is a singer/songwriter based out of Montreal, Quebec.
Influenced by guitar slinging troubadours such as Ani Difranco, Joni Mitchell, Bob Dylan, Paul Simon, and Van Morrison, her music is often about a feeling. Her muse is the amalgamation of people in her life, or an imaginary scenario. Above all she loves the journey of a song. 
Not only is Gabrielle a talented artist, she also holds a Master's Degree in History and she talks about how her education aids her music in this podcast.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Gabrielle is a singer/songwriter based out of Montreal, Quebec. Not only is Gabrielle a talented artist, she also holds a Master&apos;s Degree in History and she talks about how her education aids her music in this podcast.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Gabrielle is a singer/songwriter based out of Montreal, Quebec.
Influenced by guitar slinging troubadours such as Ani Difranco, Joni Mitchell, Bob Dylan, Paul Simon, and Van Morrison, her music is often about a feeling. Her muse is the amalgamation of people in her life, or an imaginary scenario. Above all she loves the journey of a song. 
Not only is Gabrielle a talented artist, she also holds a Master&apos;s Degree in History and she talks about how her education aids her music in this podcast.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1026%20Gabrielle%20Papillon%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="46528865" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1026%20Gabrielle%20Papillon%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 13:37:27 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:52</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Prairie Dance Club</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Prairie Dance Club is a blend of alternative rock Canadiana with heavy sonic undertones. Since their formation in the fall of 2007 they have landed gigs with established and up and coming Canadian artists such as Matt Mays and El Torpedo, Arkells, Tom Wilson, Armchair Cynics and Flash Lightnin. They have had a song featured on the PBS series "Road Trip Nation" and their first full length album has been played on radio in Canada, US and Europe. This is a track off their newest album "Won't Let You Down" released October 2010. In this podcast Jason Davies talks about the groups search for a name and how music exceeds the sum of it's parts.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Prairie Dance Club is a blend of alt-rock Canadiana and heavy sonic undertones. This podcast features a track off of their newest album &quot;Won&apos;t Let You Down&quot; released October 2010.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Prairie Dance Club is a blend of alternative rock Canadiana with heavy sonic undertones. Since their formation in the fall of 2007 they have landed gigs with established and up and coming Canadian artists such as Matt Mays and El Torpedo, Arkells, Tom Wilson, Armchair Cynics and Flash Lightnin. They have had a song featured on the PBS series &quot;Road Trip Nation&quot; and their first full length album has been played on radio in Canada, US and Europe. This is a track off their newest album &quot;Won&apos;t Let You Down&quot; released October 2010. In this podcast Jason Davies talks about the groups search for a name and how music exceeds the sum of it&apos;s parts.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1019%20Prairie%20Dance%20Club%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="62551165" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1019%20Prairie%20Dance%20Club%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2010 14:18:15 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:54</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sarah Brendel</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Sarah moves between the worlds of Folk, Indie, Rock, and Pop but cannot be pigeon-holed by any means. Whether it is Sarah by herself just with her guitar, or with a full band, whether quiet and contemplative, or loud and cranking - her music never fails to move the heart. Sarah Brendel is one of the first German songwriters who got a record deal in the USA. With her song "Fire" she reached number 86 in the U.S. Billboard Airplay charts. For several months she lived in Nashville, TN and played concerts all over the United States.
In the last two years Sarah played more than 250 shows in Germany, the USA and also on the Faroe Islands, in Scandinavia, Slovakia and Switzerland. Sarah travelled almost 4000 miles to grace our cafe with her energetic and eclectic folk/rock performance and she was backed up by Kelowna's own Graham Ord on guitar and mandolin. During our sit down she admits to favouring english over german when it comes to song writing and she retells a fairy tale moment when she recorded two songs with her long time music hero, Larry Norman.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>German born-and-bred Sarah Brendel travelled almost 4000 miles to grace our cafe with her energetic and eclectic folk/rock performance. During our sit down she admits to favouring english over german in song writing and retells a fairy tale moment.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Sarah moves between the worlds of Folk, Indie, Rock, and Pop but cannot be pigeon-holed by any means. Whether it is Sarah by herself just with her guitar, or with a full band, whether quiet and contemplative, or loud and cranking - her music never fails to move the heart. Sarah Brendel is one of the first German songwriters who got a record deal in the USA. With her song &quot;Fire&quot; she reached number 86 in the U.S. Billboard Airplay charts. For several months she lived in Nashville, TN and played concerts all over the United States.
In the last two years Sarah played more than 250 shows in Germany, the USA and also on the Faroe Islands, in Scandinavia, Slovakia and Switzerland. Sarah travelled almost 4000 miles to grace our cafe with her energetic and eclectic folk/rock performance and she was backed up by Kelowna&apos;s own Graham Ord on guitar and mandolin. During our sit down she admits to favouring english over german when it comes to song writing and she retells a fairy tale moment when she recorded two songs with her long time music hero, Larry Norman.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1012%20Sarah%20Brendel%20Podcast%2002-H.264%20for%20iPod%20video%20and%20iPhone%20640x480.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="61194236" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1012%20Sarah%20Brendel%20Podcast%2002-H.264%20for%20iPod%20video%20and%20iPhone%20640x480.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 14:19:59 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:50</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jon Bryant</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Jon released his debut album independently on October 28, 2009, the poignant 11 song record couldn’t have come any sooner for Bryant or his fans. After a fairytale journey of getting his music recorded in Calgary earlier this year, the finished product can only be described as a sigh of relief. Jon recalls his first experiences in music and talks about how pairing two typically solo singer song writers allows them observe their music in a new context.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In June 2010, Jon hopped on a train for a double feature tour with Montreal artist Gabrielle Papillon. He talks about how pairing two typically solo singer song writers allows them observe their music in a new context.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Jon released his debut album independently on October 28, 2009, the poignant 11 song record couldn’t have come any sooner for Bryant or his fans. After a fairytale journey of getting his music recorded in Calgary earlier this year, the finished product can only be described as a sigh of relief. Jon recalls his first experiences in music and talks about how pairing two typically solo singer song writers allows them observe their music in a new context.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1007%20Jon%20Bryant%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="55590480" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/1007%20Jon%20Bryant%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 11:42:28 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:31</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Catherine MacLellan</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Fresh on the heels of winning a number of Industry Awards, PEI singer/songwriter Catherine MacLellan came to Streaming Cafe on the last night of her Western Canadian tour with Olympic Symphonium. 
Canadian Folk Music Best Solo Performer of the Year, CBC Radio SongQuest winner for PEI, East Coast Music Award for Folk Recording of the Year, another ECMA for Female Performer of the Year... the list of her industry triumphs goes on and on.
MacLellan did a number of songs with 'the band' (Olympic Symphonium), but she also treated us to a few numbers on her own. Both flavours of her music were very well received; this is a talented lady who is completely at home on stage.
In this podcast, MacLellan talks about her three albums, all released on True North Records, and the different feel or focus each of them has.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Fresh on the heels of winning a number of Industry Awards, PEI singer/songwriter Catherine MacLellan came to Streaming Cafe on the last night of her Western Canadian tour with Olympic Symphonium. Canadian Folk Music Best Solo Performer indeed!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Fresh on the heels of winning a number of Industry Awards, PEI singer/songwriter Catherine MacLellan came to Streaming Cafe on the last night of her Western Canadian tour with Olympic Symphonium. 
Canadian Folk Music Best Solo Performer of the Year, CBC Radio SongQuest winner for PEI, East Coast Music Award for Folk Recording of the Year, another ECMA for Female Performer of the Year... the list of her industry triumphs goes on and on.
MacLellan did a number of songs with &apos;the band&apos; (Olympic Symphonium), but she also treated us to a few numbers on her own. Both flavours of her music were very well received; this is a talented lady who is completely at home on stage.
In this podcast, MacLellan talks about her three albums, all released on True North Records, and the different feel or focus each of them has.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0928%20Catherine%20MacLelland%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="52535123" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0928%20Catherine%20MacLelland%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 12:07:26 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:05</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Maclean</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[A comfortable group of five guys (recently adding a sixth), Maclean brought their comfortable blend of indie pop to Streaming Cafe in April of 2010. This year marks five years they've been together, and their amiability with one another was evident during both the music and the interview portions of the show.

In this vodcast episode, band members Denver and Andrew talk about their songwriting and how they went about selecting songs for their second album, "Talker".]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>A comfortable group of five guys (recently adding a sixth), Maclean brought their comfortable blend of indie pop to Streaming Cafe in April. This year marks five years they&apos;ve been together, and their amiability with one another onstage was evident.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>A comfortable group of five guys (recently adding a sixth), Maclean brought their comfortable blend of indie pop to Streaming Cafe in April of 2010. This year marks five years they&apos;ve been together, and their amiability with one another was evident during both the music and the interview portions of the show.

In this vodcast episode, band members Denver and Andrew talk about their songwriting and how they went about selecting songs for their second album, &quot;Talker&quot;.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0921%20Maclean%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="48547474" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0921%20Maclean%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 16:03:24 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:48</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Share</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Share is a five piece rock band. Share is a three member acoustic act. Share is a solo project by Andrew Sisk. Share is a duet project with Andrew Sisk and Miranda Durka. Share is, of course, all of those; in this episode it's Share the Duet.

None of us at Streaming Cafe quite knew what to expect when Share was slotted to perform. The videos we'd seen online were well-produced and very funny... and some had nothing to do with music. Whatever format Share was to take upon their arrival, we were pretty sure we'd be in for a treat. And we were.

Andrew and Miranda brought their combination of melodic acoustic-based pop and engaging humour to Streaming Cafe in March of 2010. In this podcast, Andrew addresses – with a touch of humour – some of what people might expect in coming to a Share concert, and the different reactions he gets to his songs.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Share is a five piece rock band. Share is a three member acoustic act. Share is a solo project by Andrew Sisk. Share is a duet project with Andrew Sisk and Miranda Durka. Share is, of course, all of those; in this episode it&apos;s Share the Duet.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Share is a five piece rock band. Share is a three member acoustic act. Share is a solo project by Andrew Sisk. Share is a duet project with Andrew Sisk and Miranda Durka. Share is, of course, all of those; in this episode it&apos;s Share the Duet.

None of us at Streaming Cafe quite knew what to expect when Share was slotted to perform. The videos we&apos;d seen online were well-produced and very funny... and some had nothing to do with music. Whatever format Share was to take upon their arrival, we were pretty sure we&apos;d be in for a treat. And we were.

Andrew and Miranda brought their combination of melodic acoustic-based pop and engaging humour to Streaming Cafe in March of 2010. In this podcast, Andrew addresses – with a touch of humour – some of what people might expect in coming to a Share concert, and the different reactions he gets to his songs.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0914%20Share%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="43422926" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0914%20Share%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 13:54:11 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:39</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Pat Lepoidevin</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Distinctive voice, ubiquitous and skillful use of a looper pedal, many instruments at hand; Pat LePoidevin makes an undeniable impression when he plays. 

LePoidevin was a guest at the Streaming Cafe in May of 2010, and he made instant fans among Cafe staff and the public alike. CBC Radio seems to be very supportive of his career, and it's easy to see why: the live SC show was extremely entertaining to watch in person. The Previous Show archive of LePoidevin features several of his songs that he played with his looper pedal, and it's intriguing to watch how he builds the layers of rythmn and sound that make up his music.

In this podcast episode, Streaming Cafe host Charity asks LePoidevin about his origins in music. You'll never guess what his first instrument was...]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Distinctive voice, ubiquitous and skillful use of a looper pedal, many instruments at hand; Pat LePoidevin makes an undeniable impression when he plays. When he played the SC in May of 2010 he added instantly to his fan base...</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Distinctive voice, ubiquitous and skillful use of a looper pedal, many instruments at hand; Pat LePoidevin makes an undeniable impression when he plays. 

LePoidevin was a guest at the Streaming Cafe in May of 2010, and he made instant fans among Cafe staff and the public alike. CBC Radio seems to be very supportive of his career, and it&apos;s easy to see why: the live SC show was extremely entertaining to watch in person. The Previous Show archive of LePoidevin features several of his songs that he played with his looper pedal, and it&apos;s intriguing to watch how he builds the layers of rythmn and sound that make up his music.

In this podcast episode, Streaming Cafe host Charity asks LePoidevin about his origins in music. You&apos;ll never guess what his first instrument was...</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0907%20Pat%20Lepoidevin%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="46260921" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0907%20Pat%20Lepoidevin%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 15:11:10 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:47</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Zachary Lucky</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[If there was ever such a thing as a contemporary travelling troubadour, Zachary Lucky would fit the bill. He sets up tours with other artists, serving as the booking agent and, often, the driver for the actual road trip. He usually comes through town with different artists, and it's rare to have him appear on his own. This visit, in June of 2010, was one of the rare solo appearances.
In this video podcast episode, Zachary sings the song "Blanket Tent", and shares about his love of touring with other artists. ]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>If there was ever such a thing as a contemporary travelling troubadour, Zachary Lucky would fit the bill. He sets up tours with other artists, serving as the booking agent and, often, the driver for the actual road trip. Connect with him in this podcast.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>If there was ever such a thing as a contemporary travelling troubadour, Zachary Lucky would fit the bill. He sets up tours with other artists, serving as the booking agent and, often, the driver for the actual road trip. He usually comes through town with different artists, and it&apos;s rare to have him appear on his own. This visit, in June of 2010, was one of the rare solo appearances.
In this video podcast episode, Zachary sings the song &quot;Blanket Tent&quot;, and shares about his love of touring with other artists. </itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0831%20Zachary%20Lucky%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="41328934" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0831%20Zachary%20Lucky%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 16:01:10 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:21</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jodi Pederson</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Jodi Pederson is a young singer/songwriter from the Prairies who now lives in the Okanagan. She's been at the Streaming Cafe twice to this point, and her clear voice catches peoples' attention every time.

In this podcast episode Jodi talks about how she got started as a recording artist, and shares a bit on her experience as a perfomer.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Jodi Pederson is a young singer/songwriter from the Prairies who now lives in the Okanagan. She&apos;s been at the Streaming Cafe twice to this point, and her clear voice catches peoples attention every time.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Jodi Pederson is a young singer/songwriter from the Prairies who now lives in the Okanagan. She&apos;s been at the Streaming Cafe twice to this point, and her clear voice catches peoples&apos; attention every time.

In this podcast episode Jodi talks about how she got started as a recording artist, and shares a bit on her experience as a perfomer.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0824%20Jodi%20Pederson%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="38635830" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0824%20Jodi%20Pederson%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 11:56:06 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:13</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Maurice</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Unabashed pop artists "Maurice" waltzed through Streaming Cafe back in October of 2009. Minus their drummer (well, he was there, but his kit didn't fit in the van they came in) they still put on a great-sounding show. 

Even while we were working on this podcast, different SC staff members commented on how much they'd liked this concert.

In this video podcast episode, built around the song "Kerosene", Maurice band members talk about songwriting and why they decided to sign with a label rather than remaining independent.

More of Maurice is available in the archives at www.streamingcafe.net]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Unabashed pop artists &quot;Maurice&quot; waltzed through Streaming Cafe back in October of 2010. Minus their drummer, they still put on a great show.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Unabashed pop artists &quot;Maurice&quot; waltzed through Streaming Cafe back in October of 2009. Minus their drummer (well, he was there, but his kit didn&apos;t fit in the van they came in) they still put on a great-sounding show. 

Even while we were working on this podcast, different SC staff members commented on how much they&apos;d liked this concert.

In this video podcast episode, built around the song &quot;Kerosene&quot;, Maurice band members talk about songwriting and why they decided to sign with a label rather than remaining independent.

More of Maurice is available in the archives at www.streamingcafe.net</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0817%20Maurice%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="53689764" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0817%20Maurice%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 11:40:39 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:28</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Andrew and Zachari Smith</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Andrew and Zachari Smith have both been guests at Streaming Cafe, but in January 2010 they visited as a father-and-son duo. Andrew has been on the singer-songwriter journey for many years, while Zachari is just getting started.

In this podcast, which features Andrew's song "Man in black", both father and son speak about how they keep music and songwriting fresh even though it's something they're involved in all the time.

Archive clips of each of Andrew and Zach's appearances can be found in the 'previous shows' sectionon of the Streaming Cafe.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Andrew and Zachari Smith have both been guests at Streaming Cafe, but in January 2010 they visited as a father-and-son duo. Andrew has been on the singer-songwriter journey for many years, while Zachari is just getting started.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Andrew and Zachari Smith have both been guests at Streaming Cafe, but in January 2010 they visited as a father-and-son duo. Andrew has been on the singer-songwriter journey for many years, while Zachari is just getting started.

In this podcast, which features Andrew&apos;s song &quot;Man in black&quot;, both father and son speak about how they keep music and songwriting fresh even though it&apos;s something they&apos;re involved in all the time.

Archive clips of each of Andrew and Zach&apos;s appearances can be found in the &apos;previous shows&apos; sectionon of the Streaming Cafe.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0810%20Andrew%20and%20Zachari%20Smith%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="40939942" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0810%20Andrew%20and%20Zachari%20Smith%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2010 15:26:01 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:23</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Anna Vandas</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Artist, dancer, songwriter... the creative outputs of Anna Vandas are varied, yet each one represents a different aspect of her talent. Anna's visit to the Streaming Cafe in July 2009 brought her gentle presence to our intimate venue for an evening we all enjoyed.

Anna and her husband embrace a wide range of artistic endeavours. During our break in the show we enjoyed a clip from a full-length DVD Anna's film-maker husband made while they were in New Zealand.

For more of Anna Vandas, check out the Previous Shows section on our website!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Artist, dancer, songwriter... the creative outputs of Anna Vandas are varied, yet each one represents a different aspect of her talent. Anna&apos;s visit to the Cafe brought her gentle presence to our intimate venue for an evening we all enjoyed – even her!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Artist, dancer, songwriter... the creative outputs of Anna Vandas are varied, yet each one represents a different aspect of her talent. Anna&apos;s visit to the Streaming Cafe in July 2009 brought her gentle presence to our intimate venue for an evening we all enjoyed.

Anna and her husband embrace a wide range of artistic endeavours. During our break in the show we enjoyed a clip from a full-length DVD Anna&apos;s film-maker husband made while they were in New Zealand.

For more of Anna Vandas, check out the Previous Shows section on our website!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0720%20Anna%20Vandas%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="45858262" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0720%20Anna%20Vandas%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 16:33:24 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:45</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Laurell</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[This song from pop artist Laurell shows a more tender side than some of her hook-laden singles currently climbing the Canadian radio charts.

In working toward her newest CD, Laurell engaged in a good deal of collaborative songwriting, something she hadn't done a lot of before. During her visit to Streaming Cafe in March of 2010, Laurell sat down with host Rhys Albrecht before the show to talk about how those songwriting sessions went.

Check out the previous shows at streamingcafe.net to catch more of Laurell!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Canadian acoustic pop artist Laurell engaged in collaborative songwriting for her new CD, something she hadn&apos;t done a lot of before. During her visit to Streaming Cafe, in March of 2010, Laurell sat down before the show to talk about how that went.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>This song from pop artist Laurell shows a more tender side than some of her hook-laden singles currently climbing the Canadian radio charts.

In working toward her newest CD, Laurell engaged in a good deal of collaborative songwriting, something she hadn&apos;t done a lot of before. During her visit to Streaming Cafe in March of 2010, Laurell sat down with host Rhys Albrecht before the show to talk about how those songwriting sessions went.

Check out the previous shows at streamingcafe.net to catch more of Laurell!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0713%20Laurell%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="40287020" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0713%20Laurell%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 11:40:14 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:17</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Owen Steel</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[When Owen Steel sits down at the mic his audience has no idea what they're in for - a voice that is is reminiscent of aged whiskey, a creativity that is fresh and youthful and a performance that is skilled beyond his years. Owen talks about humanity's nomadic nature and how being an artist only amplifies his desire to go out and share his craft.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>When Owen Steel sits down at the mic his audience has no idea what they&apos;re in for - a performance that is skilled beyond his years. Owen talks about humanity&apos;s nomadic nature and how being an artist only amplifies his desire to go out and share his craft.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>When Owen Steel sits down at the mic his audience has no idea what they&apos;re in for - a voice that is is reminiscent of aged whiskey, a creativity that is fresh and youthful and a performance that is skilled beyond his years. Owen talks about humanity&apos;s nomadic nature and how being an artist only amplifies his desire to go out and share his craft.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0629%20Owen%20Steel%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="34133186" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0629%20Owen%20Steel%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 10:12:31 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:50</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Zaac Pick</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Folk Singer/Songwriter Zaac Pick makes music that puts you in a mind state that is long forgotten in today's busy go-go world. At our Cafe he shares with us what drives him in a solo career pursuit and grants us a glimpse into his writing process.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Folk Singer/Songwriter Zaac Pick makes music that puts you in a mind state that is long forgotten in today&apos;s busy go-go world. At our Cafe he shares with us what drives him in a solo career pursuit and grants us a glimpse into his writing process.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Folk Singer/Songwriter Zaac Pick makes music that puts you in a mind state that is long forgotten in today&apos;s busy go-go world. At our Cafe he shares with us what drives him in a solo career pursuit and grants us a glimpse into his writing process.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0623%20ZaacPick%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="58826756" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0623%20ZaacPick%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 09:30:14 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:49</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Amy Seeley</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Pianist/Singer/Songwriter Amy Seeley was very well received when she played our Cafe in April. Amy admits her feelings of fear and admiration she has for the stage, as well as how a song's meaning will grow and evolve as time goes by.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Pianist/Singer/Songwriter Amy Seeley was very well received when she played our Cafe in April. Amy admits her feelings of fear and admiration she has for the stage, as well as how a song&apos;s meaning will grow and evolve as time goes by.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Pianist/Singer/Songwriter Amy Seeley was very well received when she played our Cafe in April. Amy admits her feelings of fear and admiration she has for the stage, as well as how a song&apos;s meaning will grow and evolve as time goes by.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0608%20Amy%20Seeley%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="37799778" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0608%20Amy%20Seeley%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 11:25:34 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:58</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Julie Doiron</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Julie Doiron is an iconic figure in indie music who packed out our Cafe last January. During our interview she reveals her 3 tried and true methods of song writing, as well as what her definition of uncompromising success looks like.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Julie Doiron is an iconic figure in indie music who packed out our Cafe last January. During our interview she reveals her 3 tried and true methods of song writing, as well as what her definition of uncompromising success looks like.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Julie Doiron is an iconic figure in indie music who packed out our Cafe last January. During our interview she reveals her 3 tried and true methods of song writing, as well as what her definition of uncompromising success looks like.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0601%20Julie%20Doiron%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="39659249" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0601%20Julie%20Doiron%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 10:17:41 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:03</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Folkshop</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[The talented trio known as Folkshop came through our Cafe almost a year ago today! Folkshop is Corwin Fox, Raghu Lokanathan and Yael Wand. Along with some catchy melodies, they share some insight on what happens when three established solo musicians decide to team up and try something a bit different!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>The talented trio known as Folkshop came through our Cafe almost a year ago today! Along with some catchy melodies, they share some insight on what happens when three established solo musicians decide to team up and try something a bit different!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The talented trio known as Folkshop came through our Cafe almost a year ago today! Folkshop is Corwin Fox, Raghu Lokanathan and Yael Wand. Along with some catchy melodies, they share some insight on what happens when three established solo musicians decide to team up and try something a bit different!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0525%20Folkshop%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="30937625" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0525%20Folkshop%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 10:30:03 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:36</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Adrian Glynn Podcast</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Let Vancouver based artist Adrian Glynn captivate you with his haunting melodies and inspired lyrics in a way that makes one feel truly hypnotized. Adrian lets his guard down as he talks with us about his younger years spent in a school choir.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Let Vancouver based artist Adrian Glynn captivate you with his haunting melodies and inspired lyrics in a way that makes one feel truly hypnotized. Adrian lets his guard down as he talks with us about his younger years spent in a school choir.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Let Vancouver based artist Adrian Glynn captivate you with his haunting melodies and inspired lyrics in a way that makes one feel truly hypnotized. Adrian lets his guard down as he talks with us about his younger years spent in a school choir.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0518%20Adrian%20Glynn%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="35311736" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0518%20Adrian%20Glynn%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 11:29:50 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:59</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Old Man&apos;s Beard</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Old Man's Beard has played our Cafe twice now, yet still manage to blow us away with a fresh and energetic set. In this episode they talk about their writing process and how they filter theirs songs to bring you the very best!]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Old Man&apos;s Beard has played our Cafe twice now, yet still manage to blow us away with a fresh and energetic set. In this episode they talk about their writing process and how they filter theirs songs to bring you the very best!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Old Man&apos;s Beard has played our Cafe twice now, yet still manage to blow us away with a fresh and energetic set. In this episode they talk about their writing process and how they filter theirs songs to bring you the very best!</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0511%20Old%20Man%27s%20Beard%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="50096395" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0511%20Old%20Man%27s%20Beard%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 10:26:56 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:06</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>James Lamb</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[In like a Lamb, rocks like a Lion...? James Lamb is our featured artists this Podcast. James talks about the joys of touring and memories of playing in heavy metal bars.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>In like a Lamb, rocks like a Lion...? James Lamb is our featured artists this Podcast. James talks about the joys of touring and memories of playing in heavy metal bars.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>In like a Lamb, rocks like a Lion...? James Lamb is our featured artists this Podcast. James talks about the joys of touring and memories of playing in heavy metal bars.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0504%20James%20Lamb%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="59271468" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0504%20James%20Lamb%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 12:50:45 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:49</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Adaline</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Adaline brought a lot to the table-a high energy performance that gave the audience goosebumps and a personality you can't help but think "I bet we could be real good friends." She talks to us about finding her name and the joy of being an indie artist.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Adaline brought a lot to the table-a high energy performance that gave the audience goosebumps and a personality you can&apos;t help but think &quot;I bet we could be real good friends.&quot; She talks to us about finding her name and the joy of being an indie artist.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Adaline brought a lot to the table-a high energy performance that gave the audience goosebumps and a personality you can&apos;t help but think &quot;I bet we could be real good friends.&quot; She talks to us about finding her name and the joy of being an indie artist.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0427%20Adaline%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="43229627" />
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/0427%20Adaline%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 10:42:10 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:32</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Justin Hewitt </title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Justin Hewitt has been a group favourite ever since he came by our cafe. With a high energy, passionate performance he consumes his audience and delivers a truly memorable performance. Justin reminisces of his days in cover bands and in the honest truth that simple can be just as beautiful.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Justin Hewitt has been a group favourite ever since he came by our cafe. Justin reminisces of his days in cover bands and in the honest truth that simple can be just as beautiful.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Justin Hewitt has been a group favourite ever since he came by our cafe. With a high energy, passionate performance he consumes his audience and delivers a truly memorable performance. Justin reminisces of his days in cover bands and in the honest truth that simple can be just as beautiful.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Justin%20Hewitt%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="44519614" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Justin%20Hewitt%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 09:53:57 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:31</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Andy Shauf</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Andy came to the Cafe on his tour with Zachary Lucky in November of 2009, and we all found him to be easy-going and unassuming. A few of the staff were already fans of his, and Andy's natural, unaffected off-stage manner cemented further loyalty among those who knew his music before he came to the Streaming Cafe.

When he sat down and picked up his guitar for the sound check, though, all of us were impressed with the maturity of his songwriting: this young man had a depth to his lyrics that defied his age. Many new fans were born that night.

One of the most talked-about and humorous moments of the show came about when our host, Brie, asked Andy about his guitar; this podcast episode shows how that question was answered. Andy also talks about how he first got started playing guitar back in his hometown of Estevan Saskatchewan.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Andy came to the cafe on his tour with Zachary Lucky in November of 2009. We all found him to be easy-going and unassuming, but when he sat down and picked up his guitar for the sound check we were impressed with the maturity of his songwriting.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Andy came to the Cafe on his tour with Zachary Lucky in November of 2009, and we all found him to be easy-going and unassuming. A few of the staff were already fans of his, and Andy&apos;s natural, unaffected off-stage manner cemented further loyalty among those who knew his music before he came to the Streaming Cafe.

When he sat down and picked up his guitar for the sound check, though, all of us were impressed with the maturity of his songwriting: this young man had a depth to his lyrics that defied his age. Many new fans were born that night.

One of the most talked-about and humorous moments of the show came about when our host, Brie, asked Andy about his guitar; this podcast episode shows how that question was answered. Andy also talks about how he first got started playing guitar back in his hometown of Estevan Saskatchewan.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Andy%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="35057017" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Andy%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 14:03:56 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:02:53</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Terra Grimard</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Terra Grimard graced the Streaming Cafe show in December of 2009 at the start of a tour in support of her new album.

Her winsome and peaceful personality off-stage, plus her rich voice and songwriting skills, made quick work of converting all of us in the production crew into her fans. She played to a full house; everyone in the Cafe was very impressed with the maturity and grace of Terra's music.

After four years of study toward a degree in music - which she completed successfully - Terra took a break from music for a couple of years to regain her focus. In this episode of the SC podcast Terra shares about her journey which was both geographical and spiritual.

We'll be bringing Terra back to the SC – we know that for sure.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>After four years of study toward a degree in music, which she completed successfully, Terra Grimard took a break from music for a couple of years to regain her focus. This episode of the Streaming Cafe podcast is from Terra&apos;s visit with us last December.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Terra Grimard graced the Streaming Cafe show in December of 2009 at the start of a tour in support of her new album.

Her winsome and peaceful personality off-stage, plus her rich voice and songwriting skills, made quick work of converting all of us in the production crew into her fans. She played to a full house; everyone in the Cafe was very impressed with the maturity and grace of Terra&apos;s music.

After four years of study toward a degree in music - which she completed successfully - Terra took a break from music for a couple of years to regain her focus. In this episode of the SC podcast Terra shares about her journey which was both geographical and spiritual.

We&apos;ll be bringing Terra back to the SC – we know that for sure.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Terra%20Grimard%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="44203695" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Terra%20Grimard%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 12:18:45 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:36</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Norm Strauss</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Norm Strauss has been part of the Streaming Cafe clan since we first hit the web. Having recorded more than a dozen albums over the years, Norm brings a wealth of songwriting and performing experience to the table. 

Germany plays at least as big a role in Norm's touring schedule as Canada and the USA does; it seems like at least once a year he's flown away from Canada to bring his music to Europe. In December when he played here at the Streaming Cafe there were Norm Strauss fans from Dresden (Germany) and other European locations making comments and interacting online with one another during the performance. Boston, Mass., and lots of different Canadian cities were also showing up on the grid.

In this episode Norm shares some thoughts on mentoring along with some straight-up advice to aspiring musicians.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Norm Strauss has been part of the SC clan since we first hit the webwaves (&apos;cause they&apos;re not airwaves). In this episode he shares his thoughts on mentoring as well as some straightforward advice to aspiring musicians.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Norm Strauss has been part of the Streaming Cafe clan since we first hit the web. Having recorded more than a dozen albums over the years, Norm brings a wealth of songwriting and performing experience to the table. 

Germany plays at least as big a role in Norm&apos;s touring schedule as Canada and the USA does; it seems like at least once a year he&apos;s flown away from Canada to bring his music to Europe. In December when he played here at the Streaming Cafe there were Norm Strauss fans from Dresden (Germany) and other European locations making comments and interacting online with one another during the performance. Boston, Mass., and lots of different Canadian cities were also showing up on the grid.

In this episode Norm shares some thoughts on mentoring along with some straight-up advice to aspiring musicians.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Norm%20Strauss%20April%201%202010.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="54091723" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Norm%20Strauss%20April%201%202010.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2010 10:28:32 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:23</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Kim McMechan</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[If anyone could be considered a stalwart at the Streaming Cafe, Kim McMechan would fit the bill. She was one of the first artists we ever hosted, and she's performed with several other artists who have done shows with us. 

Kim is a successful songwriter in different genres as well as being a writer-of-words with work published in various magazines and other sources.

This podcast is taken from Kim's second full show with us in September 2009. In this episode Kim talks about her secret radio listening habits and unpackages her thoughts about how Canadian singer/songwriters are all connected.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>This podcast is taken from Kim&apos;s second full show with us; this visit was in September 2009. In this episode Kim talks about her secret radio listening habits and unpackages her thoughts about how Canadian singer/songwriters are all connected.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>If anyone could be considered a stalwart at the Streaming Cafe, Kim McMechan would fit the bill. She was one of the first artists we ever hosted, and she&apos;s performed with several other artists who have done shows with us. 

Kim is a successful songwriter in different genres as well as being a writer-of-words with work published in various magazines and other sources.

This podcast is taken from Kim&apos;s second full show with us in September 2009. In this episode Kim talks about her secret radio listening habits and unpackages her thoughts about how Canadian singer/songwriters are all connected.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Kim%20McMechan%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="54814639" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Kim%20McMechan%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 13:48:48 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:26</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Paul O&apos;Brien</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[  Born in Birmingham to Irish parents, Paul O'Brien started the Canadian segment of his life journey as a school teacher after years as a Celtic entertainer in the UK.
  Figuring he had turned his back on a musical career, Paul dove whole-heartedly into connecting with his students and helping them rise above their circumstances - until a sunrise experience one morning on the way to work stopped him in his tracks. Re-embracing music as a singer/songwriter, Paul again ventured off the beaten track and back into a creative career.
  In this episode of the Streaming Cafe video Podcast Paul talks about his transition to Canada and how different it is than the UK.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Born in Birmingham to Irish parents, Paul O&apos;Brien started the Canadian segment of his life journey as a school teacher after years as a Celtic entertainer. In this episode Paul talks about his transition to Canada and how different it is than the UK.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>  Born in Birmingham to Irish parents, Paul O&apos;Brien started the Canadian segment of his life journey as a school teacher after years as a Celtic entertainer in the UK.
  Figuring he had turned his back on a musical career, Paul dove whole-heartedly into connecting with his students and helping them rise above their circumstances - until a sunrise experience one morning on the way to work stopped him in his tracks. Re-embracing music as a singer/songwriter, Paul again ventured off the beaten track and back into a creative career.
  In this episode of the Streaming Cafe video Podcast Paul talks about his transition to Canada and how different it is than the UK.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Paul%20O%27Brien.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="49856456" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Paul%20O%27Brien.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 10:04:19 -0700</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:10</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Treelines</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Treelines have been on Streaming Cafe twice to this point - and they were the first full-on band we'd had after a string of solo and duo singer songwriters. Their energy and music roared in and continued unabated for the full show. In this episode they share a previously unreleased song ("Summer Song" got named today just as we released this podcast)  and Matt talks about the band's future plans and songwriting process.  If you like Billy Talent you'll probably love Treelines.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Treelines have been on Streaming Cafe twice to this point - and they were the first full-on band we&apos;d had after a string of solo and duo singer songwriters. Their energy and music roared in and continued unabated for the full show.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Treelines have been on Streaming Cafe twice to this point - and they were the first full-on band we&apos;d had after a string of solo and duo singer songwriters. Their energy and music roared in and continued unabated for the full show. In this episode they share a previously unreleased song (&quot;Summer Song&quot; got named today just as we released this podcast)  and Matt talks about the band&apos;s future plans and songwriting process.  If you like Billy Talent you&apos;ll probably love Treelines.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Treelines%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="57542125" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Treelines%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 15:39:22 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:39</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music, billy talent, treelines</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Don Ross</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Don Ross's headset mic quit on him just as he started a tune. Not to be deterred, he blazed through an acoustic blues instrumental number while Streaming Cafe crew members worked on getting him a vocal mic. This boppin' little tune, entitled "Blue bear", is named after Berlin, the city where Don wrote it. Don says when Berliners pronounce the name of their city it sounds to his ear like they're saying "bear".

In this podcast Don speaks about touring in Germany as well as comparing European, Canadian, and American audiences.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Don Ross&apos;s headset mic quit on him just as he started a tune, so he blazed through an acoustic blues number while SC crew members worked on getting him a vocal mic. This boppin&apos; little tune, entitled &quot;Blue bear&quot;, is named after Berlin, a city Don loves.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Don Ross&apos;s headset mic quit on him just as he started a tune. Not to be deterred, he blazed through an acoustic blues instrumental number while Streaming Cafe crew members worked on getting him a vocal mic. This boppin&apos; little tune, entitled &quot;Blue bear&quot;, is named after Berlin, the city where Don wrote it. Don says when Berliners pronounce the name of their city it sounds to his ear like they&apos;re saying &quot;bear&quot;.

In this podcast Don speaks about touring in Germany as well as comparing European, Canadian, and American audiences.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Don%20Ross%20Podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="45740245" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Don%20Ross%20Podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 10:09:49 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:47</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Liam &amp; Brent Titcomb</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[This episode features Liam's new and unreleased song "Those three words" - due out on his next album - plus Brent's timely thoughts on the state of the music business in Canada. Brent is a legend in the Canadian folk scene, getting his start in the folk rock band "Three's A Crowd" (which in a later configuration had Bruce Cockburn as a member) and having had his songs recorded by artists including Anne Murray. These two were a big hit when they played the Streaming Cafe in September of 2009, and we'll be featuring them in two of our upcoming Webshows: Family Connections and Folk Music.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>This episode features Liam&apos;s new and unreleased song &quot;Those three words&quot; - due out on his next album- plus Brent&apos;s timely thoughts on the state of the music business in Canada. The father/son duo visited us during Liam&apos;s WarChild tour in September 2009.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>This episode features Liam&apos;s new and unreleased song &quot;Those three words&quot; - due out on his next album - plus Brent&apos;s timely thoughts on the state of the music business in Canada. Brent is a legend in the Canadian folk scene, getting his start in the folk rock band &quot;Three&apos;s A Crowd&quot; (which in a later configuration had Bruce Cockburn as a member) and having had his songs recorded by artists including Anne Murray. These two were a big hit when they played the Streaming Cafe in September of 2009, and we&apos;ll be featuring them in two of our upcoming Webshows: Family Connections and Folk Music.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Titcomb%20podcast.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="47222295" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Titcomb%20podcast.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 16:04:50 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:58</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sara Ciantar</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Sara breezed through Streaming Cafe like an ocean mist on a warm day, bringing lightness and freshness to everyone who heard her. In this podcast she talks about her switch from classical pianist to singer/songwriter (and being kicked out of Mexico!).]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Sara breezed through Streaming Cafe like an ocean mist on a warm day, bringing lightness and a freshness to everyone who heard her. In this podcast she talks about her switch from classical pianist to singer/songwriter (and being kicked out of Mexico!).</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Sara breezed through Streaming Cafe like an ocean mist on a warm day, bringing lightness and freshness to everyone who heard her. In this podcast she talks about her switch from classical pianist to singer/songwriter (and being kicked out of Mexico!).</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/SARA%20Ciantar%20podcast-H.264%20for%20iPod%20video%20and%20iPhone%20640x480.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="37846707" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/SARA%20Ciantar%20podcast-H.264%20for%20iPod%20video%20and%20iPhone%20640x480.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 09:02:27 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:11</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Twilight Hotel</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[The Alt Roots-Rock duo Twilight Hotel played Streaming Cafe in 2009 - after winning at the West Coast Music Awards and being nominated for a Juno. Vintage instruments, edgy attitude and strong songs propel this Canadian duo forward. In this episode the band speaks of their behind-the-scenes Juno experience.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>The Alt Roots-Rock duo Twilight Hotel played Streaming Cafe in 2009 - after winning at the West Coast Music Awards and being nominated for a Juno. Vintage instruments, edgy attitude and strong songs propel this Canadian duo forward.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The Alt Roots-Rock duo Twilight Hotel played Streaming Cafe in 2009 - after winning at the West Coast Music Awards and being nominated for a Juno. Vintage instruments, edgy attitude and strong songs propel this Canadian duo forward. In this episode the band speaks of their behind-the-scenes Juno experience.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Twilight%20Hotel.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="50610852" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Twilight%20Hotel.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 15:24:55 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:04</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>David Wilcox</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[David Wilcox mesmerized everyone when he visited the Cafe in June of 2009. In this vodcast of David's song "Red Eye" he shares some valuable insights on songwriting and performing - and does it in a way that speaks to all of us, performers or not.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>David Wilcox mesmerized everyone when he visited the Cafe in June of 2009. In this vodcast of David&apos;s song &quot;Red Eye&quot; he shares some valuable insights on songwriting and performing - and does it in a way that speaks to all of us, performers or not.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>David Wilcox mesmerized everyone when he visited the Cafe in June of 2009. In this vodcast of David&apos;s song &quot;Red Eye&quot; he shares some valuable insights on songwriting and performing - and does it in a way that speaks to all of us, performers or not.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/DW%20podcast%20Feb%202010.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="42631528" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/DW%20podcast%20Feb%202010.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 12:51:42 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:38</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Brooke Miller</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Brooke performed at Streaming Cafe with Don Ross in May of 2009. She blew us all away with her guitar playing, her songwriting, and her marvelous voice. In this podcast Brooke talks about her start in the music business back on the East Coast.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Brooke performed at Streaming Cafe with Don Ross in May of 2009. She blew us all away with her guitar playing, her songwriting, and her marvelous voice. In this podcast Brooke talks about her start in the music business back on the East Coast.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Brooke performed at Streaming Cafe with Don Ross in May of 2009. She blew us all away with her guitar playing, her songwriting, and her marvelous voice. In this podcast Brooke talks about her start in the music business back on the East Coast.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Brooke%20Miller%20podcast%20FINAL.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="50402392" />
			<link>http://streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Brooke%20Miller%20podcast%20FINAL.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 11:40:44 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:08</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Yukon Blonde</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[These high-energy guys bring a lot of upbeat enthusiasm to their music. Okanagan favourites who have since moved to Vancouver, we were pleased to host them in November 2009... the electrocution story was hilarious.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>These high-energy guys bring a lot of upbeat enthusiasm to their music. Okanagan favourites who have since moved to Vancouver, we were pleased to host them in November 2009... the electrocution story was hilarious.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>These high-energy guys bring a lot of upbeat enthusiasm to their music. Okanagan favourites who have since moved to Vancouver, we were pleased to host them in November 2009... the electrocution story was hilarious.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Yukon%20Blonde%20Podcast%20Jan%2020%20adjusted.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="41291155" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Yukon%20Blonde%20Podcast%20Jan%2020%20adjusted.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 16:21:08 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:28</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ari Neufeld</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Ari is always a crowd favourite at the Streaming Cafe. With his high energy and deep thoughts, plus his unique body-based rhythm instruments and stomp box, an "Ari show" covers a lot of musical territory. We've hosted him twice in 2009 and have already booked him again for early 2010.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Ari is always a crowd favourite at the Streaming Cafe. With his high energy and deep thoughts, plus his unique body-based rhythm instruments and stomp box, an &quot;Ari show&quot; covers a lot of musical territory.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Ari is always a crowd favourite at the Streaming Cafe. With his high energy and deep thoughts, plus his unique body-based rhythm instruments and stomp box, an &quot;Ari show&quot; covers a lot of musical territory. We&apos;ve hosted him twice in 2009 and have already booked him again for early 2010.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Ari%20podcast%20Jan%2011%202010.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="52619112" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/Ari%20podcast%20Jan%2011%202010.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 15:59:18 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:12</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Fall Blues Fest</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[The Streaming Cafe's Fall Blues Fest was a standing-room-only show, and the blues harp playing of Sherman Doucette, featured in this vodcast, was one of the highlights of the night.]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>The Streaming Cafe&apos;s Fall Blues Fest was a standing-room-only show, and the blues harp playing of Sherman Doucette, featured in this vodcast, was one of the highlights of the night.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The Streaming Cafe&apos;s Fall Blues Fest was a standing-room-only show, and the blues harp playing of Sherman Doucette, featured in this vodcast, was one of the highlights of the night.</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4v?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/SC091114_FallBluesFest_Podcast01.m4v" type="video/x-m4v" length="51815183" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/SC091114_FallBluesFest_Podcast01.m4v</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 13:10:19 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:04:14</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Greg Sczebel</title>
			<itunes:author>streamingcafe.net</itunes:author>
			<description><![CDATA[Singer/songwriter Greg Sczebel (pronounced seh-bell) is just your regular guy-next-door (if that guy was obsessed with music and ridiculously talented).]]></description>
			<itunes:subtitle>Singer/songwriter Greg Sczebel (pronounced seh-bell) is just your regular guy-next-door (if that guy was obsessed with music and ridiculously talented).</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Singer/songwriter Greg Sczebel (pronounced seh-bell) is just your regular guy-next-door (if that guy was obsessed with music and ridiculously talented).</itunes:summary>
			<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp4?http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/SC091120_GregSczebel_Podcast02.mp4" type="video/mp4" length="53667292" />
			<link>http://www.streamingcafe.net</link>
			<guid>http://streamingcafe.net/mp4/SC091120_GregSczebel_Podcast02.mp4</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 16:58:35 -0800</pubDate>
			<category>Music</category>
			<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:duration>00:03:49</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>streaming cafe, live music, indie music</itunes:keywords>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>