<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>BendingCorners : jazz-n-groove</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/</link>
	<description>BendingCorners is podcast of groovy jazz and jazzy grooves</description>
	<language>en-us</language>


<item>
<title>BC081 - Nebula Jazz Travels</title>
<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/nebula/</link>
<description>
BendingCorners annual Kozmigroov set where we travel thru the nebula of cosmic jazz groove.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/nebula/
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 December 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
<title>BC080 - More Hornin' 'Round</title>
<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/morehornin/</link>
<description>
Its horn time yet again at BendingCorners. BC loves them horns.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/morehornin/
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 29 September 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
<title>BC079 - Beam Me Up, Scotty</title>
<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/beamup/</link>
<description>
Interstellar warp jazz for trekking amoung the stars.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/beamup/
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 July 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>



	<item>
	<title>BC078 - 77 Exploding Suns</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/77suns/</link>
	<description>
Cosmic jazz inside a black hole created by 77 exploding suns.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/77suns/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 June 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>BC077 - Jazzatronic 2010</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/jazzatronic/</link>
	<description>
BendingCorners' annual jazzatronic set where we showcase the past year's notable examples of electronically-affected jazz grooves.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/jazzatronic/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Sat, 30 April 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>David Axelrod - Seriously Deep</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/seriously_deep/</link>
	<description>
Heavy keyboards, rubbery basslines, fuzzed-out guitars, funky drums - a cinematic jazz-funk classic!

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/seriously_deep/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Wed, 20 April 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>BC076 - Bumpin</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/bumpin/</link>
	<description>
A set of stretched out guitar grooves with funky riffs, heavy drums, and fuzzed electronics.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/bumpin/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Thu, 30 March 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>Erik Truffaz - The Mask</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/the_mask/</link>
	<description>
A forward-looking set of Miles Davis-influenced blissful cool jazz, spacey electronics, and warm acoustic drum-n-bass grooves. A cosmic nu-jazz masterpiece! 

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/the_mask/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 25 March 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>Joe Chambers - New World</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/new_world/</link>
	<description>
A great platter of mid-70's cosmic jazz-rock with spacey rhodes, smokin' guitar, and smashing drums (of course!). 

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/new_world/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Wed, 16 March 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>Tribe - Rebirth</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/rebirth/</link>
	<description>
Another in Carl Craig's bag of great jazz productions, Rebirth is essentially a modern take on classic Tribe Records material. Modern cosmic jazz groove at its finest, and BC's favorite release of 2009.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/rebirth/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Wed, 09 March 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>Masabumi Kikuchi - Wishes/Kochi</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/wishes/</link>
	<description>
Like a Japanese mix of Bitches Brew and Dark Magus (including some of Miles Davis' mid-70's personnel) with Terumasa Hino on trumpet sounding much like Davis himself! A-list Kozmigroov, and very highly recommended.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/wishes/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Wed, 02 March 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>BC075 - Extension</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/extension/</link>
	<description>
Four extended-length jazz grooves to extend your consciousness.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/extension/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 21 February 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>Hidden Orchestra - Night Walks</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/night_walks/</link>
	<description>
Emotive, lush, sweeping, and layered cinematic jazz grooves. Similar in style and sound to The Cinematic Orchestra, Bonobo, and Nostalgia 77. This was BC's favorite new release of 2010.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/night_walks/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Thu, 17 February 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>Arnold Cheatham - Thing</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/thing/</link>
	<description>
Two extended live jazz jams of A-list cosmic jazz grooves! "sprawling spacey jazz with bristly funk". Right up there with early 70's Davis and Weather Report. Yes, its that good.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/thing/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Thu, 08 February 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>New Corners</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/new_corners/</link>
	<description>
Fresh for 2011, BendingCorners has a new look (logo, fonts, colors) and a redesigned display. In addition, we intend to expand our scope beyond podcasting into full blogging.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/new_corners/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 01 February 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
	<title>BC074 - Astral Jazz Dreams</title>
	<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/astral/</link>
	<description>
Another in BC's long line of kozmigroov sets. Starting off with one of the most recognized kozmigroov masterpieces ever, we then head off into the dreamscape, and finish with another kozmigroov magnum opus. A perfect set for a late-nite chill session just before bed. Pleasant dreams.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2011/astral/
	</description>
	<pubDate>Wed, 19 January 2011 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
	</item>



		<item>
			<title>Vanguard</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/vanguard/</link>
			<description>
Late 1960s and early 1970s vanguard jazz guitar. Another in BendingCorners' occasional sets exploring the merge of jazz and rock styles. Guitar luminaries John McLaughlin and Larry Coryell are well represented.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/vanguard/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 September 2010 01:13:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Crossfire</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/crossfire/</link>
			<description>
A bit of fire and a bit of ice come together in this potpourri of 70s jazz groove.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/crossfire/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 29 August 2010 01:12:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Contemporary Corners (collection 1)</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/contemporary1/</link>
			<description>
This is the first in a series of sets where we explore the groove of contemporary jazz. If the tune was recorded in the 21st century, we consider it "contemporary". For this first collection, we highlight some of the artists that have been topping "the critic's charts" most recently.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/contemporary1/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 29 June 2010 01:11:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Nova Spirit Rhythm (Steve Reid Tribute)</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/reid/</link>
			<description>
BendingCorners' tribute to the avant-garde jazz drummer Steve Reid who passed away last month.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/reid/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 01:10:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Jazzatronic 2009, part 2 (beat wise)</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/jazzatronic2/</link>
			<description>
Part 2 of BendingCorners' annual "jazzatronic" set. As with all the previous jazzatronic sets, we showcase the past year's notable examples of electronically-affected jazz grooves. Part 2 gets wise with the beats. 

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/jazzatronic2/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 April 2010 01:09:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Jazzatronic 2009, part 1 (space ways)</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/jazzatronic1/</link>
			<description>
BC's annual "jazzatronic" set is a twofer this year. As with the all the previous jazzatronic sets, we showcase the past year's notable examples of electronically-affected jazz grooves. Part 1 travels the urban spaces ways. 

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/jazzatronic1/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 29 March 2010 01:08:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>




		<item>
			<title>Pisces Escapes</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/pisces/</link>
			<description>
Easy going, but never soft, this is an emotive set of cosmic jazz grooves to escape into a world of pleasant dreams.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/pisces/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 28 February 2010 01:07:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>




		<item>
			<title>Brasstastic</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/brasstastic/</link>
			<description>
Its a new decade which means its time to celebrate. And what better way to celebrate than with a bunch of blaring horns! This is BendingCorners homage to jazz band brass sections. Brass is fantastic!

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2010/brasstastic/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 January 2010 01:06:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Infinite Jazz Voyage</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/infinite/</link>
			<description>
BendingCorners' annual kozmigroov set where we voyage through the infinite space of cosmic jazz groove.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/infinite/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 December 2009 01:05:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>




		<item>
			<title>The Beatles: JazzBand</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/beatles/</link>
			<description>
Riffing off the recent release of The Beatles RockBand video game, BendingCorners releases a jazz and soul Beatles tribute, The Beatles JazzBand. As with most BC sets, this mix showcases the groovy side of the available material.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/beatles/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 September 2009 01:04:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Russell's Electronic Sonata</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/russell/</link>
			<description>
The innovative avant-garde composer and arranger George Russell became one with the cosmos last month. This is BendingCorners tribute to his masterpiece that is 'Electronic Sonata For Souls Loved By Nature'. Presented here is a 60 minute mix of the groovy parts of the Sonata from the 1968 and 1971 recordings.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/russell/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 August 2009 01:03:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>SunFlowers</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/sunflowers/</link>
			<description>
Jazz grooves for summer vibes.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/sunflowers/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 July 2009 01:02:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>May Flowers</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/mayflowers/</link>
			<description>
A warm and cheerful set with pleasant and colorful grooves. There may or may not be "green shoots" in the economy, but there are plenty of new growth grooves in this mix. Spring showers bring May flowers! 

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/mayflowers/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2009 01:01:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Jazzatronic 2008</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/jazzatronic/</link>
			<description>
Its time for BendingCorners' annual showcase of standout "jazzatronic" tunes from the past year. Here are some of BC's favorite modern examples of the influence of electronics on jazz.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/jazzatronic/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 27 April 2009 01:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Aries Rising</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/aries/</link>
			<description>
Heading into spring with set of adventurous and dynamic tunes. Expressive and full of energy, but not over done.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/aries/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 30 March 2009 00:59:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Chilled</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/chilled/</link>
			<description>
Its cold out there, and what better to do than chill out with a loved one in a haze of chilled grooves.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/chilled/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 28 February 2009 00:58:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Freddie Flys</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/freddie/</link>
			<description>
Freddie flys, in more ways than one. This is BendingCorners tribute to the late great jazz trumpeter Freddie Hubbard, who flew the coup just a few days ago. Presented in order of release are some of Freddie's most dope smokin' tunes from BC's favorite time - the early 70's. Freddie flys high.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2009/freddie/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 January 2009 00:57:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Empyreal Jazz Rads</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/empyreal/</link>
			<description>
This is BendingCorner's annual year-end kozmigroov set where we explore the planetary sounds and empyreal nature of the music and artists of the cosmic jazz scene.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/empyreal/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 21 December 2008 00:56:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Enigmatic Spaces</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/enigmatic/</link>
			<description>
Travels in the tunnels of modern cosmic jazz groove.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/enigmatic/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 27 October 2008 00:55:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Hot Buttered Hayes</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/hayes/</link>
			<description>
The legendary soul singer and arranger/composer Isaac Hayes passed away this month. This is BendingCorners tribute to the more jazzy groove side of his repertoire, including the full 19 minutes of 'Do Your Thing'!

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/hayes/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 18 August 2008 00:54:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Teo's Masterpieces</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/teo/</link>
			<description>
The master jazz producer Teo Macero passed away in early 2008. This is BendingCorners' tribute to his brilliant productions. Presented in order of release, is one song from each of the ledgendary Jazz Masterpieces that Teo produced during his tenure at Columbia Records.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/teo/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 29 July 2008 00:53:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Miles' Indian Trip</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/miles/</link>
			<description>
Spurred by the recent release of "Miles From India", BendingCorners explores some of the original material that inspired Bob Belden in the first place. BC has been waiting for an excuse to do a full Miles set, and this seemed like the perfect time to do so. Presented here are some of the trippier sides of Miles' Eastern inspired tunes from the early-70's.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/miles/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 28 June 2008 00:52:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Jazzatronic 2007</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/jazzatronic/</link>
			<description>
This is BendingCorners' annual showcase of standout "jazzatronic" tunes from the past year. As with previous years, this set covers some of BC's favorite modern examples of the influence of electronica on jazz and vise versa.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/jazzatronic/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 00:51:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Hornin' 'Round (modern)</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/horninround/</link>
			<description>
Its trumpet time again at BendingCorners. This is the second of a two part series, and this time around we focus on modern day trumpeters with some of BC's favorite players from the 90's thru today. Like the classic first set, we again highlight the more progressive side of the trumpet spectrum.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/horninround/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 31 March 2008 00:50:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Bending Dubs</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/bendingdubs/</link>
			<description>
Another set inspired by luminary labels. This time around we explore the dub side of the groove, as pioneered by Channel One and Studio One. Spanning 4 decades of jazzy-dub, the set starts off in a traditional 70's style dub and gets more progressive with each selection. Smoke out and dub down.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/bendingdubs/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 February 2008 00:49:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Stoned Ninja bbeats</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/bbeats/</link>
			<description>
Inspired by such luminary labels as Ninja Tune, bbe, and Stones Throw, this set explores the beat side of jazz-n-groove. Perfect for those late night dope headz sessions, this is beat heavy and groove wise.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2008/bbeats/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 21 January 2008 00:48:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Celestial Jazz Expansions</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/celestial/</link>
			<description>
Its time again for BendingCorner's annual trip down the cosmic jazzways. Like previous years, this set travels amoung the celestial bodies of the kozmigroov elite as well as the cosmic underground. From well-known to unknown we set the needle on the space groove and expand to beyond.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/celestial/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 December 2007  00:46:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Femme Fatale</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/femme/</link>
			<description>
A celebration of women bending their corners. Yes, this is a spotlight on female groovers, but its so much more... These are more than just females singing in a male band. These are tunes where the woman is front and center as the leader, the creator, the artist, the name-sake. And, though there are a number of the typical names you'll find on a "women of" collection, this set showcases the groovie bent side of the available material.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/femme/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 October 2007  00:45:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Zawinderful</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/zawinderful/</link>
			<description>
Jazz fusion legend Josef Zawinul passed away on September 11th and this is BendingCorners' homage to his genre-defining and category-bending music. The tunes presented here date from 1967 to 1975 and span Joe's three main groups: Cannonball Adderley, Miles Davis, and Weather Report. All songs were composed by Joe and feature Joe on a range of keyboards.  

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/zawinderful/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 September 2007  00:44:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Hornin' 'Round (classic)</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/horninround/</link>
			<description>
Its trumpet time at BendingCorners! This first of a two volumn series showcases some of BC's favorite trumpet players from the sixties and seventies. As per usual, we highlight the more "bent" side of the trumpet spectrum. These guys are smokin' hot!

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/horninround/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 August 2007  00:43:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Modern Architecture</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/architecture/</link>
			<description>
Rummaging through the archives, we pullout a modern jazz groove set spun live, in the field, and on the fly. This is the second half of a two part set in which BendingCorners provided the musical atmosphere for an architectural art show. Where as part one focused on classic architectural atmospheres, this set shines light on the more modern scene.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/architecture/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 28 July 2007  00:42:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>BabyCorners, Hush</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/hush/</link>
			<description>
Got an infant or toddler and are tired of cheesy new age baby lullaibies? Get hip, and try out this mix on your little one. In celebration of BC's newest edition to the family, Myles Stanton, this is the first in a new series of "BabyCorners" sets that are specifically designed for children, and their musically discerning parents. The music here was carefully choosen to soothe, chill, and hush your child (and/or you) into a pleasant bliss. 

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/hush/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 June 2007  00:41:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Afro Jazz Jive</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/afrojazz/</link>
			<description>
Spanning four decades and a number of styles this set explores African inspired jazz-n-groove. Purposely by-passing the well known acts, we go beyond the standard afrobeat fare for a deeper broader mix. Feel the groove and jive on.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/afrojazz/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2007  00:40:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>



		<item>
			<title>Jazzatronic 2006</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/jazzatronic/</link>
			<description>
April has become the month for BendingCorner's annual feature of the standout "jazzatronic" tunes from the past year. Like previous years, this set showcases BC's favorite examples of the continual use and merging of electronics, jazz instrumentation, and modern production techniques. New for this year, though, is the inclusion of 5 listener-created submissions!

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/jazzatronic/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007  00:39:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Straight-Ahead, Turn Left</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/straight/</link>
			<description>
"Straight-Ahead" jazz on BendingCorners? Yes, you heard that right. But don't worry, this ain't your standard straight fare. This is BendingCorners after all. Its straight, with a twist; shaken, not stirred. Straight jazz with bent corners.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/straight/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007  00:38:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Alice in Wonderland</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/alice/</link>
			<description>
BendingCorners tribute to the late great Alice Coltrane. On January 12th 2007 the jazz world lost another of its pioneers. Alice was a seminal player in the Kozmigroov spiritual scene and this is BC's take on her more mellow and moving material. Spark a J, relax, and float down stream.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/alice/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2007  00:37:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Trigonometry</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/trigonometry/</link>
			<description>
Music fit for winter weather, this set explores the systemic, angular, and calculating side of jazz-n-groove; prefect for those long, dark, and frigid winter nights gazing up at the crystal clear sparkling stars.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2007/trigonometry/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2007  00:36:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Mr. Dynamite</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/dynamite/</link>
			<description>
The soulfather's body may be gone, but his music remains with us forever. And so thankful (for his music) we are! Like so many others, here is BC's take on the "James Brown Tribute", with an attempt to spotlight some of his more "jazzy" numbers. These aren't the most popular or well-known of his tunes, but they definitely got the groove! Pappa's bag has popped. Peace to you, brutha. RIP.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/dynamite/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2006  00:35:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Interstellar Jazz Orbits</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/ijo/</link>
			<description>
Time again for BendingCorners's annual November excursion into Kozmigroov. This set makes orbits around many of the big and small players in the cosmic jazz groove field.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/ijo/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2006  00:34:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Fuzzadelic</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/fuzzadelic/</link>
			<description>
Another in BC's irregular series of heavy jazz-rock sets. This time we focus on fuzzed-out psychedelic sounds. Distorted guitars, modulated keys, and reverberated horns are all in the mix. Knob-twiddling for jazz heads.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/fuzzadelic/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2006  00:33:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Continental Beats</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/cbeats/</link>
			<description>
A beat heavy set, where we explore the "infinite beat" of drums, bass, and percussion focused grooves from all six of the inhabitable continents. Beats from the North American, South American, African, European, Asian, and Australian(New Zealand) continents are all represented. Not world beat, but rather beats around the world.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/cbeats/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2006  00:32:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>So Full</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/sofull/</link>
			<description>
Continuing from last month's instrumental soul journey, this month the vocals take the stage. The many sides of "soul" are explored here. Jazz, soul, funk, disco, hip-hop, drum-n-bass, downtempo, house, folk, future, and nu are all represented. Soulful grooves indeed.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/sofull/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006  00:31:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Soul Jazz</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/souljazz/</link>
			<description>
Not so much "soul-jazz" per say, as more jazz with soul, or rather the soul of jazz. Unifying and uplifting, its an instrumental excursion of groove(food) for your soul.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/souljazz/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2006  00:30:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Sundance</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/sundance/</link>
			<description>
A celebration of summer thats all over the musical map. There is a little something for everyone in this mix. From classic to modern with elements of jazz, soul, spirit, disco, house, latin, bossa, nu, and downtempo, these grooves all have an uplifting summertime vibe.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/sundance/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2006  00:29:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Medium Rare</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/medium_rare/</link>
			<description>
This is BendingCorners' take on the well worn path of "rare groove". The set starts with the traditional "rare" sound and moves thru more contemporary and progressive grooves and ends somewhat abstract.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/medium_rare/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2006  00:28:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Jazzatronic 2005</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/jazzatronic_2005/</link>
			<description>
BendingCorner's annual set of the past year's finest "jazzatronic" tunes. A collection of jazz-based electronically-influenced groovers with modern production techniques.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/jazzatronic_2005/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2006  00:27:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Fission</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/fission/</link>
			<description>
As a follow up to JazzDJ's Fusion set, BendingCorners brings you Fission, a showcase of grinding guitars and squelchy synths. Presented here in roughly chronological order we follow the progression of "fusion jazz" from beautiful guitars in the late 1960's, to fast and furious jamming in the early 70's, to heavy synth work in the mid/late 70's (capped on both ends by Miroslav Vitous).

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/fission/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2006  00:26:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Luscious</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/luscious/</link>
			<description>
Sweet, succulent, and slightly seductive, this set explores the lush and lovely side of jazz-n-groove.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/luscious/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2006  00:25:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Classic Architecture</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/classic_architecture/</link>
			<description>
Classic cosmic jazz groove spun live, in the field, and on the fly. This is part one of a two part set in which BendingCorners provided the musical atmosphere for an architectural art show.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2006/classic_architecture/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2006  00:24:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Scandiland</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/scandiland/</link>
			<description>
Acknowledging the arrival of winter, this set explores the jazz scene of Scandinavia, where the winters are cold, dark, and gloomy, yet the jazz is blinding white hot. From 1972 to 2005, from Finland to Norway and Sweden, we travel the many styles and genres of scandinavian jazz.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/scandiland/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005  00:23:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Sonic Jazz Trek</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/sonic_jazz_trek/</link>
			<description>
Another set in BC's ongoing series of kozmigroov explorations. A sonic trek through the space of cosmic jazz groove.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/sonic_jazz_trek/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2005  00:22:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Oscillations</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/oscillations/</link>
			<description>
A vibrating trip through the land of echoes, reverbs, dubs, and askew wobbles.  Spanning genres of jazz, future jazz, out rock, dub, afro-beat, and downtempo grooves, these sounds are indeed bending.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/oscillations/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2005  00:21:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Spirits Within</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/spirits_within/</link>
			<description>
As a shout out to our musical brothers at Quincy Essential, this one digs into the spiritual side of the groove. The Spirit is inside everyone of us, however we all experience and express it differently. The musicians in this set express their spirits uniquely as well. From modal moments and divine grooves to wailing saxes and soaring gospels, the spirit is definitely within. (practice tolerance)

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/spirits_within/
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2005  00:20:00 PST</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Desert Moments</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/desert_moments/</link>
			<description>
In celebration of Burning Man's 20th anniversary this mix is perfect for lazy moments around camp or solo desert strolls.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/desert_moments/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2005-08-23 00:19:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>WORD!</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/word/</link>
			<description>
An exploration of poetry, scat, spoken word, cadence, and even rap in jazz-n-groove. From jazz scat and spoken word to reggae, afro-funk and early jazz rap in the 70's right on thru to the modern phusion of jazz, cadence, and electronics. Word to your mother!

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/word/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2005-07-31 00:18:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Double Z</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/double_z/</link>
			<description>
Jazz ROCKS!! Putting the double "z" into jaZZ, this mix explores the heavy side of jazz.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/double_z/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2005-07-19 00:17:00</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Nu Standards</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/nu_standards/</link>
			<description>
Keeping jazz alive for the young'ins, here is a batch of newer live instrumentation "21st Century Jazz" by some of the recent nu cats on the scene.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/nu_standards/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2005-05-31 00:16:00</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Warm Fronts</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/warm_fronts/</link>
			<description>
Celebrate the coming of spring with this mix of nu and classic emotive jazz.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/warm_fronts/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2005-04-30 00:15:00</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Jazzatronic 2004</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/jazzatronic_2004/</link>
			<description>
A selection of high quality tunes from 2004 demonstrating the fusion of jazz, beats, electronics and modern production techniques.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/jazzatronic_2004/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2005-03-31 00:14:00</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Modes and Moods</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/modes_and_moods/</link>
			<description>
Lush, modal, and moody jazz for the love of February.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/modes_and_moods/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2005-02-17 00:13:00</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Cinematic Jazz Scenes</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/cinematic_jazz_scenes/</link>
			<description>
Moody, smokey, and cinematic jazz for an invisible soundtrack.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2005/cinematic_jazz_scenes/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2005-01-31 00:12:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Strata-Sphere</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/stratasphere/</link>
			<description>
Classic cosmic jazz groove inspired by the Strata-East record label.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/stratasphere/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2004-12-18 00:11:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Epic Jazz Brew</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/epicjazzbrew/</link>
			<description>
Classic cosmic jazz groove.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/epicjazzbrew/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2004-11-10 00:10:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Hangin Onto Summer</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/hangin/</link>
			<description>
Summertime jazz-n-groove.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/hangin/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2004-10-09 00:09:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Spaced Out</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/spacedout/</link>
			<description>
Jazz, rock, and electronics from space.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/spaceout/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2004-09-08 00:08:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Out In Between</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/outinbetween/</link>
			<description>
Jazz, rock, and electronics that defies categorization.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/outinbetween/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2004-06-07 00:07:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Jazzatronic 2003</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/jazzatronic2003/</link>
			<description>
2003 nu-jazz.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2004/jazzatronic2003/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2004-03-06 00:06:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Jam On It</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2003/jamonit/</link>
			<description>
Live jazz jams.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2003/jamonit/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2003-12-05 00:05:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Cosmic Jazz Journerys</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2003/cosmicjazzjourneys/</link>
			<description>
Classic cosmic jazz groove.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2003/cosmicjazzjourneys/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2003-11-04 00:04:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Vocalities</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2003/vocalities/</link>
			<description>
Vocal jazz groove.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2003/vocalities/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2003-03-03 00:03:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Jazzatronic 2002</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2003/jazzatronic2002/</link>
			<description>
2002 nu-jazz.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2003/jazzatronic2002/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2003-01-02 00:02:00</pubDate>
		</item>


		<item>
			<title>Galactic Jazz Trip</title>
			<link>http://www.bendingcorners.com/2002/galacticjazztrip/</link>
			<description>
Cosmic jazz groove.

http://www.bendingcorners.com/2002/galacticjazztrip/
			</description>
			<pubDate>2002-10-01 00:01:00</pubDate>
		</item>


</channel>
</rss>
