<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>313Digital Audio Podcast Channel</title>
    <link>http://www.portagemedia.com/313digital</link>
    <description>The mp3 Audio feed of the numerous digital-centric events and content of 313Digital, the premier interactive media association in the Detroit metro area.</description>
    <generator>Feeder 1.4.4 http://reinventedsoftware.com/feeder/</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2007 313digital</copyright>
    <managingEditor>jeremiah@portagemedia.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jeremiah@portagemedia.com</webMaster>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 10:42:40 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 10:42:40 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://www.portagemedia.com/audio_313_itunes.jpg</url>
      <title>313Digital Audio Podcast Channel</title>
      <link>http://www.portagemedia.com/313digital</link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>144</height>
    </image>
    <itunes:author>313Digital / Portage Media Solutions</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>313Digital, Technology, Detroit, Adcraft, Advertising, Marketing</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://www.portagemedia.com/audio_313_itunes.jpg"/>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Jeremiah Staes</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>jeremiah@portagemedia.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
    <itunes:category text="Business">
      <itunes:category text="Management &amp; Marketing"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:category text="Technology">
      <itunes:category text="Podcasting"/>
      <itunes:category text="Tech News"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Platform Video Panel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Advertisers are creating video assets to be deployed on every possible communication channel - cell phones, web pages, iTV, VOD, buildings in major cities, and others. It seems everywhere you look there is a video advertisement trying to draw your attention. But how do smart marketers take advantage of this opportunity and create positive brand connection? And how does User-Generated video impact the industry?</p>

<p>The Moderator & Panelists</p><p>Moderator: Stokes Young<br />Director of Video, MSNBC.com</p><p>Panelists:</p><p>Carolyn Forster <br />Vice President, PHD Detroit</p><p>Mark Flaharty <br />Midwest Director of Sales, YouTube</p><p>Dina Roman<br />SVP Marketing and Sales, Brightcove</p><p>Jeff Hufford <br />SVP of Distribution, Broadband Enterprises</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2007 10:42:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/portagemedia/313video-audio.mp3" length="26953557" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">crossplatform-video-panel</guid>
      <itunes:subtitle>Cross-Platform Video with MSNBC.com, YouTube, Brightcove, Broadband Enterprises and PHD-Detroit</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Advertisers are creating video assets to be deployed on every possible communication channel - cell phones, web pages, iTV, VOD, buildings in major cities, and others. It seems everywhere you look there is a video advertisement trying to draw your attention. But how do smart marketers take advantage of this opportunity and create positive brand connection? And how does User-Generated video impact the industry?

The Moderator &amp; Panelists

Moderator: Stokes Young
Director of Video, MSNBC.com

Panelists:

Carolyn Forster 
Vice President, PHD Detroit

Mark Flaharty 
Midwest Director of Sales, YouTube

Dina Roman
SVP Marketing and Sales, Brightcove

Jeff Hufford 
SVP of Distribution, Broadband Enterprises</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>57:00</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Networking Panel Discussion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Social Networking is experiencing hyper-growth with more and more people creating content and networking with friends. In order to reach consumers online, advertisers must follow them into the likes of MySpace, Facebook, etc. Yet social networking sites can present unique challenges to marketers who are concerned with the quality and appropriateness of unedited and unfiltered content. Further, consumers may look askance at advertisers interrupting conversations with friends. The formula for creating effective marketing plans using social networking sites is still in its earliest stages.</p><p> </p><p>Listed below are the distinguished panel of speakers:</p><p> </p><p>Panelists:</p><p>MySpace: David Tolkheim, SVP, Client Solutions</p><p>Evite: Harry Lin, Senior Vice President and General Manager</p><p>Microsoft: Denis Gaynor, Product Manager</p><p>Facebook: Tom Arrix, SVP of Advertising</p><p>JWT: Jason Yoder, SVP Digital Media Director</p><p>Moderator:<br />Scott Kelly, Digital Marketing Manager, Ford Motor Company</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 11:58:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/portagemedia/networkingpanel-audio.mp3" length="26643494" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">social-networking-panel-discussion</guid>
      <itunes:subtitle>Social Networking Panel Discussion Sponsored by Expedia Media Solutions</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Social Networking is experiencing hyper-growth with more and more people creating content and networking with friends. In order to reach consumers online, advertisers must follow them into the likes of MySpace, Facebook, etc. Yet social networking sites can present unique challenges to marketers who are concerned with the quality and appropriateness of unedited and unfiltered content. Further, consumers may look askance at advertisers interrupting conversations with friends. The formula for creating effective marketing plans using social networking sites is still in its earliest stages. Listed below are the distinguished panel of speakers: Panelists:MySpace: David Tolkheim, SVP, Client SolutionsEvite: Harry Lin, Senior Vice President and General ManagerMicrosoft: Denis Gaynor, Product ManagerFacebook: Tom Arrix, SVP of AdvertisingJWT: Jason Yoder, SVP Digital Media DirectorModerator:Scott Kelly, Digital Marketing Manager, Ford Motor Company</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>1:00</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adcraft Digital Day With Grady Burnett of Google</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>By now most 313 Digital members know that Google is opening an office in Ann Arbor, and that this is a really big deal, eventually planned to employ around 1,000 people. Now here's your chance to get the straight scoop from the head Googler himself, University of Michigan graduate Grady Burnett (he also has an MBA from Harvard), who has returned to Michigan to head up Online Sales and Operations for the new Google office in A2, and who will headline 313 Digital Day, presented in cooperation with Adcraft.</p><p> Burnett is responsible for hiring, customer service, account management and sales efforts supporting the Google AdWords advertising program. (If you're not sure what that is, you definitely need to be there.) Prior to building this office, he managed the national agency team at Google headquarters in Mountain View, California, which oversees Google's relationships with advertising agencies, search engine marketing consultancies and resellers. He was also a professional tennis player for three years!</p><p>Burnett's presentation will include details about what Google is going to be doing in Michigan, and should be of great interest not only to interactive folks, but to everybody in the advertising field in Detroit who wants to learn more about the newest frontier in advertising and marketing.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 12:21:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/portagemedia/grady-audio.mp3" length="28372252" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adcraft-digital-day-with-grady-burnett-of-google</guid>
      <itunes:subtitle>Adcraft Digital Day with Grady Burnett, Head of Online Sales and Operations, Google - Ann Arbor</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>By now most 313 Digital members know that Google is opening an office in Ann Arbor, and that this is a really big deal, eventually planned to employ around 1,000 people. Now here&apos;s your chance to get the straight scoop from the head Googler himself, University of Michigan graduate Grady Burnett (he also has an MBA from Harvard), who has returned to Michigan to head up Online Sales and Operations for the new Google office in A2, and who will headline 313 Digital Day, presented in cooperation with Adcraft.

 Burnett is responsible for hiring, customer service, account management and sales efforts supporting the Google AdWords advertising program. (If you&apos;re not sure what that is, you definitely need to be there.) Prior to building this office, he managed the national agency team at Google headquarters in Mountain View, California, which oversees Google&apos;s relationships with advertising agencies, search engine marketing consultancies and resellers. He was also a professional tennis player for three years!

Burnett&apos;s presentation will include details about what Google is going to be doing in Michigan, and should be of great interest not only to interactive folks, but to everybody in the advertising field in Detroit who wants to learn more about the newest frontier in advertising and marketing.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>58:54</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrossMedia Advertising: Planning, Buying and Measuring presented by Dynamic Logic, Forbes.com, 313Digital and the Adcraft Club of Detroit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CrossMedia Advertising: Planning, Buying and Measuring" presented by 313Digital, Adcraft of Detroit, Dynamic Logic and Forbes.com In the ever-changing media environment, marketers must work to develop cross-media advertising that effectively reaches their target. This breakfast discussion explored new developments and existing challenges in cross-media advertising with industry experts. This "both sides of the table" panel will offer perspectives from advertisers and media companies who are offering integrated solutions to marketers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2006 22:05:56 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/portagemedia/313D_Crossmedia.mp3" length="41457664" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">crossmedia-advertising-planning-buying-and-measu</guid>
      <itunes:subtitle>&quot;CrossMedia Advertising: Planning, Buying and Measuring&quot; presented by 313Digital, Adcraft of Detroit, Dynamic Logic and Forbes.com</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>&quot;CrossMedia Advertising: Planning, Buying and Measuring&quot; presented by 313Digital, Adcraft of Detroit, Dynamic Logic and Forbes.com


In the ever-changing media environment, marketers must work to develop cross-media advertising that effectively reaches their target. This breakfast discussion explored new developments and existing challenges in cross-media advertising with industry experts. This &quot;both sides of the table&quot; panel will offer perspectives from advertisers and media companies who are offering integrated solutions to marketers. 

The Moderator &amp; PanelistsModerator: Nick NyhanCEO, Dynamic Logic and Managing Director, Millward Brown&apos;s Futures GroupBuy Side:Lori Collins SVP, Group Director, Dodge National Planning, PHD Detroit O. Andrew JungSr. Director, Advertising and Media, Kellogg North America Chris SchembriSVP Media Planning &amp; Partnerships, Discovery Networks Sell Side:Julie Fuoti Executive Director, Meredith 360, Meredith Corporation Peter Naylor SVP, NBCU Digital Media Sales, NBC UniversalLinda Perry-Lube Automotive Category Development Director, Microsoft Digital Advertising Solutions </itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>1:26:00</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Automotive Shopper &amp; The Automotive Advertiser: Creating the Best Experience for Each</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Third-Party automotive research sites are constantly challenged with creating the most intuitive and informative user experience for their customers. They also must cater to the needs of their advertisers, their primary source of income, to ensure that they are obtaining the most favorable positioning and prime opportunity to communicate its message to the site visitors.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2006 21:25:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/portagemedia/313D_Baldwin_Aug_06.mp3" length="28483584" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">testing</guid>
      <itunes:subtitle>Third-Party automotive research sites are challenged with creating the most intuitive and informative user experience for their customers.  How do they deal with these challenges?  Listen and find out.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>The Program
Third Party automotive research sites are constantly challenged with creating the most intuitive and informative user experience for their customers. They also must cater to the needs of their advertisers, their primary source of income, to ensure that they are obtaining the most favorable positioning and prime opportunity to communicate its message to the site visitors.

The Moderator &amp; PanelistsModerator: Dennis Galbraith, Sr. Director of Digital Marketing, J.D. Power &amp; AssociatesDennis Galbraith is the Practice Leader for Digital Marketing within the Automotive section at J.D. Power and Associates. He is responsible for the firm&apos;s studies, consulting and publications regarding online and other digital marketing. Mitch Lowe, CEO, Jumpstart AutomotiveAs CEO, Mitch Lowe is responsible for the Company&apos;s overall direction, strategy and execution. He brings to the role more than ten years experience in the Internet, interactive media, direct marketing, strategic development and corporate finance. Robin Cooper, VP Advertising and Business Development, KBB.comAs Vice President, Robin Cooper is responsible for all OEM business relationships with Kelley Blue Book, including all national and regional advertising, lead generation and business development.Jennifer Dulski, General Manager, Yahoo! Autos As General Manager of the Autos business, Jennifer Dulski oversees a team dedicated to offering the best consumer automotive experience on the Web. She is responsible for the overall strategyand P&amp;L of Yahoo! Autos and leads a team that manages product development, business relationships, content, design, implementation and marketing for the Autos property.Chip Perry, CEO, AutoTrader.comChip Perry is responsible for the overall business and operations of AutoTrader.com. Perry, who was the first employee hired by Manheim Auctions in August 1997 when the company was named AutoConnect, laid the foundation of what is today the world&apos;s largest used car marketplace. Scott M. Kelly, Digital Marketing Manager, Ford Motor CompanyScott Kelly is the Ford Motor Company digital marketing manager for Lincoln Mercury. In this role Scott is responsible for all interactive communications for the Lincoln and Mercury brands including the brand websites, online media, search marketing, analytics and digital marketing strategy. </itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>59:20</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adcraft Digital Day Event, Sponsored by 313 Digital</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Keynote Speaker Ted Leonsis, Vice Chairman of AOL & President of the AOL Audience Business talks about how "Shift Happens."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2006 00:14:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/portagemedia/313_Digital_Day.mp3" length="27180971" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adcraft-digital-day-event-sponsored-by-313-digital</guid>
      <itunes:subtitle>Keynote Speaker Ted Leonsis, Vice Chairman of AOL and President of the AOL Audience Business talks about how &quot;Shift Happens.&quot;</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Keynote Speaker Ted Leonsis, Vice Chairman of AOL and President of the AOL Audience Business talks about how &quot;Shift Happens.&quot;</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>56:37</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>