<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

<channel>

<title>PBXCompare RSS Channel</title>

<link>http://www.pbxcompare.com</link>

<description>The PBXCompare RSS Channel includes news and other information about PBX software services
and related topics.  PBXCompare.com was created to consolidate and organize information about the top providers
of PBX software services so that you can make an "apples to apples" comparison of the different service providers and select
the one that best fits your needs.</description>

<image>
<url>http://www.pbxcompare.com/images/pbxcompare_logo.jpg</url>
<title>PBXCompare RSS Channel</title>
<link>http://www.pbxcompare.com</link>
</image>

<item>
<title>PBXCompare.com Research Team Tests and Compares Top Business VoIP Providers</title>
<link>http://www.pbxcompare.com/news_pbxcompare-research-team-tests-and-compares-top-business-voip-providers</link>
<description>PBXCompare.com, a comparison and review website for hosted PBX services, is in the process of expanding its reviews to include comparisons among the top four business VoIP providers, in addition to its reviews of top hosted PBX providers. The website also features new additions to the hosted PBX comparison charts on the home page.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2008 08:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.pbxcompare.com/news_pbxcompare-research-team-tests-and-compares-top-business-voip-providers</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>PBXCompare.com Launches Business VoIP Page for Businesses Wanting to Reduce Start-up Costs</title>
<link>http://www.pbxcompare.com/news_pbxcompare-launches-business-voip-page-for-businesses-wanting-to-reduce-start-up-costs</link>
<description>PBXCompare.com, a comparison and review web site for virtual PBX systems, has just launched a new page that offers in-depth comparisons between increasingly popular business VoIP systems and traditional business phone systems.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2008 08:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.pbxcompare.com/news_pbxcompare-launches-business-voip-page-for-businesses-wanting-to-reduce-start-up-costs</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ring, Ring, It's Fring: VoIP on iPhone</title>
<link>http://www.pbxcompare.com/news_iphone.php</link>
<description>A new application for the iPhone is turning your cellular phone into a fully functioning handheld computer. Now you can make calls using an internet connection instead of your paid minutes.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 08:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.pbxcompare.com/news_iphone.php</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Zilker Ventures, LLC Interviews Jay Blazensky of RingCentral</title>
<link>http://www.pbxcompare.com/rss/Interview%20FINAL%20(27).mp3</link>
<description>Gaines Kilpatrick of Zilker Ventures, LLC recently sat down with Jay Blazensky, V.P. of Business Development
for RingCentral. </description>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 08:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.pbxcompare.com/rss/Interview%20FINAL%20(27).mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>PBXCompare.com Expands to Cater to Wider Range of Customers</title>
<link>http://www.pbxcompare.com/news_expansion.php</link>
<description>PBXCompare.com expands to allow consumers to view PBX providers in order of their affordability, popularity and corporate system plans.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 08:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.pbxcompare.com/news_expansion.php</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Zilker Ventures, LLC Announces the Launch of PBXCompare.com</title>
<link>http://www.pbxcompare.com/news_launch.php</link>
<description>The Virtual Office was once just a buzzword for the future of business. Now it's a reality. Services like online fax services give people the ability to fax without hardware, software or supplies. Similarly, PBXCompare.com allows business owners to set up an office phone system without the use of hardware and phone lines and to conveniently route calls to mobile phones or home offices.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 08:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.pbxcompare.com/news_launch.php</guid>
</item>

<atom:link href="http://www.pbxcompare.com/rss/rssfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />


</channel>
</rss>

