<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  
  <channel>
      <title>The Reasoning Show</title>
    <description>Discussions of pure reasoning aimed at the very heart of matters.</description>
    <link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2007 David Quinn</copyright>
    <webMaster>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</webMaster>
      <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Discussions of pure reasoning aimed at the very heart of matters.</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>Discussions of pure reasoning aimed at the very heart of matters.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:owner>
  <itunes:name>David Quinn</itunes:name> 
  <itunes:email>davidquinn000@optusnet.com.au</itunes:email> 
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
  <itunes:category text="Philosophy" /> 
  </itunes:category>
    <item>
<title>The Nature of Knowledge</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show1.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast01.mp3</guid>
<description>This podcast explores the differences between the logical and empirical approach to gaining knowledge of the nature of our world and the kinds of knowledge to which both approaches is best suited.  Contributors also debate the idea that Truth is achievable, that absolute forms of knowledge exist and the importance of language in the construction of concepts relating to the nature of Reality.</description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast01.mp3" length="58781195" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>This podcast explores the differences between the logical and empirical approach to gaining knowledge of the nature of our world.</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>This podcast explores the differences between the logical and empirical approach to gaining knowledge of the nature of our world.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>01:05:00</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>
<item>
<title>Consciousness and the Tao</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show2.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast02.mp3</guid>
<description>This show deals with the essential nature of the Tao, the "Way" and the role of consciousness in knowing and following the Tao.</description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast02.mp3" length="51928839" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>This show deals with the essential nature of the Tao, the "Way" and the role of consciousness in knowing and following the Tao.</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>This show deals with the essential nature of the Tao, the "Way" and the role of consciousness in knowing and following the Tao.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>01:05:30</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>
<item>
<title>Tibetan Buddhism</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show3.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast03.mp3</guid>
<description>In this episode hosts David Quinn, Kevin Solway and guest Dr Alexander Berzin discuss the concept of enlightenment, the student-teacher relationship, real Buddhism v fake Buddhism, the role and significance of the Dalai Lama, reincarnation and try to come to grips with the deluded nature of modern Western Buddhism.</description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast03.mp3" length="58781190" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>In this episode hosts David Quinn, Kevin Solway and guest Dr Alexander Berzin discuss the concept of enlightenment.</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>In this episode hosts David Quinn, Kevin Solway and guest Dr Alexander Berzin discuss the concept of enlightenment.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>01:05:00</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>
<item>
<title>Truth and Humanity</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show4.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast04.mp3</guid>
<description>In this show, the seemingly indefatigable Susan Blackmore and hosts David Quinn and Dan Rowden try to come to grips with issues as diverse yet integrated as mystical experiences, memes, free will, consciousness and how truth can become integrated into the nature of what we are as humans.   In a wide ranging and stimulating discussion other subjects touched upon include reincarnation, the illusory nature of the self and what it's like to get beyond such an illusion, emotional attachments, cognitive dissonance, life and death and the nature of modern academic life.  A must listen addition to the Reasoning Show portfolio!</description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast04.mp3" length="53803073" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>In this show Susan Blackmore and hosts David Quinn and Dan Rowden try to come to grips with issues as diverse yet integrated as mystical experiences, memes, free will, consciousness and how truth.</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>In this show Susan Blackmore and hosts David Quinn and Dan Rowden try to come to grips with issues as diverse yet integrated as mystical experiences, memes, free will, consciousness and how truth.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>01:05:00</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>
<item>
<title>Fundamentalism and Fear</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show5.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast05.mp3</guid>
<description>In this installment the issue at hand is fundamentalism, its nature, its causes, its apparent increasing global reality, its anti-science and anti-reason mindset and the cultural nuances therein, and also the question of whether fundamentalism is actually far more wide-spread in human society than we might imagine and if it's really only just simmering under the surface waiting for the right conditions to emerge.  The discussion expands into the overall role and nature - for better or for worse - of religion in human culture.  Plus other themes relating to how best to improve the lot of humanity and how to avoid potential disaster.</description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast05.mp3" length="49998181" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>In this installment the issue at hand is fundamentalism, its nature, its causes, its apparent increasing global reality, its anti-science and anti-reason mindset.</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>In this installment the issue at hand is fundamentalism, its nature, its causes, its apparent increasing global reality, its anti-science and anti-reason mindset.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>01:05:00</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>
<item>
<title>The Purpose of Gurus</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show6.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast06.mp3</guid>
<description>This episode we take a peek under the robes of gurus and find some things we'd rather have not.  David Quinn, Dan Rowden and guest Philip Mistlberger go undercover the find out what guru fever is really all about.  We ask if teachers are necessary to provide guidance on the spiritual path.  We explore the nature of the teacher-student relationship, its benefits and pitfalls.  We also delve into aspects of the spiritual path itself and discuss the nature of ultimate reality.  </description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast06.mp3" length="58598214" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>This episode we take a peek under the robes of gurus and find some things we'd rather have not.  David Quinn, Dan Rowden and guest Philip Mistlberger go undercover the find out what guru fever is really all about.</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>This episode we take a peek under the robes of gurus and find some things we'd rather have not.  David Quinn, Dan Rowden and guest Philip Mistlberger go undercover the find out what guru fever is really all about.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>01:20:00</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>
<item>
<title>Physics and Causation</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show7.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast07.mp3</guid>
<description>In this edition we tackle the issue of causation and what it means both in a logical and an empirical sense, how it relates to the work being done in Quantum Physics and its implications in a broader, metaphysical context.    The show also looks at modern cosmology, the origins of the Universe, the field of physics itself, and questions the arrogance of some of its purveyors.  Hosts Kevin Solway and David Quinn also take a brief look at the Templeton Foundation, the prizes it awards and its underlying motives.</description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast07.mp3" length="47064421" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>In this edition we tackle the issue of causation and what it means both in a logical and an empirical sense, how it relates to the work being done in Quantum Physics and its implications in a broader, metaphysical context.</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>In this edition we tackle the issue of causation and what it means both in a logical and an empirical sense, how it relates to the work being done in Quantum Physics and its implications in a broader, metaphysical context.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>01:10:00</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>
<item>
<title>Christian Faith and Logic</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show8.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast08.mp3</guid>
<description>This show we deal with some classic themes and issues in Christian theology as well as some matters less orthodox.  We talk about how to establish credibility and divine inspiration in scripture, the existence of God, the nature and origins of logic, during which guest Matthew Slick offers a somewhat unique argument for the necessity of God's existence.  We also deal with matters of the nature of existence and the universe, consciousness and how to begin to select one religion from another in one's search for truth and spiritual substance.  A lively and fluid discussion!</description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast08.mp3" length="64248813" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>This show we deal with some classic themes and issues in Christian theology as well as some matters less orthodox.</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>This show we deal with some classic themes and issues in Christian theology as well as some matters less orthodox.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>01:30:00</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>
<item>
<title>The Skeptical Mind</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show9.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast09.mp3</guid>
<description>In this edition of the Reasoning Show we explore the nature of the skeptical mind, walk the high wire of doubt and examine the difference between illusion and delusion.   In his own inimitable style, Randi discusses self-delusion, credulity, the nature of science, the importance of doubt and evidence and more!  Arch nemesis to the self-styled psychic guru, Uri Geller, Randi is as sharp and pointed in his criticism as ever.  Get your copy of this show now, before it disappears!</description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast09.mp3" length="37562537" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>In this edition of the Reasoning Show we explore the nature of the skeptical mind, walk the high wire of doubt and examine the difference between illusion and delusion.</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>In this edition of the Reasoning Show we explore the nature of the skeptical mind, walk the high wire of doubt and examine the difference between illusion and delusion.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>01:05:00</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>
<item>
<title>The World of Woman</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show10.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast10.mp3</guid>
<description>In what will prove to be the Reasoning Show's most controversial production to date, host Dan Rowden and guests Rich Zubaty and Sue Hindmarsh walk the oily tightrope of the issue of Feminism and attempt to stride the gaping chasm of Woman without losing their footing and falling in headlong.    In this episode we look at the politics, psychology and spirituality of the feminist movement and the female nature per se.  Has feminism damaged or improved society and women's place in it?  Have men be falsely demonised so as to facilitate feminist demands?  Are women conscious of the dynamics involved?  You be the judge.</description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast10.mp3" length="68128810" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>In what will prove to be the Reasoning Show's most controversial production to date, host Dan Rowden and guests Rich Zubaty and Sue Hindmarsh walk the oily tightrope of the issue of Feminism.</itunes:subtitle>
  <itunes:summary>In what will prove to be the Reasoning Show's most controversial production to date, host Dan Rowden and guests Rich Zubaty and Sue Hindmarsh walk the oily tightrope of the issue of Feminism.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>01:35:00</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>
<item>
<title>Facing the Future</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show11.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast11.mp3</guid>
<description>In this edition of The Reasoning Show we're going to attempt to come to grips with something thing that most people think about from time to time, if only in limited ways and if only when it slaps them in the face: namely, the FUTURE. In the coming years and next few decades, the world as we know it will change significantly. Life spans will increase substantially. Our senses and cognitive faculties will be enhanced. We'll have greater control over most aspects of our minds. The limits of the human body will be transcended as technologies such as artificial intelligence, nanotechnology and genetic engineering converge and accelerate. With them, we will redesign ourselves and force a new paradigm of thinking with regards to who and what we are as persons and as a species. This future presents us multifarious and profound issues to grapple with and questions to be addressed, the most salient of which may well prove to be: "are we ready for or capable of dealing with this future?"!   </description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast11.mp3" length="57384147" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>In this edition we attempt to come to grips with something thing that most people think about from time to time, if only in limited ways and if only when it slaps them in the face: namely, the FUTURE.</itunes:subtitle>
  <itunes:summary>In this edition we attempt to come to grips with something thing that most people think about from time to time, if only in limited ways and if only when it slaps them in the face: namely, the FUTURE. </itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>01:20:00</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>
<item>
<title>Mystical Christianity</title>
<link>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/show12.htm</link>
<guid>http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast12.mp3</guid>
<description>In this show, host Kevin Solway and guest Father Peter Bowes explore a very broad range of matters from the nature of God and its consciousness, the self, reincarnation, the soul and the nature of good and evil, to marriage and relationships, women and the spiritual path, and the nature and status of Jesus.   Father Peter brings his own Gnostic perspectives - unconventional by mainstream Christian standards  - to each of these issues.   This show will appeal to those with Christian sympathies but who also have a distaste for the spiritual rigidity of typical Christian churches.</description>
<enclosure url="http://geniusrealms.com/reasoningshow/podcast12.mp3" length="35475772" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
  <itunes:author>danrowden@geniusrealms.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit> 
  <itunes:subtitle>In this show we explore a very broad range of matters from the nature of God and its consciousness, the self, reincarnation, the soul and the nature of good and evil, to marriage and relationships and more.</itunes:subtitle>
  <itunes:summary>In this show we explore a very broad range of matters from the nature of God and its consciousness, the self, reincarnation, the soul and the nature of good and evil, to marriage and relationships and more.</itunes:summary> 
  <itunes:duration>00:50:00</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>reasoning, genius, philosophy</itunes:keywords> 
</item>

</channel>
</rss>