<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.beststuff.com"  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
 <title>BestStuff - Podcast</title>
 <link>http://www.beststuff.com/taxonomy/term/10577/0</link>
 <description>Bill Butler and Tim Moses discuss and review new gadgets, other electronic goodies and new technologies. BestStuff.com is a network of nationally recognized reporters, authors, and industry experts, dedicated to covering the world of everything new.</description>
 <language>en</language>
<item>
 <title>Best Podcast Episode 2: Mobile Roundup</title>
 <link>http://www.beststuff.com/categories/podcast/best-podcast-episode-2.html</link>
 <description>&lt;!-- google_ad_section_start --&gt;&lt;p&gt; BestStuff.com PodCast: Mobile Roundup hosted by Bill Butler and Tim Moses. This PodCast emphasizes mobile phones and how we use the technology to make our lives easier. In this segment they address some of the issues consumers may have with syncing their phones with their Mac and PC’s. Bill and Tim cover their initial impression of the phones they reviewed, and what they wish the manufacturers should add to make the phones more functional. Their suggestions and tips may provide more insight into synchronizing the phones reviewed with various computer platforms. In addition to how much they enjoy NVDO.
&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt; The products covered in this segment are: Treo 650, Blackberry 8700, Samsung A920, Motorola Pebble, Panasonic BLC30 Wireless Camera, Shure i4c Headphones and myrateplan.com. 
&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;!--break--&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;BestStuff Podcast Episode 2&quot; href=&quot;http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE002.mp3&quot;&gt; 
  &lt;img alt=&quot;Get This BestStuff Podcast Episode&quot; src=&quot;http://www.beststuff.com/images/feeds/getepisode.gif&quot; align=&quot;bottom&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; hspace=&quot;0&quot; vspace=&quot;0&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
  &lt;br /&gt; &lt;a title=&quot;Inaugural BestStuff Podcast&quot; href=&quot;http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE002.mp3&quot;&gt; Download episode&lt;/a&gt; 
  &lt;br /&gt; 
  &lt;object classid=&quot;clsid:d27cdb6e-ae6d-11cf-96b8-444553540000&quot; codebase=&quot;http://fpdownload.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=7,0,0,0&quot; id=&quot;xspf_player&quot; align=&quot;middle&quot; height=&quot;15&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt; 
    &lt;param name=&quot;allowScriptAccess&quot; value=&quot;sameDomain&quot; /&gt; 
    &lt;param name=&quot;movie&quot; value=&quot;http://www.beststuff.com/scripts/xspf/slim/xspf_player_slim.swf?song_url=http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE002.mp3&amp;amp;ampsong_title=BestStuff%20Podcast&quot; /&gt; 
    &lt;param name=&quot;quality&quot; value=&quot;high&quot; /&gt; 
    &lt;param name=&quot;bgcolor&quot; value=&quot;#e6e6e6&quot; /&gt; 
    &lt;param name=&quot;player_title&quot; value=&quot;BestStuff Podcast - Click to Listen&quot; /&gt; 
    &lt;param name=&quot;song_title&quot; value=&quot;Premier Podcast&quot; /&gt; 
    &lt;embed src=&quot;http://www.beststuff.com/scripts/xspf/slim/xspf_player_slim.swf?song_url=http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE002.mp3&amp;amp;ampsong_title=BestStuff%20Podcast&quot; quality=&quot;high&quot; bgcolor=&quot;#e6e6e6&quot; name=&quot;xspf_player&quot; allowscriptaccess=&quot;sameDomain&quot; type=&quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot; pluginspage=&quot;http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer&quot; align=&quot;middle&quot; height=&quot;15&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; /&gt; 
  &lt;/object&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt; &lt;a target=&quot;_new&quot; href=&quot;http://www.podtrac.com/audience/start-survey.aspx?ver=1&amp;amp;pid=-73MSPMHvdY$&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://www.beststuff.com/images/podtrac_survey_120x120_v2.gif&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; height=&quot;120&quot; width=&quot;120&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt; Mobile Roundup &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;
    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt;  &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt;  Best Stuff podcast, May 12, 2006.     &lt;br&gt;     &lt;br&gt;     &lt;br&gt;  [Music]     &lt;br&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Welcome to the Best Stuff podcast. I&#039;m Bill Butler.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; And I&#039;m Tim Moses. Each month we&#039;ll discuss and recommend some of the best items in today&#039;s marketplace.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; This week, we&#039;ll discuss a variety of mobile devices.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; So, sit back and relax for the next half hour with the Best Stuff podcast.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;


             &lt;!--pagebreak--&gt;

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; All right. Well, it was pretty much gadget week. Tim and I got to play with all kinds of cool phones. We had headphones, we had wireless cameras.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; The first thing I&#039;m going to cover is the thing that I spent the most time with, and really liked. I have to start out by confessing that I am a Treo user - I love the Treos - I had the 300, I have the 600 right now, and I got to play around with the 650. Each one has been a huge leap over the past one. But, I guess before going into the specifics about the 650, I should just say what I like in general about the Treos. The big thing is just having a full keyboard. Unfortunately, I was not born at the right time to grow up with typing out text messages on a regular phone keypad. I may have just passed that by entirely; I don&#039;t know if I&#039;ll ever catch up with that.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; I think the cut-off on that is probably 1990.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Yes. So I&#039;m way off from that. But I love having a full keyboard; checking email from the phone, sending text messages, things like that. I don&#039;t want to sit there trying to figure out a keypad, I want something that works and works fast because I want to be able to type pretty fast. The Treo keyboards have all been pretty good; I can type with two thumbs and do that at a pretty good rate. Aside from that, you have the Palm software; you can do a lot of stuff with the phone, and at different times I&#039;ve done a lot of different things with it. There&#039;s more software out there for Palm than for any other mobile device, even Windows CE. It&#039;s just, by far, more stuff available. But, to get into the 650 itself, the cool thing the 650 has that past Treos didn&#039;t is Bluetooth. Bluetooth works very well; I also am a Mac user, so being able to sync the phone with my Mac has been a big deal. Plus, the synching; normally with these phones you get the Palm desktop software, which is free and does the basics, but if you really want to have all the slick features, there&#039;s a separate product out there called Missing Sync for the Mac. The product is specifically for Treos, I guess they have a version for Windows CE devices.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Is that the Mark/Space product?     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Yes, Mark/Space. It&#039;s just such slick software, it does everything. It syncs iPhoto, it syncs any of the photos you take on the camera with iPhoto, and sends photos back. It syncs with iTunes to the player on the phone. It syncs with iCal, your calendar, address book and each one of those, there&#039;s so many different options. You can pick your playlist, pick your albums, and there&#039;s so many different options for going back and forth between them. That&#039;s true on any of the Treos, but with the 650, you now do it wirelessly. So, that&#039;s pretty cool. The other thing, the camera is a little bit better on the 650 than the 600. If under a lot of light, I still get about the same quality pictures, but in lower light, it does just so much better than the 600 did. It has video recording built in, and the video is actually pretty decent. It&#039;s not too much worse than the still camera I have, a Sony Cybershot that does video, and it actually does pretty decent video for being a phone.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; The number of colors on the screen is incredible too.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Yes, that&#039;s true. It&#039;s twice the resolution of the older screen, so it looks great.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; In addition to resolution though, it&#039;s color depth, the number of pixels it can display, I think the gradient of pixels it can display is greater as well.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; I have no idea. I wasn&#039;t even thinking about it, the resolution just made it look so much better.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; I don&#039;t know if you noticed, but when you have the keypad up, the standard default keypad for typing in a phone number, there&#039;s actually gradients on the buttons.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Oh, yes.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; So you can see that they&#039;ve added thousands of colors, instead of 256 colors on the previous. I didn&#039;t see the specs on that.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Maybe so, hold the 600 next to the 650 and there&#039;s an unmistakable difference. It looks so much slicker. Even though you&#039;re running the same software, it just looks so much better. The phone that I&#039;ve been using has Versamail on it. I had Versamail on the 600; I think it may be included with the 650. Versamail is just a really slick email client; it will do IMAP and POP and has a ton of features. The great thing is, I keep lots of folders in my IMAP account and I&#039;m able to get to everything from that program, so email wise, it works very well for me. In fact, the only complaints I could bring up about the 650 would be, it doesn&#039;t support e-video through Sprint, so I don&#039;t get the high speed access. I guess I could always wish for it to be a little smaller, too.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Well, they do have a version through Cingular that does support Edge, so if someone really wanted that high speed functionality, the Edge network is kind of the complementary high speed network on the Cingular side. So they could opt for a different provider, I suppose.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Who knows, maybe with the 700 they&#039;ll have Edge in there as well, if you&#039;re not on T-Mobile. Anyway, I&#039;ve been very happy with it, and I wish I could keep this one and replace my 600.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             &lt;!--pagebreak--&gt;

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Well, I guess you have to talk to Jeff about that. I&#039;m going to review the Blackberry 8700, so this is the arch nemesis of the Treo product line. Blackberrys are most notably in the PC realm; they&#039;re typically dealt with for enterprise type applications, and they excel at push email and synching calendar, all within the confines of, like, Outlook. All within the confines of kind of the standard business mantra, and I&#039;m kind of trying to use mine in a bit more of an open source sort of a way. What I&#039;ve found is that it can be done but there aren&#039;t as many applications, there isn&#039;t as much support as there is for Palm, as Tim said. Everything that you do with the Blackberry right now, as far as the Mac goes, is a little tricky. Although, I&#039;ve got to give credit to the Blackberry folks because there&#039;s a product that used to be a pay product called Pocket Mac, and apparently Blackberry is allowing, I don&#039;t know if there is a monetary exchange going on there or not, but I can download Pocket Mac for free and I can sync everything I want to for free. I can sync my iCal without problems, I can sync my contacts, which is the other main thing. It cannot sync email across it, but contacts are the largest thing anyway because if I have 600 contacts, entering those in the phone can be tedious otherwise. I can edit my contacts on the phone and when I do the sync, it syncs it back into my address book.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Let&#039;s see, just going down the list: it has excellent battery life. I&#039;ve been very happy with that. They advertise four hours of talk time; I would say it&#039;s probably more. I haven&#039;t actually done the test but I talk a ton on my phone every day and I&#039;ve never had a situation where I&#039;ve been a quarter or even a third of the used battery life in a day. And they have an advertised ten day standby time on the battery, which is pretty incredible as well.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Bluetooth connectivity; it does connect via Bluetooth to my laptop and it does sync my contacts across Bluetooth. Edge network capability as well; this is an amazing thing. It is on the high speed Edge network, it also has a Google map program you can download for it, so the same things that work on the Samsung, which we&#039;ll be talking about later, the Google map and direction finding functionality is beautiful, especially with the large screen.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Now on the PC, you can use this device as a modem. There&#039;s an independent 3rd party company called MobiShark,

        &lt;a href=&quot;http://mobishark.com/&quot;&gt; mobishark.com &lt;/a&gt;

    , and you install that software on your PC and it can make a connection to the Blackberry and the Blackberry acts across that high speed Edge network. You don&#039;t have to have another provider, it just uses the existing data service that you have with your provider. It lets your PC surf the web across this device. So, Bluetooth to the Blackberry and then Edge and out from there. I have not used that so I can&#039;t vouch for it, but I&#039;ve read a number of reviews online and people seem very happy with it.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; As far as the synching, I may have misspoken earlier. I think that I actually, when I&#039;ve synched this, I&#039;ve synched it over my USB cable. Bluetooth, I have not been able to actually sync anything across that yet, but, I can form the connection. At this point, I&#039;ve put in a lot of requests to Blackberry to see what we can do about improving things for Mac users. From a PC standpoint, and if you&#039;re getting it for your business, it&#039;s an incredible tool for push and pull email. I&#039;ve got to say their IMAP functionality on the Mac needs a little bit of work. When I receive an email on the Blackberry, if I delete it on the Blackberry, it deletes it on my inbox, like I would expect for IMAP. But if I delete it from the inbox on my PC or on my Mac, it doesn&#039;t delete it from the inbox.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Oh, even the next time you sync up and check mail?     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Right.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Oh, that&#039;s weird.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; So, something&#039;s strange with the way Blackberry handles IMAP pushes and pulls, but I&#039;m sure that will be resolved at some time in the future.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             &lt;!--pagebreak--&gt;

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Not having used a Blackberry and having used a Treo all this time, I always look at the Treo as being chock full of features, everything works great for the Mac. Is there also a price difference, because the Treos are pricey?     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; These are pricey too, but I don&#039;t think quite as pricey as the Treo. This, with the rebates, is about $300.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Oh, okay, that&#039;s about the same.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; The Treo 650 might be coming in close, what&#039;s that, $450?     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; I think it&#039;s $300 with the rebates, around that.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Okay, so fairly similar. I think if you live and die by getting emails instantaneously, this is probably the choice, the Blackberry is probably the choice. If you can wait fifteen minutes to get your emails, then I think having a standard IMAP client on the Palm is probably the better choice. Or I could also say, if you&#039;re more of a Mac user than a PC user, the Palm is probably the better choice.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; That&#039;s interesting.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Whereas if you&#039;re a corporate enterprise PC user, the Palm doesn&#039;t really touch the Blackberry in terms of the integration it can offer.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Okay good, thanks. That&#039;s the first time I&#039;ve actually had a decent comparison of the two. I should add that I was able to connect to the internet, albeit slowly, I was able to connect over Bluetooth through Sprint on the Treo 650 from my Mac. It was easy to set up, it really didn&#039;t take much to do.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Cool. I did have one other feature request here, and I imagine on the Treo too, I&#039;m starting to use Google calendar a lot, because I love the interface.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; I think I have an answer for you too. Go ahead.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Oh, really? I want to see Blackberry and Palm and anyone who has a calendar app, offer that additional piece, where you can say publish this calendar to my Google calendar.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Here&#039;s my answer. If you, again, this is is if you&#039;re on a Mac, but you can probably do something similar on a PC, you can subscribe to your Google calendar from iCal and then you can sync your iCal to your phone. That&#039;s a one way calendar, because if you make changes on your phone it&#039;s not going to make it all the way back to Google. But, that does at least get your Google calendar to your phone, and that works pretty easily. So the iCal, you subscribe to your Google calendar, that&#039;s an easy step, and if you&#039;re synching your calendar then that comes across and shows up on your phone.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Yes≈, the only caveat to that is that the Pocket Mac people, the way they&#039;ve done this is anything you enter on your Blackberry actually gets pushed to your iCal, but it doesn&#039;t pull from anywhere. It only pulls and pushes from that Pocket Mac sync category. Little caveat there. I want to see, and it&#039;s a great stopgap measure, but since these devices are wireless and on the internet, I really want to see them talking straight to Google, and ideally talking straight to the same calendar app that my PC, that my Mac is talking to, that my PC might be talking to and all synchronizing to that one central source. But, I&#039;m probably asking too much.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Keep dreaming. Someday.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; We might have to wait a couple years on that request. OkayTim, you&#039;ve got the next one.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; One last thing I was just comparing size here too, because -     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Because size matters.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Because size matters. Got to be careful how I word this, but the Treo is narrower, it&#039;s a little bit taller, it is narrower, but the Blackberry is definitely lighter, too. Kind of weird.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Because it&#039;s plastic.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; About the same thickness. So, if you&#039;re going to pick the two of them up, the Treo has got a nice hefty feel, so if you needed a phone to whack somebody over the head, the Treo would be better. The Blackberry is lighter if you&#039;re, I don&#039;t know, I guess it really wouldn&#039;t matter. Close enough.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Well the screen&#039;s a little wider.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; That&#039;s true, it&#039;s a bigger screen.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; If you like watching widescreen HD movies, which you can&#039;t do on this, but it has a wider screen.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             &lt;!--pagebreak--&gt;

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; All right. I guess that&#039;s beaten that to death. The next product is the Samsung A920, through Sprint, and I had got that the same time I got the Treo 650, so I started playing around with both. You can&#039;t really compare the two, so you really have to -     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; So we&#039;re not going to.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; It&#039;s not a phone that&#039;s in the same range with these other two, but as a regular phone, it&#039;s a pretty impressive phone to look at. When you start it up, you get this full color screen, real nice screen on it. All the icons and the menu are animated; very slick interface on it. Probably the best thing I could say is on a trip to Chattanooga, my eight year old son got a hold of the phone and wouldn&#039;t let go of it. He figured out how to take pictures, take video; he was playing games on it, played with Google maps, and the phone&#039;s using e-video and so the Google maps are coming up fast and it was all I could do to pry that phone out of his hands. He still refers to it as his phone; he&#039;s going to be very sad to see that one go. According to my son, it&#039;s the best phone ever.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; I had the A900, actually, personally, I was using that phone, and the battery life wasn&#039;t quite where I needed to be, but the feature set was really quite incredible. It had voice dialing, it had Bluetooth, it had e-video network, so, all the things I needed. I was actually able to send photos from the phone to my laptop, to my Mac. I was actually also able to send contacts - one by one - I couldn&#039;t actually synchronize contacts but I could send the important contacts without having to re-key them into my phone, which was good too. Samsung probably has to work a little bit on its software for the Mac, I&#039;m not sure about its PC.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; That&#039;s an important thing to note if you&#039;re a Mac user; there is no synching; there is file copying though. Although I wasn&#039;t able to get the 920, I wasn&#039;t able to get the photos off, using Bluetooth or the USB cable.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Which was different from the 900, we just want to clarify that the 900, even though it has a lower number, we believe it is a newer phone, and so we assume that Samsung&#039;s probably added that functionality to the 900. Which is the Razr killer, it&#039;s the very ultra-thin, sort of sexy phone that Samsung has out now. The 920 has better battery life than the 900 by a long shot though, so, if you&#039;re looking for battery life and a good solid phone with a nice interface, I think the 920 is a good choice.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; All right, on to the Motorola Pebl. The Motorola Pebl is probably the kind of, I just imagine like Paris Hilton or someone wearing this phone. It looks like, I described it in one of my blogs, it looks like a pebble you would find -     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; You mean your contact list can be stolen?     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Right. It looks like a little pebble you would find on the bottom of a trout stream or something. It has a very -     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Is that what the name is for?     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; I think so.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Because it does, it&#039;s very rounded.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; It looks like a pebble. I assume they meant to draw that. It took me about a week to figure out how to open the front. It&#039;s extremely easy, but it&#039;s so easy that I couldn&#039;t figure out, it&#039;s kind of like a lot of Mac products out there. You actually slide down with your thumb and it flips open.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Oh, that&#039;s cool.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; It&#039;s got a magnet on the hinge that closes the clamshell, instead of a clip and I guess that clip will never go bad because it&#039;s a magnet, obviously. The good things: it is a cool looking phone, it&#039;s a great conversation piece, I think. The battery life is very good, it&#039;s a cool flip design. It does not have Edge service. From my standpoint and when I review things, when I see a phone this new, my first thought is that it needs to have Edge, it needs to have these higher speed networks, and I assume they&#039;re saving costs by not including them. Motorola does have nice synching features with the Mac and with PCs, but to not have Edge, means that you can&#039;t use it as a high speed modem. It means that if you&#039;re trying to pull up data on the internet, you&#039;re not going to get the speeds. But if your needs are not data oriented, if you just need a cool phone with a reasonably good interface, the Pebl is a sharp phone and it&#039;s a nice statement and it&#039;s got good weight to it.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Yeah, you could whack somebody on the head with this too.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; It does have Bluetooth also, so Bluetooth means that you can easily sync your contacts to it, you could sync your calendar entries to it.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; So what&#039;s the display on the front used for?     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; It&#039;s kind of funny, it&#039;s really down the lines of aesthetics that we&#039;re talking about with this whole phone. It says the time on it, but it breaks it up into, like if it&#039;s 12:24, it puts the 12 on the top and the 24 on the bottom. What I found is that as I looked at that phone, time looks so much more interesting when it&#039;s vertical like that. It&#039;s almost like art, everytime you look to see what time it is, it&#039;s like, oh wow, that&#039;s such a nice looking way to display it. It&#039;s a conversation piece, and a phone that functions really well. We used it on the T-Mobile network the whole time we had it. It&#039;s not one that I would personally use, it doesn&#039;t fit my needs because it doesn&#039;t have a full keyboard and the types of things that I need on a PDA, because I need a PDA phone integrated. The one flaw with it that I found that is kind of an issue with Mac users is if you do sync it up with your Mac, it instead of putting one person with their three contact numbers, it actually enters that person three times. So, it would have multiple entries for the person instead of aggregating the phone numbers. Anyway, that&#039;s the one thing that I think Motorola could, it&#039;s probably a fairly simple fix in the iSync program in the Mac.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Now, normally on this phone, can you give one person multiple phone numbers?     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Yes, you can. It&#039;s built that way.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; You can. Okay. It&#039;s the synching software that&#039;s the problem.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; A minor software fix, I would say.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; It is cool looking, I&#039;ve got to say, and the way it opens is really slick. I wish you hadn&#039;t run the battery all the way out because I want to see what it looks like.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Here&#039;s what I was doing for the first week, I was trying to grab one of these almost nonexistent seams to pull it open.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; It&#039;s definitely well manufactured, and everything about it looks very smooth, fits together very well.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             &lt;!--pagebreak--&gt;

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; I have had the Panasonic BLC30 wireless camera for a while now, and that&#039;s not really a very catchy name for what this thing is. It&#039;s a remote video camera, so you could use it for security, or for keeping up with anything. Cool thing about it is, it has a decent color camera built in, and it has a web server built in, so you can access this camera, see what&#039;s going on on the camera, you can even control pan and tilt on it from a web page. It&#039;s a pretty small camera, it&#039;s about maybe 2 - 2.5 inches wide by 3 - 3.5 inches tall, very small thing. It just works very well. To go into a little more detail, when you get the camera, probably my only complaint about it is that while it&#039;s pretty easy to set up if you have a standard configuration, standard network set up, or you have a standard wireless network set up. It will connect over ethernet, or over wireless, B or G. The only problem is, if you don&#039;t have a standard setup, it can be a hassle to configure. You do have to do that through a web browser on a PC. Once you have it configured, though, you can get to it from any web browser, you can pan and tilt from the web browser, see still shots, see video. It even has some cool extra features like a heat sensor and timers built in, so you can have it automatically send an email when something is triggered.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Does it send an email with a picture, or does it -     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Actually I never sent one of the emails, I was just playing with the web page. Anyway, it&#039;s very slick. They really did a good job. It&#039;s just a nice, complete package. It does what it does very well. It has a lot of features to it. Price points, I just looked up on Amazon; they have it for $260, so it fits in, a little pricier than the super cheap wireless cameras you might get from Exten or someplace like that. But, the fact that it has the web server built in, it&#039;s this all in one product. Once it&#039;s configured you can put it any place you can get a wireless connection. You do have to plug in to power, but you don&#039;t have to have a PC anywhere around to make this thing work. It works entirely on it&#039;s own, which, for $260, is amazing.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Now you said the initial configuration required a PC, but after that, it&#039;s web based?     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; Yeah, so the one thing I&#039;d say, I don&#039;t see that as a barrier to getting it, even if you&#039;re on a Mac. It&#039;s really a one time thing; once you configure it, you&#039;re set. So you might need to get to a PC that first time, and that&#039;s something to keep in mind if you are going to drive out 100 miles to set it up some place without a PC, it&#039;s probably not a good idea. But, when you look at other cameras with these same kind of features, you&#039;re really looking at cameras that are several hundred dollars or more, and to have some $260 device that gives decent 640x480 video, works in pretty low light and gives you a great picture, I think it&#039;s really hard to beat.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Okay, so that&#039;s the Panasonic BLC30. Great, well, I&#039;m going to talk about these Shure headphones. It&#039;s the Shure I4C and the main purpose behind these headphones is to allow you to have your cell phone plugged in at the same time you have, say, your iPod. So, it&#039;s got two cords coming out, one with a mini plug for a phone and one with a mini plug for an iPod, and then it has a switch on it. You can just toggle the switch between telephone and music. It&#039;s a great concept, and the sound was very good on the earbuds. Personally, my ears are too small; I tried all those adapters and I couldn&#039;t quite get them to fit into my ears. My wife used them and she was very impressed with the audio quality, and of course, it&#039;s great to have the switch, to be able to go between your phone and your music device, if the two aren&#039;t integrated, which most aren&#039;t yet. If you have that need, I think it&#039;s a great choice. As a matter of fact, I&#039;m speaking on a Shure SM58 microphone, so we all love Shure products around here.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; The only other thing that we&#039;re going to review today, and it&#039;s not really a review so much as a mention, because I think it really fits in the vein of what we&#039;re talking about, and it&#039;s a site called

        &lt;a href=&quot;http://myrateplan.com/&quot;&gt; myrateplan.com &lt;/a&gt;

    . Basically, if you go to

        &lt;a href=&quot;http://myrateplan.com/&quot;&gt; myrateplan.com &lt;/a&gt;

    you have the ability to look up phones by feature, service plans across various phones and features, everything we&#039;ve talked about today including Bluetooth and Edge and battery life on phones and ability to sync and those types of things. It&#039;s difficult to research every phone and I found that

        &lt;a href=&quot;http://myrateplan.com/&quot;&gt; myrateplan.com &lt;/a&gt;

    was very helpful in order to navigate, in particular they have one area of their site where you can specify I want Bluetooth, I want high speed data connectivity, I want a PDA, and I want the weight to be at this level, all the features you want. You can basically drag the sliders and phones will sort of disappear as they get filtered down to the level that you want to see, and so you can really cull it down to two or three phones that you want to make your final decision on.     &lt;br&gt;     &lt;br&gt;     &lt;br&gt; [Music]     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; Thanks for tuning in to this week&#039;s edition of the Best Stuff podcast.     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_2_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_2&quot;&gt; Tim Moses: &lt;/cite&gt; And be sure to visit

        &lt;a href=&quot;http://beststuff.com/&quot;&gt; beststuff.com &lt;/a&gt;

    . If you&#039;d like to contact us with story ideas or general questions, please email Bill or Tim at

        &lt;a href=&quot;http://beststuff.com/&quot;&gt; beststuff.com &lt;/a&gt;

    .     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;

             

    &lt;blockquote class=&quot;speaker_1_text&quot;&gt; &lt;cite class=&quot;speaker_1&quot;&gt; Bill Butler: &lt;/cite&gt; For Best Stuff, we&#039;re Bill Butler, and Tim Moses. Thanks for listening!     &lt;br&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;!-- google_ad_section_end --&gt;&lt;table id=&quot;attachments&quot; class=&quot;sticky-enabled&quot;&gt;
 &lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;Attachment&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Size&lt;/th&gt; &lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
 &lt;tr class=&quot;odd&quot;&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE002.mp3&quot;&gt;BCPE002.mp3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;13.27 MB&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
 <comments>http://www.beststuff.com/categories/podcast/best-podcast-episode-2.html#comments</comments>
 <category domain="http://www.beststuff.com/taxonomy/term/10577">Podcast</category>
 <enclosure url="http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE002.mp3" length="13919065" type="audio/mpeg" />
 <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2006 15:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>jessica</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">10902 at http://www.beststuff.com</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Best Podcast Number 1</title>
 <link>http://www.beststuff.com/podcast/best-podcast-number-1.html</link>
 <description>&lt;!-- google_ad_section_start --&gt;&lt;p&gt; Inaugural podcast. Download, subscribe, or play the show here.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;!--break--&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;Inaugural BestStuff Podcast&quot; href=&quot;http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE001.mp3&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img alt=&quot;Get This BestStuff Podcast Episode&quot; src=&quot;http://www.beststuff.com/images/feeds/getepisode.gif&quot; align=&quot;bottom&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; hspace=&quot;0&quot; vspace=&quot;0&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a title=&quot;Inaugural BestStuff Podcast&quot; href=&quot;http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE001.mp3&quot;&gt;
Download episode&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;object classid=&quot;clsid:d27cdb6e-ae6d-11cf-96b8-444553540000&quot; codebase=&quot;http://fpdownload.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=7,0,0,0&quot; id=&quot;xspf_player&quot; align=&quot;middle&quot; height=&quot;15&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt;
&lt;param name=&quot;allowScriptAccess&quot; value=&quot;sameDomain&quot;&gt;
&lt;param name=&quot;movie&quot; value=&quot;http://www.beststuff.com/scripts/xspf/slim/xspf_player_slim.swf?song_url=http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE001.mp3&amp;ampsong_title=BestStuff%20Podcast&quot;&gt;
&lt;param name=&quot;quality&quot; value=&quot;high&quot;&gt;
&lt;param name=&quot;bgcolor&quot; value=&quot;#e6e6e6&quot;&gt;
&lt;param name=&quot;player_title&quot; value=&quot;BestStuff Podcast - Click to Listen&quot;&gt;
&lt;param name=&quot;song_title&quot; value=&quot;Premier Podcast&quot;&gt;
&lt;embed src=&quot;http://www.beststuff.com/scripts/xspf/slim/xspf_player_slim.swf?song_url=http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE001.mp3&amp;ampsong_title=BestStuff%20Podcast&quot; quality=&quot;high&quot; bgcolor=&quot;#e6e6e6&quot; name=&quot;xspf_player&quot; allowscriptaccess=&quot;sameDomain&quot; type=&quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot; pluginspage=&quot;http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer&quot; align=&quot;middle&quot; height=&quot;15&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt;
&lt;/object&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a target = &quot;_new&quot; href=&quot;http://www.podtrac.com/audience/start-survey.aspx?ver=1&amp;pid=-73MSPMHvdY$&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/podtrac_survey_120x120_v2.gif&quot; height = &quot;120&quot; width = &quot;120&quot; border = &quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p class=&quot;html-head2&quot; style=&quot;margin: 0in 0in 11pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Best Podcast Number 1&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;
&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; BestStuff Podcast, April 1st, 2006. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[music] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; Welcome to the BestStuff Podcast. I&#039;m Bill Butler. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; And I&#039;m Tim Moses. Each month we&#039;ll discuss and recommend some of the best items in today&#039;s marketplace. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;This week we&#039;ll discuss the best of the new web, also called Web 2.0. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; So sit back and relax for the next half-hour with the BestStuff Podcast. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--pagebreak--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[music] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; All right, well thank you for joining us. This is our first episode of the BestStuff Podcast, and it&#039;s coming to you from &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.BestStuff.com&quot;&gt;BestStuff.com&lt;/a&gt;. You can find all sorts of interesting reviews and data on the best products on the web, and this week Tim and I have decided we&#039;re going to talk about the best websites out on the internet. Since this is our first podcast, we&#039;re still in the process of evaluating different pieces of hardware that we intend will probably be the mainstay of this. But we&#039;re constantly looking at new websites and new ways for people to interact or be more productive in their businesses, and we have some good ideas, things we&#039;d like to share with you. So I&#039;m going to start out with &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.Writely.com&quot;&gt;Writely&lt;/a&gt;. I found out about Writely I guess about three or four months ago. I read a website, a blog basically, called TechCrunch, and it&#039;s pretty good about outlining all the new Web 2.0 players, and Writely really, really stands out. I think it stands out because much like email, where it&#039;s that indispensable office productivity tool, Writely is a substitute for Microsoft Word. It has a good portion of the functionality of Word without a lot of the bloat that you find in some of that software. You&#039;re not installing a program onto your desktop, but instead you&#039;re going to a web page, Writely.com, and you simply sign up with an email address and a password and you have access to pretty extensive features which give you.. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; Spell-checking would be one of those, so if Bill writes how he speaks, that would be useful. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;Yes. Let&#039;s see. The other coolest thing about Writely that I like is that -- and this is a real problem, I think, in larger businesses, and even small companies, but larger businesses to a greater extent -- is when you write something, you try to get other people&#039;s feedback on it or input and perform revisions. While Word has red-lining capabilities, you have to go to the time of saving that document, you have to attach it to an email and send it out to a group of people. Writely eliminates a lot of those extra steps and let&#039;s you share that document on the website with other people. So if I have a document and Tim is interested, and I&#039;m interested in getting his feedback, I can invite him to that document with his email address, and he can simply make the change he wants to make or even offer suggestions.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; The cool part is that you can both be, or any number of people can work on the same document at the same time. So it&#039;s not like in Word where you take it and send it to somebody, wait for them to finish, they send it back. You&#039;re waiting for somebody else to have time to work on something and then send it back, in which case it may be small changes and you can spend a lot of time going back and forth. The cool part is two people could be working on it at once. That&#039;s what I think. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;Yeah, absolutely. And above and beyond that, it has beautiful security built into it as well. Because if I specifically invite someone, they can actually come to it with a secured user name and password. But I can also publish it publicly. Or I can invite five people to actually view the document but not actually give them permissions to make any changes to that document, to maybe get a general impression but not to allow them to physically make changes, which I may not want to lose control over. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; My big question about Writely is, it&#039;s great that you can start from scratch and write something here, but what if you have an existing document? Or what if you need to take it out and send it to somebody who&#039;s not on the internet, if there are any people like that anymore? What options do you have there? 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;Writely&#039;s done a really good job of this. It&#039;s not perfect yet, but it&#039;s awfully good. And it&#039;s better actually -- I&#039;ve downloaded a lot of programs that claim that they&#039;re Microsoft Word substitutes on my Mac, and I&#039;ve got to say it&#039;s probably better than almost any Word emulator out there, except for maybe OpenOffice, which does an awfully good job. So you can take a Word document and you can actually upload it to Writely. It has a very easy interface for doing that, the same way you&#039;re used to uploading pictures or anything like that to the web. And once it comes into Writely, it looks like the Writely document, it&#039;s actually formatted for the most part like your Word document. By the same token, if you finish a Writely document and you have it complete the way you want it, you can either elect to export that document to your local desktop -- so save it locally, and it&#039;ll save it with a .DOC extension or an .RTF if you want rich text, or .PDF even. I think PDFs, if they&#039;re not here yet, it might be a pro version. So it&#039;s very flexible from that standpoint. You can also print directly from the web page. It has a print button, and it does an excellent job of formatting the text the way you see it on screen as the Word document. The other things I think are extremely cool about it is that it&#039;s tag-friendly. For those of you who are not used to the Web 2.0 environment, you know we&#039;re all used to thinking in terms of directories or folders, creating a new folder and dropping documents into it. And while that is helpful, the tag mindset is becoming a little more prevalent on the web. The idea is that if I had something that was a proposal for one of my clients, I could tag it as &quot;proposal&quot; and I could tag it with the client&#039;s name. And that way if I ever decided to come back and wanted to look at all my proposals, I would just choose the tag &quot;proposal&quot; and I would view all my proposals. And if I wanted to actually view a proposal for that particular client, I would choose &quot;proposal&quot; for that client name and would view just those documents. So instead of having to create hierarchies, the tags sort of on the fly create these hierarchical ways of managing your information. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; Which if you&#039;d try to do that with folders, you&#039;d be making multiple folders, making aliases or shortcuts to your documents to put into multiple places. Tagging seems like such a simple way of handling things, but really the flexibility you get out of it is pretty amazing. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; Yeah. And now you have these things called &quot;tag clouds&quot;. If you&#039;ve seen them before, I didn&#039;t get it into recently. It seems like I should have gotten it, but when you see a bunch of tags on a page and some are bigger and some are little, I was thinking that was just for artistic merit, that it was just a way to display those tags. In fact, the larger tags tend to be the most popular tags, so the tags on a tag cloud grow with popularity. So when you go to scan a page that has a bunch of tags on it, BOOM!, there&#039;s the biggest tag and that&#039;s the most popular one, and the littlest tag is the least popular tag. So it&#039;s a really clever way of keeping the social. Web 2.0 is all about the social aspects. It&#039;s all about trying to reuse information to the best of your ability. The other obvious things. It tracks revisions automatically, and you can fall back to different revisions. If you have revisions, it&#039;s saving constantly, so you can look at revisions 11 seconds ago or three minutes ago or five minutes ago. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; So you&#039;re not marking each revision, it&#039;s just automatically doing that? 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;It is on top of it. It just marks revisions constantly. Every two to five minutes you&#039;ve got a revision. You can also hit the save button if you want to stamp a revision. But this document -- for instance, Tim and I are working off our show notes in a Writely document, and we could very easily click on revisions and look to see what each of us did over the last 30 minutes preparing for this. We talked about uploading documents, but it can also insert graphics. It&#039;s great. If you have a signature you need to insert or if you have a logo you need to insert, that&#039;s very easy to do. Multiple browser support. Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari -- all the main browsers have great support under it. And by the way, Google just purchased them. That&#039;s another great endorsement for this product. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; So they should be around for a little while. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;Right. If it wasn&#039;t Google, it would have been Yahoo, because of the way they&#039;re fighting over properties and what they want.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses: &lt;/b&gt;Well, the little bit that I have looked at it, it seems very slick. The nice part about it is that it&#039;s fast and responsive, the interface is very fast. I&#039;ve used some other 2.0 that just feel real sluggish. And I&#039;m not running it on a really speedy machine, but I haven&#039;t noticed anything in here that seems slow or painful to use at all. It seems very streamlined, and all the important things are readily available. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; Yeah, it&#039;s just the opposite of what you come to look at this present... 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; As opposed to using Word. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;Right. Well, using Word, using Excel, using PowerPoint -- any of the applications where you have these egregious licensing deals when you go purchase the software, you have a fairly painstaking installation process. You have more features than probably most people would use. I would say 95% of the people are going to use the very, very basic features when it comes to Word, Excel and Powerpoint, and those kinds of applications. So it&#039;s kind of refreshing to come to something that&#039;s going to have all the features I need and it&#039;s not going to have any of that bloat, so I don&#039;t have all that confusion in the menus as I&#039;m going to do things. But yeah, we&#039;ve belabored Writely enough. Do you have any comments on it before we head on to my next one? 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses: &lt;/b&gt;Probably should move on. I could go on for a long time about it. The best thing to do is go out and give it a try. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; It&#039;s Writely.com. Tim, do you want to do one of yours? 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--pagebreak--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; Sure, I can put one in here. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; Great. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses: &lt;/b&gt;The next site for me has come in handy a number of times lately. It might not be something I&#039;d normally use, but it is &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.Meebo.com&quot;&gt;Meebo.com&lt;/a&gt;. It&#039;s sole purpose is to let you do instant messaging. If you go to the website, you can log in with your AIM, ICQ, .Mac, Jabber, GoogleTalk, MSN, whatever service you happen to use, or you can log into multiple at a time, and from the website it&#039;s your instant messaging client. So your buddy list shows up in a window. Any message that pops up, pops up in a different window. They&#039;re all within your web browser. And the feel of it feels just like a desktop application all inside your web browser window. So the great part about this is you can get your instant messaging -- it has all the regular instant messaging features -- but you don&#039;t actually have to have any client software to do it. So if you sit down at a friend&#039;s machine and you want to get on instant messaging, you don&#039;t have to install something to get to what you need, you can just start using it. Just go to the website and it&#039;s all there, and it remembers a lot of your settings. What&#039;s been especially useful for me recently, if you ever go someplace where there&#039;s a public network and they may not have all the proper ports open for doing instant messaging, that can be a problem for a lot of people. Or it could be a problem at work. So if you&#039;re at work and they&#039;ve locked things down so that you can&#039;t do instant messaging, this is your way around it. You just go to the website, log in, and it all happens through the main web port, port 80, so anything which supports web stuff, any firewalls that have that open, you can do your instant messaging from many of those services. So it&#039;s been pretty slick. It&#039;s a nice site.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; I had a hard time understanding why people wanted these services, and you just touched on it right there. I work in a location that&#039;s not behind a firewall, and so I can use all my native applications to do everything. I can use iChat for communicating with chat, and I can use Jabber or any of the other clients I want to use. But I think this also is why Gmail has also gotten so popular -- the idea that you can have encrypted, secure email over port 80, anywhere. I&#039;m not sure, but I&#039;m fairly sure that most of the people that use Gmail and have come to rely on it, it&#039;s their personal email for their non-work-related things, and they know they can get to it anywhere because it&#039;s on port 80. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses: &lt;/b&gt;Yeah. And I feel like there are a lot more people who have multiple devices. Their work computer, their home computer, their laptop, their phone or whatever else it is. People are used to using more devices and more machines, and rather than trying to keep all of their favorite software up to date on all of those different machines, it&#039;s just a whole lot easier to use a website. And these websites are getting to the point where they&#039;re really starting to feel like a desktop application. Here you don&#039;t have to worry about updating anything. You just sit down at any computer you want to and you&#039;ve got all your stuff, and it&#039;s got your preferences. Like Writely, you&#039;ve got all your documents in one place. You don&#039;t have to worry about sharing those or burning them on a CD to take with you... 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;Or coordinating a network drive. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; It&#039;s just all of the hassle involved with administrating your own machines is eliminated with this. You just have a web browser, you get to your stuff. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--pagebreak--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; Cool. Well, I&#039;m going to jump into Basecamp. Basecamp is really cool site. Actually, while I&#039;m talking about it, would you mind looking up the website? Because I don&#039;t think it&#039;s Basecamp.com, I think it&#039;s... 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses: &lt;/b&gt;Cwork? If I remember. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; ...something else like that. Well, there&#039;s a couple different URLs for it. You might just want to Google it. But basically, Basecamp is this really cool way to manage projects and to manage tasks in your business. It would probably replace something like Microsoft Project or any one of the myriad of project manager software. It&#039;s not like the other Web 2.0 apps. It&#039;s got kind of the bare-bones functionality, but once again for 85-95% of the people who are projected-oriented, Basecamp is going to meet your needs for dealing with groups. Did you find that URL? 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; Yeah. &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.BasecampHQ.com&quot;&gt;BasecampHQ.com&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; Oh, I missed the &quot;HQ&quot;, that&#039;s what it is. BasecampHQ.com. I think, to me the cornerstone feature of Basecamp is this concept of a milestone. Basically what you can do is you can say, &quot;Look, I&#039;ve got a milestone&quot; -- I think people in the corporate world probably call them deadlines, but a milestone&#039;s a much nicer word for it -- &quot;I&#039;ve got this milestone in two months and it has to be done, and this is the person responsible for doing it.&quot; And so beyond that, within that milestone, you can actually go in and assign to-dos that have to be done in order to meet that milestone, and then you can check off the milestone. But as you have more and more milestones, they automatically put themselves on a calendar, because each milestone is associated with a date. One of the really neat things is that you can actually subscribe to that with your iCal, and you can see on your calendar right in front of you, right next to your appointments and meetings, all the milestones that you have set for you and your business. The other thing I really like about Basecamp is that they don&#039;t sell it by subscriber or by individual. They sell it to a company and it&#039;s for managing X number of projects. So I can buy a one project -- well, the one project is free -- then you can buy, I think, five or 15 project packs. I have the 15 project pack, and it&#039;s great because you can have up to 15 projects simultaneously running. Now if you get to 15 and you want to put the 16th, you can retire a project. And so you can continually retire projects, and as long as you don&#039;t have more than 15 irons in the fire on projects, it&#039;s going to meet your needs beautifully. It&#039;s a fairly nominal monthly fee, I think it&#039;s $40 or $50 for the 15 project? 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses: &lt;/b&gt;Oh, no. It&#039;s $25 a month for the 15, and $50 for the 35. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; Yeah. It also has a great message board area, and this is good when you&#039;re working remotely, and also for setting up the project. You don&#039;t always use the milestone features. For instance, I did a web project recently where I was coordinating with an external developer, and in the message board area I gave this developer all the information that he might need in terms of usernames, passwords, common information, information from another developer who was going to be providing some input, and we put all this in one area. We even uploaded files and attached those to the specific messages that the developer could use. It streamlined the process so much, because we didn&#039;t find ourselves sending emails back and forth, saying, &quot;Could you hand me this? Could you give me this? Oh, I lost this. Could you give me this?&quot; It was all sitting in one common place in Basecamp. I can&#039;t say enough good things about it. It&#039;s great! 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses: &lt;/b&gt;The experience I&#039;ve had with it so far. I think the sign of a really well-designed application is that you can get into it and feel that it&#039;s very simple, there&#039;s not a whole lot you need to look through to start using it. But the more I use it, the more I realize there&#039;s a whole lot of complexity behind it, where it&#039;s doing a lot of work but you don&#039;t even think about it, it keeps you focused on the main stuff that you need. When it comes to project management, that&#039;s something -- I&#039;ve tried a lot of other web-based software and programs for doing it, and most of the programs just seem to get more in the way of doing your projects than they are really helping. Basecamp&#039;s been the first thing I&#039;ve used that really has been useful, it&#039;s been easy to use, it hasn&#039;t been a pain to keep up with things, and it really is very well-designed, with a straightforward interface. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;Cool. All right, let&#039;s move on to the next one. Looks like you have a couple more. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--pagebreak--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; I do. First of all, I&#039;ll just cover something I see is a feature that you&#039;ll start seeing all over the place in websites. Surprisingly, it&#039;s from Microsoft, and that&#039;s surprising in a number of ways because it is a very cool feature, it works in any web browser, and the javascript that makes it work is available under one of the standard licenses used by open source, so they&#039;re basically just making this available for anyone to use. The feature is Microsoft&#039;s Live Clipboard. What is does is it provides a way to copy and paste information between web pages or between applications in web pages. For instance, you might copy your address information from your address book, and when you&#039;re ordering something from a website and you need to enter your shipping information, you can just copy your contact information and paste it in. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; Not line by line, but the whole block. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; The whole [xx], so it takes all the fields, drops them into all the appropriate places. What&#039;s more, you can copy things from a web page. So if you go to a web page, you want the contact information off of a site, you do a single copy using your browser&#039;s copy functions -- it&#039;s not some weird actions or no extensions or plug ins involved -- you use your regular browser copy function, and then skip over to your address book and paste it in. Or do it within a site. So hopefully as more people use this feature, as you manage a site you have copy and paste, which you normally don&#039;t see in a website, but here you can copy and paste complex information back and forth all over the place. So it could be a contact. Or it could be an event. Or it could be a photo with a caption and title information and everything else with it. The demonstrations that were used for this that actually work -- I opened up Firefox on a Mac, and it&#039;s all there, it works, it&#039;s purely web-based to make this stuff happen -- the example they gave was copying at a modified Flickr website, where they copied one photo and then copied an entire album, then pasted in to something else, and it all came across with all the necessary information. Anyway, it just worked very well and it was very slick. It&#039;s one of the big pieces that you need for making a web application feel like a desktop application, and it&#039;s actually working right now and works in just about any browser. And it came from Microsoft and it&#039;s freely available. Very, very cool. So hopefully we&#039;ll start seeing that on a lot of websites here in the near future. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;Yeah, and just to clarify. I know Tim did make it fairly clear, but this is not just a website you go to, but this is actually technology that will be, hopefully, incorporated into websites to make it easier for information to be transferred to and from. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; So there&#039;s not really a website to send you to to go start using this feature all over the place. It&#039;s just something that hopefully you&#039;ll start seeing in a lot of places. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; But if you want to learn more about it, just go to Google and type &quot;Microsoft Live Clipboard&quot;, and you&#039;ll be able to see video presentations and some actual demos you can try out. Probably the TechCrunch Microsoft Live Clipboard is the best link. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--pagebreak--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; Well, my next one is amazing for a number of reasons, and it&#039;s pretty complex so I&#039;m going to try to explain this and have it make sense. I saw a demo of DabbleDB, and I believe the website for it is &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.DabbleDB.com&quot;&gt;DabbleDB.com&lt;/a&gt;. Right now, I just think you can sign up for future information. If you Google for it, you can find a Quicktime presentation of it. It&#039;s an amazing website that lets you import a database or create a database right from the site, and it has all the features that you&#039;d need in a basic database application, you can do relational data. But the amazing part about it is that the interface is so slick. It feels just like a desktop application. It has a lot of the elements that you just really wouldn&#039;t find other than in a nicely-developed desktop application. The demo will step you through copying. You&#039;re just selecting a bunch of data out of Excel, copy it, paste it into the first step of DabbleDB. It looks at it, figures out a bunch of stuff automatically, and let&#039;s you change field names if you need to, but right off the bat you suddenly have your database, one table of information is right there in DabbleDB. You can sort, filter on it, you can choose what columns to display, you can change the types of columns -- all the kinds of stuff that you&#039;re used to having in a spreadsheet or a database -- and then you can very easily choose some data to separate out into another table. So if you have a list of customers, and the customers may have multiple addresses, you can separate that out into another table without much work. So without much effort, you quickly go from building a database online from a simple table into something much more complex and much more useful, with all sorts of great features. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;Yeah, they really trumped, I think -- I mean, Google Base has a whole different purpose -- but they really trumped what you can do with an online database. I think they took it so far beyond just the basic data capture that Google&#039;s currently doing. The immediate thought I had was, think about all these -- I&#039;m on several boards and a lot of times you have to manage member lists, and usually one person is stuck with managing those member lists and managing every aspect of them, because no one has the knowledge or expertise to deal with the database, and it&#039;s never in a nice format. Not everyone has FileMaker on their machines is, I guess, what I&#039;m trying to say. FileMaker is such a nice, easy thing to use. But this brings this really easy user interface to people who -- I could really see if we were going after, let&#039;s say we were grooming new members for an organization I was in and we had 25 prospects who came to the November 15th meeting -- being able to assign someone to go through and call each of those prospects and check them off, to say, &quot;I called them, &quot; so that all the statuses could be updated in an easy way. No longer are you relegated to chopping out pieces of Excel spreadsheets and emailing those individuals, you can actually let them interact directly with the database. And that&#039;s kind of where I see the long-term. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; It&#039;s got similar benefits to using Writely or something like that. It&#039;s on the web, it&#039;s available to all the people who need to be able to get to it. And they have some cool ways of tying in to the database, like it produces an RSS feed so you can subscribe to see what changes take place in the database. Or export it to a PDF for printing. Or a comma-delimited text file so you could import it back into Excel or something else. So you have great ways of getting data into it, great ways of getting data back out of it. And it can even do some more sophisticated things, like time, if you have any time fields... 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;I was going to mention that. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses: &lt;/b&gt;...there&#039;s a calendar view. You can export it as an iCal calendar to import into iCal or Outlook. It really has some amazing features to it. It is not out yet, though, it&#039;s not released, but I believe they&#039;re getting pretty close, and it really is amazing. And as Bill had mentioned before, I really see it as more of a competitor to desktop applications like FileMaker Pro or Microsoft Access than I see it so much as Google Base or competing with one of the online things. It really is a slick website. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;I agree. All right. Well, we&#039;ve reviewed about five products or websites that we felt were the best in their class, and we hope you enjoyed it. In the future, we will be reviewing, most likely, more hardware-based products, but if a great piece of software comes along we will definitely bring it to the mix as well. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; And as our point is this week, software doesn&#039;t necessarily mean something to install on your machine anymore, it could be a website. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler: &lt;/b&gt;That&#039;s exactly. So thanks for tuning in to this month&#039;s edition of the BestStuff Podcast. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tim Moses:&lt;/b&gt; Be sure to visit BestStuff.com today. If you&#039;d like to contact us with story ideas or general questions, please email Tim or &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.beststuff.com/user/3/contact&quot;&gt;Bill AT BestStuff.com&lt;/a&gt;. That&#039;s not one email address, that&#039;s two different ones. Bill or &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://www.beststuff.com/user/4/contact&quot;&gt;Tim AT BestStuff.com&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bill Butler:&lt;/b&gt; For BestStuff, we are Bill Butler and Tim Moses. Thanks for listening.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; [music]
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;!-- google_ad_section_end --&gt;&lt;table id=&quot;attachments&quot; class=&quot;sticky-enabled&quot;&gt;
 &lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;Attachment&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Size&lt;/th&gt; &lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
 &lt;tr class=&quot;odd&quot;&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE001.mp3&quot;&gt;BCPE001.mp3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;20.47 MB&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
 <comments>http://www.beststuff.com/podcast/best-podcast-number-1.html#comments</comments>
 <category domain="http://www.beststuff.com/taxonomy/term/10577">Podcast</category>
 <enclosure url="http://www.beststuff.com/sites/www.beststuff.com/files/podcasts/BCPE001.mp3" length="21459245" type="audio/mpeg" />
 <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2006 15:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>jessica</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">1 at http://www.beststuff.com</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
