<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
        <channel>
        <title>Idyllic Music</title>
	<link>http://www.idyllicmusic.com/index.html</link>
	<language>en</language>
	<copyright>Creative Commons(CC)</copyright>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2006 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
	<managingEditor>idyllicmusic@cox.net (Jim Nye)</managingEditor>
	<webMaster>idyllicmusic@cox.net (Jim Nye)</webMaster>
        <ttl>180</ttl>
	<category>Music</category>
        <itunes:subtitle>The Very Best Mix of Downtempo, Ambient, Trip Hop, Electronica and Dub Music from around the World</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Mindbeats - Jim Nye</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>A Weekly Podcast featuring Trip Hop, Ambient, Electronica, Dub and Downtempo songs by outstanding bands from around the globe. Music that is subtle, less intense but more rhythmic and melodic than current pop music. Show notes are available at www.idyllicmusic.com</itunes:summary>
        <description>The Very Best Mix of Downtempo, Ambient, Trip Hop, Electronica and Dub Music from around the World</description>
        <itunes:owner>
        <itunes:name>Jim Nye</itunes:name>
        <itunes:email>idyllicmusic@cox.net</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/idyllic.jpg"/>
        <itunes:category text="Music">
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>downtempo,trip hop,chill,dub,ambient,electronica,chillout,triphop</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
        <generator>RSSeditor v0.9.54 (http://www.rss-info.com)</generator>
	<image>
		<url>http://www.idyllicmusic.com/idyllic.jpg</url>
		<title>Idyllic Music</title>
		<link>http://www.idyllicmusic.com/index.html</link>
	</image>
<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #181</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring White Blush, Bioscape, Niyaz, Soulacybin, Winterstrand and Kate Martin</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we look at emotional isolation. It seems the more we reach out the less we feel. It might be the continuing reliance on the intrawebs or fragmentation of society but increasingly many of us are alone and not by choice. Next time you are at a restaurant and see a couple glowing with the bluish tint of their separate mobile phones or simply sitting together but not talking, you'll understand what I mean. Demonstrating the ways we've becoming isolated on this episode of Idyllic Music are White Blush, Bioscape, Niyaz, Soulacybin, Winterstrand and Kate Martin. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week we look at emotional isolation. It seems the more we reach out the less we feel. It might be the continuing reliance on the intrawebs or fragmentation of society but increasingly many of us are alone and not by choice. Next time you are at a restaurant and see a couple glowing with the bluish tint of their separate mobile phones or simply sitting together but not talking, you'll understand what I mean. Demonstrating the ways we've becoming isolated on this episode of Idyllic Music are White Blush, Bioscape, Niyaz, Soulacybin, Winterstrand and Kate Martin. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/181050606Podcast181.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/181050606Podcast181.mp3" length="29528398" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:45</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #180</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Globular, Jah Wobble, Zeus Scientist, EeBoO, mmpsuf, and Chriss SoLo</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at loves first heartbreak. When young untested emotions are at their most potent and everything seems so damned important. As George Eliot so aptly put it. There is no despair so absolute as that which comes from the first moments of our first great sorrow, when we have not yet known what it is to have suffered and be healed, to have despaired and recovered hope. On this episode of Idyllic Music we'll hear from Globular, Jah Wobble, Zeus Scientist, EeBoO, mmpsuf, and Chriss SoLo. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at loves first heartbreak. When young untested emotions are at their most potent and everything seems so damned important. As George Eliot so aptly put it. There is no despair so absolute as that which comes from the first moments of our first great sorrow, when we have not yet known what it is to have suffered and be healed, to have despaired and recovered hope. On this episode of Idyllic Music we'll hear from Globular, Jah Wobble, Zeus Scientist, EeBoO, mmpsuf, and Chriss SoLo. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/180050606Podcast180.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/180050606Podcast180.mp3" length="
31513287" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>32:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #179</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Maido Project, Joel Enzo, The Flavor Foundation, Dubtrak and First Rebirth</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll head to the sub-continent for inspiration. In particular, Saraswati, the goddess of knowledge, music, arts and science. While it's not unusual for ancient cultures to personify this manifestation of consciousness through art, Saraswati expands to include the sciences. We can all take as our Muse this expression of modern progress. Moving forward with us on this episode of Idyllic Music are Maido Project, Joel Enzo, TheFlavor Foundation, Dubtrak and First Rebirth. I'm Jim Nye.Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll head to the sub-continent for inspiration. In particular, Saraswati, the goddess of knowledge, music, arts and science. While it's not unusual for ancient cultures to personify this manifestation of consciousness through art, Saraswati expands to include the sciences. We can all take as our Muse this expression of modern progress. Moving forward with us on this episode of Idyllic Music are Maido Project, Joel Enzo, TheFlavor Foundation, Dubtrak and First Rebirth. I'm Jim Nye.Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/179050606Podcast179.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/179050606Podcast179.mp3" length="28866769" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #178</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Nicky Cairney, ShaMANoiD, Mustard Tiger, Rabbit Hole Revelations, Artemis and Merge of Equals.</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at mirages. In particular the superior mirage known as Fata Morgana, named after the fairy shapeshifting half-sister of King Arthur. We come to rely on the normally stable optic perceptions that make up our daily experiences but now and again the physical world will throw you off. It's those moments that are the true reality of our existence. Testing us this week are Nicky Cairney, ShaMANoiD, Mustard Tiger, Rabbit Hole Revelations, Artemis and Merge of Equals. I'm Jim Nye.Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at mirages. In particular the superior mirage known as Fata Morgana, named after the fairy shapeshifting half-sister of King Arthur. We come to rely on the normally stable optic perceptions that make up our daily experiences but now and again the physical world will throw you off. It's those moments that are the true reality of our existence. Testing us this week are Nicky Cairney, ShaMANoiD, Mustard Tiger, Rabbit Hole Revelations, Artemis and Merge of Equals. I'm Jim Nye. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/178050606Podcast178.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/178050606Podcast178.mp3" length="28795298" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #177</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Nicolas Eller, Radioactive Sandwich and Ovalys</itunes:subtitle><description>This week's episode of Idyllic Music is brought to you by the number 3. It is, I believe, the most ubiquitous symbol man has created throughout history. From religion to physics and beyond, the number 3 is found everywhere. The atom is made up of 3 components. Almost all faiths have a core aspect containing 3 parts. Shakespere, Tolkien and a host of modern authors have found the trilogy or number 3 irresistible. All of this despite the overwhelming dominance of the number 2 in our own biology, 2 eyes, ears, arms and legs. What is it about that added digit? Exploring the musical end of the number 3 for us are Nicolas Eller, Radioactive Sandwich and Ovalys. I'm Jim Nye.Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week's episode of Idyllic Music is brought to you by the number 3. It is, I believe, the most ubiquitous symbol man has created throughout history. From religion to physics and beyond, the number 3 is found everywhere. The atom is made up of 3 components. Almost all faiths have a core aspect containing 3 parts. Shakespere, Tolkien and a host of modern authors have found the trilogy or number 3 irresistible. All of this despite the overwhelming dominance of the number 2 in our own biology, 2 eyes, ears, arms and legs. What is it about that added digit? Exploring the musical end of the number 3 for us are Nicolas Eller, Radioactive Sandwich and Ovalys. I'm Jim Nye. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/177050606Podcast177.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/177050606Podcast177.mp3" length="29760784" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>31:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #176</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Hinkstep, Subroute Roots, General Fuzz, Marilyn Carino and Scopes</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll explore the many paths to spiritual enlightenment. It might come in a journey, a ritual of repetition or a chemical. Each method is personal. I'm Jim Nye.Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll explore the many paths to spiritual enlightenment. It might come in a journey, a ritual of repetition or a chemical. Each method is personal. I'm Jim Nye. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/176050606Podcast176.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/176050606Podcast176.mp3" length="28440869 " type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #175</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring TSmarton Trio, Viola, Karmacoda, Hello Mellow, Twin Muses and Earsauce</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll experience Epic Dreams. Dreams that are so compelling and so vivid the details remain with you for years. When you wake up from an Epic Dream, you feel that you have discovered something profound or amazing about yourself or about the world. They are the dreams shaped by Morpheus and dreamt by Siddhartha and Gilgamesh. Dreaming on with us on this episode of Idyllic Music are Smarton Trio, Viola, Karmacoda, Hello Mellow, Twin Muses and Earsauce. I'm Jim Nye.Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll experience Epic Dreams. Dreams that are so compelling and so vivid the details remain with you for years. When you wake up from an Epic Dream, you feel that you have discovered something profound or amazing about yourself or about the world. They are the dreams shaped by Morpheus and dreamt by Siddhartha and Gilgamesh. Dreaming on with us on this episode of Idyllic Music are Smarton Trio, Viola, Karmacoda, Hello Mellow, Twin Muses and Earsauce. I'm Jim Nye. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/175050606Podcast175.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/175050606Podcast175.mp3" length="31328549" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>32:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #174</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring The National Pool, Auma, Metaharmoniks, Lovespirals, The Esoteric Gender and Korev</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we will consider those times when things get wobbly. Not the early 20th century trade union but the feeling that things that once seemed solid and unchanging are now less so. They may be in politics and sexuality, personally or sonically. We will hear from 6 artists finding their footing in an unstable world. They are The National Pool, Auma, Metaharmoniks, Lovespirals, The Esoteric Gender and Korev.Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week we will consider those times when things get wobbly. Not the early 20th century trade union but the feeling that things that once seemed solid and unchanging are now less so. They may be in politics and sexuality, personally or sonically. We will hear from 6 artists finding their footing in an unstable world. They are The National Pool, Auma, Metaharmoniks, Lovespirals, The Esoteric Gender and Korev. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/174050606Podcast174.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/174050606Podcast174.mp3" length="28799896" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #173</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Esza Kaye, All India Radio, Andreia Dacal, Daybehavior, Aphone, Giyz and Curly Jefferson.</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we'll look at the Zeitgeist. This moment in time, our collective meme and the era of uncertainty. It's an era that portends the age of human technology while celebrating a kind of spirtitual nostalgia. On this episode of Idyllic Music we'll hear from seven artists reflecting "the spirit of the times". They are Esza Kaye, All India Radio, Andreia Dacal, Daybehavior, Aphone, Giyz and Curly Jefferson.Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week we'll look at the Zeitgeist. This moment in time, our collective meme and the era of uncertainty. It's an era that portends the age of human technology while celebrating a kind of spirtitual nostalgia. On this episode of Idyllic Music we'll hear from seven artists reflecting "the spirit of the times". They are Esza Kaye, All India Radio, Andreia Dacal, Daybehavior, Aphone, Giyz and Curly Jefferson. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/173050606Podcast173.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/173050606Podcast173.mp3" length="27927197" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #172</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Jordan Reyne, Secret Archives of the Vatican, Tikki Masala, Project 5am, My Bubba and Mi and Chris Pettit</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll ponder the summer travel season. The world's a mighty big place filled with destinations that can be both beautiful and dangerous, often times in the same city. We'll hear from six artists with a musical itinerary stretching from Copenhagen to Christchurch, Calcutta to Brixton. Leading our tour on this edition of Idyllic Music are Jordan Reyne, Secret Archives of the Vatican, Tikki Masala, Project 5am, My Bubba and Mi and Chris Pettit. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll ponder the summer travel season. The world's a mighty big place filled with destinations that can be both beautiful and dangerous, often times in the same city. We'll hear from six artists with a musical itinerary stretching from Copenhagen to Christchurch, Calcutta to Brixton. Leading our tour on this edition of Idyllic Music are Jordan Reyne, Secret Archives of the Vatican, Tikki Masala, Project 5am, My Bubba and Mi and Chris Pettit.  Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/172050606Podcast172.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/172050606Podcast172.mp3" length="27516343" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:39</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #171</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Endless Blue, Boleros En Femeni, Fuji Kureta, Babbaracos, The Crisis Project and Sarah Fimm</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we'll look at women and men and the equally compelling perspectives they bring to music. We have come a long way from days when gender roles were specific and restricting. Now we find even in parts of the world where traditional divisions between men and women remain, within the arts those walls are collapsing. Helping illustrated that on this episode of Idyllic Music are Endless Blue, Boleros En Femeni, Fuji Kureta, Babbaracos, The Crisis Project and Sarah Fimm.Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week we'll look at women and men and the equally compelling perspectives they bring to music. We have come a long way from days when gender roles were specific and restricting. Now we find even in parts of the world where traditional divisions between men and women remain, within the arts those walls are collapsing. Helping illustrated that on this episode of Idyllic Music are Endless Blue, Boleros En Femeni, Fuji Kureta, Babbaracos, The Crisis Project and Sarah Fimm. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/171050606Podcast171.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/171050606Podcast171.mp3" length="29463615" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:41</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #170</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Orange Crush, Natalie Walker, Motionfield, Vitamins for You, Text Adventure and Asaguare</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll consider the contemplative life most often associated with religious devotion. On this episode of Idyllic Music we'll focus instead on the secular. The conscious decision to notice things. The little details of life that we often skip right past.  We get help from Orange Crush, Natalie Walker, Motionfield, Vitamins for You, Text Adventure and Asaguare. I'm Jim Nye. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll consider the contemplative life most often associated with religious devotion. On this episode of Idyllic Music we'll focus instead on the secular. The conscious decision to notice things. The little details of life that we often skip right past.  We get help from Orange Crush, Natalie Walker, Motionfield, Vitamins for You, Text Adventure and Asaguare. I'm Jim Nye. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/170050606Podcast170.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/170050606Podcast170.mp3" length="27855308" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #169</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Planets Citizens, Naoned, Dave Gerard, Floating Spirits, Ovalys and Alik Project</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at deceptions and delusions and how the two often blend into the other in a sort of symbiotic fashion. It requires the need to believe and ultimately deceive. It is one of our most powerful tools in coping with emotional pain. Providing a bit of regression therapy for us on this episode of Idyllic Music are PlanetsCitizens, Naoned, Dave Gerard, Floating Spirits, Ovalys and AlikProject. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at deceptions and delusions and how the two often blend into the other in a sort of symbiotic fashion. It requires the need to believe and ultimately deceive. It is one of our most powerful tools in coping with emotional pain. Providing a bit of regression therapy for us on this episode of Idyllic Music are PlanetsCitizens, Naoned, Dave Gerard, Floating Spirits, Ovalys and AlikProject. Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/169050606Podcast169.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/169050606Podcast169.mp3" length="26938723" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #168</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Dr Freebs, Cling, Twin Muses, PiliPili, Merlune and Dub One!</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll explore the search for self. Looking for the light that makes us strive for something better. It might be the agonizing reappraisal of one's efforts and motives over a lifetime or the search for enlightenment contained in so many faiths. Finding your true self is so daunting a project that many simply never try. We'll hear from six of the bold ones on this episode of Idyllic Music. They are Dr Freebs, Cling, Twin Muses, PiliPili, Merlune and Dub One! Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll explore the search for self. Looking for the light that makes us strive for something better. It might be the agonizing reappraisal of one's efforts and motives over a lifetime or the search for enlightenment contained in so many faiths. Finding your true self is so daunting a project that many simply never try. We'll hear from six of the bold ones on this episode of Idyllic Music. They are Dr Freebs, Cling, Twin Muses, PiliPili, Merlune and Dub One! Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/168050606Podcast168.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/168050606Podcast168.mp3" length="27522194" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #167</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Adam and Alma, Artemis, Blear Moon, Massive Attack, SackJo22 and Sunspot and Sect23</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll explore the belief that all that we know of God can just as easily be attributed to the sun. Of course, sun worship is as old as civilization and even in an Old Testament context, the sun can be just as punishing or life sustaining as God. So rather than worship, we'll marvel at the hope and happiness, love and warmth we get from the sun with help from Adam and Alma, Artemis, Blear Moon, Massive Attack, SackJo22 and Sunspot and Sect23 Try the new Idyllic Music app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll explore the belief that all that we know of God can just as easily be attributed to the sun. Of course, sun worship is as old as civilization and even in an Old Testament context, the sun can be just as punishing or life sustaining as God. So rather than worship, we'll marvel at the hope and happiness, love and warmth we get from the sun with help from Adam and Alma, Artemis, Blear Moon, Massive Attack, SackJo22 and Sunspot and Sect23 Try the new Idyllic Music app.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>

<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/167050606Podcast167.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/167050606Podcast167.mp3" length="28134822" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:20</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #166</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Dee W, Dive Index, Maido Project, Kesakoo, Uniform Motion and Black Widow Voodoo Cult</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll welcome the cleansing power of fire. It's a concept so broad as to include ancient elements of Egyptian, Christian and Druid rituals as well modern ideas about the birth of the universe. On a personal level, Fire can lead either to brilliance or devastation. As Tennessee Williams noted "We all live in a house on fire". So we'll burn to hear from Dee W, Dive Index, Maido Project, Kesakoo, Uniform Motion and Black Widow Voodoo Cult. Try the new Idyllic Music iPhone app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll welcome the cleansing power of fire. It's a concept so broad as to include ancient elements of Egyptian, Christian and Druid rituals as well modern ideas about the birth of the universe. On a personal level, Fire can lead either to brilliance or devastation. As Tennessee Williams noted "We all live in a house on fire". So we'll burn to hear from Dee W, Dive Index, Maido Project, Kesakoo, Uniform Motion and Black Widow Voodoo Cult. Try the new Idyllic Music iPhone app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/166050606Podcast166.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/166050606Podcast166.mp3" length="29134822" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #165</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring 2 per cent, The Reverend Shortboy, WEED, Alien S, Alec Troniq and Rho.</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at abbreviations and acronyms. You see them everywhere from texts and license plates to government forms and love notes. They might be cute and clever or confusing and inscrutable but these brevis or shortenings have become the bane of writers and lovers of language everywhere. We'll hear from six artists, PDQ, who use them in name and title only. LOL. They are 2 percent, The Reverend Shortboy, WEED, Alien S, Alec Troniq and Rho. Try the new Idyllic Music iPhone app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at abbreviations and acronyms. You see them everywhere from texts and license plates to government forms and love notes. They might be cute and clever or confusing and inscrutable but these brevis or shortenings have become the bane of writers and lovers of language everywhere. We'll hear from six artists, PDQ, who use them in name and title only. LOL. They are 2%, The Reverend Shortboy, WEED, Alien S, Alec Troniq and Rho. Try the new Idyllic Music iPhone app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/165050606Podcast165.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/165050606Podcast165.mp3" length="29138442" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #164</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Delgarma, Garmisch, Cobrider, Billy Cote and Uniit Carruyo, Tumc, and Full Source</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the unbearable sadness that marks the end of relationships. Whether the result of the discovery or admission of infidelity or the euphemism of 'growing apart', the cold numbness deep inside of those unaware and most pained lives on in a hundred ways. Its never about them as protested but the left behind deal in anger and recriminations, self-doubt and what-ifs. It is a sadness that lessens over time but never heals. Seven heartbreaking tales are offered up this week by Delgarma, Garmisch, Cobrider, Billy Cote and Uniit Carruyo, Tumc, and Full source. Try the new Idyllic Music iPhone app.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the unbearable sadness that marks the end of relationships. Whether the result of the discovery or admission of infidelity or the euphemism of 'growing apart', the cold numbness deep inside of those unaware and most pained lives on in a hundred ways. Its never about them as protested but the left behind deal in anger and recriminations, self-doubt and what-ifs. It is a sadness that lessens over time but never heals. Seven heartbreaking tales are offered up this week by Delgarma, Garmisch, Cobrider, Billy Cote and Uniit Carruyo, Tumc, and Full source. Try the new Idyllic Music iPhone app.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/164050606Podcast164.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/164050606Podcast164.mp3" length="26040947" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #163</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Raja, Calander Girl, Arze Kareem, Pili Pili, Nu Shooz Orchestra, Tracing Arcs and Jah Wobble</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll breathlessly await a world of possibilities. The future is more open, blended and diverse than it was even a generation ago. That means there is more opportunity for progress and enlightenment even in the face of retrenchment. The tide is inevitably against the forces of the status quo. It's called progress and it's not limited to the macro. Everyone has the possibility of growth. Moving forward this week are Raja, Calander Girl, Arze Kareem, Pili Pili, Nu Shooz Orchestra, Tracing Arcs and Jah Wobble. Try the new Idyllic Music iPhone app. I'm Jim Nye.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll breathlessly await a world of possibilities. The future is more open, blended and diverse than it was even a generation ago. That means there is more opportunity for progress and enlightenment even in the face of retrenchment. The tide is inevitably against the forces of the status quo. It's called progress and it's not limited to the macro. Everyone has the possibility of growth. Moving forward this week are Raja, Calander Girl, Arze Kareem, Pili Pili, Nu Shooz Orchestra, Tracing Arcs and Jah Wobble. Try the new Idyllic Music iPhone app. I'm Jim Nye.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/163050606Podcast163.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/163050606Podcast163.mp3" length="26262047" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #162</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring the x-structure, Tang Kai, Dive Index, Sister Overdrive, Sekotis and Secret Archives of the Vatican</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll try to fathom the hidden world of Esotericism. It's a fool's errand; really, because the point is certain things are kept by a narrow circle of the enlightened or initiated away from the rest of us. The most obvious are in the government or religious arena but the idea cascades down to much smaller things like school or office politics. Holding the torch whilst we search the catacombs are the x-structure, Tang Kai, Dive Index, Sister Overdrive, Sekotis and Secret Archives of the Vatican.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll try to fathom the hidden world of Esotericism. It's a fool's errand; really, because the point is certain things are kept by a narrow circle of the enlightened or initiated away from the rest of us. The most obvious are in the government or religious arena but the idea cascades down to much smaller things like school or office politics. Holding the torch whilst we search the catacombs are the x-structure, Tang Kai, Dive Index, Sister Overdrive, Sekotis and Secret Archives of the Vatican.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/162050606Podcast162.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/162050606Podcast162.mp3" length="28792372" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #161</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Kate Martin, Drifting In Silence, Jelle, Bill Laswell, CC Asia and Peter Gabriel</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the wars men wage with all its glory and tragedy. How something so awful can be a source of honor and how Napoleonic ego can lead us into horrific conflict. It's the story of mankind for better or worse and war's moral paradox largely defines the human race. Informing us in ways large and small are Kate Martin, Drifting In Silence, Jelle, Bill Laswell, CC Asia and Peter Gabriel. I'm Jim Nye.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the wars men wage with all its glory and tragedy. How something so awful can be a source of honor and how Napoleonic ego can lead us into horrific conflict. It's the story of mankind for better or worse and war's moral paradox largely defines the human race. Informing us in ways large and small are Kate Martin, Drifting In Silence, Jelle, Bill Laswell, CC Asia and Peter Gabriel. I'm Jim Nye.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/161050606Podcast161.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/161050606Podcast161.mp3" length="26306351" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #160</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Guitorb, Sunburn In Cyprus, Incidental Fusion, Peach Stealing Monkeys, This One and John E. Flash</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll lay back and take in Camus' invincible summer. In times of ambiguous environments, artificial seasons, climate controlled offices and 24 hour shopping malls, its nice to revel in the easy season. Summer. Its sprinklers, beaches, vacations and slower pace. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll lay back and take in Camus' invincible summer. In times of ambiguous environments, artificial seasons, climate controlled offices and 24 hour shopping malls, its nice to revel in the easy season. Summer. Its sprinklers, beaches, vacations and slower pace. </itunes:summary><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/160050606Podcast160.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/160050606Podcast160.mp3" length="27273091" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #159</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Sabian, Vela, Null Device, Wordless Poem and Lucky Cat</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at Promises and Lies. When Ali Campbell sang of the sorrow and pain from the serpent's song of a lovers deceptiveness, he also implied that acknowledging those lies led to hope and healing. Setting down that road this week are Sabian, Vela, Null Device, Wordless Poem and Lucky Cat.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at Promises and Lies. When Ali Campbell sang of the sorrow and pain from the serpent's song of a lovers deceptiveness, he also implied that acknowledging those lies led to hope and healing. Setting down that road this week are Sabian, Vela, Null Device, Wordless Poem and Lucky Cat.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/159050606Podcast159.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/159050606Podcast159.mp3" length="28793208" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #158</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Rho, Hands Upon Black Earth, Analog Fury, Sitchin, and Seth Master</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll marvel at the plant world.  Turning the sun's energy into life from nutrients in the soil and atmosphere is so fundamental to our existence that it is hard to believe we would do anything to disrupt it. Taking us through the first trophic level are Rho, Hands Upon Black Earth, Analog Fury, Sitchin, and Seth Master.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll marvel at the plant world.  Turning the sun's energy into life from nutrients in the soil and atmosphere is so fundamental to our existence that it is hard to believe we would do anything to disrupt it. Taking us through the first trophic level are Rho, Hands Upon Black Earth, Analog Fury, Sitchin, and Seth Master.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/158050606Podcast158.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/158050606Podcast158.mp3" length="27665554" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #157</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Ixtlan, Erosops, Refrag. Sounda, Botany Bay and Capt. Beefheart.</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at tall tales. Stories and fables of exaggeration and entertainment some fantastic and others with morals. They often contain a morsal of truth spun out to the absurd across every culture but reaching a zenith in 19th century American folktales like Paul Bunyan, Brer Rabbit, Little Babaji and John Henry. Ixtlan, Erosops, Refrag. Sounda, Botany Bay and Capt. Beefheart.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at tall tales. Stories and fables of exaggeration and entertainment some fantastic and others with morals. They often contain a morsal of truth spun out to the absurd across every culture but reaching a zenith in 19th century American folktales like Paul Bunyan, Brer Rabbit, Little Babaji and John Henry. Ixtlan, Erosops, Refrag. Sounda, Botany Bay and Capt. Beefheart.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/157050606Podcast157.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/157050606Podcast157.mp3" length="28426240" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #156</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Mar.ch, Sirk, Yagya, USB and Heartical</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at migrations and aspirations. For millennia, people have moved from one place to another seeking better lives. Whether it was for better hunting, soil or jobs the migration was like rivers to the ocean, constant and inevitable. The sorrow of leaving behind the old and struggles to establish the new have marked every one of us. Immigrant and resident alike.

"We cannot seek achievement for ourselves and forget about progress and prosperity for our community... Our ambitions must be broad enough to include the aspirations and needs of others, for their sakes and for our own." - Cesar Chavez</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at migrations and aspirations. For millennia, people have moved from one place to another seeking better lives. Whether it was for better hunting, soil or jobs the migration was like rivers to the ocean, constant and inevitable. The sorrow of leaving behind the old and struggles to establish the new have marked every one of us. Immigrant and resident alike.

"We cannot seek achievement for ourselves and forget about progress and prosperity for our community... Our ambitions must be broad enough to include the aspirations and needs of others, for their sakes and for our own." - Cesar Chavez</itunes:summary><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/156050606Podcast156.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/156050606Podcast156.mp3" length="28980872" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:11</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #155</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring MudVille, Sliptone, Gone, King Dubby, graphiqsgroove and Terence Blanchard.</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at at the sweet and lowdown. It don't mean a thing if it ain't got that swing. Ellington knew it and Irving Mills codified it but many of today's singer-songwriters from Jack Johnson, John Mayer, Nora Jones and notably Amos Lee's  "Sweet Pea" have taken it to heart. From it's pre-war origins, swing music's rhythmic style based on a triplet subdivision of the beat was what moved hips out on the dance floor. On this edition of Idylic Music we'll take a 21st century spin out on the tiles with MudVille, Sliptone, Gone, King Dubby, graphiqsgroove and Terence Blanchard.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at at the sweet and lowdown. It don't mean a thing if it ain't got that swing. Ellington knew it and Irving Mills codified it but many of today's singer-songwriters from Jack Johnson, John Mayer, Nora Jones and notably Amos Lee's  "Sweet Pea" have taken it to heart. From it's pre-war origins, swing music's rhythmic style based on a triplet subdivision of the beat was what moved hips out on the dance floor. On this edition of Idylic Music we'll take a 21st century spin out on the tiles with MudVille, Sliptone, Gone, King Dubby, graphiqsgroove and Terence Blanchard.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/155050606Podcast155.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/155050606Podcast155.mp3" length="26410005" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:30</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #154</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring The Twombley Spiders, The Atomica Project, Ray Garrido, Metastaz, Boneshaman and Innereyefull</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we'll scan the skies of high altitude air travel. Nothing strikes the imagination like following contrails left behind a jet aircraft in the late afternoon sky. Who is on board? Where are they going? Are they beginning an adventure or heading home? Looking up can bring a touch of envy. Providing the lift for us this week are The Twombley Spiders, The Atomica Project, Ray Garrido, Metastaz, Boneshaman and Innereyefull.</description><itunes:summary>This week we'll scan the skies of high altitude air travel. Nothing strikes the imagination like following contrails left behind a jet aircraft in the late afternoon sky. Who is on board? Where are they going? Are they beginning an adventure or heading home? Looking up can bring a touch of envy. Providing the lift for us this week are The Twombley Spiders, The Atomica Project, Ray Garrido, Metastaz, Boneshaman and Innereyefull.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/154050606Podcast154.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/154050606Podcast154.mp3" length="26615223" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:43</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #153</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Entertainment For The Braindead, Enjumi, Artemis, Peterloo Massacre,Stockfinster and Synaecide</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll examine the drought. At any one time a goodly part of the world experiences Meteorological Drought with consequences measured in tens of thousands or even millions of lives. The images of drought, the cracked and barren soil, the dust clouds and snapshots of fishing boats stranded in a dry lake bed speak to the loneliness of emotional drought. So too do the 6 songs on this edition of Idyllic Music.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll examine the drought. At any one time a goodly part of the world experiences Meteorological Drought with consequences measured in tens of thousands or even millions of lives. The images of drought, the cracked and barren soil, the dust clouds and snapshots of fishing boats stranded in a dry lake bed speak to the loneliness of emotional drought. So too do the 6 songs on this edition of Idyllic Music.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/153050606Podcast153.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/153050606Podcast153.mp3" length="28131997" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:18</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #152</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring New Haven, Hungry Lucy, Alik Project, Youth Reference, Usted No!, Rude Corps, and Massive Attack</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we'll look at chapters. Readers know how an author uses them to pace a story, setting up cliffhangers, jumping storylines and setting natural breaks at the end of a sitting so you can go to bed but chapters are even more apparent in our life stories. The titles of the 7 songs we'll hear on this episode of Idyllic Music simply sound like chapters and, perhaps, they are. They come from New Haven, Hungry Lucy, Alik Project, Youth Reference, Usted No!, Rude Corps, and Massive Attack.</description><itunes:summary>This week we'll look at chapters. Readers know how an author uses them to pace a story, setting up cliffhangers, jumping storylines and setting natural breaks at the end of a sitting so you can go to bed but chapters are even more apparent in our life stories. The titles of the 7 songs we'll hear on this episode of Idyllic Music simply sound like chapters and, perhaps, they are. They come from New Haven, Hungry Lucy, Alik Project, Youth Reference, Usted No!, Rude Corps, and Massive Attack.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/152050606Podcast152.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/152050606Podcast152.mp3" length="27893760" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #151</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Eugene Kha, Double6project, Electrobone, Arnolds Records and Psilodump.</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we'll look at life along the world's great rivers. Despite the fact that nearly every major inland city is located along side a major waterway, life down on the banks is often rough, hard scrabbled and often dangerous. McCarthy's Cornelius Suttree personifies the descent from sophisticated urban living to the hand to mouth life along the river. He's not alone. We will hear from Eugene Kha, Double6project, Electrobone, Arnolds Records and Psilodump. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week we'll look at life along the world's great rivers. Despite the fact that nearly every major inland city is located along side a major waterway, life down on the banks is often rough, hard scrabbled and often dangerous. McCarthy's Cornelius Suttree personifies the descent from sophisticated urban living to the hand to mouth life along the river. He's not alone. We will hear from Eugene Kha, Double6project, Electrobone, Arnolds Records and Psilodump. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/151050606Podcast151.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/151050606Podcast151.mp3" length="30359608" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>31:13</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #150</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring MisoSoundz, Screenatorium, Eskazed, Stemvelta, PiliPili and korogho</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll celebrate Idyllic Music's 150th episode by looking forward. Fifty shows ago we offered up two CD ready mixes of the best vocal and instrumental tracks of the previous 100 programs. This time around we enter the new decade having kicked over the last and not looking back. I'm Jim Nye.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll celebrate Idyllic Music's 150th episode by looking forward. Fifty shows ago we offered up two CD ready mixes of the best vocal and instrumental tracks of the previous 100 programs. This time around we enter the new decade having kicked over the last and not looking back.I'm Jim Nye.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/150050606Podcast150.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/150050606Podcast150.mp3" length="27359608" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:30</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #149</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Jen Gloeckner, First Rebirth, Zoe Leela, Swoon, A Beautiful Curse and Ruxpin</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we'll look at beauty and terror as seen in the mythology of women. Stories though out history mostly told by men of power and tragedy, love and treachery featuring the likes of Aphrodite, Xi Shi, the Gorgon Medusa and Goddess Kali. These tales are endlessly fascinating yet rarely illuminating of the lives of actual women. So we'll hear from six songs offering a modern twist to these myths. They come from Jen Gloeckner, First Rebirth, Zoe Leela, Swoon, A Beautiful Curse and Ruxpin. I'm Jim Nye.</description><itunes:summary>This week we'll look at beauty and terror as seen in the mythology of women. Stories though out history mostly told by men of power and tragedy, love and treachery featuring the likes of Aphrodite, Xi Shi, The Gorgon Medusa and Goddess Kali. These tales are endlessly fascinating yet rarely illuminating of the lives of actual women. So we'll hear from six songs offering a modern twist to these myths. They come from Jen Gloeckner, First Rebirth, Zoe Leela, Swoon, A Beautiful Curse and Ruxpin. I'm Jim Nye.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/149050606Podcast149.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/149050606Podcast149.mp3" length="29825985" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>31:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #148</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Ed Drury, Melorman, Northcape, Bitbasic and Wordless Poem</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at five artists making deeply layered dense and hypnotic electronica. In the early part of the decade Minimalism, glitch and even chiptunes were a reaction to what became a pretty predictable set of recordings featuring 4 chord progressions and pedestrian beats. Now finding a new mix of drama and subtlety are Ed Drury, Melorman, Northcape, Bitbasic and Wordless Poem.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at five artists making deeply layered dense and hypnotic electronica. In the early part of the decade Minimalism, glitch and even chiptunes were a reaction to what became a pretty predictable set of recordings featuring 4 chord progressions and pedestrian beats. Now finding a new mix of drama and subtlety are Ed Drury, Melorman, Northcape, Bitbasic and Wordless Poem.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/148050606Podcast148.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/148050606Podcast148.mp3" length="27997414" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:09</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #147</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Secret Podsafe Mystery Artists</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we'll look at known knowns, known unknowns and unknown unknowns. For several weeks, half a dozen great songs have lingered on the desktop as I've looked for ways to include them on the show. They are by unknown, unsigned artists, well known indie bands and arena popular stars. All podsafe. This week I'll string them together and let you guess who they are. Film at 11.</description><itunes:summary>This week we'll look at known knowns, known unknowns and unknown unknowns. For several weeks, half a dozen great songs have lingered on the desktop as I've looked for ways to include them on the show. They are by unknown, unsigned artists, well known indie bands and arena popular stars. All podsafe. This week I'll string them together and let you guess who they are. Film at 11.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/147050606Podcast147.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/147050606Podcast147.mp3" length="29135517" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #146</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Idmer, Owen, Aydio, Gilo, The Sugar Clouds and Aereal</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the downcast and sorrowful. Baruch Spinoza defined sadness as the transfer of a person from a large perfection to a smaller one. All the songs on the show this week have an underlying sadness. They are small vignettes of personal loss and helplessness and yet they are not uncomfortable or painful. There is a soul cleansing purging quality that makes you feel raw and renewing. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the downcast and sorrowful. Baruch Spinoza defined sadness as the transfer of a person from a large perfection to a smaller one. All the songs on the show this week have an underlying sadness. They are small vignettes of personal loss and helplessness and yet they are not uncomfortable or painful. There is a soul cleansing purging quality that makes you feel raw and renewing..</itunes:summary><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/146050606Podcast146.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/146050606Podcast146.mp3" length="29658802" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:53</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #145</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Cycle Hiccups, Nulleins, Omnisine, Kiri Nami, Kosik and Rs3</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the final day. It's something we all have in common. The fact that everyone of us will die. To some it's simply a transition from one world to another. While others see it as the moment our atoms are dispersed back into the universe. How we choose to approach the final day defines almost everything we do in all the days that precede it.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the final day. It's something we all have in common. The fact that everyone of us will die. To some it's simply a transition from one world to another. While others see it as the moment our atoms are dispersed back into the universe. How we choose to approach the final day defines almost everything we do in all the days that precede it.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/145050606Podcast145.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/145050606Podcast145.mp3" length="28799478" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #144</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Blisaed, Bersarin Quartett, God Is An Astronaut, Kesakoo and Messian Dread</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at enormity and scale. Whether it's astrophysical or personal, size and distance is often difficult to gauge. Everyone has seen artist renderings of the solar system depicting the sun and planets but the scale of those drawing can't begin to reflect the actual distance between those satellites. The same is true with opinions and feelings. Often we feel so distant when in fact we share much more in common with each other than not. Other times not so much. Offering a guide this week are Blisaed, Bersarin Quartett, God Is An Astronaut, Kesakoo and Messian Dread.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at enormity and scale. Whether it's astrophysical or personal, size and distance is often difficult to gauge. Everyone has seen artist renderings of the solar system depicting the sun and planets but the scale of those drawing can't begin to reflect the actual distance between those satellites. The same is true with opinions and feelings. Often we feel so distant when in fact we share much more in common with each other than not. Other times not so much. Offering a guide this week are Blisaed, Bersarin Quartett, God Is An Astronaut, Kesakoo and Messian Dread.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/144050606Podcast144.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/144050606Podcast144.mp3" length="27889998" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #143</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Canola Tenderfoot, the silk demise, Makaras Pen, Anonymous Horses and Gabriel</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we marvel at the July 20th 1969 landing on the moon. Although this achievement took place 40 years ago and great strides have been made is subsequent years on furthering our reach into the stars, It continues to awe and inspire. Celebrating with us this week are Canola Tenderfoot, the silk demise, Makaras Pen, Anonymous Horses and Gabriel.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we marvel at the July 20th 1969 landing on the moon. Although this achievement took place 40 years ago and great strides have been made is subsequent years on furthering our reach into the stars, It continues to awe and inspire. Celebrating with us this week are Canola Tenderfoot, the silk demise, Makaras Pen, Anonymous Horses and Gabriel.  </itunes:summary><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/143050606Podcast143.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/143050606Podcast143.mp3" length="26871432" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #142</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Aphone, Eigenheimer, The Orientalist, Phour Trakk, Hands upon Black Earth and Ecovillage</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll examine the Phoenix. The Firebird, Feng-Huang, Ho-oo,  Benu, or Yel.  The myth of this self- rejuvenating bird cuts across almost every ancient culture often symbolizing death and rebirth. The Phoenix is said to consumed by fire every 500 years only to be reborn from its own ashes. Aphone, Eigenheimer, The Orientalist, Phour Trakk, Hands upon Black Earth and Ecovillage</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll examine the Phoenix. The Firebird, Feng-Huang, Ho-oo,  Benu, or Yel.  The myth of this self- rejuvenating bird cuts across almost every ancient culture often symbolizing death and rebirth. The Phoenix is said to consumed by fire every 500 years only to be reborn from its own ashes. Aphone, Eigenheimer, The Orientalist, Phour Trakk, Hands upon Black Earth and Ecovillage</itunes:summary><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/142050606Podcast142.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/142050606Podcast142.mp3" length="25264797" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:19</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
<title>Idyllic Music #141</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring J.S. Marti, Idyllic, Will Kriski, Tronic Koi, Scarlet Hideout, Half Past Sun, The Flavor Foundation, One Blue Nine and Jardin Solar</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at Angels and derivations, warnings and votaries. These nine artists are unafraid the bare the unvarnished, emblazon their influences and balance the devilish with the angelic. Some of the tracks are complete others remain ideas to be fleshed out but all compel. We'll hear from J.S. Marti, Idyllic, Will Kriski, Tronic Koi, Scarlet Hideout, Half Past Sun, The Flavor Foundation, One Blue Nine and Jardin Solar.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at Angels and derivations, warnings and votaries. These nine artists are unafraid the bare the unvarnished, emblazon their influences and balance the devilish with the angelic. Some of the tracks are complete others remain ideas to be fleshed out but all compel. We'll hear from J.S. Marti, Idyllic, Will Kriski, Tronic Koi, Scarlet Hideout, Half Past Sun, The Flavor Foundation, One Blue Nine and Jardin Solar.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/141050606Podcast141.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/141050606Podcast141.mp3" length="28321332" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:30</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music - One Hundred Forty</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Chris Martin, Phasen, Degiheugi, Azzurro, Hyqo, Volfoniq, Refrag, All India Radio and the Bombay Dub Orchestra</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the increasingly antiquated idea of old world versus new world especially in music and art. Cultures measured by millennia rather than centuries are borrowing and incorporating sounds and instruments in ways unthinkable in the past</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the increasingly antiquated idea of old world versus new world especially in music and art. Cultures measured by millennia rather than centuries are borrowing and incorporating sounds and instruments in ways unthinkable in the past</itunes:summary><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/140050606Podcast140.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/140050606Podcast140.mp3" length="29825985" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>31:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music - One Hundred Thirty Nine</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Mister Frendo, Subtronix, CD, Colab, Rude Corps and The Chill Conspiracy</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the human tendency to put off until later what we could do today. It is the period of time between when we can exercise influence over events and that moment when they are decided for us. That fine line between free will and fate.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the human tendency to put off until later what we could do today. It is the period of time between when we can exercise influence over events and that moment when they are decided for us. That fine line between free will and fate.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/139050606Podcast139.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/139050606Podcast139.mp3" length="25496764" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:33</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music - One Hundred Thirty Eight</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Bangguru, Nobara Hayakawa, Artemis, Jikjax, Elam, PiliPili and Bruce McCosar</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, it's world studies as we look at education and educators from around the world from ancient Greece to the local school down the street. The syllabus is wide open as we hear from Bangguru, Nobara Hayakawa, Artemis, Jikjax, Elam, PiliPili and Bruce McCosar.</description><itunes:summary>This week, it's world studies as we look at education and educators from around the world from ancient Greece to the local school down the street. The syllabus is wide open as we hear from Bangguru, Nobara Hayakawa, Artemis, Jikjax, Elam, PiliPili and Bruce McCosar.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/138050606Podcast138.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/138050606Podcast138.mp3" length="38256706" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:53</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music - One Hundred Thirty Seven</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring 46 Bliss, Pierre the Moon, MoVox, Screenatorium, Classic SciFi and Catsauce</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at memories and the way we twist them inside out sometimes to serve our own purposes. Looking back on this episode of Idyllic Music are 46 Bliss, Pierre the Moon, MoVox, Screenatorium, Classic SciFi and Catsauce. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at memories and the way we twist them inside out sometimes to serve our own purposes. Looking back on this episode of Idyllic Music are 46 Bliss, Pierre the Moon, MoVox, Screenatorium, Classic SciFi and Catsauce. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/137050606Podcast137.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/137050606Podcast137.mp3" length="39857006" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music - One Hundred Thirty Six</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Bernd Burnson, Kristan Mainhart, Kesakoo, Skipless and Beatropolis</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the great American art form as it finds its way into the 21st century. Jazz continues to evolve in ways that are both striking and familiar. Just as Charlie Parker and Charlie Christian took popular music and stripped it to its core before radically making it their own, today's musicians are taking the cut and paste technology of hip hop and using it to disassemble, rearrange and rethink the process of improvisation. As Frank Zappa famously said "Jazz is not dead...it just smells funny"</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the great American art form as it finds its way into the 21st century. Jazz continues to evolve in ways that are both striking and familiar. Just as Charlie Parker and Charlie Christian took popular music and stripped it to its core before radically making it their own, today's musicians are taking the cut and paste technology of hip hop and using it to disassemble, rearrange and rethink the process of improvisation. As Frank Zappa famously said "Jazz is not dead...it just smells funny"</itunes:summary><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/136050606Podcast136.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/136050606Podcast136.mp3" length="25202521" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music - One Hundred Thirty Five</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Mujaji, Proviant Audio, The Orb, DJ Limpet and Dr.Ektoplazmic</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at solids. The two hardest things to grasp about them are that objects that appear to be solid are made up of molecules that are never actually in contact with each other and that because solids have thermal energy, their atoms vibrate. Firming up this concept for us are Mujaji, Proviant Audio, The Orb, DJ Limpet and Dr. Ektoplazmic.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at solids. The two hardest things to grasp about them are that objects that appear to be solid are made up of molecules that are never actually in contact with each other and that because solids have thermal energy, their atoms vibrate. Firming up this concept for us are Mujaji, Proviant Audio, The Orb, DJ Limpet and Dr. Ektoplazmic.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/135050606Podcast135.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/135050606Podcast135.mp3" length="25100539" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:09</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
<title>Idyllic Music - One Hundred Thirty Four</title> 
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Band of Mad Women, Margareds, Mat's,Gosprom, Stockfinster and Line</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the shortcomings and foibles of the post modern character. Not nearly the deadly sins but some common universal human weaknesses we all can recognize. Pointing them out to us on the episode of Idyllic Music are Band of Mad Women, Margareds, Mat's,Gosprom, Stockfinster and Line.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the shortcomings and foibles of the post modern character. Not nearly the deadly sins but some common universal human weaknesses we all can recognize. Pointing them out to us on the episode of Idyllic Music are Band of Mad Women, Margareds, Mat's,Gosprom, Stockfinster and Line.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/134050606Podcast134.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/134050606Podcast134.mp3" length="26499030" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:36</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Thirty Three</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Cris Tanzi, Prototype 68, CDK, The Reverent Shortboy, Steen Throtrup and iambic</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the unlikelihood of finding true love. Not that it doesn't happen all the time, it's just that's it's amazing that it happens at all. Bookstores are filled with  attempting to explain how and why relationships succeed or fail. The odds of finding someone with whom you are truly compatible with is daunting. Taking the plunge anyway are Cris Tanzi, Prototype 68, CDK, The Reverent Shortboy, Steen Throtrup and iambic</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the unlikelihood of finding true love. Not that it doesn't happen all the time, it's just that's it's amazing that it happens at all. Bookstores are filled with  attempting to explain how and why relationships succeed or fail. The odds of finding someone with whom you are truly compatible with is daunting. Taking the plunge anyway are Cris Tanzi, Prototype 68, CDK, The Reverent Shortboy, Steen Throtrup and iambic</itunes:summary><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/133050606Podcast133.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/133050606Podcast133.mp3" length="26629016" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:44</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Thirty Two</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring All India Radio, Plastik Joy, Matisse and Deeper Sublime, Eskazed, Blind Divine and Gate Zero</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the many aspects  of melencolia. In particular, German Renaissance master Albrecht Durer engraving of the same name. We can linger over the many symbols of mathematics and alchemy portrayed in the work but ultimately it's all about how one feels. Expounding and deflecting for us this week are All India Radio, Plastik Joy, Matisse and Deeper Sublime, Eskazed, Blind Divine and Gate Zero</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the many aspects  of melencolia. In particular, German Renaissance master Albrecht Durer engraving of the same name. We can linger over the many symbols of mathematics and alchemy portrayed in the work but ultimately it's all about how one feels. Expounding and deflecting for us this week are All India Radio, Plastik Joy, Matisse and Deeper Sublime, Eskazed, Blind Divine and Gate Zero</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/132050606Podcast132.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/132050606Podcast132.mp3" length="28592170" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:47</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Thirty One</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring USB, Tracing Arcs, General Fuzz, Orange Fuzz and Lili Hirakawa</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the life giving and restorative power of water. While water is the most abundant molecule on Earth's surface and nearly 60% of the human body is water, we often take for granted is enormous importance. Since all water is essentially the same, it is what is dissolved into it that accounts for the differences we consume whether our freshwater comes from deep in Lake Baikal or from the muddy Mississippi. Having recovered recently from a lingering flu virus, I came tell you water..and drinking huge glasses of it were instrumental in ridding me of that illness. And so the show is all about water. Drink up.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the life giving and restorative power of water. While water is the most abundant molecule on Earth's surface and nearly 60% of the human body is water, we often take for granted is enormous importance. Since all water is essentially the same, it is what is dissolved into it that accounts for the differences we consume whether our freshwater comes from deep in Lake Baikal or from the muddy Mississippi. Having recovered recently from a lingering flu virus, I came tell you water..and drinking huge glasses of it were instrumental in ridding me of that illness. And so the show is all about water. Drink up.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/131050606Podcast131.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/131050606Podcast131.mp3" length="27538913" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:41</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Thirty</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Downliners Sekt, Naoned, Sans Edge, Tryad and Silence </itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the need to move beyond our troubled pasts and embrace hope for the future. Each of these tracks evokes a specific moment particular to American political history. We'll hear from Downliners Sekt, Naoned, Sans Edge, Tryad and Silence.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the need to move beyond our troubled pasts and embrace hope for the future. Each of these tracks evokes a specific moment particular to American political history. We'll hear from Downliners Sekt, Naoned, Sans Edge, Tryad and Silence.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/130050606Podcast130.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/130050606Podcast130.mp3" length="25127288" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:10</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Twenty Nine</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Owen, DigiTube, Argon 40, Vate, 33Canales and Babbaracos</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the path to redemption. Waiting to hit bottom to know when to climb back up often ignores the notion that the journey may well be circular. Redeeming them selves for us this week at Owen, DigiTube, Argon 40, Vate, 33Canales and Babbaracos.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the path to redemption. Waiting to hit bottom to know when to climb back up often ignores the notion that the journey may well be circular. Redeeming them selves for us this week at Owen, DigiTube, Argon 40, Vate, 33Canales and Babbaracos.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/129050606Podcast129.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/129050606Podcast129.mp3" length="28758100" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Twenty Eight</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring enLounge, Victoria Mosley  and The Sublimes, Indidginus, Null Device and Electric Salmon </itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the mind expanding possiblities of travel. Whether global or microbiological, it the movement of bodies, objects and, ultimately, ideas, that allow us the benefits of progress. And so We'll hear from enLounge, Victoria Mosley and The Sublimes, Indidginus, Null Device and Electric Salmon.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the mind expanding possiblities of travel. Whether global or microbiological, it the movement of bodies, objects and, ultimately, ideas, that allow us the benefits of progress. And so We'll hear from enLounge, Victoria Mosley and The Sublimes, Indidginus, Null Device and Electric Salmon.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/128050606Podcast128.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/128050606Podcast128.mp3" length="25317878" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Twenty Seven</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Peach Stealing Monkeys, Electricwest, Entertainment for the Braindead, Picou and Dep. </itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at a human weakness. Whether physical, emotional or spiritual, we all make blunders and mistakes. It's what we do afterward that counts. We'll hear from five artists who realize this and take the next step toward  growth and healing. We'll begin with something new from Peach Stealing Monkeys.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at a human weakness. Whether physical, emotional or spiritual, we all make blunders and mistakes. It's what we do afterward that counts. We'll hear from five artists who realize this and take the next step toward  growth and healing. We'll begin with something new from Peach Stealing Monkeys.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/127050606Podcast127.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/127050606Podcast127.mp3" length="24219648" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:13</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Twenty Six</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Dive Index, Alikproject, Under, Asa Zen'Sei and Nenes</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at what's underneath. Not necessarily inferior, lesser, or subordinate but from the unique perspective of looking up. Gazing upward are Dive Index, Alikproject, Under, Asa Zen Sei and Nenes.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at what's underneath. Not necessarily inferior, lesser, or subordinate but from the unique perspective of looking up. Gazing upward are Dive Index, Alikproject, Under, Asa Zen Sei and Nenes.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/126050606Podcast126.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/126050606Podcast126.mp3" length="27091696" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:13</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Twenty Five</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Kmotiv, Secret Archives of the Vatican, Bone Shaman, Banderlog and Sara Ayers</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll take a look at idea that the visible world is pervaded by invisible forces or spirits, which affect the lives of the living. It's a belief that predates most mainstream religions and remains in many ways we may not immediately recognize. Much of today's electronic club music employs many techniques shared by shamanism. The beat, repetitive vocal samples and binaural beats. There is a reason we call it Trance. Displaying some of this otherworldliness are Kmotiv, Secret Archives of the Vatican, Bone Shaman, Banderlog and Sara Ayers.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll take a look at idea that the visible world is pervaded by invisible forces or spirits, which affect the lives of the living. It's a belief that predates most mainstream religions and remains in many ways we may not immediately recognize. Much of today's electronic club music employs many techniques shared by shamanism. The beat, repetitive vocal samples and binaural beats. There is a reason we call it Trance. Displaying some of this otherworldliness are Kmotiv, Secret Archives of the Vatican, Bone Shaman, Banderlog and Sara Ayers.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/125050606Podcast125.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/125050606Podcast125.mp3" length="26920751" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:02</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Twenty Four</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Dikital, Cling, Lesley Dodd, David Byrne and Brian Eno, J-CLX and Vincent Wood</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at Strange Overtones. It's not only the title of a new collaboration between modern music Giants, David Byrne and Brian Eno but also in a harmonic sense, it's a complex and intriguing musical tone. We'll hear from six artists who take this familiar but different approach to their sound. There is Dikital, Cling, Lesley Dodd, David Byrne and Brian Eno, J-CLX and Vincent Wood. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at Strange Overtones. It's not only the title of a new collaboration between modern music Giants, David Byrne and Brian Eno but also in a harmonic sense, it's a complex and intriguing musical tone. We'll hear from six artists who take this familiar but different approach to their sound. There is Dikital, Cling, Lesley Dodd, David Byrne and Brian Eno, J-CLX and Vincent Wood. </itunes:summary><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/124050606Podcast124.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/124050606Podcast124.mp3" length="26597669" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:42</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Twenty Three</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Pipo Pegoraro, Obedientbone, Mavro, ElodieO and Crystal Palace</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at cosmetics or altering the appearance without affecting the body's structure or functions. It's by definition superficial but can change perceptions of oneself and others often for the better but not necessarily. Musical remixes are in essence cosmetics but so are tattoos and eyeliner. Setting the foundation for us are Pipo Pegoraro, Obedientbone, Mavro, ElodieO and Crystal Palace.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at cosmetics or altering the appearance without affecting the body's structure or functions. It's by definition superficial but can change perceptions of oneself and others often for the better but not necessarily. Musical remixes are in essence cosmetics but so are tattoos and eyeliner. Setting the foundation for us are Pipo Pegoraro, Obedientbone, Mavro, ElodieO and Crystal Palace.</itunes:summary><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/123050606Podcast123.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/123050606Podcast123.mp3" length="26593907" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:42</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Twenty Two</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Sub Dub, Conduct Unbecoming, Fraud Fix, Lendi Vexer, DJ Diganta, Queenie and Siberian Newspaper</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll listen to the percussive side of World Music. Seven bands will add subtle electronics to the inherently primitive act of striking a note. Providing the variation for us are Sub Dub, Conduct Unbecoming, Fraud Fix, Lendi Vexer, DJ Diganta, Queenie and Siberian Newspaper. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll listen to the percussive side of World Music. Seven bands will add subtle electronics to the inherently primitive act of striking a note. Providing the variation for us are Sub Dub, Conduct Unbecoming, Fraud Fix, Lendi Vexer, DJ Diganta, Queenie and Siberian Newspaper. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/122050606Podcast122.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/122050606Podcast122.mp3" length="29228304" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:26</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Twenty One</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Anneke Laurent, Yimino, Gilo, Nihaya Tree and Annie Goliath</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the essential symbiosis of independent artist and podcaster. This mutualism is best put forward by an association of cooperative relationships. In particular, an Association of Music Podcasting. Visit myspace.com/musicpodcasters to learn how artists and podcasters can help each other in a world of tight play list and tighter labels. We'll hear from Anneke Laurent, Yimino, Gilo, Nihaya Tree and Annie Goliath. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the essential symbiosis of independent artist and podcaster. This mutualism is best put forward by an association of cooperative relationships. In particular, an Association of Music Podcasting. Visit myspace.com/musicpodcasters to learn how artists and podcasters can help each other in a world of tight play list and tighter labels. We'll hear from Anneke Laurent, Yimino, Gilo, Nihaya Tree and Annie Goliath. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/121050606Podcast121.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/121050606Podcast121.mp3" length="26333518" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:25</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Twenty</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Avatar, Psychedelicious, Sharon Robinson, Chillerstadt, Groove Inc and Beatropolis</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, it's the many flavors of America's great art form. Jazz. For more than a century this style of music has refused strict categorization. From Bop to Rag, Funk to Swing the cool sounds of Jazz are always mixing with and attaching itself to other genres. Today the polyrhythms, syncopation, and blue notes blend seamlessly with electronic beats, bass and melody. Exploring this musical confluence are Avatar, Psychedelicious, Sharon Robinson, Chillerstadt, Groove Inc and Beatropolis. </description><itunes:summary>This week, it's the many flavors of America's great art form. Jazz. For more than a century this style of music has refused strict categorization. From Bop to Rag, Funk to Swing the cool sounds of Jazz are always mixing with and attaching itself to other genres. Today the polyrhythms, syncopation, and blue notes blend seamlessly with electronic beats, bass and melody. Exploring this musical confluence are Avatar, Psychedelicious, Sharon Robinson, Chillerstadt, Groove Inc and Beatropolis. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/120050606Podcast120.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/120050606Podcast120.mp3" length="27671824" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Nineteen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Antony Raijekov, Dildo, G (HU), Messian Dread, Moosefrog and Meme</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we'll try unlikely pairings. Nowhere are they more readily accepted than in music. When Joe Venuti's violin first played jazz, or Kraftwerk hit the top of the charts with computer music, listeners nodded and said "Yeah'. When Kate Bush brought the mystery of Eastern European harmonies to the west or the Beatles covered Little Richard new rock n' roll music, the world got a bit smaller, less separate and more inclusive. Today we listen to songs by people from across the globe we would, likely, not have had a chance to hear in a lifetime. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week we'll try unlikely pairings. Nowhere are they more readily accepted than in music. When Joe Venuti's violin first played jazz, or Kraftwerk hit the top of the charts with computer music, listeners nodded and said "Yeah'. When Kate Bush brought the mystery of Eastern European harmonies to the west or the Beatles covered Little Richard new rock n' roll music, the world got a bit smaller, less separate and more inclusive. Today we listen to songs by people from across the globe we would, likely, not have had a chance to hear in a lifetime.I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/119050606Podcast119.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/119050606Podcast119.mp3" length="25582864" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Eighteen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Way, The Stringed Theory, postscript, Roll Film and Ronan Dec</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, it's feedback and reverb, the mathematics of sound and physics of music. Looking into this super symmetry are Way, The Stringed Theory, postscript, Roll Film and Ronan Dec. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week, it's feedback and reverb, the mathematics of sound and physics of music. Looking into this super symmetry are Way, The Stringed Theory, postscript, Roll Film and Ronan Dec. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/118050606Podcast118.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/118050606Podcast118.mp3" length="24382067" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:23</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Seventeen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Azoora, Kesakoo, My Toys Like Me, Juliet Hotel, Darren Scott Nesbit and The Chill Conspiracy.</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at artists in exile. Not those forced from their homes through political or legal turmoil but the more romantic expatriation of the kind envisioned by Henry Miller, Ernest Hemingway and Graham Greene. The 'Lost Generation', living in hotels, on allowance and awaiting inspiration. Finding their muse this week are Azoora, Kesakoo, My Toys Like Me, Juliet Hotel, Darren Scott Nesbit and The Chill Conspiracy. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at artists in exile. Not those forced from their homes through political or legal turmoil but the more romantic expatriation of the kind envisioned by Henry Miller, Ernest Hemingway and Graham Greene. The 'Lost Generation', living in hotels, on allowance and awaiting inspiration. Finding their muse this week are Azoora, Kesakoo, My Toys Like Me, Juliet Hotel, Darren Scott Nesbit and The Chill Conspiracy. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/117050606Podcast117.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/117050606Podcast117.mp3" length="27776731" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Sixteen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Screenatorium, Lasswell, Synthetic, Electric Hippies, Fauna and Endlos.</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll examine the creative process. Painter Kimberly Brooks offers up and octet of stages of which six match the songs on this episode of Idyllic Music. They are Vision and Hope. Excitement, Clarity, Obsession and Resolution. Look for these in music of Screenatorium, Lasswell, Synthetic, Electric Hippies, Fauna and Endlos. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll examine the creative process. Painter Kimberly Brooks offers up and octet of stages of which six match the songs on this episode of Idyllic Music. They are Vision and Hope. Excitement, Clarity, Obsession and Resolution. Look for these in music of Screenatorium, Lasswell, Synthetic, Electric Hippies, Fauna and Endlos. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/116050606Podcast116.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/116050606Podcast116.mp3" length="28270341" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:26</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Fifteen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Polished Chrome, Return To Mono, Letters In Numbers and Cassettes Won't Listen</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the tension created when fashion comes full circle. As Massive Attack's Tricky points out you have "A dread of the past and fear of the future. You're brand new, You're retro" Finding that singular point for us on the edition of Idyllic Music are Polished Chrome, Return To Mono, Letters In Numbers and Cassettes Won't Listen. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the tension created when fashion comes full circle. As Massive Attack's Tricky points out you have "A dread of the past and fear of the future. You're brand new, You're retro" Finding that singular point for us on the edition of Idyllic Music are Polished Chrome, Return To Mono, Letters In Numbers and Cassettes Won't Listen. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/115050606Podcast115.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/115050606Podcast115.mp3" length="27143105" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:16</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Fourteen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Trifonic, QuiOui, the silk demise, Orange Crush, DRT, Humus Luminus-Quinslonn and Tacet</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we'll spotlight mendacity. There was a time, not long ago, when you could assume a benchmark of truthfulness. Not from everyone or about everything but you could feel fairly secure in the notion that you weren't being lied to about the big things, all the time, with a straight face. Exploring the sad state of this tendency to lie are Trifonic, QuiOui, the silk demise, Orange Crush, DRT, Humus Luminus-Quinslonn and Tacet. </description><itunes:summary>This week we'll spotlight mendacity. There was a time, not long ago, when you could assume a benchmark of truthfulness. Not from everyone or about everything but you could feel fairly secure in the notion that you weren't being lied to about the big things, all the time, with a straight face. Exploring the sad state of this tendency to lie are Trifonic, QuiOui, the silk demise, Orange Crush, DRT, Humus Luminus-Quinslonn and Tacet. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/114050606Podcast114.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/114050606Podcast114.mp3" length="25913887" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Thirteen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Steric Hindrance, NeiLicis, Clear Plastic, Rude Corps, Sardinia Bass Legalize and Electric Salmon</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at ruins and relics. Places long abandoned for more promising prospects. Whether ancient or post-modern they recall a measure of greatness that evokes more sadness than nostalgia. Leading our tour on this episode of Idyllic Music are Steric Hindrance, NeiLicis, Clear Plastic, Rude Corps, Sardinia Bass Legalize and Electric Salmon. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at ruins and relics. Places long abandoned for more promising prospects. Whether ancient or post-modern they recall a measure of greatness that evokes more sadness than nostalgia. Leading our tour on this episode of Idyllic Music are Steric Hindrance, NeiLicis, Clear Plastic, Rude Corps, Sardinia Bass Legalize and Electric Salmon. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/113050606Podcast113.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/113050606Podcast113.mp3" length="24559282" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Twelve</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring The Uberkids, The Artificial Sea, Monotronaut, Dive Index, onkgusD, Stabilizer and Schev</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we'll explore the edge of the world. A point on the horizon that marks the end of what is known and all that lies beyond. It's a gray, ill-defined area that defies the usual measurements. Making concerted efforts to try this week are The Uberkids, The Artificial Sea, Monotronaut, Dive Index, onkgusD, Stabilizer and Schev. </description><itunes:summary>This week we'll explore the edge of the world. A point on the horizon that marks the end of what is known and all that lies beyond. It's a gray, ill-defined area that defies the usual measurements. Making concerted efforts to try this week are The Uberkids, The Artificial Sea, Monotronaut, Dive Index, onkgusD, Stabilizer and Schev. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/112050606Podcast112.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/112050606Podcast112.mp3" length="26983027" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:06</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Eleven: The Orb Special</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring The Orb</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll feature the music of the Orb. Of all the bands that inspired us and helped formulate the scope of this program, it was The Orb's determination to move the mind as well as the hips. Blending the pioneering electronica of Tangerine Dream and the beats of Chicago's warehouse scene with the deep dub of Scratch Perry and Byrne and Eno's Bush of Ghosts sampling, The Orb remain a central pillar of today's electronic music.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll feature the music of the Orb. Of all the bands that inspired us and helped formulate the scope of this program, it was The Orb's determination to move the mind as well as the hips. Blending the pioneering electronica of Tangerine Dream and the beats of Chicago's warehouse scene with the deep dub of Scratch Perry and Byrne and Eno's Bush of Ghosts sampling, The Orb remain a central pillar of today's electronic music.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/111050606Podcast111.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/111050606Podcast111.mp3" length="27739115" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:53</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Ten</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Canola Tenderfoot, Salaryman, Scanlan, I Awake and Elika</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the great choice each of us must make between the physical and the moral, happiness and virtue. How we choose to define the greater good sets the path we follow in life. The great challenge is to find a way to bring these mutually exclusive, incompatible values together and find some way of reconciling them. We'll hear from Canola Tenderfoot, Salaryman, Scanlan, I Awake and Elika. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the great choice each of us must make between the physical and the moral, happiness and virtue. How we choose to define the greater good sets the path we follow in life. The great challenge is to find a way to bring these mutually exclusive, incompatible values together and find some way of reconciling them. We'll hear from Canola Tenderfoot, Salaryman, Scanlan, I Awake and Elika. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/110050606Podcast110.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/110050606Podcast110.mp3" length="26404571" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:30</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Nine</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Ten and Tracer, l Orchestre A-Dakar, Black Era, MarinuZz and Please</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, it's another globetrotting episode of Idyllic Music as we find inspiration in 3 continents in a mashup from 5 countries including Italy, Senegal, The U.S. Sweden and the Netherlands. We'll hear from Ten and Tracer, l Orchestre A-Dakar, Black Era, MarinuZz and Please. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week, it's another globetrotting episode of Idyllic Music as we find inspiration in 3 continents in a mashup from 5 countries including Italy, Senegal, The U.S. Sweden and the Netherlands. We'll hear from Ten and Tracer, l Orchestre A-Dakar, Black Era, MarinuZz and Please. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/109050606Podcast109.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/109050606Podcast109.mp3" length="25102211" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Eight</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Inadubstate, Soo P and the Outsider, Yamasaki, Dr.Awkward, Atomica, Jah Wobble and Foa Hoka</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll take a poke at Satan, The Devil, Beelzebub or El Diablito. Whether or not you think he is an actual being or a manifestation of our universal need to personify evil, the concept of hell is as pervasive an idea as there is. From Robert Johnson to the White Stripes, there is no denying the fear or promise of hell has been a part of music for a long time. Sorting it all out for us this week are Inadubstate, Soo P and the Outsider, Yamasaki, Dr.Awkward, Atomica, Jah Wobble and Foa Hoka. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll take a poke at Satan, The Devil, Beelzebub or El Diablito. Whether or not you think he is an actual being or a manifestation of our universal need to personify evil, the concept of hell is as pervasive an idea as there is. From Robert Johnson to the White Stripes, there is no denying the fear or promise of hell has been a part of music for a long time. Sorting it all out for us this week are Inadubstate, Soo P and the Outsider, Yamasaki, Dr. Awkward, Atomica, Jah Wobble and Foa Hoka. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/108050606podcast108.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/108050606podcast108.mp3" length="26150452" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:14</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Seven</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Iambic, Karmacoda, Plastercluster, TCK and Rafael Aragon</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at metaphors, similes and allegories. These Figures of Rhetoric color our languages and influence the way we describe music. Adding relish and piquancy to this addition of Idyllic music are Iambic, Karmacoda, Plastercluster, TCK and Rafael Aragon. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at metaphors, similes and allegories. These Figures of Rhetoric color our languages and influence the way we describe music. Adding relish and piquancy to this addition of Idyllic music are Iambic, Karmacoda, Plastercluster, TCK and Rafael Aragon. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/107050606podcast107.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/107050606podcast107.mp3" length="25707416" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Six</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Kristin Hersh, Merlune, Weigl and Hoffman, Telafonica, Mudville and SoundShifter</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the excitement, obsession, twists, and serenity of first romance. The magic of first love is our ignorance that it can ever end. Exploring the first time on this edition of Idyllic Music are Kristin Hersh, Merlune, Weigl and Hoffman, Telafonica, Mudville and SoundShifter. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the excitement, obsession, twists, and serenity of first romance. The magic of first love is our ignorance that it can ever end. Exploring the first time on this edition of Idyllic Music are Kristin Hersh, Merlune, Weigl and Hoffman, Telafonica, Mudville and SoundShifter. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/106050606podcast106.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/106050606podcast106.mp3" length="27798465" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Five</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Fauna, Milieu, Sirk, Bersarin Quartett and Margareds</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, the chillout continues in the land of the long winters. Five artists from the Baltic region provide the heat for this frigid episode of Idyllic music. They are Fauna, Milieu, Sirk, Bersarin Quartett and Margareds. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week, the chillout continues in the land of the long winters. Five artists from the Baltic region provide the heat for this frigid episode of Idyllic music. They are Fauna, Milieu, Sirk, Bersarin Quartett and Margareds. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/105050606podcast105.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/105050606podcast105.mp3" length="25953176" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:02</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Four</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Korev, Artemis, Lex Nasa and Savoir Vivre.</itunes:subtitle><description>This week, we'll look at the coming and going, beginnings and ends and the state of things at those two points. Starting and stopping with us on this episode are Korev, Artemis, Lex Nasa and Savoir Vivre. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the coming and going, beginnings and ends and the state of things at those two points. Starting and stopping with us on this episode are Korev, Artemis, Lex Nasa and Savoir Vivre. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/104050606podcast104.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/104050606podcast104.mp3" length="25502198" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:33</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Three</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Fringe, Musetta, Jamdeluxe, Minor Chill, Echo TM and Peach Stealing Monkeys.</itunes:subtitle><description>This week we'll consider the boarding house. Where people of all stripes rent rooms for one or more nights, and sometimes weeks, months and years. Boarders who otherwise would have nothing in common might share evening meals and a common living room. And so this week's Idyllic lodgers include Fringe, Musetta, Jamdeluxe, Minor Chill, Echo TM and Peach Stealing Monkeys. I'm the proprietor, Jim Nye.</description><itunes:summary>This week we'll consider the boarding house. Where people of all stripes rent rooms for one or more nights, and sometimes weeks, months and years. Boarders who otherwise would have nothing in common might share evening meals and a common living room. And so this week's Idyllic lodgers include Fringe, Musetta, Jamdeluxe, Minor Chill, Echo TM and Peach Stealing Monkeys. I'm the proprietor, Jim Nye.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/103050606podcast103.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/103050606podcast103.mp3" length="25831131" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred Two</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Sublimatus, Daakoon, Conrad Belfort, Juno6, Orbique and Synthastazia.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, it's adventure. The kind imagined by the great turn of the century authors like Kipling, Burroughs, Wells and Verne. 100 years hence on Idyllic Music, we offer Sublimatus, Daakoon, Conrad Belfort, Juno6, Orbique and Synthastazia. </description><itunes:summary>This week, it's adventure. The kind imagined by the great turn of the century authors like Kipling, Burroughs, Wells and Verne. 100 years hence on Idyllic Music, we offer Sublimatus, Daakoon, Conrad Belfort, Juno6, Orbique and Synthastazia. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/102050606podcast102.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/102050606podcast102.mp3" length="25756735" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred One</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Cling, Omihoshbin, Subtronik, 2 Bone Giants, Vim Cortez and Amanda Jayne</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at the Sun. The periodic table lists 117 elements in the universe yet the sun is mostly just hydrogen and helium. Its simplicity belies its enormous life giving value in both a physical and spiritual sense. Exploring this paradox for us on this edition of Idyllic Music are Cling, Omihoshbin, Subtronik, 2 Bone Giants, Vim Cortez and Amanda Jayne. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the Sun. The periodic table lists 117 elements in the universe yet the sun is mostly just hydrogen and helium. Its simplicity belies its enormous life giving value in both a physical and spiritual sense. Exploring this paradox for us on this edition of Idyllic Music are Cling, Omihoshbin, Subtronik, 2 Bone Giants, Vim Cortez and Amanda Jayne. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/101050606podcast101.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/101050606podcast101.mp3" length="25505541" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred (Instrumentals)</title>
<itunes:subtitle> 100th Episode Listener Appreciation 'Instrumentals' CD</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, on the 100th episode of Idyllic Music, we hope to honor the many regular listeners of this podcast with CD ready mixes of the best instrumental tracks heard on the show over the past two years. Don, Mika, Stephen and I have gleaned the archives and will offer up these two mixes unencumbered by the usual patter so that you can burn them directly to the blank CD of your choice. We have two podcast mp3 files of nearly 80 minutes worth of the best music featured over the two years.</description><itunes:summary>This week, on the 100th episode of Idyllic Music, we hope to honor the many regular listeners of this podcast with two CD ready mixes of the best vocal and instrumental tracks heard on the show over the past two years. Don, Mika, Stephen and I have gleaned the archives and will offer up these two mixes unencumbered by the usual patter so that you can burn them directly to the blank CD of your choice. We have two podcast mp3 files of nearly 80 minutes worth of the best music featured over the two years.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/100imix.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/100imix.mp3" length="76484083" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>79:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One Hundred (Songs)</title>
<itunes:subtitle> 100th Episode Listener Appreciation 'Songs' CD</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, on the 100th episode of Idyllic Music, we hope to honor the many regular listeners of this podcast with CD ready mixes of the best vocal tracks heard on the show over the past two years. Don, Mika, Stephen and I have gleaned the archives and will offer up these two mixes unencumbered by the usual patter so that you can burn them directly to the blank CD of your choice. We have two podcast mp3 files of nearly 80 minutes worth of the best music featured over the two years.  Picking only these songs proved difficult.</description><itunes:summary>This week, on the 100th episode of Idyllic Music, we hope to honor the many regular listeners of this podcast with two CD ready mixes of the best vocal and instrumental tracks heard on the show over the past two years. Don, Mika, Stephen and I have gleaned the archives and will offer up these two mixes unencumbered by the usual patter so that you can burn them directly to the blank CD of your choice. We have two podcast mp3 files of nearly 80 minutes worth of the best music featured over the two years.  Picking only these songs proved difficult.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/100vmix.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/100vmix.mp3" length="76718140" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>79:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Ninety Nine</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring HerbalJ, Audiokonstrukte, Terence Blanchard, Wurlitztraction and Misosoup</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll contemplate the patient ear. The following five tracks require time. At least they did for me. Each one finds its stride at precisely the right moment for that song and that make them special. Taking their own sweet time about it are HerbalJ, Audiokonstrukte, Terence Blanchard, Wurlitztraction and Misosoup.  At the end of the program, I'll have a few words about our 100th episode and give away.</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll contemplate the patient ear. The following five tracks require time. At least they did for me. Each one finds its stride at precisely the right moment for that song and that make them special. Taking their own sweet time about it are HerbalJ, Audiokonstrukte, Terence Blanchard, Wurlitztraction and Misosoup.  At the end of the program, I'll have a few words about our 100th episode and give away.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/99050606podcast99.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/99050606podcast99.mp3" length="26775301" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:53</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Ninety Eight</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring DubDriver, Tokyo507, Omnisine, Mystic Village and Soma Sonic</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, East meets West for a soft clash or happy mesh of global culture. It's the musical migration that may be our best hope toward understanding and acceptance of each other. Helping us along are DubDriver, Tokyo507, Omnisine, Mystic Village and Soma Sonic. </description><itunes:summary>This week, East meets West for a soft clash or happy mesh of global culture. It's the musical migration that may be our best hope toward understanding and acceptance of each other. Helping us along are DubDriver, Tokyo507, Omnisine, Mystic Village and Soma Sonic. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/98050606podcast98.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/98050606podcast98.mp3" length="27016046" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Ninety Seven</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Laki Mera, The Chill Conspiracy, Lich, to the sea with me and Radio Orphans</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at fair-trade music. Over the past several years, three things have changed the course of popular music, for better or worse. First came the marriage of music and video and the overwhelming marketing power it presented. It was an expensive tool requiring serious funding by record labels loathe to take chances on what they viewed as a commodity. Next was the advent of personal digital recording allowing bands to record professional quality music on a shoestring and finally the Internet offered the ability for bands to market their own music. Fair-trade music acknowledges this and offers a new relationship between artist and fan. Embracing the new paradigm are Laki Mera, The Chill Conspiracy, Lich, to the sea with me and Radio Orphans. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at fair-trade music. Over the past several years, three things have changed the course of popular music, for better or worse. First came the marriage of music and video and the overwhelming marketing power it presented. It was an expensive tool requiring serious funding by record labels loathe to take chances on what they viewed as a commodity. Next was the advent of personal digital recording allowing bands to record professional quality music on a shoestring and finally the Internet offered the ability for bands to market their own music. Fair-trade music acknowledges this and offers a new relationship between artist and fan. Embracing the new paradigm are Laki Mera, The Chill Conspiracy, Lich, to the sea with me and Radio Orphans. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/97050606podcast97.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/97050606podcast97.mp3" length="24333166" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:20</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Ninety Six</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring AguaFlames, Neko Neko, Alu, Neil Smith, Indidginus and Orange Crush</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look beyond the Lost Horizon for the mythical places, hidden and elusive. They are known by names like El Dorado, Shangri-La, Avalon, Atlantis or Utopia. Guiding our way on this episode of Idyllic music are AguaFlames, Neko Neko, Alu, Neil Smith, Indidginus and Orange Crush. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look beyond the Lost Horizon for the mythical places, hidden and elusive. They are known by names like El Dorado, Shangri-La, Avalon, Atlantis or Utopia. Guiding our way on this episode of Idyllic music are AguaFlames, Neko Neko, Alu, Neil Smith, Indidginus and Orange Crush. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/96050606podcast96.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/96050606podcast96.mp3" length="27809750" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:58</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Ninety Five</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring USB, Under, Crisopa, Aquanaut and HypNo</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at transportation. It's the getting from one place to another that takes up so much of our time whether it's physically or spiritually. So we'll explore the conventional and not so conventional ways of getting around with the help of USB, Under, Crisopa, Aquanaut and HypNo. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at transportation. It's the getting from one place to another that takes up so much of our time whether it's physically or spiritually. So we'll explore the conventional and not so conventional ways of getting around with the help of USB, Under, Crisopa, Aquanaut and HypNo. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/95050606podcast95.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/95050606podcast95.mp3" length="27059931" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:11</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Ninety Four</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Bluba Lu, Kalahari Surfers, QuiOui and Volfoniq</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look for the lost, the secret, the rushed and hypnotic with the help of four bands who have made distinctive contributions to independent music in their home countries. They are Bluba Lu, Kalahari Surfers, QuiOui and Volfoniq. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look for the lost, the secret, the rushed and hypnotic with the help of four bands who have made distinctive contributions to independent music in their home countries. They are Bluba Lu, Kalahari Surfers, QuiOui and Volfoniq. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/94050606podcast94.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/94050606podcast94.mp3" length="24975151" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Ninety Three</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring DJ Shiro, Dive Index, Confused Man, Danieto and Macrostructure</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at city life and the effort it takes not to be overwhelmed by it. Taking us through the structure, disorientation, density and sanctuaries of respite are DJ Shiro, Dive Index, Confused Man, Danieto and Macrostructure. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at city life and the effort it takes not to be overwhelmed by it. Taking us through the structure, disorientation, density and sanctuaries of respite are DJ Shiro, Dive Index, Confused Man, Danieto and Macrostructure. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/93050606podcast93.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/93050606podcast93.mp3" length="27675167" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Ninety Two</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Alif Tree, I am Open, Krael, Gisela, Jeff Mallon and Anji Bee</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at the brusque and abrupt. It seems as if we live in a time of rapid change, speeding up yet halting in fits and jerks. It is demonstrated in the area of climate change, where the theory of abrupt, tipping point change is becoming more widely accepted. On this episode we'll hear 7 songs whose precipitous changes and Unexpected endings represent that new reality. They are from Alif Tree, I am Open, Krael, Gisela, Jeff Mallon and Anji Bee. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the brusque and abrupt. It seems as if we live in a time of rapid change, speeding up yet halting in fits and jerks. It is demonstrated in the area of climate change, where the theory of abrupt, tipping point change is becoming more widely accepted. On this episode we'll hear 7 songs whose precipitous changes and Unexpected endings represent that new reality. They are from Alif Tree, I am Open, Krael, Gisela, Jeff Mallon and Anji Bee. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/92050606podcast92.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/92050606podcast92.mp3" length="25106390" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:09</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Ninety One</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Blind Divine, Chris Martin, Dive Index, Countertop Hero and Lemonchill</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at the One and no other. Novelist Iris Murdoch said 'The absolute yearning of one human body for another particular body and its indifference to substitutes is one of life's major mysteries" It explains how years after love goes sour, you can be haunted by that failure. Accepting no substitutes this week are Blind Divine, Chris Martin, Dive Index, Countertop Hero and Lemonchill. </description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the One and no other. Novelist Iris Murdoch said 'The absolute yearning of one human body for another particular body and its indifference to substitutes is one of life's major mysteries" It explains how years after love goes sour, you can be haunted by that failure. Accepting no substitutes this week are Blind Divine, Chris Martin, Dive Index, Countertop Hero and Lemonchill. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/91050606podcast91.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/91050606podcast91.mp3" length="26702576" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:48</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Ninety</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Big Wheel, Kristin Mainhart, The Banjo Consorsium, Fez Dispenser, Velvet Chain and Deerfoot</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at the blue side of love. The agonizing reappraisal that comes after infatuation with the help of Big Wheel, Kristin Mainhart, The Banjo Consorsium, Fez Dispenser, Velvet Chain and Deerfoot. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at the blue side of love. The agonizing reappraisal that comes after infatuation with the help of Big Wheel, Kristin Mainhart, The Banjo Consorsium, Fez Dispenser, Velvet Chain and Deerfoot. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/90050606podcast90.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/90050606podcast90.mp3" length="28040882" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>29:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eighty Nine</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Amanda Jayne, Virculum, Suzanne Vega, Stervhia and the Lion of Joppa Soundsystem</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll hear five songs by artists and musicians who have internalized the sounds of their adopted homes or stepped outside their native cultures to embrace the beats of another. They are Amanda Jayne, Virculum, Suzanne Vega, Stervhia and the Lion of Joppa Soundsystem. I'm Jim Nye</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll hear five songs by artists and musicians who have internalized the sounds of their adopted homes or stepped outside their native cultures to embrace the beats of another. They are Amanda Jayne, Virculum, Suzanne Vega, Stervhia and the Lion of Joppa Soundsystem. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/89050606podcast89.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/89050606podcast89.mp3" length="25508049" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eighty Eight</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Mavro, Chill Factor-5, Tricky and Bubblelawn</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at sister cities. Not in any formal sense but closely related nonetheless. We have four bands and four cities whose cultural and artistic proximity could just as easily be one. They are Mavro, Chill Factor-5, Tricky and Bubblelawn. I'm Jim Nye
</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at sister cities. Not in any formal sense but closely related nonetheless. We have four bands and four cities whose cultural and artistic proximity could just as easily be one. They are Mavro, Chill Factor-5, Tricky and Bubblelawn. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/88050606podcast88.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/88050606podcast88.mp3" length="24669623" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:41</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eighty Seven</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Jamdeluxe, Nihaya, Owen, Tryad, and Coil</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at foreknowledge and hindsight. The ability to know what might happen and inability to profit from that knowledge.  Like Camus' unused train ticket found at his fatal car crash or lyrics of a song made clear over time. We'll visit that paradox with Jamdeluxe, Nihaya, Owen, Tryad, and Coil. 
</description><itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at foreknowledge and hindsight. The ability to know what might happen and inability to profit from that knowledge.  Like Camus' unused train ticket found at his fatal car crash or lyrics of a song made clear over time. We'll visit that paradox with Jamdeluxe, Nihaya, Owen, Tryad, and Coil. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/87050606podcast87.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/87050606podcast87.mp3" length="24384575" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:25</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eighty Six</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Lacunae, Aaron the cutter, DS-Art, Max Cavallera and Egon</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll search for the empty space, the gap or missing part. A spot devoid of all things but meaning through the help of the definitive Lacunae, Aaron the cutter, DS-Art, Max Cavallera and Egon. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we'll search for the empty space, the gap or missing part. A spot devoid of all things but meaning through the help of the definitive Lacunae, Aaron the cutter, DS-Art, Max Cavallera and Egon. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/86050606podcast86.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/86050606podcast86.mp3" length="25880869" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eighty Five</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Motionfield, Ecovillage, SAHR, Peach Stealing Monkeys, Waverider and Gabriel.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll look at points in time that determine an endless series of possibilities. Paths that diverge then meander back and cross again. The future may be unwritten but which future. Presenting their respective cases are Motionfield, Ecovillage, SAHR, Peach Stealing Monkeys, Waverider and Gabriel. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll look at points in time that determine an endless series of possibilities. Paths that diverge then meander back and cross again. The future may be unwritten but which future. Presenting their respective cases are Motionfield, Ecovillage, SAHR, Peach Stealing Monkeys, Waverider and Gabriel. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/85050606podcast85.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/85050606podcast85.mp3" length="26639047" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:44</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eighty Four</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Jeankal, Synthastazia dot exe, Frank Molder, Mabafu and Jah Wobble.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we look at ones and zeros, the choice of on or off. Calculations for a digital age where the earthly pursuits of the past are but nostalgia. Forging on and remembering the old at Jeankal, Synthastazia dot exe, Frank Molder, Mabafu and Jah Wobble. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we look at ones and zeros, the choice of on or off. Calculations for a digital age where the earthly pursuits of the past are but nostalgia. Forging on and remembering the old at Jeankal, Synthastazia dot exe, Frank Molder, Mabafu and Jah Wobble. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/84050606podcast84.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/84050606podcast84.mp3" length="24800026" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eighty Three</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Calm, Mr.S, Peeping Tom, Two Loons for Tea and Terence Blanchard.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week's Rorschach looks at things that might have been had we taken the time to see what was hidden in plain sight. Providing the hindsight without recrimination are Calm, Mr.S, Peeping Tom, Two Loons for Tea and Terence Blanchard. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week's Rorschach looks at things that might have been had we taken the time to see what was hidden in plain sight. Providing the hindsight without recrimination are Calm, Mr.S, Peeping Tom, Two Loons for Tea and Terence Blanchard. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/83050606podcast83.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/83050606podcast83.mp3" length="24197747" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eighty Two: Kristin Hersh Special</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Kristin Hersh</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at sustainability and cooperation. One of the searing truths of the music you listen to is that it don't come easy. Musicians create and if they are good enough or plain lucky, they can take their songs on the road and sell a few tickets. Independent artists ask only a bit of cooperation from us. This podcast is entirely dependent on the bands that offer up their music for us to play for free. In turn, they ask only that you buy a ticket or a song or a CD directly from them. One of these is the enormously gifted songwriter Kristen Hersh.</description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at sustainability and cooperation. One of the searing truths of the music you listen to is that it don't come easy. Musicians create and if they are good enough or plain lucky, they can take their songs on the road and sell a few tickets. Independent artists ask only a bit of cooperation from us. This podcast is entirely dependent on the bands that offer up their music for us to play for free. In turn, they ask only that you buy a ticket or a song or a CD directly from them. One of these is the enormously gifted songwriter Kristen Hersh.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/82050606podcast82.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/82050606podcast82.mp3" length="28929881" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eighty One</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Portal, Surbahar, Omihoshbin, Band of Mad Women, and The HellBus</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll explore the essentials. In fact, The Sun and water are the key ingredients for life, as we know it. I'd like to suppose cool music to that short list as well. We'll hear all three in the voice of Portal, Surbahar, Omihoshbin, Band of Mad Women, and The HellBus. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we'll explore the essentials. In fact, The Sun and water are the key ingredients for life, as we know it. I'd like to suppose cool music to that short list as well. We'll hear all three in the voice of Portal, Surbahar, Omihoshbin, Band of Mad Women, and The HellBus. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/81050606podcast81.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/81050606podcast81.mp3" length="25379318" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:26</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eighty</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring MoShang, Ikarus, K-Shan, The Silk Demise, The Twombley Spiders and Toneless Symphony</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, it's the current state of electronic music. It's become the laziest handle for a genre since Alternative. For a long time it was defined as music played on synthesizers but that time has come and gone. Today's electronic music is so broad as to defy easy categorization but for one element. It is, more often than not, assembled digitally. So, we'll peer into the electronic future with the help of MoShang, Ikarus, K-Shan, The Silk Demise, The Twombley Spiders and Toneless Symphony. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, it's the current state of electronic music. It's become the laziest handle for a genre since Alternative. For a long time it was defined as music played on synthesizers but that time has come and gone. Today's electronic music is so broad as to defy easy categorization but for one element. It is, more often than not, assembled digitally. So, we'll peer into the electronic future with the help of MoShang, Ikarus, K-Shan, The Silk Demise, The Twombley Spiders and Toneless Symphony. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/80050606podcast80.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/80050606podcast80.mp3" length="27160660" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:17</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seventy Nine</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Simone and Flu, Grove of Hellion, All About Max, Hungry Lucy, Chico Correa and Ici Aussi</itunes:subtitle>
<description>Just as a sad movie can raise your spirits and the blues make you joyful sometimes being alone can be rejuvinating, This week we'll feel out the many aspcts of being alone through the music of Simone and Flu, Grove of Hellion, All About Max, Hungry Lucy, Chico Correa and Ici Aussi. </description>
<itunes:summary>Just as a sad movie can raise your spirits and the blues make you joyful sometimes being alone can be rejuvinating, This week we'll feel out the many aspcts of being alone through the music of Simone and Flu, Grove of Hellion, All About Max, Hungry Lucy, Chico Correa and Ici Aussi. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/79050606podcast79.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/79050606podcast79.mp3" length="23990439" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seventy Eight</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Natalie Walker, cognitive dissonance, Karmacoda, A Weekend At Lesters, Blue Vitriol and Org</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at that short period between emerging from sleep to actually opening your eyes. A state of near consciousness through the music of Natalie Walker, cognitive dissonance, Karmacoda, A Weekend At Lesters, Blue Vitriol and Org.</description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at that short period between emerging from sleep to actually opening your eyes. A state of near consciousness through the music of Natalie Walker, cognitive dissonance, Karmacoda, A Weekend At Lesters, Blue Vitriol and Org.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/78050606podcast78.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/78050606podcast78.mp3" length="25625913" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:41</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seventy Seven</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Robert Stephan, BlackEra, Siksha, Phasen, Mark.Nine and Matera</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll examine the illusion of contact. The sheer counter-intuitiveness that on a sub-atomic level  nothing actually touches anything else. Whether it's the landing of a boxer's blow or the gentle lapping of waves on a shore, contact remains elusive. On this episode we'll hear from Robert Stephan, BlackEra, Siksha, Phasen, Mark.Nine and Matera. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we'll examine the illusion of contact. The sheer counter-intuitiveness that on a sub-atomic level  nothing actually touches anything else. Whether it's the landing of a boxer's blow or the gentle lapping of waves on a shore, contact remains elusive. On this episode we'll hear from Robert Stephan, BlackEra, Siksha, Phasen, Mark.Nine and Matera. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/77050606podcast77.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/77050606podcast77.mp3" length="27561064" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:42</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seventy Six</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Chillerstadt, prod13F, Messian Dread, William Lamy and Alchemy Groove</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll explore tongues and grooves from 5 bands who build on individual contributions to realize a vision beyond a single person. They are Chillerstadt, prod13F, Messian Dread, William Lamy and Alchemy Groove. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we'll explore tongues and grooves from 5 bands who build on individual contributions to realize a vision beyond a single person. They are Chillerstadt, prod13F, Messian Dread, William Lamy and Alchemy Groove. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/76050606podcast76.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/76050606podcast76.mp3" length="22856934" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>23:48</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seventy Five</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Elsiane, Big Wheel, Conduct Unbecoming, Radium88 and Bitkit</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll revel in elegance. To some it's an antiquated old world charm but in troubled times it really more a last stand against barbarism in all its forms. Showing their poise on this episode of Idyllic Music are Elsiane, Big Wheel, Conduct Unbecoming, Radium88 and Bitkit. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we'll revel in elegance. To some it's an antiquated old world charm but in troubled times it really more a last stand against barbarism in all its forms. Showing their poise on this episode of Idyllic Music are Elsiane, Big Wheel, Conduct Unbecoming, Radium88 and Bitkit. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/75050606podcast75.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/75050606podcast75.mp3" length="23202168" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:10</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Chill,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seventy Four</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Amy Abdou, Judith Owen, Beatropolis, DRY and Blip Blop</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll tour the American West, where the sunsets are purple and red and yellow and on fire. A west not of Wayne but McCarthy with a myth of epics and truths in small stories. So with a narrative bass, we'll hear the tales from Amy Abdou, Judith Owen, Beatropolis, DRY and Blip Blop. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we'll tour the American West, where the sunsets are purple and red and yellow and on fire. A west not of Wayne but McCarthy with a myth of epics and truths in small stories. So with a narrative bass, we'll hear the tales from Amy Abdou, Judith Owen, Beatropolis, DRY and Blip Blop. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/74050606podcast74.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/74050606podcast74.mp3" length="23223902" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:11</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seventy Three</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Indy, Compulsive Behavior, Sexmusic, Benzene Vapours and Grzyb</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we look at the summer beach novel, preferably a mystery with clues, characters, steamy scenes and exotic locales. We'll find all that and more with the help of Indy, Compulsive Behavior, Sexmusic, Benzene Vapours and Grzyb. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we look at the summer beach novel, preferably a mystery with clues, characters, steamy scenes and exotic locales. We'll find all that and more with the help of Indy, Compulsive Behavior, Sexmusic, Benzene Vapours and Grzyb. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/73050606podcast73.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/73050606podcast73.mp3" length="23705809" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:41</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seventy Two</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Puracane, Acid42, Mudville, Syrin, Susis Manner and Datassette</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at home, a place both physical and emotional. Where you want to return to when away and get away from whilst there. whether your feelings are warm, cold, nostalgic or presently realistic. Everyone has a home whether they admit it to themselves or not. So we will hear from Puracane, Acid42, Mudville, Syrin, Susis Manner and Datassette. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at home, a place both physical and emotional. Where you want to return to when away and get away from whilst there. whether your feelings are warm, cold, nostalgic or presently realistic. Everyone has a home whether they admit it to themselves or not. So we will hear from Puracane, Acid42, Mudville, Syrin, Susis Manner and Datassette. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/72050606podcast72.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/72050606podcast72.mp3" length="24526263" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seventy One</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring AMY B, The Drake Equation, Sr. Aye, Balun and Saurio</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week,we'll look at perceptions and expectations. Bringing personal prejudice to the sensory world. The slate this week includes AMY B, The Drake Equation, Sr. Aye, Balun and Saurio.</description>
<itunes:summary>This week,we'll look at perceptions and expectations. Bringing personal prejudice to the sensory world. The slate this week includes AMY B, The Drake Equation, Sr. Aye, Balun and Saurio.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/71050606podcast71.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/71050606podcast71.mp3" length="23782296" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seventy</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring IamOpen, R. Stimpson, Zero State Reflex, USB, Scanlan and Rajaz</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we look and the ominous and foreboding. The unsettling feeling that something is about to happen. Filmmakers know the power of a soundtrack to convey this and so do the six artist on Idyllic Music this week. They include IamOpen, R. Stimpson, Zero State Reflex, USB, Scanlan and Rajaz. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we look and the ominous and foreboding. The unsettling feeling that something is about to happen. Filmmakers know the power of a soundtrack to convey this and so do the six artist on Idyllic Music this week. They include IamOpen, R. Stimpson, Zero State Reflex, USB, Scanlan and Rajaz. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/70050606podcast70.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/70050606podcast70.mp3" length="25039099" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Sixty Nine</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Garden Hose Universe, Luminous, PNFA and Jotch, Finn The Giant Meets Sandmonk and Mr. Frendo</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we look at matchings, successful pairings in twos and threes through the music of Garden Hose Universe, Luminous, PNFA and Jotch, Finn The Giant Meets Sandmonk and Mr. Frendo. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we look at matchings, successful pairings in twos and threes through the music of Garden Hose Universe, Luminous, PNFA and Jotch, Finn The Giant Meets Sandmonk and Mr. Frendo. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/69050606podcast69.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/69050606podcast69.mp3" length="25303667" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Sixty Eight</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Bersarin Quartett, Dream LAX, Chris Martin, Sirk, Corwin Trails, Idyllic, The Dandelion Council and The Serendipitous Cacophonies</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we consider the glacier, a force of nature whose pace is so deliberate as to define slowness of movement yet whose disappearance is so rapid we may never truly know its relationship to the planet and ourselves. The chillout this week includes Bersarin Quartett, Dream LAX, Chris Martin, Sirk, Corwin Trails, Idyllic, The Dandelion Council and The Serendipitous Cacophonies. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week we consider the glacier, a force of nature whose pace is so deliberate as to define slowness of movement yet whose disappearance is so rapid we may never truly know its relationship to the planet and ourselves. The chillout this week includes Bersarin Quartett, Dream LAX, Chris Martin, Sirk, Corwin Trails, Idyllic, The Dandelion Council and The Serendipitous Cacophonies. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/68050606podcast68.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/68050606podcast68.mp3" length="26154632" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:14</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Sixty Seven</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Your Hand in Mine, Subtronik, Cling, Der Grosse Reibach and Ice Sun</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll look at love, sex and romance in unusual places. Where lovers meet in body, soul and locale through the music of Your Hand in Mine, Subtronik, Cling, Der Grosse Reibach and Ice Sun. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll look at love, sex and romance in unusual places. Where lovers meet in body, soul and locale through the music of Your Hand in Mine, Subtronik, Cling, Der Grosse Reibach and Ice Sun. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/67050606podcast67.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/67050606podcast67.mp3" length="24609437" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Sixty Six</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring The Projects, PAXX, I Am Dog Biscuit, Ekayani and Analog Chill</itunes:subtitle>
<description>Joni Mitchell once sang of seeing angels hair and feather canyons everywhere whilst looking at clouds and this week we'll look at this phenomenon musically through the work of The Projects, PAXX, I Am Dog Biscuit, Ekayani and Analog Chill. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>Joni Mitchell once sang of seeing angels hair and feather canyons everywhere whilst looking at clouds and this week we'll look at this phenomenon musically through the work of The Projects, PAXX, I Am Dog Biscuit, Ekayani and Analog Chill. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/66050606podcast66.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/66050606podcast66.mp3" length="27186573" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:19</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Sixty Five</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Neko Neko, Tricky, The Divine Madness, JT25, Estado Avanzado and Lily Lavandula</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we look at barriers, stumbling blocks and things that hold you back through the music of Neko Neko, Tricky, The Divine Madness, JT25, Estado Avanzado and Lily Lavandula. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week we look at barriers, stumbling blocks and things that hold you back through the music of Neko Neko, Tricky, The Divine Madness, JT25, Estado Avanzado and Lily Lavandula. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/65050606podcast65.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/65050606podcast65.mp3" length="25235958" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:16</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Sixty Four</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Munkie, Noise Relations, Simon V, Sardinia Bass Legalize and Juno6</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, We give a nod to a loyal and substantial listenership in Europe. A number helped, in no small measure, by my comedic inability to correctly pronounce names and song titles is so many languages. Our exercise continues through the Music of Munkie, Noise Relations, Simon V, Sardinia Bass Legalize and Juno6. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, We give a nod to a loyal and substantial listenership in Europe. A number helped, in no small measure, by my comedic inability to correctly pronounce names and song titles is so many languages. Our exercise continues through the Music of Munkie, Noise Relations, Simon V, Sardinia Bass Legalize and Juno6. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/64050606podcast64.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/64050606podcast64.mp3" length="26852624" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:58</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Sixty Three</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Black Era, Orange Crush, Artemis, Dan West and Mist</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we 'Step It Up' as part of the worldwide effort to stem climate change as musicians and artists in hundreds, perhaps, thousands of places rally against pollution. We step it up with the help of Black Era, Orange Crush, Artemis, Dan West and Mist. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we 'Step It Up' as part of the worldwide effort to stem climate change as musicians and artists in hundreds, perhaps, thousands of places rally against pollution. We step it up with the help of Black Era, Orange Crush, Artemis, Dan West and Mist. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/63050606podcast63.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/63050606podcast63.mp3" length="25777633" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Downtempo,Trip Hop,Electronica,Jazz,Dub,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Sixty Two</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Essenza, Sixx, Waverider, Zeos and Jules Nerve</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we explore the world of the somnambulist, whose cycles of sleep and states of conscience are represented by Essenza, Sixx, Waverider, Zeos and Jules Nerve. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we explore the world of the somnambulist, whose cycles of sleep and states of conscience are represented by Essenza, Sixx, Waverider, Zeos and Jules Nerve. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/62050606podcast62.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/62050606podcast62.mp3" length="26508643" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:36</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Sixty One</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Winterstrand, Kryptide, Beatnik, Uniquetunes and Single Cell Orchestra</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we look at the remarkable windup music box. A device simple in design yet sophisticated enough to play everything from bedtime lullabies to Mozart. This episode's songs share those same qualities. They are by Winterstrand, Kryptide, Beatnik, Uniquetunes and Single Cell Orchestra. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we look at the remarkable windup music box. A device simple in design yet sophisticated enough to play everything from bedtime lullabies to Mozart. This episode's songs share those same qualities. They are by Winterstrand, Kryptide, Beatnik, Uniquetunes and Single Cell Orchestra. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/61050606podcast61.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/61050606podcast61.mp3" length="25526439" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:35</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Sixty</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Mudville, Jeff D. Clark, Ema Walker, Saurio and Lex Nasa</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we look at the influence of the great international cities of New York, Leon, Montevideo and Hong Kong through the music of Mudville, Jeff D. Clark, Ema Walker, Saurio and Lex Nasa. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we look at the influence of the great international cities of New York, Leon, Montevideo and Hong Kong through the music of Mudville, Jeff D. Clark, Ema Walker, Saurio and Lex Nasa. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/60050606podcast60.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/60050606podcast60.mp3" length="26726818" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fifty Nine</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Velvet Chain, Tough Chic, Sunburn in Cyprus, Orange Crush and Misosoundz</itunes:subtitle>
<description>First a reminder that all show notes and band website links can be found at www.idyllicmusic.com where you will find a wealth of information about the music you hear on this and every other episode of Idyllic Music. This week, well hear from Velvet Chain, Tough Chic, Sunburn in Cyprus, Orange Crush and Misosoundz.  </description>
<itunes:summary>First a reminder that all show notes and band website links can be found at www.idyllicmusic.com where you will find a wealth of information about the music you hear on this and every other episode of Idyllic Music. This week, well hear from Velvet Chain, Tough Chic, Sunburn in Cyprus, Orange Crush and Misosoundz.  </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/59050606podcast59.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/59050606podcast59.mp3" length="25907200" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fifty Eight</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring 6-lyss, Spinning Merkaba, Evolve, Portal and P-Vibes</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll explore the 'Folkartronica' made possible by the Creative Commons license. Dozens of websites have cropped up offering sound clips of various elements of established songs. These clips are then mixed, blended or mashed into something new. This new license allows artists to use the work of others under specific, usually, non-commercial guidelines. It has a kind of 'Folk Art' appeal that is, at turns, democratic and subversive. We'll hear from 5 bands that may or may not employ this new movement in music. They are 6-lyss, Spinning Merkaba, Evolve, Portal and P-Vibes. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll explore the 'Folkartronica' made possible by the Creative Commons license. Dozens of websites have cropped up offering sound clips of various elements of established songs. These clips are then mixed, blended or mashed into something new. This new license allows artists to use the work of others under specific, usually, non-commercial guidelines. It has a kind of 'Folk Art' appeal that is, at turns, democratic and subversive. We'll hear from 5 bands that may or may not employ this new movement in music. They are 6-lyss, Spinning Merkaba, Evolve, Portal and P-Vibes. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/58050606podcast58.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/58050606podcast58.mp3" length="23934851" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:55</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fifty Seven</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Mavro, I Awake, Kyran, Skizzo Franick and Rude</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll look at the blue. The space between the white and the black where notes have freedom to bend creating color, emotion and feeling. To that end, we'll enlist the music of Mavro, I Awake, Kyran, Skizzo Franick and Rude. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll look at the blue. The space between the white and the black where notes have freedom to bend creating color, emotion and feeling. To that end, we'll enlist the music of Mavro, I Awake, Kyran, Skizzo Franick and Rude. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/57050606podcast57.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/57050606podcast57.mp3" length="23475096" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:27</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fifty Six</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Victoria Mosley and The Sublimes, Big Wheel, Onderboven, Soo P and the Outsider, The Publicity Stunt and The Flavor Foundation</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll look at youth and experience as we hear from 6 artists running from the teens to midlife. We'll hear from Victoria Mosley and The Sublimes, Big Wheel, Onderboven, Soo P and the Outsider, The Publicity Stunt and The Flavor Foundation. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll look at youth and experience as we hear from 6 artists running from the teens to midlife. We'll hear from Victoria Mosley and The Sublimes, Big Wheel, Onderboven, Soo P and the Outsider, The Publicity Stunt and The Flavor Foundation. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/56050606podcast56.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/56050606podcast56.mp3" length="27832738" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>28:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fifty Five</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring EeBoO, Welder, Katie Turner and Ruby Jean and the Thoughtful Bees</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll look at colors at night. Not the neon variety but the colors you might not even notice at first. When the spectrum of light just might be playing tricks on you. Our guides this week are EeBoO, Welder, Katie Turner and ruby jean and the thoughtful bees. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll look at colors at night. Not the neon variety but the colors you might not even notice at first. When the spectrum of light just might be playing tricks on you. Our guides this week are EeBoO, Welder, Katie Turner and ruby jean and the thoughtful bees. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/55050606podcast55.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/55050606podcast55.mp3" length="25212970" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fifty Four</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Irina Mikhailova, Dreaming Blue, Conduct Unbecoming, Alchemystic and Salam</itunes:subtitle>
<description>Again I am reminded of just how small our world has become and the richness given to our lives when we experience the music and culture of others around the globe. Contributing to that wealth this week are Irina Mikhailova, Dreaming Blue, Conduct Unbecoming, Alchemystic and Salam. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>Again I am reminded of just how small our world has become and the richness given to our lives when we experience the music and culture of others around the globe. Contributing to that wealth this week are Irina Mikhailova, Dreaming Blue, Conduct Unbecoming, Alchemystic and Salam. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/54050606podcast54.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/54050606podcast54.mp3" length="25630511" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:41</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fifty Three</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Mr. Frendo, Mystical Sun, Endlos and Emzk</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we look at the circular, whether in travels, time or logic with help from Mr. Frendo, Mystical Sun, Endlos and Emzk. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week we look at the circular, whether in travels, time or logic with help from Mr. Frendo, Mystical Sun, Endlos and Emzk. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/53050606podcast53.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/53050606podcast53.mp3" length="24131291" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fifty Two</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Day One Symphony, Electric Salmon, The Chill Conspiracy, Tricky and DRT</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll look at flattery in its more sincere form with five bands that readily show their influences while remaining unique and individual. They are Day One Symphony, Electric Salmon, The Chill Conspiracy, Tricky and DRT. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll look at flattery in its more sincere form with five bands that readily show their influences while remaining unique and individual. They are Day One Symphony, Electric Salmon, The Chill Conspiracy, Tricky and DRT. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/52050606podcast52.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/52050606podcast52.mp3" length="26318054" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fifty One</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Apjiw, Munkie, Kalahari Surfers and Alienation</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll visit both hemispheres in search of the Idyllic found in the music of Apjiw, Munkie, Kalahari Surfers and Alienation.</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll visit both hemispheres in search of the Idyllic found in the music of Apjiw, Munkie, Kalahari Surfers and Alienation.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/51050606podcast51.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/51050606podcast51.mp3" length="23297045" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:16</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fifty</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Ikarus, Ventriloquist, Smashed Toy, Artemis, Fear Called Living and I am Dog Biscuit</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week will mark the 50th episode of Idyllic Music. Several messages reached me this week at idyllicmusic@cox.net asking how we intend celebrate this milestone. The answer is to follow through on our commitment from the onset to present the very best music we find for any particular week. And so we will hear from Ikarus, Ventriloquist, Smashed Toy, Artemis, Fear Called Living and I am Dog Biscuit and </description>
<itunes:summary>This week will mark the 50th episode of Idyllic Music. Several messages reached me this week at idyllicmusic@cox.net asking how we intend celebrate this milestone. The answer is to follow through on our commitment from the onset to present the very best music we find for any particular week. And so we will hear from Ikarus, Ventriloquist, Smashed Toy, Artemis, Fear Called Living and I am Dog Biscuit and </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/50050606podcast50.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/50050606podcast50.mp3" length="29583987" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:48</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Forty Nine</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Sleeve Channel, A.W.A.L, Adam Fielding, Postscript and Lunar</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll look at Break Downs, Breaking Points and tough Breaks, in general with the help of Sleeve Channel, A.W.A.L, Adam Fielding, Postscript and Lunar. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll look at Break Downs, Breaking Points and tough Breaks, in general with the help of Sleeve Channel, A.W.A.L, Adam Fielding, Postscript and Lunar. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2007 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/49050606podcast49.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/49050606podcast49.mp3" length="24973897" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>
	
<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Forty Eight</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Elsiane, Sirk, Ici Aussi, Classic SciFi and Greenman</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, it's the classical world of tragedy, love and war. Telling the tales are Elsiane, Sirk, Ici Aussi, Classic SciFi and Greenman. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, it's the classical world of tragedy, love and war. Telling the tales are Elsiane, Sirk, Ici Aussi, Classic SciFi and Greenman. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/48050606podcast48.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/48050606podcast48.mp3" length="25143589" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:11</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Forty Seven</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Aeroflux, Cantaloup, Contact, Martin Herzberg and Jeff Rosiana</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, it's the solstice. The true measure of the New Year as dictated by the planet. It marks the seasonal change, the longest and shortest and in their way it is celebrated by Aeroflux, Cantaloup, Contact, Martin Herzberg and Jeff Rosiana.</description>
<itunes:summary>This week, it's the solstice. The true measure of the New Year as dictated by the planet. It marks the seasonal change, the longest and shortest and in their way it is celebrated by Aeroflux, Cantaloup, Contact, Martin Herzberg and Jeff Rosiana.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/47050606podcast47.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/47050606podcast47.mp3" length="24493662" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:30</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Forty Six</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Maido Project, The Engineer, Aphone, Sound(e)scape and Tryad</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll look at Opportunity and we'll start this episode with Maido Project's breezy mix of electronic music and acoustic instruments from their home base in France.</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll look at Opportunity and we'll start this episode with Maido Project's breezy mix of electronic music and acoustic instruments from their home base in France.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/46050606podcast46.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/46050606podcast46.mp3" length="23638518" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Forty Five</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Owen, Centerpole, My Toys Like Me, Joana Smith and The Reel Banditos</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we consider the boudoir, whether furnished with a bed of grass, four posts or cardboard, through the music of Owen, Centerpole, My Toys Like Me, Joana Smith and The Reel Banditos. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we consider the boudoir, whether furnished with a bed of grass, four posts or cardboard, through the music of Owen, Centerpole, My Toys Like Me, Joana Smith and The Reel Banditos. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/45050606podcast45.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/45050606podcast45.mp3" length="23600483" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:35</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Forty Four</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Totosh, to the sea with me, Mr.S and Xenn, Justin R and Nervegasm</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week it's a mix of soft and loud, rough and smooth, of heaven and earth, sometimes within the same song. It comes from the music of Totosh, to the sea with me, Mr.S and Xenn, Justin R and Nervegasm. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week it's a mix of soft and loud, rough and smooth, of heaven and earth, sometimes within the same song. It comes from the music of Totosh, to the sea with me, Mr.S and Xenn, Justin R and Nervegasm. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/44050606podcast44.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/44050606podcast44.mp3" length="24046864" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:02</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Forty Three</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Tinta, Volfoniq, Bitstream Dream, LaLuceNazione, Qui? Oui! and David Last</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week's cornucopia includes the musical bounty offered up by Tinta, Volfoniq, Bitstream Dream, LaLuceNazione, Qui? Oui! and David Last. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week's cornucopia includes the musical bounty offered up by Tinta, Volfoniq, Bitstream Dream, LaLuceNazione, Qui? Oui! and David Last. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/43050606podcast43.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/43050606podcast43.mp3" length="26120777" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>27:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Forty Two</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Zero State Reflex, The Drake Equation, MichL Bridge and Brigitte Bijoux.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we'll look at states of Solitude, in place and time, by way of the music of Zero State Reflex, The Drake Equation, MichL Bridge and Brigitte Bijoux. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we'll look at states of Solitude, in place and time, by way of the music of Zero State Reflex, The Drake Equation, MichL Bridge and Brigitte Bijoux. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/42050606podcast42.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/42050606podcast42.mp3" length="23744679" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:44</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Forty One</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Endless Blue, Indy, Projexam, Juliet Hotel and Ella Blame.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week its resurrection and return. We'll mark the moment with the music of Endless Blue, Indy, Projexam, Juliet Hotel and Ella Blame. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>This week its resurrection and return. We'll mark the moment with the music of Endless Blue, Indy, Projexam, Juliet Hotel and Ella Blame. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/41050606podcast41.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/41050606podcast41.mp3" length="25194580" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:14</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Forty</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring The Projects, Chico Correa, Morcheeba, Monotape and Rettward von Doernberg.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll seek contrasts and connections from the music of The Projects, Chico Correa, Morcheeba, Monotape and Rettward von Doernberg. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll seek contrasts and connections from the music of The Projects, Chico Correa, Morcheeba, Monotape and Rettward von Doernberg. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/40050606podcast40.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/40050606podcast40.mp3" length="25904274" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Thirty Nine</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Acidhead, Aidor, USB, Idyllic and Electric Salmon.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>In the spirit of the season this week, we'll slip through mists and apparitions to hear the music of Acidhead, Aidor, USB, Idyllic and Electric Salmon.</description>
<itunes:summary>In the spirit of the season this week, we'll slip through mists and apparitions to hear the music of Acidhead, Aidor, USB, Idyllic and Electric Salmon.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/39050606podcast39.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/39050606podcast39.mp3" length="24654994" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Thirty Eight (Unplugged)</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Jen Gloeckner, Under, Brian Dondo, Juli and The Brobdingnagian Bards.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>Although the term 'unplugged' has become cliche, nothing could be more Idyllic. Over the past few months, these switched off songs have accumulated and become inevitable. This week, we'll hear from Jen Gloeckner, Under, Brian Dondo, Juli and The Brobdingnagian Bards. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>Although the term 'unplugged' has become cliche, nothing could be more Idyllic. Over the past few months, these switched off songs have accumulated and become inevitable. This week, we'll hear from Jen Gloeckner, Under, Brian Dondo, Juli and The Brobdingnagian Bards. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/38050606podcast38.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/38050606podcast38.mp3" length="23712496" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:42</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Thirty Seven</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Obedientbone, Chris Martin, Omnisine and Symbiosis.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll attempt to capture musical moments in time that might otherwise be lost like tears in the rain by way of Obedientbone, Chris Martin, Omnisine and Symbiosis. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll attempt to capture musical moments in time that might otherwise be lost like tears in the rain by way of Obedientbone, Chris Martin, Omnisine and Symbiosis. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/37050606podcast37.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/37050606podcast37.mp3" length="22216202" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>23:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Thirty Six</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Vitamins For You, Hungry Lucy, Slam Orchid and Sublimatus.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll hear from Vitamins For You, Hungry Lucy, Slam Orchid and Sublimatus. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll hear from Vitamins For You, Hungry Lucy, Slam Orchid and Sublimatus. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/36050606podcast36.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/36050606podcast36.mp3" length="21711726" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>22:36</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Thirty Five</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Coma Research, Base-Box, Izmar, Mabafu and Sans Edge.  .</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week I must apologize beforehand because nearly all the bands in this podcast were found at remarkable German or Dutch language websites and I am embarrassingly ill-equipped to translate their content. It's a small thing in that the music speaks eloquently enough to make up for my shortcomings. Featuring Coma Research, Base-Box, Izmar, Mabafu and Sans Edge.</description>
<itunes:summary>This week I must apologize beforehand because nearly all the bands in this podcast were found at remarkable German or Dutch language websites and I am embarrassingly ill-equipped to translate their content. It's a small thing in that the music speaks eloquently enough to make up for my shortcomings. Featuring Coma Research, Base-Box, Izmar, Mabafu and Sans Edge.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/35050606podcast35.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/35050606podcast35.mp3" length="22446498" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>23:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Thirty Four</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Amy, Azeruz, Nexus6, Demetrius Neutaja and Rude Corps.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>The term amateur shares the root of amour or to love. Making music just for the love of it is as noble an enterprise as one can undertake. This week we'll hear from Amy, Azeruz, Nexus6, Demetrius Neutaja and Rude Corps. </description>
<itunes:summary>The term amateur shares the root of amour or to love. Making music just for the love of it is as noble an enterprise as one can undertake. This week we'll hear from Amy, Azeruz, Nexus6, Demetrius Neutaja and Rude Corps. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/34050606podcast34.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/34050606podcast34.mp3" length="24742766" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Thirty Three</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Digital Droo, gROUSe, Nucleus Roots and Digital Love.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>Idyllic Music is all about reflection, prayers, meditation and a sense of calm. To that end we'll hear the music of Digital Droo, gROUSe, Nucleus Roots and Digital Love. </description>
<itunes:summary>Idyllic Music is all about reflection, prayers, meditation and a sense of calm. To that end we'll hear the music of Digital Droo, gROUSe, Nucleus Roots and Digital Love. </itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/33050606podcast33.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/33050606podcast33.mp3" length="24140069" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Thirty Two</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Artemis, Texture, Spiral Soundsystem, X-Ray Dogs and Keito.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>On this edition of idyllic music, acuity and detail are the watchwords as we hear from Artemis, Texture, Spiral Soundsystem, X-Ray Dogs and Keito.</description>
<itunes:summary>On this edition of idyllic music, acuity and detail are the watchwords as we hear from Artemis, Texture, Spiral Soundsystem, X-Ray Dogs and Keito.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/32050606podcast32.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/32050606podcast32.mp3" length="23178762" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Thirty One</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring 
Force Theory, DJ Eric ILL, Null Device, Worried about Satan and Fall of Snow</itunes:subtitle>
<description>The very best music often defies easy categorization.  This week we'll hear 5 songs by bands that are simply impossible to pigeonhole. Beginning with Brooklyn-based Force Theory who combine the melodic phrasing of soul with an organic baroque electronica. This is 'Boards' 
</description>
<itunes:summary>The very best music often defies easy categorization.  This week we'll hear 5 songs by bands that are simply impossible to pigeonhole. Beginning with Brooklyn-based Force Theory who combine the melodic phrasing of soul with an organic baroque electronica. This is 'Boards' 
</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/31050606podcast31.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/31050606podcast31.mp3" length="21366073" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>22:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Thirty</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Kat Yidaki, Egyptian Nursery,PNFA, Paddington Breaks and Strekie</itunes:subtitle>
<description>Milestones come and go while in the Idyll like a lazy summers day without nearly enough time to do all the nothing you had planned on doing. This one features Kat Yidaki, Egyptian Nursery,PNFA, Paddington Breaks and Strekie. Dutch bass player Kat Yidaki begins this 30th episode of Idyllic Music with 'H2' 
</description>
<itunes:summary>Milestones come and go while in the Idyll like a lazy summers day without nearly enough time to do all the nothing you had planned on doing. This one features Kat Yidaki, Egyptian Nursery,PNFA, Paddington Breaks and Strekie. Dutch bass player Kat Yidaki begins this 30th episode of Idyllic Music with 'H2' 
</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/30050606podcast30.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/30050606podcast30.mp3" length="25508467" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Twenty Nine</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring The Digital Nasty, Modular Heaven, Thomas Trotter, Jahspre, Jillene and Siegfried Gautier</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we'll hear from the Digital Nasty, Modular Heaven, Thomas Trotter, Jahspre, Jillene and Siegfried Gautier</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we'll hear from The Digital Nasty, Modular Heaven, Thomas Trotter, Jahspre, Jillene and Siegfried Gautier</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/29050606podcast29.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/29050606podcast29.mp3" length="23656908" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Twenty Eight</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Axiotronic, Netrix, COGITO ERGO SUM, Flower Of Cables and Euch</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we look for perspective from other worlds both inside and out by way of songs by Axiotronic, Netrix, COGITO ERGO SUM, Flower Of Cables and Euch. 
</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we look for perspective from other worlds both inside and out by way of songs by Axiotronic, Netrix, COGITO ERGO SUM, Flower Of Cables and Euch. 
</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/28050606podcast28.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/28050606podcast28.mp3" length="22086217" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>23:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Twenty Seven</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Aralow, Collide, Dynamik and SCUM</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, episode 27 runs from the strident to the haunting and nuanced featuring the music of Aralow, Collide, Dynamik and SCUM and a my space spotlight. 
</description>
<itunes:summary>This week, episode 27 runs from the strident to the haunting and nuanced featuring the music of Aralow, Collide, Dynamik and SCUM and a my space spotlight. 
</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/27050606podcast27.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/27050606podcast27.mp3" length="21034214" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>21:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Twenty Six</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring The Chill Conspiracy, Lunascape, Mist, Numina and Karmacoda</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we climb the highest mountains and search the foggy lowlands for Idyllic Music. We have found it in The Chill Conspiracy, Lunascape, Mist, Numina and Karmacoda. I'm Jim Nye
</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we climb the highest mountains and search the foggy lowlands for Idyllic Music. We have found it in The Chill Conspiracy, Lunascape, Mist, Numina and Karmacoda. I'm Jim Nye
</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/26050606podcast26.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/26050606podcast26.mp3" length="25857463" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Twenty Five</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Thulla, The Grooveblaster, Floex, Dan West, Curium and FSP</itunes:subtitle>
<description>Episode 25 finds us globe hopping once again, from Copenhagen, Prague, Raleigh, San Francisco and Warsaw. We'll hear from Thulla, The Grooveblaster, Floex, Dan West, Curium and FSP. 
</description>
<itunes:summary>Episode 25 finds us globe hopping once again, from Copenhagen, Prague, Raleigh, San Francisco and Warsaw. We'll hear from Thulla, The Grooveblaster, Floex, Dan West, Curium and FSP. 
</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/25050606podcast25.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/podcast25.mp3" length="25419024" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>26:28</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Electronica,Downtempo,Jazz,Dub,Indie,Chill,Ambient</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Twenty Four</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring USB, Indy, Putty and General Fuzz</itunes:subtitle>
<description>Stephen McAlister has a new feature this week that points out some great streaming music by influential artists found on MySpace. More on that later in the show. This week we'll hear from USB, Indy, Putty and Gen. Fuzz. I'm Jim Nye</description>
<itunes:summary>Stephen McAlister has a new feature this week that points out some great streaming music by influential artists found on MySpace. More on that later in the show. This week we'll hear from USB, Indy, Putty and Gen. Fuzz. I'm Jim Nye</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/24050606podcast24.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/24050606podcast24.mp3" length="20338312" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>21:11</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo,Indie,Chill</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Twenty Three</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Bipolar, Authist and Dubone, The Hellbus, Mangomad and Youth Reference</itunes:subtitle>
<description>A reminder that many of the songs you hear on this podcast can by purchased through the Cornershop at idyllicmusic.com to help support the artists. This week, we'll hear from Bipolar, Authist and Dubone, The Hellbus, Mangomad and Youth Reference.
</description>
<itunes:summary>A reminder that many of the songs you hear on this podcast can by purchased through the Cornershop at idyllicmusic.com to help support the artists. This week, we'll hear from Bipolar, Authist and Dubone, The Hellbus, Mangomad and Youth Reference.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/23050606podcast23.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/23050606podcast23.mp3" length="23650304" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>23:31</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo,Indie,Chill</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Twenty Two</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Lendi Vexer, Sexmusic, The Silk Demise, Puracane and Profetas de Zion.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This podcast plays podsafe music or songs played with specific permission of the artist. This week I was lucky enough to obtain that go ahead from 5 bands I have admired for many months. They are Lendi Vexer, Sexmusic, The Silk Demise, Puracane and more recently, Profetas de Zion. </description>
<itunes:summary>This podcast plays podsafe music or songs played with specific permission of the artist. This week I was lucky enough to obtain that go ahead from 5 bands I have admired for many months. They are Lendi Vexer, Sexmusic, The Silk Demise, Puracane and more recently, Profetas de Zion.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/22050606podcast22.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/22050606podcast22.mp3" length="22587768" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo,Indie</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Twenty One</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Invisable Asps, Vim Cortez, Queenie, Kommbat and Shadowproject.</itunes:subtitle>
<description>The music that I find most interesting is often least likely to be heard widely. It might be a bit off kilter, unpredictable or somewhat out of balance. Koyaanisqatsi, if you will. Each of the next 5 songs displays those qualities to one degree or another. We'll hear from Invisible Asps, Vim Cortez, Queenie, Kommbat and Shadowproject.
</description>
<itunes:summary>The music that I find most interesting is often least likely to be heard widely. It might be a bit off kilter, unpredictable or somewhat out of balance. Koyaanisqatsi, if you will. Each of the next 5 songs displays those qualities to one degree or another. We'll hear from Invisible Asps, Vim Cortez, Queenie, Kommbat and Shadowproject.
</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/21050606podcast21.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/21050606podcast21.mp3" length="21376000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>22:48</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop, Chill, Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo,Indie</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Twenty</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Compulsive Behavior, Victoria Mosley and The Sublimes, Cyndi Vellmure and a Coisa Louca</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This 20th episode of Idyllic Music reminds me how utterly universal a language music is.We'll hear recordings from Russia, the U.S. France and the U.K. from the likes of Compulsive Behavior, Victoria Mosley and The Sublimes, Cyndi Vellmure and a Coisa Louca. 
</description>
<itunes:summary>This 20th episode of Idyllic Music reminds me how utterly universal a language music is.We'll hear recordings from Russia, the U.S. France and the U.K. from the likes of Compulsive Behavior, Victoria Mosley and The Sublimes, Cyndi Vellmure and a Coisa Louca. 
</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/20050606podcast20.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/20050606podcast20.mp3" length="23557000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo,Indie</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Nineteen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Sunburn in Cyprus, the Maido project, Judith Owen, 22 and Refrag</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week we celebrate the Grand Opening of the Cornershop at idyllicmusic.com. You will find links to many of the songs you hear on this podcast and a quick, easy way to support those bands and this podcast. Musically, this week we'll hear from Sunburn in Cyprus, the Maido Project, Judith Owen, 22 and Refrag.
</description>
<itunes:summary>This week we celebrate the Grand Opening of the Cornershop at idyllicmusic.com. You will find links to many of the songs you hear on this podcast and a quick, easy way to support those bands and this podcast. Musically, this week we'll hear from Sunburn in Cyprus, the Maido Project, Judith Owen, 22 and Refrag.
</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/19050606podcast19.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/19050606podcast19.mp3" length="20982000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>22:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo,Indie</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eighteen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Falling You, Portal, Tems and Minor Chill. </itunes:subtitle>
<description>Idyllic Music always invites introspection. Sometimes you'll find it in a rural village, sometimes a stretch of beach or a large American city. This week we'll hear from Falling You, Portal, Tems and Minor Chill.</description>
<itunes:summary>Idyllic Music always invites introspection. Sometimes you'll find it in a rural village, sometimes a stretch of beach or a large American city. This week we'll hear from Falling You, Portal, Tems and Minor Chill.
</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/18050606podcast18.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/18050606podcast18.mp3" length="21474000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>22:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo,Indie</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seventeen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Featuring Mellow Dramas, MI:GFU, Shagg, Isotrak and Sideway. </itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week a trans-Atlantic exchange sets the mood as we hear from Mellow Dramas, MI:GFU, Shagg, Isotrak and Sideway. </description>
<itunes:summary>This week a trans-Atlantic exchange sets the mood as we hear from Mellow Dramas, MI:GFU, Shagg, Isotrak and Sideway. 
</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/17050606podcast17.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/17050606podcast17.mp3" length="21012000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>22:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo,Indie</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Sixteen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>The Very Best in Downtempo, Ambient, Trip Hop, Jazz and Dub Music from around the World</itunes:subtitle>
<description>This week, we hear the music of artists from the great cities of Milan, San Francisco, Montreal by way of Caracas and also the hinterlands of Wales. They are represented by The Warheads, Musetta, Subtronix and Triple Erre.</description>
<itunes:summary>This week, we hear the music of artists from the great cities of Milan, San Francisco, Montreal by way of Caracas and also the hinterlands of Wales. They are represented by The Warheads, Musetta, Subtronix and Triple Erre.</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/16050606podcast16.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/16050606podcast16.mp3" length="19985000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>21:19</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fifteen</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Sunburn, elika, Huttenlocher, The Geminiac and Jigli B</itunes:subtitle>
<description>On tap this week we'll hear from Sunburn, elika, Huttenlocher, The Geminiac and Jigli B</description>
<itunes:summary>On tap this week we'll hear from Sunburn, elika, Huttenlocher, The Geminiac and Jigli B</itunes:summary>
<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/15050606podcast15.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/15050606podcast15.mp3" length="18360000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>19:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Fourteen</title>
<description>This week we'll hear the music of Natalie Walker, Syrin, MoShang and Zeropage. 
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/14050606podcast14.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/14050606podcast14.mp3" length="21225030" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>22:06</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Thirteen</title>
<description>Featuring Mr.s, Leroy Forbes, Ivan Kapec, Deerfoot and Stabilizer. This week the groove is the thing as we bounce from Poland to the UK to Croatia then Canada and finally Pennsylvania.
We begin with remarkable Polish artist Mr.S and his beguiling mix of chill out, Jazz and scat. Don't bother knocking. You are expected in 'Room 23'.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/13050606podcast13.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/13050606podcast13.mp3" length="24332330" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>25:20</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Twelve</title>
<description>This week we look to Canada, the U.K., Dallas and Chicago for the music of Adam Fielding, Acapulco Soundlab
Monotronaut, The Flavor Foundation and Quantum Soul</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/12050606podcast12.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/12050606podcast12.mp3" length="22887000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>24:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eleven (Podcaster Special Edition)</title>
<description>Featuring Anji Bee, Permanent4, Radio Orphans, Idyllic and Misanthropy. This is a podcasters special edition. This week we focus on music by those who work both sides of the podcasting microphone. Many bands publish podcasts for self-promotion. Other podcasters look to promote the work of others as well.
Anji Bee is vocalist of the band Love Spirals as well as host of The Chillcast. Here she is teamed up with producer Bitstream Dream and 'Love Me Leave Me'</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/11050606podcast11.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/11050606podcast11.mp3" length="21184000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>22:35</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Ten</title>
<description>Downtempo, Ambient, Trip Hop, Jazz and Dub featuring Green Man, Korpus Kallosum, Alu, and Gamsters</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 7 Apr 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/10050606podcast10.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/10050606podcast10.mp3" length="19776000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>21:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Nine</title>
<description>This week we'll explore the music of Jeff Rosiana, Scanlan, Psychonada and Zool</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/9050606podcast9.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/9050606podcast9.mp3" length="19974000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>21:18</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Eight</title>
<description>Downtempo, Ambient, Trip Hop, Jazz and Dub featuring Kmotiv, The Sleeper's Opera, Danny K, Digit All Love and Antony Raijekov</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/8050606podcast8.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/8050606podcast8.mp3" length="20715000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>22:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Seven</title>
<description>Downtempo, Ambient, Trip Hop, Jazz and Dub featuring Pale Beneath the Blue, Spacebum, Broken Sleep and Point of Good Origins</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/7050606podcast7.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/7050606podcast7.mp3" length="20876000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>22:01</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Six</title>
<description>Downtempo, Ambient, Trip Hop, Jazz and Dub featuring Indy, Karmacoda, Djust Feel It, The Engineer and Brozil</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2006 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/6050606podcast6.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/6050606podcast6.mp3" length="20494000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>21:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Five</title>
<description>On this edition of the Idyllic Music Podcast we hear from Hungry Lucy, Blaminak, Idyllic, Kristen Mainhart and Kojima This week remain statesside in the search of good music.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2006 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/5050606podcast5.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/5050606podcast5.mp3" length="19933000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>21:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>	

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Four</title>
<description>Downtempo, Ambient, Trip Hop, Jazz and Dub featuring 
The Hellbus, Aqualash, Nevertheless, Dub One and Cling</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2006 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/4050606podcast4.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/4050606podcast4.mp3" length="22575000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>20:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>	

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Three</title>
<description>Downtempo, Ambient, Trip Hop, Jazz and Dub featuring Atomica, Zerobae, Refrag and The Sound Gallery. This week's edition of Idyllic Music takes us across two oceans in search of music. </description>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2006 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/3050606podcast3.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/3050606podcast3.mp3" length="19494000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>20:47</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>	

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  Two</title>
<description>Downtempo, Ambient, Trip Hop, Jazz and Dub featuring Kevin Christensen, TriGMTar, absentmachine and Day One Symphony</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2006 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/2050606podcast2.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/2050606podcast2.mp3" length="19025084" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>19:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>	

<item>
<title>Idyllic Music  One</title>
<description>Downtempo, Ambient, Trip Hop, Jazz and Dub featuring Endless Blue, Joy, Takfrequenz and Idyllic  {podshow-f21e5de0bf554c3c9b2b29d7b1075341}</description> 
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2006 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/1050606podcast1.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.idyllicmusic.com/Podcasts/1050606podcast1.mp3" length="17450000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>18:36</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Trip Hop,Ambient,Jazz,Dub,Downtempo</itunes:keywords>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>