<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Clay Nelson Life Balance Hour</title>
    <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
    <description>The Clay Nelson Life Balance&#x2122; Hour radio show takes the motivational message of Clay Nelson, personal and business coach extraordinaire, to the airwaves every Wednesday at 2:00 PM PT and he has also made it available in podcast form. His program is designed to provide you with tools, information, guidance, and support in living your life.  He isn't likely to tell you anything you don’t already know in your heart of hearts, but what he will do is remind you of your power to have a say in how your life turns out!</description>
    <itunes:summary>The Clay Nelson Life Balance&#x2122; Hour radio show takes the motivational message of Clay Nelson, personal and business coach extraordinaire, to the airwaves every Wednesday at 2:00 PM PT and he has also made it available in podcast form. His program is designed to provide you with tools, information, guidance, and support in living your life.  He isn't likely to tell you anything you don’t already know in your heart of hearts, but what he will do is remind you of your power to have a say in how your life turns out!</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:subtitle>Only YOU have the power to have a say in how your life turns out!</itunes:subtitle>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <language>en</language>
    <pubDate>Wed, 4 Oct 2006 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 4 Oct 2006 10:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <itunes:author>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/podcast/cnlb_podcast_itms.jpg"/>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>cnlb@claynelsonlifebalance.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
      <itunes:category text="Business">
      <itunes:category text="Management &amp; Marketing"/>
	  </itunes:category>
      <itunes:category text="Kids &amp; Family"/>
      <itunes:category text="Health">
      <itunes:category text="Self-Help"/>
	  </itunes:category>
	  <item>
      <title>Completing Your Year with Power, Plan and Prospect</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key to not getting caught up in negativity is to stay present to your power!  Original airdate 12-Nov-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081112.mp3" length="5765452" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>The key to not getting caught up in negativity is to stay present to your power!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Life never gives us a break – there will always be more “stuff” waiting. The key to not getting caught up in negativity, and instead being powerful in your own behalf, is to stay present to your power! My challenge to you as we enter the last weeks of this year is staying present to this power by living from the 80% of life that is great, having a plan that gets us from where we are to where we want to be and having a clear vision that allows us to see what’s next in terms of prospects for our future.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>47:58</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081112.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Participating in Your Future</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What do you want your future to look like? And are you willing to participate to make it happen?  Original airdate 05-Nov-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 7 Nov 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081105.mp3" length="5754089" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>What do you want your future to look like? And are you willing to participate to make it happen?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Whether “your guy” won or not, the success of our collective future and your individual future does not rest in who will be sworn in to office in January! Your success and the success of our nation rests on us – the citizens of this nation – to be active participants in creating and building an outrageous future! None of us can expect to get to where we want to go, if we fail to get into action in our own behalf… and if we fail to tell those who are in leadership positions what we want! So what do you want your future to look like? And are you willing to participate to make it happen?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>47:56</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081105.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Truth</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Are you being true to yourself… and are you living a life that makes you happy?  Original airdate 29-Oct-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 4 Nov 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081029.mp3" length="5822906" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Are you being true to yourself… and are you living a life that makes you happy?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>The word “Truth” conjures up many thoughts about what truths one could be referring to.  But the truth that I most want to address with this show is are you being true to yourself… and are you living a life that makes you happy? Asking these questions of yourself – and being truthful with the answers – could be difficult! None of us are comfortable having the “mirror” held up in front of us, but if we don’t willingly take a look at how we feel about the life we live, the person we are, and the difference we make on the planet… how do we know if we are being true to ourselves?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:27</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081029.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Confusion</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Confusion is really a result of what we are feeling about our surroundings – and our own lack of commitment.  Original airdate 22-Oct-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 1 Nov 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081022.mp3" length="5823433" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Confusion is really a result of what we are feeling about our surroundings – and our own lack of commitment.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Confusion comes in all shapes and sizes.  There is confusion regarding how something is done, why something is done the way it is, confusion over why someone is doing what they are doing, what they are trying to say or an idea they are attempting to convey, confusion over who is supposed to be doing what, or confusion over a decision you need to make. But the truth is that “confusion” is really a result of what we are feeling about our surroundings – and our own lack of commitment. Confusion is just a place you get to in life where you forget what you are committed to!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:27</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081022.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Being Accountable... for Being Responsible</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accountability in Washington D.C., accountability in our schools, accountability in our homes starts with us!  Original airdate 08-Oct-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081008.mp3" length="5763594" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Accountability in Washington D.C., accountability in our schools, accountability in our homes starts with us!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>What if every single one of us REALLY took on accountability for our own lives? Do you see how that kind of responsibility would breed responsibility everywhere? The truth is that we don’t hold those in office to the highest levels of accountability, because all of us shun accountability on some level. We all talk a good talk, but when it comes to having our feet held to the fire we make excuses for our shortcomings, our children’s shortcomings…We don’t want to make people mad, we want to be liked. Accountability in Washington D.C., accountability in our schools, accountability in our homes starts with us! When each of us individuals are willing to be accountable for doing what is within our reach… then and only then can we hold our leaders to the same standard!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>47:57</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081008.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Trust</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Living from a place where you have no trust in the world or people around you is a hard thing to do.  Original airdate 01-Oct-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 6 Oct 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081001.mp3" length="5830639" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Living from a place where you have no trust in the world or people around you is a hard thing to do.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Trust is something we put out into the world - believing in the overall goodness of humanity. As our relationships and experiences expand and are generally positive, our trust deepens and grows.  But when that trust is broken, it often takes a lot to repair it. Living from a place where you have no trust in the world or people around you is a hard thing to do. If you don’t believe and trust in the integrity of your connection to someplace, some person, or some thing then what do you have? To build trust in anything… or anyone… you have to first and foremost trust yourself. After all, the only person who has a say in how you think and feel is you!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:31</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20081001.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>The Costs of Putting Yourself Last</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If we actually took the time to be with the person in the mirror, would we like what we see? Original airdate 24-Sep-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080924.mp3" length="5827011" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>If we actually took the time to be with the person in the mirror, would we like what we see?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>We all know people who put everyone else’s needs above their own. But concentrating on the needs of others is a really great place to not have to be with ourselves.  Think about it… if we actually took the time to be with the person in the mirror, would we like what we see?  The truth is that it is much easier for all of us to help do for and fix others than it is to deal with ourselves. If everything you do keeps you from taking care of you… from keeping your own batteries fully charged… from being 100% happy and having fun… from taking on your own growth… then it is time to stop do-do-doing for everyone else and start doing for YOU!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:29</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080924.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Managing Unexpected Change</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[You can choose to be in action around the changes you are faced with or you can be a victim of change… the choice is yours! Original airdate 17-Sep-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080917.mp3" length="5764622" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>You can choose to be in action around the changes you are faced with or you can be a victim of change… the choice is yours!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>It is one thing to talk about managing change, but when the change you are faced with is so rapidly life altering, how do you really “manage” something so big; something you really don’t have a say in? Well, the solution isn’t so much in a step 1-2-3 type of answer – it is bigger than “how” you manage unexpected changes! It is up to you to make your life whatever it is you want it to be, regardless of what the world has in store. You can choose to be in action around the changes you are faced with or you can be a victim of change… the choice is yours!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>47:58</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080917.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Your Life's Priorities</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the midst of doing “it all”, don’t give into the temptation to drop taking care of you out! Original airdate 03-Sep-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080903.mp3" length="5879975" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>In the midst of doing “it all”, don’t give into the temptation to drop taking care of you out!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>The only person who can set the priorities in your life is you.  You know what is important to you. And when setting priorities you have to remember to keep you first… you’ve got to take care of you first so that you have the energy (both physical and mental) to manage everything else in your life! In the midst of doing “it all”, don’t give into the temptation to drop taking care of you out!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:55</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080903.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Hearing vs. Really Listening</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our worlds are filled with a constant barrage of input, but what are we learning from it? Original airdate 27-Aug-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 4 Sep 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080827.mp3" length="5817809" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Our worlds are filled with a constant barrage of input, but what are we learning from it?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>There is so much going on around us – so much noise – that we tend to hear everything, but what are we actually listening to? Our worlds are filled with a constant barrage of input, but what are we learning from it? If we are constantly talking… if we constantly tune people out… if we merely hear things in the background without really listening to what is being communicated to us, chances are that we aren’t learning anything! Rarely do any of us really listen 100% of the time.  But what if we did?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:24</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080827.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Choosing to Have a Powerful 4th Quarter</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We can learn a lot from the amazing accomplishments of Olympic athletes about what it takes to succeed in whatever our goals are. Original airdate 20-Aug-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080820.mp3" length="5823150" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>We can learn a lot from the amazing accomplishments of Olympic athletes about what it takes to succeed in whatever our goals are.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>As you consider what you want to accomplish in the last quarter of this year, I’d like you to think about the Olympic athletes that are now competing with other athletes from all over the globe. What an amazing thing they do! They train their bodies AND their minds so that they can create phenomenal results. Do all of them bring home Olympic gold (or even silver or bronze)? No, but do they deliver their personal best?  Yes!!  Guess what, they have the same distractions that you do -- and yet they have pushed, planned, gotten coaching, and trained in order to accomplish what it is they say they want.  I believe that we can learn a lot from these amazing athletes about what it takes to succeed in whatever our goals are!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:26</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080820.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Taking Care of You</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Have you done what you really set out to do this summer? Original airdate 13-Aug-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080813.mp3" length="5767749" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Have you done what you really set out to do this summer?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>The stark realization that the lazy days of summer are coming to an abrupt end can be downright disappointing. But the summer isn’t over yet, so I have to ask: Have you done what you really set out to do this summer? Have you taken the time for you that you deserve? And if not, it isn’t too late, but it is time to get going!! The “best of intentions” aren’t nearly enough to take us from wanting to take care of ourselves to actually doing it, we have to put a few tools in place that help us take care of us!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>47:59</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080813.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Lightening Your Mood</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If our default way of going through our day is to focus on the negatives, grumble and be down on life, how do we change our default way of being from negative to positive? Original airdate 06-Aug-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080806.mp3" length="5823026" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>If our default way of going through our day is to focus on the negatives, grumble and be down on life, how do we change our default way of being from negative to positive?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>It occurred to me that we talk a lot about focusing on the positive and having a smile on our faces. However, how do we be positive when work is stressing us out…bills are stressing us out…gas prices are stressing us out…or we’re torn between wanting to spend more time with our families and the need to bring in more money to meet the family’s needs? Let’s face it. We have a lot to be stressed about! So, if our default way of going through our day is to focus on the negatives, grumble and be down on life, how do we change our default way of being from negative to positive?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:26</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080806.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>The Start of a Positive Mental Evolution</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What would happen if we all woke up to the power each of us has to turn our mediocre, complacent, life-is-hard attitudes around? Original airdate 23-Jul-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080723.mp3" length="5832869" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>What would happen if we all woke up to the power each of us has to turn our mediocre, complacent, life-is-hard attitudes around?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>As a business coach, I talk with business owners from around the country each day. I am privy to all of their ups and downs, and I have to tell you, I’m hearing a lot of downs right now. And the truth is that I’m frustrated, because no matter what the economy is doing, no matter what circumstances are going on around us: LIFE DOESN’T HAVE TO BE HARD… WE DON’T HAVE TO SETTLE… WE CAN HAVE THE LIFE AND BUSINESSES WE WANT! Now, I am not trivializing the problems many Americans are now facing. I simply want to wake all of us up to the power we have to turn our mediocre, complacent, life-is-hard attitudes around.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:31</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080723.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Acknowledging and Appreciating Others</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The more we can look at the world from a greater perspective – appreciate the simple things in life, rather than worrying about what we don’t have – the more easily appreciation becomes part of who we are. Original airdate 09-Jul-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080709.mp3" length="5830670" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>The more we can look at the world from a greater perspective – appreciate the simple things in life, rather than worrying about what we don’t have – the more easily appreciation becomes part of who we are.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>No matter how difficult our personal situation may be, we all have things that we can be appreciative of. The really cool thing is that the more we openly acknowledge our appreciation, the more good and happiness that will return to us! Unfortunately, the exact opposite is true too! When we fail to show our appreciation for even the “smallest” things, eventually those around us will stop doing things for us!! The more we can look at the world from a greater perspective – appreciate the simple things in life, rather than worrying about what we don’t have – the more easily appreciation becomes part of who we are.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:31</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080709.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Managing Chaos</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How do we manage unexpected events without going upside down? Original airdate 02-Jul-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080702.mp3" length="5756355" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How do we manage unexpected events without going upside down?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Chaos is one of those things that send some people running for cover and others absolutely thrive on it! How do we manage unexpected events without going upside down? Most of us are creatures of habit, and chaos does little to calm those of us who operate from a very A + B = C existence.  But the truth is that Chaos is really more of a normal occurrence than Order, and the better we are at managing the chaos in our lives the more we will learn and grow from the chaos that is around us! After all, where do we learn the most from – those things we do day in and day out OR those things that sneak into our tidy, orderly worlds?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>47:53</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080702.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Getting Back to Basics</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is something to be said for living life simply. How about getting back to the basics of living? Maybe we could even learn something from our own children? Original airdate 25-Jun-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080625.mp3" length="5832954" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>There is something to be said for living life simply. How about getting back to the basics of living? Maybe we could even learn something from our own children?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>There is something to be said for living life simply. Now, I’m not talking about selling your house and living in a tent somewhere. I’m talking about living life without so much stuff… at least the stuff that doesn’t make us happier! The truth is, for me at least, that the more stuff I have… the more things are piled around me, the less organized I am, the less peace of mind I have! The point is not to shut down your life, or your way of living if the way you are living works for you. However, if you are stretched to the maximum in terms of time, finances, serenity, and happiness… something needs to change! Change what? How about getting back to the basics of living! Maybe we could even learn something from our own children?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:32</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080625.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Complain or Create</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Complaining gets you nowhere. To find a solution through or around life's circumstances, create one! Original airdate 18-Jun-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080618.mp3" length="5822710" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Complaining gets you nowhere. To find a solution through or around life's circumstances, create one!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>One thing I have learned in my 64 years on this planet is that as bad as a situation in my life might be, there is always someone, somewhere who is worse off than me! There are people out there with much bigger things going on in their lives, and what strikes me most is that those people aren’t complaining!  They aren’t pouting in a corner somewhere.  They are out living life… they are out creating a way around or through their circumstances.  They create instead of complain!!!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:27</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080618.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Making a Difference</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Every single one of us has an opportunity to make a difference on this planet. Original airdate 11-Jun-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080611.mp3" length="5821457" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Every single one of us has an opportunity to make a difference on this planet.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Every single one of us has an opportunity to make a difference on this planet. No matter what our financial status might be, the color of our skin, our gender, our physical or mental abilities, where we live, the kind of car we drive or the clothes we wear - we all can make a difference! I want to encourage others to get involved and make a difference in their communities, for organizations and causes that are tugging on their hearts, and I want to show everyone that making a difference is really an easy thing to do!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:26</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080611.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Having Fun Doing the Same Ole, Same Ole</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We create our own boredom... and on the flip-side, we have the power to choose and create our own happiness. Original airdate 28-May-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080528.mp3" length="5457123" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>We create our own boredom... and on the flip-side, we have the power to choose and create our own happiness.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>No matter how much we have to do – no matter how much our jobs or our homes and families demand of us, everyone encounters boredom. Yet, we can’t just chuck our responsibilities out the window because we aren’t lit up about what we are doing! And besides that, what if our boredom with life isn’t about life, but instead our attitude toward life? We create our own boredom... and on the flip-side, we have the power to choose and create our own happiness.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:24</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080528.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Enjoying the Journey</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What would your life’s journey be like if you slowed down enough to really enjoy getting to where you want to be? Original airdate 21-May-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080521.mp3" length="5889337" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>What would your life’s journey be like if you slowed down enough to really enjoy getting to where you want to be?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>We’re always in such a hurry to do something... to reach an end goal. We want what we want NOW, and we sometimes focus so intently on the end result, have you ever considered what you are missing out on along the way? Consider this question: What would your life’s journey be like if you slowed down enough to really enjoy getting to where you want to be? What would your life be like if you took on everything you do as if it were a garden that you are growing, nurturing, and preparing for harvest?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:00</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080521.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>A Few of My Favorite Things</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clay Nelson is interviewed by Alyce Faye Eichelberger Cleese.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080514.mp3" length="5468507" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Clay Nelson is interviewed by Alyce Faye Eichelberger Cleese.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Alyce Faye Eichelberger Cleese, a well-known psychotherapist, published author, and radio show host, interviewed Clay Nelson on her weekly radio show, A Few of My Favorite Things.  This fun and playful discussion will help you get to know Clay Nelson as a person – his likes, his dislikes, his background, his passions, and so much more!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:29</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080514.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Having Fun With the Family...</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What would it be like to not have to drive somewhere to be entertained, and have just as much fun, if not more fun, just being a family? Original airdate 07-May-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080507.mp3" length="5826712" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>What would it be like to not have to drive somewhere to be entertained, and have just as much fun, if not more fun, just being a family?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>...and Not Having to Drive Anywhere! With prices skyrocketing – from the gas we need in our cars, to airline tickets, and the food we put on our tables – the majority of us are looking to cut back on our spending. What’s the first thing to get cut out?  Entertainment and travel! Yes, the kids are groaning, because they are bored! Parents may even feel a bit stir crazy! But what if spending recreational time as a family wasn’t about the money you spend while you do what you do? What would it be like to not have to drive somewhere to be entertained, and have just as much fun, if not more fun, just being a family?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:33</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080507.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Managing Unmanageable Change</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Don’t relate to change like it is something that “just happens” and then you react to it. Think ahead about changes. Have a plan, and then choose to live it! Original airdate 30-April-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 May 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080430.mp3" length="5828892" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Don’t relate to change like it is something that “just happens” and then you react to it. Think ahead about changes. Have a plan, and then choose to live it!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Who do we have to be to have a say in how our life turns out... even when we are faced with change that we don’t have a say in? The price of gas, the state of the economy, road construction making us late for an appointment, children growing older, the loss of a loved one — these are all examples of change that we don’t have a say in.  We don’t create it, it just happens and we are left with the aftereffects. These are the very types of changes that can put us into a huge victimized pit of despair, but only if we CHOOSE to go there!!! Don’t relate to change like it is something that “just happens” and then you react to it. Think ahead about changes. Have a plan, and then choose to live it!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:30</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080430.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Dumping Disappointment</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The odds of being successful in everything we do is very small. But when we are disappointed it can hit us hard. How do you deal with the disappointment you’ve encountered? Original airdate 23-April-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080423.mp3" length="5772037" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>The odds of being successful in everything we do is very small. But when we are disappointed it can hit us hard. How do you deal with the disappointment you’ve encountered?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Disappointment is a reality of life.  The odds of being successful in everything we do is very small and besides, if we only do the things that we are sure to excel at, then we probably aren’t reaching high enough! But when we are disappointed it can hit us hard. So what do you do?  How do you deal with the disappointment you’ve encountered?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:01</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080423.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Taking a Stand</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Have you ever watched a bully attempt to push someone around… maybe you’ve been pushed around too.  What happened? Original airdate 16-April-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080416.mp3" length="5881743" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Have you ever watched a bully attempt to push someone around… maybe you’ve been pushed around too.  What happened?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Have you ever watched a bully attempt to push someone around… maybe you’ve been pushed around too.  What happened?  Frequently we give in, but why? Because most of us don’t really believe that we have a choice in what goes on in our lives and in and around our world. But the truth is, we DO have a choice and we all have the power to make a difference in our lives and the lives of others, and only we can make it happen!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:56</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080416.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Dealing with I Don't Wanna</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We all have days when we “don’t wanna”, but what separates you from others is your making the CHOICE to play anyway! Original airdate 02-April-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080402.mp3" length="5812687" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>We all have days when we “don’t wanna”, but what separates you from others is your making the CHOICE to play anyway!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Getting going when you don’t wanna is all about recognizing that you are stopped and then making the CHOICE to play… making the CHOICE to have fun… making the CHOICE to be your word, and asking for help when your brain is stopping you. We can’t always lay around on the beach or wherever your preferred place to get away from it all is.  But you can have a clear mind and a go get’em attitude whenever you choose to have them. Remember:  You can complain about the life you have or create the life you love.  Choose!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:22</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080402.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Patience</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being patient is really no more than a choice we make to not act impulsively, give things the time they deserve and give people the respect they deserve. Original airdate 26-March-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080326.mp3" length="5819775" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Being patient is really no more than a choice we make to not act impulsively, give things the time they deserve and give people the respect they deserve.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Being patient is really no more than a choice we make to not act impulsively, give things the time they deserve and give people the respect they deserve. Meaning -- patience is really about self-control! Choosing not to yell, and instead calmly discussing an upset. Choosing to not be crabby with the check-out clerk, because of the long line. Choosing to slow down and be respectful, even when you don’t feel like you have the time to do so. Choosing to make room for others to learn at their own pace and to even contribute to you! Mastering self-control and patience takes practice, choosing to be patient when we might not otherwise have been! Get present to who you are being… where you leave people… and what you ultimately want to accomplish.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:25</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080326.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>How to Hear and Be Heard</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real listening is one of the greatest gifts that you can give-—to another and to yourself. Original airdate 12-March-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080319.mp3" length="5755954" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Real listening is one of the greatest gifts that you can give-—to another and to yourself.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>How many times has someone said this to you… or how many times have you felt this way about another? “You never listen to me... You didn’t hear what I said!” Do you ever hear complaints like this from the people in your life? What are they really saying? Well, it’s not about hearing someone… it’s about getting the communication! Real listening is one of the greatest gifts that you can give-—to another and to yourself. So let’s take a look at what it’s like to listen effectively and get the communication.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>47:53</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080319.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Avoiding Avoidance</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The more time we spend “avoiding”, the more time we waste! So how do we avoid avoidance and take on life head on? Original airdate 12-March-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080312.mp3" length="5827419" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>The more time we spend “avoiding”, the more time we waste! So how do we avoid avoidance and take on life head on?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>If we allow ourselves to crawl under a rock, because we are avoiding an uncomfortable situation, what might we miss out on? If we soldier on with a chip on our shoulder or fear in our step, what do we lose? If we make others wrong consistently for how we feel, what relationships are we giving up on? The more time we spend “avoiding”, the more time we waste! So how do we avoid avoidance and take on life head on? It’s about clearing, communicating, and getting committed.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:29</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080312.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Managing the Circumstances of Life</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is never a good time to deal with all of the things that come up in our lives. So how do you keep from becoming overwhelmed by your circumstances? Original airdate 05-March-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080305.mp3" length="5834644" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>There is never a good time to deal with all of the things that come up in our lives. So how do you keep from becoming overwhelmed by your circumstances?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Life has a way of throwing things at us… getting us right in the gut when we least expect it, and it all happens on top of the balls we are already juggling and very often even dropping! There is never a good time to deal with all of the things that come up in our lives. So how do you keep from becoming overwhelmed by your circumstances? How do you keep “it” all together, manage the changes in your life, and manage the demands that are placed upon you each and every day? This is called dealing with your circumstances!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:33</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080305.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Being Bold</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being bold is about standing up for what you believe in – whether it be a cause or even yourself! Original airdate 20-February-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080220.mp3" length="5406310" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Being bold is about standing up for what you believe in – whether it be a cause or even yourself!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Boldness isn’t about who is loud and who isn’t. Being bold is about standing up for what you believe in – whether it be a cause or even yourself! What do you choose when you are pushed? When you step out and visibly take a bold stand on any issue, there are going to be people who don’t agree.  So why do it… why go out on a limb? TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>44:58</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080220.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Goal Setting</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Often times, setting goals and then accomplishing them is not enough - we all need a purpose, and not just any random purpose. What is your purpose in life? Why are you on the planet? Original airdate 13-February-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080213.mp3" length="5475695" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Often times, setting goals and then accomplishing them is not enough - we all need a purpose, and not just any random purpose. What is your purpose in life? Why are you on the planet?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Goal setting and accomplishing those goals should and can be fun and made more meaningful when paired with the power of purpose. Most people, when first asked, describe their purpose in life rather casually as “to be a good father” or “to be a successful businesswoman.” While these are great things to "be", what about YOU and who you are committed to being not only for others, but also for yourself?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:33</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080213.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Really Loving Life!</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How do we get past negativity and create our own happiness, when happiness and really being at peace with the world comes from the inside? Original airdate 06-February-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080206.mp3" length="5827614" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How do we get past negativity and create our own happiness, when happiness and really being at peace with the world comes from the inside?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Have you ever looked at two different people… one who seems really happy and one who doesn’t?  What do you think is the difference between them? How unstoppable could you become by giving up the belief that life is supposed to be hard, getting present to the positives of your life, communicating fully with those around you and learning to ask for help when you need it? Remember: You are the only person who has a say in how your life turns out… this includes how happy you are!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:29</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080206.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Keeping Your Life Moving Forward...</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[...When the World is Pushing Back. We can complain about life's circumstances and let them stop us, but why not create a way through them that keeps us moving? Original airdate 30-January-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080130.mp3" length="5818226" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>...When the World is Pushing Back. We can complain about life's circumstances and let them stop us, but why not create a way through them that keeps us moving?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Have you turned on the news lately? The economy, bad weather…Did you let the news get you down? As with everything in life, we have a choice.  We can complain about life's circumstances and let them stop us or we can create a way around life's circumstances (or even through them), and choose to keep moving forward. Why not take on the world with the unstoppable attitude of “Watch out World, because here I come!”?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:24</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080130.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Giving Up the Only I Can Do It Syndrome</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Often times we behave as if we are super-human and can be all things to all people and do everything there is to be done. But the truth is, we can't! Original airdate 23-January-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080123.mp3" length="5882314" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Often times we behave as if we are super-human and can be all things to all people and do everything there is to be done. But the truth is, we can't!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Many people operate in a work-work-work mode on the premise that at some point in the future all of their hard work and sacrifice will pay off with success, fun and happiness. We behave as if we are super-human and can be all things to all people and do everything there is to be done. But the truth is, we can't! This program looks at the "Only I Can Do It" syndrome, the costs it brings with it, and tips for putting a stop to your "control freak" ways and how to ask for help both on the job and at home.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:26</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080123.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Giving Up Complacency</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Complacency plagues all of us at one time or another, but it doesn’t have to stop us. Original airdate 16-January-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080116.mp3" length="5825326" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Complacency plagues all of us at one time or another, but it doesn’t have to stop us.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Complacency plagues all of us at one time or another, but it doesn’t have to stop us.  Instead of limping through each day, we can choose actions that restore our sharp edge, invigorate our spirit and lighten our step. Thinking won't do it... action will! This program looks at the causes and costs of becoming complacent, and offers tips to get yourself moving again.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:28</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080116.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Commitment: Really Wanting What You Want Part II</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A continuation of last week's discussion on commitment and really wanting what you want. Original airdate 09-January-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080109.mp3" length="5828689" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>A continuation of last week's discussion on commitment and really wanting what you want.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>When it comes to commitment, it is easy to say, "I am going to do this." Or "Who I am committed to being is this...", but what actions do you follow those words with? Since our brains are so creative at keeping us in what we know, sticking to our commitments...making a change in who we chose to be takes Planning, Action, Team and Accountability.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:31</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080109.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Commitment: Really Wanting What You Want</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When it comes to commitment, it is easy to say, "I am going to do this." Or "Who I am committed to being is this...", but what actions do you follow those words with? Original airdate 02-January-2008.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080102.mp3" length="5828689" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>When it comes to commitment, it is easy to say, "I am going to do this." Or "Who I am committed to being is this...", but what actions do you follow those words with?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>When it comes to commitment, it is easy to say, "I am going to do this." Or "Who I am committed to being is this...", but what actions do you follow those words with? Since our brains are so creative at keeping us in what we know, sticking to our commitments...making a change in who we chose to be takes Planning, Action, Team and Accountability.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:30</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20080102.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Acknowledging Your Accomplishments</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The best way to get the New Year off to a great start is to get complete with the old one! Original airdate 26-December-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071226.mp3" length="5748785" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>The best way to get the New Year off to a great start is to get complete with the old one!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Making New Year Commitments...The best way to get the New Year off to a great start is to get complete with the old one!  This program will show you how to give yourself a hearty pat on the back and powerfully create a plan for doing whatever it is you say you want to do in 2008!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>47:50</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071226.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Taking Time for You and Your Family</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learn how to propel you and your family to the top of your priority list! Original airdate 19-December-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071219.mp3" length="5830466" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Learn how to propel you and your family to the top of your priority list!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>When work-work-work gets the best of us, whether it is work for the job you do or getting ready for the holidays, our families and our own personal well-being gets the short end of the stick.  This program addresses how to propel you and your family to the top of your priority list!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:30</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071219.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>How to Really Hear What is Being Said</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How many times have you been in a conversation where the real meaning of what is being said is lost on you? Original airdate 05-December-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071205.mp3" length="5761708" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How many times have you been in a conversation where the real meaning of what is being said is lost on you?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>How many times have you been in a conversation where the real meaning  of what is being said is lost on you? Sometimes we don’t understand  what the other person is saying but are embarassed to admit it; other  times we’re simply not present to the conversation. This program  offers tips at making sure everyone involved in a conversation understands  what is being said, and ways to get back to being present to the person  in front of you when you catch yourself wishing you were somewhere else!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:26</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071205.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sharing your knowledge and teaching what you know to another person is one of the greatest gifts you can give. Original airdate 28-November-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071128.mp3" length="5821969" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Sharing your knowledge and teaching what you know to another person is one of the greatest gifts you can give.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Sharing your knowledge and teaching what you know to another person is one of the greatest gifts you can give. After all, how much more could we all accomplish each day if we just took the time to participate in the growth of another human being? At the least, you might realize what you know and what you don't know about what it is you are teaching!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:26</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071128.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Being Present to the Life You Are Living</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rediscover what's missing, put it back into place, and get back to Being Present to where your feet are in this world! Original airdate 21-November-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071121.mp3" length="5818031" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Rediscover what's missing, put it back into place, and get back to Being Present to where your feet are in this world!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>How many times have you been in a conversation with someone, and instead of being present to what the person is saying, you are thinking about and present to the shirt they are wearing...or who they remind you of...or how hungry you are...or maybe even that you don't want to be there? What are the costs of letting your mind be distracted because you weren’t present to where your feet are? Being present is all about being who we need to be, hearing what we need to hear, and saying what we need to say. Rediscover what's missing, put it back into place, and get back to Being Present!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:24</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071121.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Turning Down the Mind Chatter</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What if you could turn down mind chatter and keep it from getting in the way of the job you do, your relationships, and even how you feel about yourself? Original airdate 7-November-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071107.mp3" length="5888236" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>What if you could turn down mind chatter and keep it from getting in the way of the job you do, your relationships, and even how you feel about yourself?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>We’ve all had moments when our heads are so filled with our thoughts that we can’t hear what anyone else has to say.  This is what we call mind chatter.  This program is all about how to turn down mind chatter and keep it from getting in the way of the job we do, our relationships, and even how we feel about ourselves!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:59</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071107.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>The Value of Full and Complete Communication II</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What would happen if everyone on the planet communicated fully and completely at all times? Original airdate 31-October-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 2 Nov 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071031.mp3" length="5886793" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>A continuation of the October 24, 2007 show topic - What would happen if everyone on the planet communicated fully and completely at all times?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Consider this: What would happen if everyone on the planet communicated fully and completely at all times?  The potential result is absolutely mind-bogging! So during this program we break-down the costs of not communicating fully and completely and how to take on communication in a new and empowering way… you’ll not only learn the value of full and complete communication but you’ll learn how to do it too!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:59</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071031.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>The Value of Full and Complete Communication</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What would happen if everyone on the planet communicated fully and completely at all times? Original airdate 24-October-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071024.mp3" length="5823678" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>What would happen if everyone on the planet communicated fully and completely at all times?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Consider this: What would happen if everyone on the planet communicated fully and completely at all times?  The potential result is absolutely mind-bogging! So during this program we break-down the costs of not communicating fully and completely and how to take on communication in a new and empowering way… you’ll not only learn the value of full and complete communication but you’ll learn how to do it too!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:27</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071024.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Sharpening the Edge of Integrity</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How do I clean up any problems I’ve created and put my integrity back into place? Original airdate 17-October-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071017.mp3" length="5815516" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How do I clean up any problems I’ve created and put my integrity back into place?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Every once in a while we all should give ourselves an integrity check-up.  After all, if we are out in the world shaking things up, we’re more apt to stumble than most, but that is okay, as long as we get back up!  Ask yourself: Do I do what I say I am going to do, and if I don’t, what do I do about it?  (How do I clean up any problems I’ve created and put my integrity back into place?)  Listen to this program and find out how!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:23</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071017.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Dealing with Change</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[You are the only person who has a say in how your life turns out! Original airdate 03-October-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071003.mp3" length="5875688" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>You are the only person who has a say in how your life turns out!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Change is inevitable. It comes at us and the only thing we can do is choose to dance inside of that change, or not. Meaning, you are the only person who has a say in how your life turns out. This program breaks down how to deal with change and even how to use it to your advantage!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:53</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20071003.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Asking for What You Want</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regain your courage to ask for what you want and what you need! Original airdate 26-September-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070926.mp3" length="5843510" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Regain your courage to ask for what you want and what you need!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Many people avoid asking for what they want because they don’t want to appear selfish or self-centered.  Yet, how many people can do everything there is to do, gather everything they need themselves and operate 100% on their own?  They can’t, and this program will help to us regain our courage to ask for what we want and what we need!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:37</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070926.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Getting What You Say You Want</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What are the keys to having the life we say we want to live? Original airdate 19-September-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070919.mp3" length="5822512" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>What are the keys to having the life we say we want to live?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Have you ever thought about how much easier/happier/more productive life would be if we chose to stand up and be responsible for everything we do and say, and everything we don’t do and don’t say?? How much more fun would we have?  How much easier would it be to actually get what we say we want?  This program is all about how accountability, and our willingness to commit to having a life and building a team that supports us in our efforts, are key to having the life we say we want to live! </itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:26</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070919.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Energizing Your Life</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regaining your passion for living is simple to do when you have a personal plan that keeps you on track! Original airdate 12-September-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070912.mp3" length="5783947" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Regaining your passion for living is simple to do when you have a personal plan that keeps you on track!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Boredom is something that overcomes each and every one of us at one time or another.  So what if regaining your spark and energizing your life was as simple as putting YOU back into your life???  Well, luckily regaining your passion for living is that simple, and it is even simpler to do when you have a personal plan that keeps you on track!  This program walks you through what a personal plan is, how to create one and how to one to work in your life!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:07</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070912.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Fear</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How can you have fear become something that drives you, rather than stops you? Original airdate 5-September-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 7 Sep 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070905.mp3" length="5781109" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How can you have fear become something that drives you, rather than stops you?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Fear is something that grips each and every one of us at various times in our lives. Yet, it doesn’t have to be something that causes us to turn and run a different direction. This program discusses how to have fear be something that fuels you, instead of stops you and asks the question: What much fun would it be to have just enough fear in front of you such that the hair on your arms stood up one or twice a day?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:05</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070905.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Communication Within the Family Part 2</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A continuation of our discussion on strengthening families through talking and listening! Original airdate 29-August-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070829.mp3" length="5773412" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>A continuation of our discussion on strengthening families through talking and listening!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>A continuation of our August 22, 2007 show about communication within the family. Whether it is our parents and siblings or our “family” made up of friends, we all want to feel “related” to another human being, and the tug is so strong that we’ll create “family” with the wrong types of people just to fulfill our need to belong.  This program is about how to strengthen our family bonds through communication and listening and will provide tips on how to get the children in your life talking and how to open their hearts up to listening too!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:01</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070829.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Communication Within the Family</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to get the children in your life talking and how to open their hearts up to listening too! Original airdate 22-August-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2007 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070822.mp3" length="5806944" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How to get the children in your life talking and how to open their hearts up to listening too!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Family is the nucleus to which all of us are bound.  Whether it is our parents and siblings or our “family” made up of friends, we all want to feel “related” to another human being, and the tug is so strong that we’ll create “family” with the wrong types of people just to fulfill our need to belong.  This program is about how to strengthen our family bonds with communication and will provide tips on how to get the children in your life talking and how to open their hearts up to listening too!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:18</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070822.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>The Art of Listening</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In today’s fast-paced world we listen to a great deal of stuff around us, but are we really “listening”?  Do we really hear what is being said? Original airdate 15-August-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070815.mp3" length="5806203" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>In today’s fast-paced world we listen to a great deal of stuff around us, but are we really “listening”?  Do we really hear what is being said?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>In today’s fast-paced world we listen to a great deal of stuff around us, but are we really “listening”?  Do we really hear what is being said, and just as important, do we hear what isn’t being said?  This program takes a look at what gets in the way of our really listening to what is being said, how to get around it, and reap the benefits of listening and being listened to!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:18</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070815.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Giving Up Worry</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lets take a look at why we worry, how to give up worry, and choosing to take on life as fun, instead of hard and worry filled! Original airdate 08-August-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070808.mp3" length="5809960" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Lets take a look at why we worry, how to give up worry, and choosing to take on life as fun, instead of hard and worry filled!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Worry is something that most people do really well, but there is a difference between someone who worries and allows that worry to stop them and those who worry, but continue to move forward no matter what. (In other words, they are unstoppable.)  They give up their worry and instead focus on what they can do in a situation, instead of what they can’t!  This program breaks down why we worry, how to give up worry, and choosing to take on life as fun, instead of hard and worry filled!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:20</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070808.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Change!</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How can we get present enough in our cluttered worlds to see changes coming and then smart enough to use those changes to our best advantage? Original airdate 01-August-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070801.mp3" length="5810056" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How can we get present enough in our cluttered worlds to see changes coming and then smart enough to use those changes to our best advantage?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Our worlds and everything around us can change in the blink of an eye.  Some of it is unexpected and other changes you can see coming for a mile.  The challenge, however, is being present enough in our cluttered worlds to see those changes coming and then smart enough to use those changes to our best advantage instead of being trampled by them, and that is what this program is all about!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:20</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070801.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Getting Going When You Don't Wanna</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How can we get going when we’d rather be at the beach or still in bed? How do we get going when we are stopped cold? Original airdate 25-July-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070725.mp3" length="5805695" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How can we get going when we’d rather be at the beach or still in bed? How do we get going when we are stopped cold?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>The lazy days of summer are nearly upon us… those days when we want to soak up the last speck of summertime fun and do very little of anything else.  Unfortunately, the world, our lives, our responsibilities, and the things we are accountable for don’t take a summer vacation… or a spring, fall, or winter vacation for that matter! So how can we get going when we’d rather be at the beach or still in bed? How do we get going when we are stopped cold?  This program addresses these questions and provides tips on getting yourself motivated and enthusiastic about living life!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:18</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070725.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Healthy Living II: The Power of Mental Calisthenics</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mental fitness and physical fitness go hand-in-hand, why not get them both in order? Original airdate 18-July-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070718.mp3" length="5808289" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Mental fitness and physical fitness go hand-in-hand, why not get them both in order?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>When we think about healthy living most of us immediately think about: exercise, food choices, and getting adequate rest.  Rarely do we think about the role our mental health has in the healthy living equation!  Instead we think about our mental well-being separate from our physical well-being. Yet mental/emotional stress, as an example, has clearly negative effects on us physically. So when our emotional/mental fitness and physical fitness go hand-in-hand, why not get them both in order?  That’s what this program is all about… balancing our physical and mental well-being to create a complete and healthy life.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:19</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070718.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Healthy Living I</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to live a life you love, you have to have a body that will allow you to live it. Original airdate 11-July-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070711.mp3" length="5804941" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>In order to live a life you love, you have to have a body that will allow you to live it.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>In order to live a life you love, you have to have a body that will allow you to live it. You must take care of your physical well-being! Yet, physical fitness is something we hear about so much that many of us have tuned it out.  So this program is all about taking the dread out of this topic, having fun, and helping our listeners not only get motivated to take better care of their physical well-being but provides tips for helping them do so!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:17</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070711.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Family: Can’t Live with Em, Can’t Live Without Em</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How do we get past all of the things that make us crazy and back to how important all of our family members are to us? Original airdate 27-June-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 3 Jul 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070627.mp3" length="5796097" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How do we get past all of the things that make us crazy and back to how important all of our family members are to us?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Family, for the great majority of us, is at the core of all we do, but at the same time have you ever noticed how much time we spend avoiding our families? The truth is, no matter how much we LOVE our families we don’t always want to be with them and sometimes we don’t even like them.  So how do we handle it? How do we get past all of the things that make us crazy and back to how important all of our family members are to us?  That is what this program is about.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:13</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070627.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Time Management</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Every second that goes by, is a second we can’t ever get back. So how do you spend your time? Original airdate 20-June-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070620.mp3" length="5572140" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Every second that goes by, is a second we can’t ever get back. So how do you spend your time?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Time. Every second that goes by, is a second we can’t ever get back. So how do you spend your time? Do you spend it wisely? Do you make every second count or do you find yourself wasting the time you do have wishing you had more time? The fact is the faster our worlds go, the faster our time goes, and when you literally have the world at your fingertips it is tough to feel like the only thing in our way is the clock!  Now, since the clock isn’t going away, how can we best manage the time we have? That is what this program is all about!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>46:21</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070620.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Dancing with Communication</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What can we do to sharpen the edge on our communication skills? Original airdate 13-June-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070613.mp3" length="5812477" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>What can we do to sharpen the edge on our communication skills?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>The dance of communication is something we do day-in and day-out, and some days, we’re better at it than others!  So when we aren’t at our best in our communications, what steps can we take so that everyone involved is left whole and complete?  And what can we do to sharpen the edge on our communication skills?  That’s what this program is all about.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:21</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070613.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Planning For Your Vacation? Why not Plan for Your Life Too?</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Take on planning your life with gusto and make this game we call life more fun and inspiring. Original airdate 23-May-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070523.mp3" length="5786599" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Take on planning your life with gusto and make this game we call life more fun and inspiring.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>You’ve got to love this time of year. People everywhere are either putting the finishing touches on their vacation plans or, if they don’t have their summer vacation mapped out yet, they are frantically working on where they are going and when and with whom!!! Too bad we don’t put this kind of effort into planning for our lives! This program will teach you how to take on planning your life with gusto and making this game we call life would be much more fun and inspiring to play!!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:08</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070523.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Getting Started When You’re Stopped</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Take a look at the reasons we get stopped, how we know that we are stopped, and how to get going again. Original airdate 9-May-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070509.mp3" length="5807472" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Take a look at the reasons we get stopped, how we know that we are stopped, and how to get going again.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Late spring brings with it not only beautiful flowers and budding trees, it often times brings with it an air of tiredness, excuses, and reasons for not wanting to play; instead of holding on to the energy that early spring brings us, we get caught in the drama of the impending summer, and many, many people get stopped!  This program is all about taking a look at the reasons we get stopped, how we know that we are stopped, and how to get going again.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:18</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070509.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Assumptions</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assumptions, we all make them.  But what if you gave up assuming all those things you assume to be true… even just for a day? Original airdate 02-May-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 7 May 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070502.mp3" length="5808070" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Assumptions, we all make them.  But what if you gave up assuming all those things you assume to be true… even just for a day?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Assumptions, we all make them.  But what if you gave up assuming all those things you assume to be true… even just for a day?  How different might your day turn out?  During this program we explore this question and the reasons behind the assumptions we make and how to give up our assuming ways!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:19</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070502.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Communication and the Family</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What can you do to open the lines of communication within your family? Original airdate 25-April-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 7 May 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070425.mp3" length="5806833" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>What can you do to open the lines of communication within your family?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>We’ve all heard the saying “Blood is thicker than water”, and while that may be the case, there are many of us who have better “family” ties with people we aren’t related to than with those we do.  Why is that and what are we willing to do about?  This program explores these very questions and guides the listener in what they can do to open the lines of communication within their family.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:18</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070425.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>The Cost of Boredom</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learn what boredom costs you and tips for finding the “gold” in everything you encounter. Original airdate 18-April-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070418.mp3" length="5805262" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Learn what boredom costs you and tips for finding the “gold” in everything you encounter.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>No matter how much we have to do, everyone encounters boredom, and the boredom we encounter is about our surroundings or the lack of things to do.  It is about what we find interesting in a particular moment and what we don’t.  In other words, we create our own boredom!  During this program we discuss what boredom costs you and tips for getting past boredom and finding the “gold” in everything you encounter.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:17</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070418.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Doing the Impossible</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learn how to turn the negative into positive and how to turn “impossible” into “possible”! Original airdate 11-April-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070411.mp3" length="5811323" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Learn how to turn the negative into positive and how to turn “impossible” into “possible”!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Doing the impossible… this topic could take us on a great philosophical debate, but we aren’t going to go there. Instead, as you listen to this program think about what you believe is “impossible” in your life, and consider taking those “impossibilities” on as possibilities! Listen and learn how to turn the negative into positive and how to turn “impossible” into “possible”!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:20</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070411.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>When there’s More to Do than You Can Do</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to fit in what we are committed to doing and responsible for doing with all of the fun stuff that we want to do. Original airdate 04-April-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070404.mp3" length="5812388" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How to fit in what we are committed to doing and responsible for doing with all of the fun stuff that we want to do.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>As anxious as many people are for the spring and summer months to arrive, spring and summer time bring with it a host of new busyness… of stuff to do on top of your already extremely full life.  So how do we manage it all… how do we fit in what we are committed to doing and responsible for doing with all of the fun stuff that we want to do?  This lively program addresses this question and much more!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:20</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070404.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Accountability</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learn how to harness the power of accountability for both personal and professional success. Original airdate 28-March-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 3 Apr 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070328.mp3" length="5810899" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Learn how to harness the power of accountability for both personal and professional success.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Accountability touches each and every facet of our lives – both personally and professionally!  It is a force that drives us and our teams toward excellence and great success, and when accountability is missing it can create a force that causes chaos and unnecessary distress!  During this program you will learn more about accountability and how to harness the power of accountability, build your team, communicate more fully and completely, and move forward easily and successfully.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:20</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070328.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Building Excitement for Living</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wouldn’t it be great to get to a place where you love living life without first having something bad come your way to snap you into shape? Original airdate 21-March-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070321.mp3" length="5806735" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Wouldn’t it be great to get to a place where you love living life without first having something bad come your way to snap you into shape?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Wouldn’t it be great to get to a place where you love living life… you have a spring in your step… without having to have something bad come your way to snap you into shape?  Well you can!  You can create the space to go from “This is the worst day; I can’t wait to go to bed” to “Wow this is the best day I’ve ever had!” and this program will show you how.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>48:18</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070321.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Dealing with Disappointment</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discover how we can best deal with our disappointments and move on! Original airdate 14-March-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070314.mp3" length="5494933" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Discover how we can best deal with our disappointments and move on!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Disappointment is a reality of life. The odds of being successful in everything we do is very small and besides, if we only do the things that we are sure to excel at, then we probably aren’t reaching high enough! So if we aren’t perfect, then how can we expect those around us to be perfect and to not disappoint from time to time too? This program explores this question and takes on how we can best deal with our disappointments and move on!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:47</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070314.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Overcoming Workaholic Ways</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Once a workaholic realizes what they are doing to themselves and their family, the cycle can be broken! Original airdate 07-March-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070307.mp3" length="5506532" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Once a workaholic realizes what they are doing to themselves and their family, the cycle can be broken!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Recognizing your workaholic ways sooner than later isn’t always easy to do. We are so programmed to work-work-work that anything short of working, feels like failure, and it generally takes a hard knock to send us running the other direction, but the good news is that once the workaholic realizes what they are doing to themselves and their family, the cycle can be broken!  This program discusses how to break the cycle and the keys to creating life balance and overcoming workaholic ways.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:48</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070307.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>The Only I Can Do It Syndrome</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ever catch yourself trying to be super-human and do all there is to be done by yourself? Original airdate 28-February-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070228.mp3" length="5263805" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Ever catch yourself trying to be super-human and do all there is to be done by yourself?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>We work so hard toward the nebulous goal of success that we begin to believe that if we aren’t working… if we ask for help… or delegate tasks… there is something wrong with us.  We think that we are the only ones who can complete a job the way we want it to be completed.  We behave as if we are super-human and can be all things to all people and do everything there is to be done.  But, we can’t!  And this program is how to overcome this syndrome I call, The Only I Can Do it Syndrome!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>43:47</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070228.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Dealing with Overwhelm</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to deal with the circumstances in your life and be unstoppable. Original airdate 21-February-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070221.mp3" length="5506634" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How to deal with the circumstances in your life and be unstoppable.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>There is never a good time to deal with all of the things that come up in our lives.  So how do you keep from becoming overwhelmed?  How do you keep “it” all together, manage the changes in your life, and manage the demands that are placed upon you each and every day? This program takes you through how best to deal with the circumstances in your life and be unstoppable.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:48</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070221.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Standing Up for What You Believe In</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Why it is important for us to stand up for those things we hold most dear, and what do we teach ourselves and others by doing so? Original airdate 14-February-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070214.mp3" length="5510304" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Why it is important for us to stand up for those things we hold most dear, and what do we teach ourselves and others by doing so?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>We’re all familiar with the Rosa Parks and Martin Luther King’s of the world… those who have valiantly stood up for what they believed in, and, in some cases, even died standing up for what they believed in.  This program is all about why it is important for us to stand up for those things we hold most dear and what we teach ourselves and others by doing so!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:50</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070214.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Being Stopped</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How do successful people get there? By becoming unstoppable! Original airdate 07-February-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070207.mp3" length="5530442" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How do successful people get there? By becoming unstoppable!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>We’ve all known people who go-go-go.  They don’t ever seem to slow down, they love what they do, they have a great family, life is good, and they’ve always got a smile on their face and a kind word to say.  How do they do it?  Well, among other things they are what I call Unstoppable!!  This program will help you to be unstoppable too!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>46:00</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070207.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Beyond Success</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Take a look at what keeps us from stepping out of the status quo and reaching our greatest potential. Original airdate 31-January-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070131.mp3" length="5505887" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Take a look at what keeps us from stepping out of the status quo and reaching our greatest potential.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>No matter how comfortable we are in life, in our relationships, spiritually, financially… no matter what we achieve… no matter where we’ve come from, there is still a nagging question of “What’s next and how do I get there?”  This program takes a look at what keeps us from stepping out of the status quo and reaching our greatest potential… how to break through your fears and get what you say you want!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:48</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070131.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Team Building</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Why do we allow ourselves to be plagued with the “Only I can Do It Syndrome”? Original airdate 24-January-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070124.mp3" length="5541623" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Why do we allow ourselves to be plagued with the “Only I can Do It Syndrome”?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Life is about humanity… it is about other people. So, why do we insist on being Lone Rangers… why do we allow ourselves to be plagued with the “Only I can Do It Syndrome”? This program takes you through understanding why team is so important for all of us and how to go from being plagued by the Only I Can Do It Syndrome to having a healthy and vibrant team!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>46:06</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070124.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Fear of Actually Getting What You Ask For!</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted something, but your fear of actually getting it stopped you from asking for it? Original airdate 10-January-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070110.mp3" length="5496205" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Have you ever wanted something, but your fear of actually getting it stopped you from asking for it?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Have you ever wanted something, but your fear of actually getting it stopped you from asking for it?  Yes, it sounds a bit crazy, yet we human beings do it all of the time! Anytime we want to change the way something is done or we want something new in our lives it means that we and/or those around us are going to have to change in order for what we want to be incorporated into our lives… and the great majority of us fear change! This program is all about why we’re sometimes afraid of getting what you want and how to get past the question of “What do I do when I get there?”</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:43</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070110.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Commitment</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following through on your commitments and the tools you need to put in place in order to ensure that you are your word every time! Original airdate 03-January-2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070103.mp3" length="5497963" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Following through on your commitments and the tools you need to put in place in order to ensure that you are your word every time!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>When it comes to commitment, it is easy to say, “I am going to do this.” Or “Who I am committed to being is this...”, but what actions do you follow those words with?  This program is all about going from simply saying you will do something to actually following through on your commitment to do it and the tools you need to put in place in order to ensure that you are your word every time!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:48</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20070103.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>What Did You Get Done, and Now What Do You Want and By-When?</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To get what you want - get complete with where you have been and get clear about where you are going. But how do you do that? Original airdate 27-December-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061227.mp3" length="5492948" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>To get what you want - get complete with where you have been and get clear about where you are going. But how do you do that?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>The key to getting what you want – doing what you want to do is to 1) know what it is and 2) get whatever is in the way of getting what you want out of the way – which involves getting complete with where you have been and being clear about where you are going. How do you do that?? This program answers this question and more!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:46</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061227.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Making You and Your Family a Priority</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How asking for accountability is a valuable tool to keep your priorities straight and avoid falling into the trap of work-work-work. Original airdate 20-December-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061220.mp3" length="5500587" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How asking for accountability is a valuable tool to keep your priorities straight and avoid falling into the trap of work-work-work.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>We’ve all heard it said: We are often meanest to those we love most, and unfortunately that statement is true.  Yet, when it is all said and done, all you have is your family; money can’t hug you, money isn’t going to give you better health, money isn’t going to make you happy.  This program addresses why we default to work-work-work and how to get our priorities back in order and asking for accountability to keep them there.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:45</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061220.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Moving Forward No Matter What</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When you allow your feelings or your circumstances to keep you from moving forward who wins, you or the circumstance? Original airdate 13-December-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2007 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061213.mp3" length="5500784" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>When you allow your feelings or your circumstances to keep you from moving forward who wins, you or the circumstance?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>When you allow your feelings or your circumstances to keep you from moving forward who wins, you or the circumstance?  This program provides tips for moving forward no matter what… no matter what season… no matter what circumstance comes before you.  Learn how to be unstoppable and reclaim your passion for living life to the fullest!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:50</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061213.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Creative Alignment</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Creative alignment is doing what we need to do so that the masses around us get what they need or what is best for the mass. Original airdate 06-December-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2006 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061206.mp3" length="5245292" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Creative alignment is doing what we need to do so that the masses around us get what they need or what is best for the mass.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Creative alignment is incredibly powerful, and it is nothing more than doing what we need to do so that the masses around us get what they need or what is best for the mass.  For example: stopping at a traffic light when it turns red, when you don’t want to or sitting at the dinner table and eating salad, even though you wanted dessert first.  Creative alignment is something we take on from the simplest of every day activities to some of the more difficult things we will tackled in our life times.  And if we can see how creative alignment serves us; the people around us; and the people in our care, it is easier to do.  It becomes easier to be a part of the solution, rather than the person who gets to be right all by themselves and this program will help show you how.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>43:37</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061206.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Committing without Knowing How</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Getting what you say you want – it is all about your commitment to do so. Original airdate 29-November-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2006 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061129.mp3" length="5499632" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Getting what you say you want – it is all about your commitment to do so.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Getting what you say you want – accomplishing a personal or business goal, meeting a tight deadline, pushing through life's stops – it is all about your commitment to do so. And in order to fully commit to getting what you say you want, you have to give up having to know how to get what you want before you will commit to getting what you want!  This program addresses the keys to going from uncertainty and worry over how to being unstoppable everywhere, no matter what!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:45</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061129.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Effective Listening</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This program address how to listen effectively and really "get" any communication, and the characteristics of great/effective listeners! Original airdate 22-November-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2006 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061122.mp3" length="5519578" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>This program address how to listen effectively and really "get" any communication, and the characteristics of great/effective listeners!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Effective listening is one of the greatest gifts that you can give--to another and to yourself.  This program takes a look at what it’s like to listen effectively and really "get" any communication and the characteristics of great/effective listeners!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:55</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061122.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Teaching What You Know</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If you don’t teach what you know... if you don’t give away your experience, you can’t make room for what is next for you. Original airdate 15-November-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2006 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061115.mp3" length="5522507" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>If you don’t teach what you know... if you don’t give away your experience, you can’t make room for what is next for you.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>If you don’t teach what you know... if you don’t give away your experience, you can’t make room for what is next for you, and making room for what is next for you is what life is all about. This program illustrates not only how to teach what you know, but what there is to learn in taking the time and opportunity to teach what you know to those around you!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:56</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061115.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Being Present</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to be present to family, the conversations we are having, our jobs, and our lives, so that we don’t miss out. Original airdate 01-November-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2006 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061101.mp3" length="5503481" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How to be present to family, the conversations we are having, our jobs, and our lives, so that we don’t miss out.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>We’ve all had moments when we’ve been driving our car and reached our destination, but don’t remember anything about the drive.  This is what we call NOT being present.  We all do it, and this program is about how to be present to our family, the conversations we are having, the jobs we have to do, and the lives we have to live, so that we don’t miss out on what there is to learn and contribute along the way.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:46</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061101.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Dealing with Mind Chatter</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Your mind is designed to keep you in your past. Original airdate 25-October-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2006 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061025.mp3" length="5531274" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Your mind is designed to keep you in your past.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Your mind is designed to keep you in your past and it does that by telling you stuff that stops you like, “I don’t want to”, “This is no fun”, “Why do I have to deal with this”, etc.  This program addresses how to deal with both negative and positive mind chatter; how to clear negative mind chatter, and how to have positive mind chatter actually serve you!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>46:00</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061025.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Full and Complete Communication</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being your word. Doing what you say you are going to do. Original airdate 18-October-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2006 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061018.mp3" length="5530981" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>What would your life would be like if you were fully communicated with everyone around you and they with you?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Just imagine for a second what your life would be like if you were fully communicated with everyone around you and they with you. What would your life be like?  What would work be like?  How much more would you get accomplished?  This program takes a look at all of these questions and more and takes you step by step through what it takes to be in full and complete communication everywhere!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>46:00</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061018.mp3</guid>
    </item>
	  <item>
      <title>Integrity</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being your word. Doing what you say you are going to do. Original airdate 11-October-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061011.mp3" length="5498261" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Being your word. Doing what you say you are going to do.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Integrity.  Being your word. Doing what you say you are going to do.  It is the one thing in this world that doesn’t ever change.  We either are our word or we aren’t.  This program addresses integrity from its definition to how we put our integrity back in place when it is missing.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:51</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061011.mp3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with Change</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While we often resist change, our ability to grow is all about our being able to change. Original airdate 04-October-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2006 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061004.mp3" length="5511964" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>While we often resist change, our ability to grow is all about our being able to change.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>The only real constant in the world is change. It is unavoidable! While we often resist change, our ability to grow is all about our being able to change. This program looks at why we resist change and why it is necessary to manage the changes that come before us, rather than attempting to hide from them. You’ll never really go anywhere… you’ll never really have what you want… you’ll never really live, if you hide from change. Why not learn how to deal with it in a powerful and effective way?</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:51</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20061004.mp3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asking for What You Want</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered why you don't have what you want? Original airdate 27-September-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2006 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20060927.mp3" length="5508829" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Have you ever wondered why you don't have what you want?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Have you ever wondered why you don't have what you want? Have you ever considered just asking for it? If you don't ask for what you want, there is no way people can give it to you; there is no way you can have it, simply because people cannot read your mind! This program takes a look at fear's role in stopping us from asking for what we want and how to ask for what we want and get it!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:49</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://shop.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20060927.mp3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accountability</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How an accountability team will help you succeed. Original airdate 20-September-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 4 Oct 2006 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20060920.mp3" length="5513328" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>How an accountability team will help you succeed.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>What specific areas do you struggle with in terms of accountability?  How do you hold other people accountable?  Where is accountability missing in your life?  This program takes you through the definition of accountability; the role accountability has in helping us get past our stops, and how to build a team that you allow to hold you accountable for doing and being all that you say you are going to do and be!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:51</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20060920.mp3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Planning</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clay discusses the power of a personal plan. Original airdate 13-September-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 4 Oct 2006 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20060913.mp3" length="5519584" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Discover the power of having a personal plan.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Life is all about having fun, and unfortunately too many of us have forgotten how to smile, let alone have fun!  This program is all about how to get back to taking care of you, to living a balanced life, and how a personal plan can help you do it.  So do you want to get past believing there is a fun prison?  Take a listen!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>45:56</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20060913.mp3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Let Fear Serve You</title>
      <link>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Get past your fears and turn them into something that moves you forward. Original airdate 6-September-2006.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2006 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20060906.mp3" length="5532879" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <itunes:author>Clay S. Nelson</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Get past your fears and turn them into something that moves you forward.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>What has you stopped... what are you dreading... what are you worried about and how is it keeping you from being who you are committed to be?  This program is all about how to get past your fears and turn them into something that actually moves you forward rather than stops you.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>46:02</itunes:duration>
<guid>http://www.claynelsonlifebalance.com/sounds/radio/CNLB_20060906.mp3</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>