<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>The Secret Magdalene - Interview</title>
	<link>http://www.thesecretmagdalene.com/index.html</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<copyright>&#xA9; 2006 Eio Books</copyright>
	<itunes:subtitle>Ki Longfellow reveals her secret.</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:author>Ki Longfellow</itunes:author>
	<itunes:summary>Eio Books Broadcasting interviews Ki Longfellow regarding her novel The Secret Magdalene published by Crown/Random House in early 2007.  A 42 minute interview presented in MP3 format. Ms. Longfellow describes her inspiration for the character of Mary Magdalene and Jesus the Christ. Also she explains the mystery of Judas as hero.  The interview provides revealing insight into the philosophy and spirituallity of the times during which Jesus taught, and the source of Gnosis is also exposed. See: www.thesecretmagdalene.com</itunes:summary>

	<description>As a non-Christian this book came to me highly recommended by a friend. And I cannot recommend it highly enough myself. I have never felt so immersed in such a vivid depiction of the ancient world. Ki Longfellow brought Jerusalem, and its surrounding desert tribes, alive for me, as well as Egyptian Alexandria which held me in awe as the story carried me there across the Nile, and into the city and its famed library during its heyday. The story was a page turner, and the philosophy of gnosticism it depicts, during the time of its origins, fascinated me. The philosophy evolves naturally with the story, and humanizes Jesus as he struggles with his personal questions and doubts. As a non-Christian, THIS is a Jesus I could believe in. I had no idea of the complexities of Jewish culture during those times, and the story of Jesus moved me deeply. So much so that I cried both times I read the book, and books don't make me cry! If you're looking for a tale of magic, mystery and suspense, in which to lose yourself. This is the one! - A Reader
	</description>
	<itunes:owner>
		<itunes:name>Eio Books</itunes:name>
		<itunes:email>info@eiobooks.com</itunes:email>
	</itunes:owner>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.thesecretmagdalene.com/graphics/eiopodcast.jpg" />
	<itunes:category text="Literature">
		<itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituallity"/>
	</itunes:category>
	<itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituallity"/>

	<item>
		<title>The Secret Magdalene</title>
		<itunes:author>Ki Longfellow</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Ki Longfellow reveals her secret.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Ki Longfellow discusses her novel about the life of Mary Magdalene entitled THE SECRET MAGDALENE.</itunes:summary>
		<enclosure url="http://thesecretmagdalene.com/20060810_Ki_Longfellow.mp3" length="20277984" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://thesecretmagdalene.com/20060810_Ki_Longfellow.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2006 01:43:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>42:14</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>Mary Magdalene Jesus Christ Religion Spirituallity Novels Novel Spirituality Ki Longfellow Eio Books</itunes:keywords>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>

