<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>RSS Feed Podcast</title>
        <description>Podcast explaining the ins and outs of RSS, RSS feeds, feed creation, optimization and use as a marketing technology. The podcast is prepared using voice synthesis, reading articles related to RSS.</description>
        <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/rss-articles.htm</link>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2006 17:59:28 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2006 17:55:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.0.4) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <item>
            <title>What is Fair Use?</title>
            <description>As the Internet matures, users and governments are struggling to manage controversial issues. Lets face it, the Internet did not exist when the US copyright laws were written;let us not forget, while many countries respect copyright laws, the Internet is global without a governing body. There are not only different laws, rules and regulations, but also jurisdiction issues. RSS didn&apos;t exist when copyright laws were written either. While ardent supporters feel any content in a feed can be syndicated, other equally fervent publishers contend that original works are just that--original works, and in many countries protected by copyright laws. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/what-is-fair-use.mp3&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; &gt;What is Fair Use MP3&lt;/a&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/what-is-fair-use.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/what-is-fair-use.mp3" length="1010698" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/what-is-fair-use.mp3</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2006 17:55:25 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>RSS More than Just News Headlines</title>
            <description>The core use for RSS is generally considered news headlines and blog syndication, but innovative businesses are learning to use RSS in different ways. Consider RSS as a communication channel that can provide current, targeted information as it appears within a very targeted audience. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/rss-more-than-headlines.mp3&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; &gt;RSS More Than Just News Headlines MP3&lt;/a&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/rss-more-than-headlines.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/rss-more-than-headlines.mp3" length="1194376" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/rss-more-than-headlines.mp3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2006 17:52:31 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Profiting from RSS Feeds</title>
            <description>Publishers are evaluating options and determining how they can profit from RSS feeds. The two obvious contenders that publishers are considering to profit from their RSS feeds are: subscription RSS feeds and RSS feed advertisements. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/profiting-from-rss.mp3&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; &gt;Profiting From RSS MP3&lt;/a&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/profiting-from-rss.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/profiting-from-rss.mp3" length="999424" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/profiting-from-rss.mp3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2006 17:50:07 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Marketing Optimization for Blogs</title>
            <description>Truth be told, most blogs aren&apos;t really optimized for marketing effectiveness. Even more so, some blogs are absolute marketing machines, but they at the same time fail to fully capitalize on that fact by not being really optimized marketing-wise. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Here are the absolute 101 basics you really shouldn&apos;t ignore ... &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rss-specifications.com/marketing-optimization-blogs.htm&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Marketing Optimization 101 for Blogs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/marketing-optimization-blogs.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/marketing-optomization-blog.mp3" length="23122944" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2005 10:21:24 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tracking and Measuring RSS Feeds</title>
            <description>Measuring and tracking RSS while a fairly simple concept, is really anything but. Unlike websites, RSS have the added caveat of potential syndication, making accurate tracking a challenge to anyone but the extremely tech savvy. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
It is not unrealistic for marketers to want to know how many subscribers they have, which items in their feeds attract the most interest, or how many click-throughs are generated as a result of an RSS feed.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
There are a number of 3rd party providers who focus on tracking the consumption of RSS feeds. Some solutions are rudimentary but likely sufficient for a small business testing the waters with RSS. Other RSS tracking solutions are more complex and while they can come close to being accurate, with syndication there is no solution that tracks with 100% accuracy. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rss-specifications.com/measuring-tracking-rss.htm&quot;&gt;Measuring and Tracking RSS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/measuring-tracking-rss.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/measuring-tracking-rss.mp3" length="23122944" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 6 Dec 2005 09:23:51 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Convert a Text Article to a Podcast in Seconds</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<b>Instant Content; Converting a Text Article to a Podcast</b><br>
<br>
We are taught to recycle paper, cans, bottles and plastic but marketers rarely discuss the value of repackaging and repurposing content. Publishers and marketers alike have embraced content syndication and RSS but few have considered the value beyond the actual syndication. Consider an alternative communication channel that reaches a new or different audience. <br>
<br>
Repurposing and repackaging content or information so that it can be consumed through a variety of mediums is not a new concept. Many businesses today sight increased communication as a common goal. Cost conscious businesses with tight budges are often interested in minimizing work loads and cost, while increasing communication. By presenting the same information in different ways and formats, businesses are able to increase the reach and communication, while remaining cost conscious. <br>
<br>
<a href="http://www.rss-specifications.com/instant-podcasts.htm" target="blank">Instant Podcasts</a><br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/instant-podcasts.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/instant-podcasts.mp3" length="840467" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2005 10:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Creative Commons</title>
            <description>Creative Commons is a nonprofit organization that allows artists, authors, publishers and musicians the option of creating and defining a flexible copyright for their creative works. Creative Commons was officially launched in 2001 by a group of intellectual property experts, lawyers and web publishers. Creative Commons licenses cover art, music, and writing, but is not designed for software.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rss-specifications.com/creative-commons.htm&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;What is Creative Commons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/creative-commons.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/creative-commons.mp3" length="988425" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2005 10:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>RSS Ego Searches</title>
            <description>Ego searches are free and simple searches designed to monitor blogs and news portals for mentions of your company, product, competitors or other specific keywords. Conducting ego searches not only allows you to stay informed, but also allows you to maintain a strategic advantage over competing companies. A number of new Internet services are freely available that make these &apos;ego searches&apos; painless and easy. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Complete Article - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rss-specifications.com/rss-ego.htm&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;RSS Ego Searches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/rss-ego.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/ego-search.mp3" length="1318508" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2005 10:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>RSS Won the Syndication Standard Battle</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<b><i>RSS Won the Battle</i></b><br>
RSS appears to have conquered the last hurtle in becoming the industry syndication standard.<br>
<br>
Microsoft's inclusion of RSS into the newest version of Internet Explorer and reports that RSS will be in Longhorn's coming release appears to be the final nail in the coffin of the Atom specification. Even Atom's steadfast supporter Google, appears to have seen the light. Google had previously acquired Blogger, a popular blogging tool that uses the Atom specification to syndicate the contents of blogs created on the Blogger platform. In the past Google had strategically steered clear of endorsing the RSS specification hoping that Atom, would take hold.<br>
<br>
<a href="http://www.rss-specifications.com/rss-won.htm" target="blank">RSS Won the Battle</a><br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/rss-won.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/rss-won.mp3" length="894976" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2005 10:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Copyright Debate and RSS</title>
            <description>RSS is commonly defined as really simple syndication. So, this means that any material contained in a feed is available for syndication, right? Well no, not exactly. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rss-specifications.com/the-copyright-debate.htm&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;The Copyright Debate and RSS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/the-copyright-debate.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/copyright-debate.mp3" length="9573888" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2005 10:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Displaying RSS Feeds</title>
            <description>RSS offers webmasters a unique opportunity to display fresh content on websites. While publishing an RSS feed is a great way to generate site interest and increase communication, syndicating and displaying feeds from related relevant sources can also generate interest, increase traffic and improve search engine ranking.</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/displaying-rss-feeds.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/displaying-rss-feeds.mp3" length="2311266" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 9 Aug 2005 11:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Future of RSS, is Not Blogs</title>
            <description>Blogs vaulted RSS into the limelight but are unlikely to be the force that sustains RSS as a communication medium. The biggest opportunities for RSS are not in the blogosphere but as a corporate communication channel. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Even now, businesses that were initially reluctantly evaluating RSS are beginning to realize the power and benefit of the RSS information avenue. The inherent capacity for consumers to select the content they wish to receive will be the driving mechanism for keeping advertisements to a minimum and content quality consistent.</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/future-rss.htm</link>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/the-future-rss.mp3" length="971707" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 1 Aug 2005 10:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tips to Creating a Blog</title>
            <description>Tips for creating a blog.&lt;br&gt;
There are no hard and fast rules on how to blog. Having said that, bloggers will likely increase their exposure by following some simple blog guidelines. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
1.) Stay on topic.&lt;br&gt;
Opinions are generally accepted but the content of the items in the blog should all relate to a general theme. Unless you have an uncanny knack for wit, humor or cynicism, the majority of your readers will be interested in the content that relates to a specific defined theme or loosely defined area of interest. Most readers won&apos;t care that you eat Cheerios for breakfast. They may, however, be interested in the fact that vinegar takes out stains and that toilet paper rolls make great wreaths. Define a topic and stick to it. This will ensure that you create a loyal following of interested readers.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/10-tips-for-bloggers.htm</link>
            <author>webmaster@feedforall.com</author>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/tips_to_creating_a_blog.mp3" length="1157907" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2005 10:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Search Engine Optimization for RSS Feeds</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<b><i>Tips for Helping Your RSS Feed Perform!</i></b><br>
In some ways RSS is very similar to HTML, the language commonly used to create websites. Just as with HTML, webmasters using traditional search engine optimization tactics when creating an RSS feed will find that their RSS feed receives additional exposure and interest. <br>
<br>
<a href="http://www.rss-specifications.com/rss-seo.htm" target="blank">Complete Article</a> or <a href="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/Search%20Engine%20Optimization%20for%20Feeds.mp3" target="blank">Listen</a><br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/rss-seo.htm</link>
            <author>webmaster@feedforall.com</author>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/Search%20Engine%20Optimization%20for%20Feeds.mp3" length="1421222" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 5 Jul 2005 10:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>RSS Feeds</title>
            <description>&lt;b&gt;RSS Feeds&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
RSS also known as rich site summary or real simply syndication, arrived on the scene a number of years ago, but was only recently embraced by webmasters as a means to effectively syndicate content. RSS Feeds provide webmasters and content providers an avenue to provide concise summaries to prospective readers. Thousands of commercial web sites and blogs now publish content summaries in an RSS feed. Each item in the feed typically contains a headline; article summary and link back to the online article.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rss-specifications.com/everything-rss.htm&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Complete Article&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/RSS%20Feeds.mp3&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Listen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/everything-rss.htm</link>
            <author>webmaster@feedforall.com</author>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/RSS%20Feeds.mp3" length="1322583" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 4 Jul 2005 15:32:27 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>More on RSS Feeds</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<b>RSS FEEDS </b><br>
Lets face it as much as we all rely on email communications it is not really a reliable technology. <br>
<br>
<b><i>Why Should I care about RSS Feeds</i></b><br>
SPAM and viruses have wreaked havoc with a communication medium and reduced its value. Users have become admittedly paranoid about privacy issues and have begun "tuning out" and mentally filtering mail. <br>
<br>
<br>
<a href="http://www.rss-specifications.com/rss-feeds-article.htm" target="blank">Entire Article </a>or <a href="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/More%20On%20RSS%20Feeds.mp3" target="blank">Listen</a><br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://www.rss-specifications.com/rss-feeds-article.htm</link>
            <author>webmaster@feedforall.com</author>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rss-specifications.com/podcasts/More%20On%20RSS%20Feeds.mp3" length="652490" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Fri, 1 Jul 2005 15:41:48 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
