<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/Sources/rss2html.xsl" version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Focus Podcast - CareerFastTrack</title>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk</link>
<description>'If I knew then what I know now!' ... some very successful people share the secrets of their success. </description>
<image>
<url>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/images/focusbizlogo.gif</url>
<title>Focus Podcasts</title>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk</link>
</image>
<copyright>Copyright 2006, FOCUS BUSINESS</copyright>
<language>en</language>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2006 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>

<item>
<title>Rob Stewart, VP Marketing for Xerox Office Systems</title>
<description>Rob Stewart, VP Marketing for Xerox Office Systems talks about his career to date. Career Fast Track brings you advice from successful people for those who are still early in their careers.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/rob.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/rob.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/rob.mp3" length="8911314" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Shane Redding, MD for ThinkDirect and Chair of the Institute of Direct Marketing Business to Business Council</title>
<description>Shane Redding, Chair of the Institute of Direct Marketing Business to Business Council talks about her career. Career Fast Track brings you advice from successful people for those who are still early in their careers.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/Shane.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/Shane.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/Shane.mp3" length="8911314" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Marketing Agency MD, Ann Brine</title>
<description>Ann Brine, MD of AMB Marketing (www.ambmarketing.co.uk) talks about her career in marketing and management, how she got started, and how she has managed to build a very successful career at the same time as enjoying her young family. Career Fast Track brings you advice from successful people for those who are still early in their careers.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/ann01.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/ann01.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/ann01.mp3" length="8911314" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Senior European IT Marketing Director, Steve Jack</title>
<description>Steve Jack is Senior European Marketing Director of an international business in the IT Industry and he has a passion for communicating.  Listening to him will enliven your day and give you enthusiasm for tomorrow and the day after!  Career Fast Track brings you advice from successful people for those who are still early in their careers.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/steve01.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/steve01.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/steve01.mp3" length="8428548" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Advertising Agency MD, Richard Knight</title>
<description>Richard Knight is MD of Focal Point Advertising (www.focal.co.uk) and he has built a successful advertising agency. Richard always dreamed of having his own business but it wasn’t all easy.  Career Fast Track brings you advice from successful people for those who are still early in their careers.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/richardk01.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/richardk01.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/richardk01.mp3" length="12217366" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Chartered Accountant, Roger Williams</title>
<description>Roger Williams is a Chartered Accountant and a partner in Wilkins Kennedy (www.wilkinskennedy.com).  As an accountant he sees people and businesses at every stage of their development and has some very useful perspectives on what every business needs to succeed. Career Fast Track brings you advice from successful people for those who are still early in their careers.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2006 13:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/rogerw01.mp3</link>
<guid>http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/rogerw01.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.focusbiz.co.uk/podcast/audio/career/rogerw01.mp3" length="13169059" type="video/mp3" />
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
