<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Spectrum Analysis</title>
  <link>http://www.spectrumanalysis.org/</link>
  <description>Spectrum Analysis is a podcast by me, Ben Shewmaker.  Its aim is to explore the myriad of ways to create music electronically by interviewing artists, teachers, audio engineers, or whoever else might be knowledgable enough to share some information.  And since I am interested enough in this field to create a podcast, it will feature my music as I try to teach myself how to do the things I learn during my interviews and research.</description>
  <lastBuildDate>Tues, 12 Dec 2006 15:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  <item>
   <title>Spectrum Analysis Episode 5</title>
   <link>http://www.spectrumanalysis.org/?p=12</link>
   <description>Whew!  10 months!  Spectrum Analysis kind of fell on its face after only a few steps.  So I'm going to try this again.  Episode 5 is a great interview with Andrew Malott, a recent graduate from Ball State University, and currently an intern at Echo Park Studios.  We discuss being an intern, and audio engineer, and the music industry in general. </description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.spectrumanalysis.org/shows/Spectrum%20Analysis%20Episode%205.mp3" length="30023947" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2006 17:21:31 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Spectrum Analysis Episode 4</title>
   <link>http://www.spectrumanalysis.org/?p=10</link>
   <description>Episode 4 is finally here and features an informative interview with Dr. De Sena, professor of electronic music at the University of Miami. He helps explain some more basics of synthesis, tips on good composition, career ideas, and other great advice.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.spectrumanalysis.org/shows/Spectrum%20Analysis%20Episode%204.mp3" length="30023947" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2006 17:21:31 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Spectrum Analysis Episode 3</title>
   <link>http://www.spectrumanalysis.org/?p=7</link>
   <description>This week I talk to David Sims, aka Shockshadow. We discuss everything from learning digital audio concepts to great free VST plugins to other things interesting and noteworthy.&lt;a href=&quot;http://odeo.com/claim/feed/1f9f796b574b3457&quot;&gt;My Odeo Channel&lt;/a&gt; (odeo/1f9f796b574b3457)</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.spectrumanalysis.org/shows/Spectrum%20Analysis%20Episode%203.mp3" length="25626801" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 18:41:06 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Spectrum Analysis Episode 2</title>
   <link>http://www.spectrumanalysis.org/?p=6</link>
   <description>This week I speak with Grant Robertson about Creative Commons and why its a fantastic tool for artists to get their music out there.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.spectrumanalysis.org/shows/Spectrum%20Analysis%20Episode%202.mp3" length="25234454" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 18:39:20 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Spectrum Analysis Episode 1</title>
   <link>http://www.spectrumanalysis.org/?p=5</link>
   <description>Episode 1 features a fantastic interview with Victor Stone, who gives some great tips on starting out, where to upload your music, and why you should worry about obscurity, not piracy.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.spectrumanalysis.org/shows/Spectrum%20Analysis%20Episode%201.mp3" length="30029007" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 18:38:48 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
