<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

<channel>

<atom:link href="http://www.buzzbender.com/RSS/bb.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

<title>BuzzBender</title>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com</link>
<description>BuzzBender features interviews with movie, TV, and music personalities making news doing their own thing. Promising to never conduct a press junket style interview, producer and host Mitchell Anthony keeps these informative and on-target conversations flowing, so you get the most from listening. Want more? Subscribe now.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2007 - 2010 Mitchell Anthony</copyright>
<image>
<title>BuzzBender</title>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com</link>
<url>http://www.buzzbender.com/Graphics/RSS/BB2008.jpg</url>
</image>

<item>
<title>BB 18: Kip Winger, performer and composer</title>
<description>Many will remember Kip Winger for the Platinum selling Miles Away. But this innovative musician, performer, and songwriter proves again he is much more than a power balladeer with the release of the new album Karma available on Frontier Records in the US October 27th. For more information please visit www.kipwinger.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_18.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_18.mp3" length="905752" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_18.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 17: George Lynch of Lynch Mob, Souls of We</title>
<description>Very busy is the best way I can describe rock guitarist George Lynch. Besides just having finished a tour with Souls of We, Lynch Mob returns with the studio album Smoke and Mirrors available on Frontier Records in the US October 13th. For more information please visit www.georgelynch.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_17.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_17.mp3" length="6040791" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_17.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 16: Ade Fenton, Techno DJ and record producer</title>
<description>Call it what you like: Industrial, Techno, or Electronica. Ade Fenton's schedule takes him across the globe performing fierce and unique sets that fuse thunderous beats with layers upon layers of surprising sounds. Ade discusses movie soundtrack work, ongoing projects with Gary Numan, and what it really means to be a professional DJ. For more information please visit www.adefenton.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_16.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_16.mp3" length="16512758" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_16.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 15: Galactic Cowboys guitarist Wally Farkas</title>
<description>Galactic Cowboys are back playing three shows for the first time in ten years in Texas from August 13th through the 15th. Guitarist Wally Farkas discusses these upcoming shows, the big sound he gets from his guitar setup, and how truth is more intriguing than fiction when it comes to the Jibbs. For more information please visit www.galacticcowboys.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_15.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_15.mp3" length="14112837" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_15.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 14: Bee Movie's director Simon J. Smith</title>
<description>How many bees does it take to help land a 747? Approximately 750,000. How many to form a beautiful floral pattern on the ground? About 350,000 as you will see for yourself in Bee Movie opening November 2nd. Simon J. Smith directs this latest creative tour de force from DreamWorks. For more information please visit www.beemovie.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_14.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_14.mp3" length="18241020" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_14.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 13: Dark Funeral's Emperor Magus Caligula</title>
<description>Sweden's Dark Funeral may be one of the most notorious and highly regarded Death Metal bands, but I found singer Emperor Magus Caligula to be an affable lad while talking with him from the band's New York hotel suite on the eve of their North American tour. Listen to my interview with Caligula as we discuss Dark Funeral's new DVD Attera Orbis Terrarum available through Regain Records. For more information please visit www.darkfuneral.se. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_13.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_13.mp3" length="6720811" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_13.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 12: Prong's Tommy Victor</title>
<description>Tommy Victor leads the charge for truth, justice, and the metal way as Prong returns with the hard-hitting record Power of the Damager available October 2nd on 13th Planet Records. Tommy discusses the art of detachment, power of automatic writing, and how big mojo in the form of negative karma helps him write and perform his brand of metal music. For more information please visit www.prongmusic.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_12.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_12.mp3" length="14400811" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_12.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 11: Paul Nelson, Johnny Winter's guitarist and manager, part two</title>
<description>Paul Nelson discusses money: how to earn and keep more of it while perfoming on tour in the above average rock band. For more information please visit www.paulnelsonguitar.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_11.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_11.mp3" length="15360863" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_11.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 10: Paul Nelson, Johnny Winter's guitarist and manager, part two</title>
<description>Paul Nelson discusses how long-term financial and creative success for the above average rock guitarist and manager comes from being a musician onstage and a businessman offstage, and explains the importance of having his cell phone within reaching distance as he performs. For more information please visit www.paulnelsonguitar.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_10.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_10.mp3" length="9600967" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_10.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 9: Paul Nelson, Johnny Winter's guitarist and manager, part one</title>
<description>Fairness, awareness, and business savvy wrapped in a package that delivers the goods to the fans: Paul Nelson discusses quality tour etiquette in action as the Johnny Winter band tours the world including their upcoming appearance at the Crossroads Guitar Festival on July 28th. For more information please visit www.paulnelsonguitar.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_9.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_9.mp3" length="6720811" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_9.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 8: Ratatouille supervising animator Dylan Brown</title>
<description>Dylan Brown is supervising animator of Pixar's Ratatouille opening in movie theaters June 29th. Dylan discusses the art of making rats come alive on screen, not to mention fish, ants, and happy-go-lucky monsters, and explains how "The Universe" reveals creative promise to those with the time and inclination to look. For more information please visit www.ratatouille.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_8.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_8.mp3" length="10561020" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_8.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 7: Deal Breakers author Dr. Bethany Marshall, part two</title>
<description>Dr. Bethany Marshall concludes discussing of her new book Deal Breakers as she describes handling partners with personality disorders and the upsides and downsides of acting in a committed fashion while accepting growth and change. For more information please visit www.bethanymarshall.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_7.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_7.mp3" length="6720811" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_7.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 6: Deal Breakers author Dr. Bethany Marshall, part one</title>
<description>Dr. Bethany Marshall wrote Deal Breakers, an unconventional do-it-yourself manual for the lovelorn looking to fix a broken relation or get out of Dodge. Dr. Marshall describes the personality types of difficult men. And yes I am in one or two of her descriptions somewhere. For more information see her on Good Morning America June 4th and 5th, and visit www.bethanymarshall.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_6.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_6.mp3" length="7680863" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_6.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 5: Shrek the Third director Chris Miller</title>
<description>Chris Miller is director of DreamWorks' Shrek the Third opening in movie theaters May 18th. Chris discusses what it was like making the second sequel of the great Shrek franchise and the value of creative collaboration. For more information please visit www.shrek.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_5.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_5.mp3" length="10561020" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_5.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 4: Ade Fenton</title>
<description>Coproducing Gary Numan's album Jagged and being an in-demand DJ with a schedule taking him around the globe are only a few of Ade Fenton's varied accomplishments including his new album Artificial Perfect available on May 7th. Listen to my interview with Ade over the phone from his studio in England as we discuss his new album, working with Gary Numan, and how his inability to stop helps him create some of the more interesting techno to come down the pike in years. For more information please visit www.adefenton.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_4.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_4.mp3" length="13440761" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_4.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 3: Jessica Tivens</title>
<description>Having performed in concert with such musical luminaries as Michael Crawford, Josh Groban, Davis Gaines, and jazz pianist Mike Garson, Jessica Tivens sings with a maturity twice her age in Broadway musicals and operas from Madison Square Garden to Carnegie Hall. Listen to my interview with Jessica as she discusses her new album Unlimited, and explains why trying to pigeonhole her artistic versatility is next to impossible. For more information please visit www.jessicativens.com and www.cdbaby.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_3.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_3.mp3" length="9600967" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_3.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 2: Bill Plympton, Hair High director and writer</title>
<description>In the fine tradition of drawing pictures of men punching themselves in the face and pulling on ten-foot long nose hairs, Bill Plympton created his critically acclaimed film Hair High opening on April 13th. Bill discusses his new film and how he makes the impossible possible with little more than a pencil, a lot of energy, and even more imagination. For more information please visit www.hairhigh.com and www.plymptoons.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_2.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_2.mp3" length="6720814" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_2.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>BB 1: Glen Wexler, Secret Life of Cows photographer</title>
<description>Making a cow perform martial arts and leap tall buildings in a single bound is all in a day's work for photographer Glen Wexler. Glen discusses his new book The Secret Life of Cows, and offers proof positive that Americans love cows more than beautiful women. For more  information please visit secretlifeofcows.com. For more information on BuzzBender, please visit www.buzzbender.com.</description>
<link>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_1.mp3</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_1.mp3" length="17280970" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.buzzbender.com/Podcasts/P_1.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2007 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>