<?xml version="1.0"?> <rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>Fusion : Denver</title> <link>http://www.trinityumc.org/Fusion</link> <description>It is more than great people, atmosphere, and music. It is a fusion of your everyday-life and something deeper... The sermons are postmodern and exciting looks at Christianity and how the Christian Faith still relevant in today's world, from the perspective of a young pastor. Blending humor, pop-culture, scripture, and young idealism, this is Gods message for a post-modern world. Send Brad an e-mail with any feed-back or Sermon Requests.</description> <language>en-us</language> <copyright>2006</copyright> <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2007 23:59:00 MST</lastBuildDate> <ttl>1</ttl><itunes:author>Brad Laurvick - blaurvick@trinityumc.org</itunes:author>    <itunes:subtitle>Casual and Upbeat Evening Worship in Denver </itunes:subtitle>    <itunes:summary>It is more than great people, atmosphere, and music. It is a fusion of your everyday-life and something deeper... The sermons are postmodern and exciting looks at Christianity and how the Christian Faith still relevant in today's world, from the perspective of a young pastor. Blending humor, pop-culture, scripture, and young idealism, this is Gods message for a post-modern world. Send Brad an e-mail with any feed-back, prayer requests, or sermon requests. </itunes:summary><itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">      <itunes:category text="Christianity" />  </itunes:category>    <itunes:owner>           <itunes:name>Bradley Laurvick</itunes:name>           <itunes:email>blaurvick@trinityumc.org</itunes:email>    </itunes:owner><itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit><itunes:image href="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/logo2.jpg" />

<item><title>Getting to Know Our Main Character</title><description>Have you ever caught the last few moments of a movie... where all the emotions are high and the plot is coming to its high point, and since you didn't see the movie- you don't care. Well, as we approach Easter, the death and resurrection of Christ, we need to take the time to invest in the characters and plot- specifically our main character, Jesus.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2007 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>28:48</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon3-18.m4a" length="6956205" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>Where Are You Going?</title><description>When was the last time you asked yourself, "Where am I going?" Sure this question applies to driving, walking, and traveling in general... but more importantly when was the last time you asked yourself, "Where am I going with my life?" We all have, do, and will ask ourselves this question. It is an important one. It also one that is important to think about with others and with God.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2007 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>23:39</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon3-11.m4a" length="6956205" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>Extreme Temple Make-Over</title><description>You know those shows where they come in and do all sorts of work to put a house in better shape? Image that extreme make-over happening to a temple, now imagine that temple is your body. We are called to care for ourselves- let's take a little time and check in.</description><pubDate>Sun, 3 Mar 2007 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>34:56</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon3-4.m4a" length="6956205" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>And the Winner Is...</title><description>Another week, another Award Show on TV. All the glitz and glamour... and all the winners and losers. Though we may not get statues and a chance to make a teary speech, we deal with winning and losing everyday. So when it comes to life- the winner is...</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2007 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>24:19</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon2-25.m4a" length="6956205" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>Decisions, Decisions...</title><description>Rocky Road, Cookie Dough, Cherry Garcia... so many ice-cream flavors, so little time. At least when you are deciding on ice-cream you get to taste them all on those cute little spoons, but not all of life's decisions are so sweet... How are we to make good decisions in our lives, and does God have any input? </description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>30:16</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon2-18.m4a" length="6956205" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>I Get By With a Little Help...</title><description> Be it Valentines day or just a sappy movie, society loves romantic relationships... but man, so much of love gets left out. Friendship is soooo under-rated, but not by God. God calls us into deep relationship with others. </description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2007 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>21:11</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon2-11.m4a" length="6956205" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>I'm On the List</title><description>The guy with the headphone in his ear and a clipboard in his hand looks up and down the paper... "You're on the list"... There are lists everywhere- not just at the trendy clubs. </description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2007 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>26:52</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon1-28.m4a" length="6956205" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>Gotta Be Me</title><description>Gotta Be Me... This is a story of a person who decided to be who they were no matter what anyone else thought... </description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2007 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>21:48</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon1-21.m4a" length="5654825" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>The First Year Was Just the Beginning</title><description>The first year was just the beginning... Welcome to 2007. There are a lot of ways to look at an anniversery, but how does God call us to look at where we are and what we have done? Here's to many years to come. </description><pubDate>Sun, 7 Jan 2007 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>23:42</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon1-7.m4a" length="6165897" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>Better Days</title><description>As one year ends and another begins, we pause to ask "What do we want out of the new year, and what does God want for us?" This New Year's Eve sermon was an 'unplugged' evening- guitar, voices, candlelight, and the promise of a Better Days to come in the year to come...</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>18:54</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon12-31.m4a" length="4942003" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>"All In" at Christmas</title><description>“Lights please” this Christmas we look at how to bring what is really important into focus and commit ourselves to something that offers something back. And there is one more thing... we also look at God’s decision to go “All in” for us</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>25:25</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon12-10.m4a" length="5559074" type="audio/AAC" /></item>


<item><title>Frosty Possibilities</title><description>What can an old silk hat and a jolly man made of snow tell us about hope at Christmas? The possibilities are endless as we look at Frosty Possibilities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 3 Dec 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>22:35</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon12-3.m4a" length="5559074" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>What Are You Preparing For?</title><description>Only how many days until Christmas? With stores putting Christmas stuff out earlier and earlier every year, we now have over two months of red and green on the shelves. But is that all it takes to get ready for Christmas? How do we truly prepare ourselves for Christmas?</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>23:58</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon11-26.m4a" length="5559074" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>Cranberry Fusion</title><description>Cranberry Fusion, it sounds like it should be a new drink from Ocean Spray, but instead it is a look at one the iconic elements of Thanksgiving (ok, iconic might be a stretch but it sounded good) Who would have thought that such a little berry could offer us such deep meaning...</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>20:52</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon11-19.m4a" length="5559074" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>No Name, but Great Faith</title><description>If you read too quickly you might miss her, a woman with no name. This woman has great faith, but not like you might think...</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>19:30</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon11-12.m4a" length="5215331" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Anybody Have the Time?</title><description>No matter how hard we try, time keeps moving on. No matter if we feel we have enough of it or not. Do you have the time? Do you have the time you really need and deserve? Tonight we look at how to get more out of the time we have...</description><pubDate>Sun, 5 Nov 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>15:54</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon11-5.m4a" length="4306031" type="audio/AAC" /></item>

<item><title>Taking Off the Costumes</title><description>I am sure you have had your fair share of rockin' Halloween costumes over the years, but what costumes are you wearing the rest of the year? Who are we, who should we be, and what do we show the world...</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>21:14</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon10-29.m4a" length="5650323" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Do You Love Me?</title><description>Remember those notes "Do you like me? Check one... yes, no, maybe" Well, Jesus asks us: Do we love him? But the answer isn't where it ends... in fact the answer is just a begining. Yes to Jesus is about a relationship that takes us out into the world.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>17:17</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon10-22.m4a" length="4686748" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Moving Past The Pain- Not Letting Our Past Control Our Present</title><description>It doesn't matter where it came from, pain is pain. Be it the pain of a past mistake or a pain that arises when you feel your life isn't where you want it to be. God wants us to move past the pain- and not allow our past to control our present. There are concrete ways for us to do this and we find them in the way Jesus dealt with sin.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>26:06</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon10-15.m4a" length="6876269" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>What's a Gospel and Who's Mark? pt.4 - What's That In There For?</title><description>Have you ever been assembling something and when you're done you have parts elft over, and all you can ask is. "What's that in there for?" There are parts of the Bible that can raise the same question- but they are in there for good reason. So even if you are wearing blended fabric and eating a ham sandwhich... enjoy the sermon.</description><pubDate>Sun, 8 Oct 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>18:29</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon10-08.m4a" length="4958725" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>What's a Gospel and Who's Mark? pt.3 - Compassion Takes A Walk</title><description>Jesus always seems to answer questions one of two ways: with a question or with a story. Tonight he does both. Won't you be my neighbor, and talk a walk with compassion?</description><pubDate>Sun, 1 Oct 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>16:33</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon10-01.m4a" length="4438534" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>What's a Gospel and Who's Mark? pt.2 - That Reminds Me of a Story</title> <description>Wanna talk about a bad day? Try getting thrown off a boat and thrown up by a fish... The story of Jonah offers insights into God's faithfulness no matter what we have done or are doing with our lives.  The Bible is rich with stories that if you know, will make you say "that reminds me of a story" no matter what the situation in life.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>23:11</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon9-24.m4a" length="6177010" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>What's a Gospel and Who's Mark? pt.1</title> <description>Read any good books lately? Get to know a book that has been used and abused over the years- and if you think you already know the Bible, prepare to know it in a whole new way... See what these stories have in store for us.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>24:29</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon9-17.m4a" length="6504281" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>God, Us, and Prepositions</title> <description>Jesus calls us to be "in the world" but not "of the world". What does that mean... and do you have to diagram a sentence to figure out the difference? We take a look at how these prepositions are different in very important ways. Here's to being "in" but not "of"! (And snaps for 4th grade English)</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>16:40</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon9-10.m4a" length="4507445" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Sara Went Out to Do Some Gardening</title> <description>What does the Word have for you? Jesus told some great stories, what was so cool was how easy they were to relate to. This week, we find an update to the parable of the sower. Sara went out to do some gardening... and we all can learn what it is to sustain what God offers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 3 Sep 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>23:46</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon9-03.m4a" length="6284721" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Why God, Why?</title> <description>It quite possibly is humanity's oldest question. Whether we ask it out of curiousity or despair, "Why" is an important and life shapoing question. So what does it mean to ask Why? Is there an answer to Why? And How does God fit in to "Why God, Why?"</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>23:11</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon8-27.m4a" length="6119688" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Fill 'Er Up</title> <description>Our cars aren't the only things that can run on empty. Have you been there? Have you been, are you right now, running on empty? There are a lot of things the world offers to help fill us up, but they just don't seem to cut it. So where do we go to truly, fill 'er up...</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>17:02</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon8-20.m4a" length="4634420" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Waiting On the World to Change?(w/ special appearance by John Mayer)</title> <description>John Mayer has a new song out called "Waiting On the World to Change". I love the groove he lays down, but the words made me pause. Why should we wait? The song offers several key points for reflection. If you haven't heard the whole song, check it out, and then check out this sermon.</description><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>20:02</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon8-13.m4a" length="5266922" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>We've Got Spirit, How 'Bout You?</title> <description>So there's all sorts of spirit at sporting events, but how about in our own lives? How does the Holy Spirit engage us an how do we live into that spirit? We've got spirit, yes we do! We've got spirit, how 'bout you?</description><pubDate>Sun, 6 Aug 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>25:04</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon8-6.m4a" length="6453802" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Yall Come Back Now, Ya Hear!</title> <description>Southern Hospitality is not a myth. In fact, hospitality is how I have come to understand our call to evangelism. We are called to invite people into God's story with a sense of hospitality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>23:44</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon7-30.m4a" length="6201484" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>I Meant To Do That</title> <description>Have you ever noticed that sometimes things can work out even without you meaning them to? Times when all you can do is say "I meant to do that", even though it couldn't have gone better if you had tried. Life can be one of those things that may be going just fine, but completely unintentionally. Join us as we look at how we can go from just existing, to living intentionally...</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>21:11</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon7-23.m4a" length="5556131" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Oops I Did It Again...</title> <description>In one of those moments where an everyday situation offers an insight into something much deeper, I locked my keys in my car this week. I learned a lot about locksmiths, and even more about forgiveness. Listen to how Gods justifying grace accepts, pardons, and loves us no matter what our mistakes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>23:05</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon7-16.m4a" length="5827806" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>How Is It With Your Soul? - Best Of 7:07</title> <description>I was on vacation this week and our guest preacher did not get recorded. So we are doing what my favorite radio morning show does when they are out of town, a 'best of' episode. This sermon is from the first month of Evening Worship, so many of you have not heard it. So, take a moment, stop all the rushing and busyness, and ask yourself, "How is it with my soul?"</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>19:31</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon7-9.m4a" length="5136772" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Cookie Monster Asks the Big Questions</title> <description>Who would have thought that a furry blue monster with a cookie addiction could ask the kind of questions that cause us to look at the very core of our being. Are we authentic? Are we hypocrites? Does how we live match up with what we believe?</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>25:08</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon7-2.m4a" length="6904808" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Where Do We Go from Here?</title> <description>It has been a first six months, but where do we go from here? The Church needs to ask itself what kind of Church it wants to be, and we are the Church my friends! Just a heads up, I do curse in the sermon this week, incase you are listening with any young ears around. It's not gratuitous, it is theological :-)</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>28:58</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon6-25.m4a" length="7361462" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Thanks... Now What Am I Supposed To Do With It?- 6-11-2006</title> <description>It has happened to all of us. We get a gift and all we can say is "Thanks... Now what am I supposed to do with it?"The same could be asked of Spiritual Gifts. What are they? How are we supposed to use them? Can I return them without a receipt? We look this week at what Spiritual Gifts are and what they can mean for us.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>18:04</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon6-18.m4a" length="4611597" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>What A Wonderful World- 6-11-2006</title> <description>It is amazing how easy it is to take Colorado for granted. It is just as easy to forget how wondefully created each of us are. What does it mean to be made in Gods image? What does it say about how we should see ourselves, and treat others? ***This sermon was outside, I used every means possible to remove the wind noise, sorry I couldn't do more.***</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>19:20</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon6-11.m4a" length="4931503" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>I Once Caught a Fish...- 6-4-2006</title> <description>Some people say fishing is relaxing, others say its boring, but Jesus says it should be for people. We look this week at what it means to be true disciples, as we learn to fish. PS- next week service will be out on the green!</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>23:46</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon6-4.m4a" length="6048277" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>DaVinci Goes Quadrilateral- 5-28-2006</title> <description>Questions? Concerns? wondering about The DaVinci Code? This week we take not so much a point by point, controversy by controversy, but a look at how to understand The DaVinci Code in a faithful way, while still enjoying a good book!</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>19:05</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon5-28.m4a" length="4867053" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Well Isnt That Just Perfect!- 5-21-2006</title> <description>You know that expression "Nobodys Perfect", well what if I told you that I knew someone who disagreed. John Wesley (the founder of Methodism) believed you could be made perfect in love in this lifetime! This week we look at what Christian Perfection is,what it is not, and why on earth you should care.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>19:05</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon5-21.m4a" length="4867053" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>You Aint My Mama!- 5-14-2006</title> <description>Leave it to me to pick a scripture for Mothers Day where Jesus disowns his mom. Was he really saying something bad about his family, or was he saying something good about what Christian family is supposed to be? [Next week- Well Isnt That Perfect...]</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2006 23:59:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>16:06</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon5-14.m4a" length="4117080" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Where'd All the Good People Go?- 5-7-2006</title> <description>Looking around, what Christ preached and what we see on reality shows couldn't be further apart! So this week the sermon asks, "Where'd All the Good People Go?" (For you Jack Johnson fans out there, yeah, we used the song)</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>15:09</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon5-7.m4a" length="3965920" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Magic 8-Ball Jesus- 4-30-2006</title> <description>Wouldn't it be nice if you could ask Jesus a question and get an instant answer? Well you can! ( http://www.answermejesus.com ) He joins us take a look at what we ask of Jesus... and what/how he answers...</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>16:43</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon4-30.m4a" length="4330376" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Fusion: Pyrotechnics &amp; Strawberry Banana- 4-23-2006</title> <description>This service is supposed to be a fusion of your everyday life and something deeper, but what does that mean? What would it look like to find deeper meaning infused into every part of our lives... it's there and so is God- offering you an on fire, banana strawberry life.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>19:43</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon4-23.m4a" length="9820605" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>What's So Good About Friday? (Forsaken)- 4-14-2006</title> <description>As Christ is dying on the cross, he speaks seven times. One of those moments, he cries out, "My God, why hast thou forsaken me?" This question is a reference to something much greater, a reference to a faith that we could all hope to have amidst suffering and persecution. [There is no evening service on Easter, so this will be this week's podcast. Happy Easter, see you next week]</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>11:26</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon4-14.m4a" length="5713016" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>A Holy Montage- 4-9-2006</title> <description>You know those movie montages where they fit a lot of important stuff into a small amount of time to give you background before something important happens? Holy week is the montage that makes Easter mean something. [This service followed a different format mixing message, music and ritual. Copyright prohibits including the music. At the end of the service, the papers nailed to the cross burned and disappeared.]</description><pubDate>Sun, 9 Apr 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>22:36</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon4-9.m4a" length="12230158" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>A Preacher Says What?!?!- 4-2-2006</title> <description>You know, the church says some crazy things. And on top of that, they have their own crazy words to talk about it all. So what does it all mean, and how does that 'religious language' translate to everyday life?</description><pubDate>Sun, 2 Apr 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>24:35</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon4-2.m4a" length="12230158" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>You Know the Plan... But What About Me?!?!- 3-26-2006</title> <description>Every day, each minute... decisions and choices... but how do they fit into God's plan for us? What if we make the wrong choice. Jeremiah says God has a plan for us... then why hasn't God filled us in! [Next Week: A Preacher Says What?]</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>20:15</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon3-26.m4a" length="10138268" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Sin and Dog Crap- 3-19-2006</title> <description>There you are minding your own business, when suddenly you've stepped in it. A big, steaming pile of... sin. It happens to all of us- but thanks to God's grace, sin is a lot easier to get rid of than the brown stuff. [Next Week: You know the plans... but what about me!]</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>15:48</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon3-19.m4a" length="9672618" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Prayer- 3-12-2006</title> <description>Prayer is such a beautiful and powerful thing, but it can also feel empty and frustrating. Douglas Wood's book "Grandad's Prayers of the Earth" offers an insightful and moving look at prayer. **Sorry for the day delay, I have had finals this week** Next week, Sin and Dog Crap (don't miss it!)</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>12:15</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon3-12.m4a" length="9672618" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Worship: What's it all about?- 3-5-2006</title> <description>We gather every week for an hour (or more if the sermon goes long) for worship... What's it all about? What makes worship, worship? And with so many different kinds of worship out there, how do I know what's right... [next week, Why Pray?]</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>19:26</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon3-5.m4a" length="9672618" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Church: What's the point?- 2-26-2006</title> <description>So why go to (or listen to) church? It's an important question to ask, and the answer might just surprise you- and help you get a lot more out of it... [next week, Why worship?]</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>25:19</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon2-26.m4a" length="12591627" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>It Happens, and so does Faith- 2-19-2006</title> <description>When the storms of life are raging, how does our faith fit in? How does Jesus fit in? And what do I have to do to keep this boat from rocking? **The recording missed the first 30sec, so it had to be re-recorded. That is why the sound changes a little bit in**</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>19:33</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon2-19.m4a" length="7089248" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Love... more than pink and red- 2-12-2006</title> <description>Feb. 14th... whether you love it or hate it, the pink and red day comes every year. What if there is more to this whole love thing than corporate America lets on...</description> <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>23:21</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon2-12.m4a" length="7089248" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Like... - 2-5-2006</title> <description>Like. It's a part of the American vernacular and has been used by Valley Girls and PhD's alike. It also is a wonderful way for us to think about God, just Like Jesus did in Luke 13:18-21. This pod-cast is enhanced with the photos mentioned in the sermon. They will appear in the Album Art box in iTunes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>13:38</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon2-5.m4a" length="7089248" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>The Cool Table - 1-29-2006</title> <description>If you stop and think about it, that 'cool table' from elementary school never went away. People are excluded in all sorts of ways; sometimes we are on the outside looking in, other times we're the ones at the table. We are called to invite people to a new table, Christ's table.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2006 12:01:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>17:34</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon1-29.m4a" length="7673768" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>How Is It With Your Soul? - 1-22-2006</title> <description>Take a moment, stop all the rushing and busyness, and ask yourself, "How is it with my soul?"</description> <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2006 12:00:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>16:15</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon1-22.m4a" length="8050327" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Abundant Life... and Crayons - 1-15-2006</title> <description>How God's love for us is like a box of new crayons... Rom. 8:1-4</description> <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2006 12:00:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>15:27</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon1-15.m4a" length="7568273" type="audio/AAC" /></item><item><title>Taking On the Tagline: Open Hearts, Open Minds, Open Doors - 1-8-2006</title> <description>A look at what the Igniting Ministries slogan means for us as a Church. Rom. 15:5-7</description> <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2006 12:00:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>22:37</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon1-8.m4a" length="10986369" type="audio/AAC" /></item> <item><title>Welcome to Trinity's Podcast - 1-1-2006</title> <description>A welcome and explanation of Trinity's Podcast. Also includes service and contact information.</description> <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2006 12:00:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>1:13</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon1-1.m4a" length="731499" type="audio/AAC" /></item> <item><title>Here's to the Crazy One's - 10-16-2005</title> <description>This is a version of the sermon I delivered at Trinity. When I delivered it, Trinity was not yet digitally recording, so this sermon was actually delivered at Lakewood UMC, but it is essentially the same.</description> <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2005 12:00:00 MST </pubDate><itunes:duration>23:38</itunes:duration><enclosure url="http://www.trinityumc.org/podcast/Sermon10-16.m4a" length="11522358" type="audio/AAC" /></item> </channel> </rss>