<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[StarSearchCasting.com Audition Notices]]></title>
	<description><![CDATA[StarSearchCasting.com Audition Notices]]></description>
	<link>http://auditions.starsearchcasting.com</link>
	<atom:link href="http://starsearchcasting.com/rss/notices.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<ttl>25</ttl>
	<image>
		<title><![CDATA[StarSearchCasting.com Audition Notices]]></title>
		<url>http://starsearchcasting.com/ssc.png</url>
		<link>http://auditions.starsearchcasting.com</link>
	</image>

	<item>
	<title><![CDATA[TV SERIES]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/_TV_SERIES__5</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Shannon Heights Television Inc. a Seattle based production company is seeking actors to fill casting needs for its television series Lakeside Manor. The following talants are needed is needed to complete our pilot episode and for potential roles in the longer term services: 
One Asian female at least age 21 to 27 to play Britta Kwon the older daughter of a minister. Britta works at Finnermans Deptment store working in the womens shoe department and has an unemployed boyfriend named Jake,
One Asian female at least age 16 to 19 to play high school student Stephanie Kwon. She is Britta's younger sis. She's now getting stolen jewelry from her new boyfriend Clay.
One Ethnic or African American female at least 17 and up to 20 years of age to play character Tiffany Parks who is not liking Stephanie Kwon much these days.
One male character to play the role of a 16 to 17 year old high school student named Kyle Brier.
Scenes will be generally shot during the weekends beginning June 15 and through July. Most of the scenes for the above roles for the high school students will be filmed at Nathan Hale High school and the role of Stephanie maybe at other locations as well.]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/_TV_SERIES__5</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Co-Host]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/_CoHost_8</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you a female? Do you consider yourself liberal? Are you opinionated? If so, then you just may be what
we're looking for.

In the early stages of putting together a weekly radio talk show on Freedom 1590 AM that would
consist of debating various issues from politics to pop culture and everything in between.
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/_CoHost_8</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[sexy photo shoot]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/_sexy_photo_shoot</link>
	<description><![CDATA['m looking for a busty Hispanic model for a photo shoot at Eagle Falls near Index WA. This photo shoot would take either in late July or sometime in August during the week. Please have a variety of bikini's, white button up shirt, maybe a bra or two. I also would like to maybe do a couple implied photos. Pay is $80.00 plus your choice of high res digital images. I'm only looking for models with at least some experience. Please email examples of your work as well as stats. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/_sexy_photo_shoot</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Adult Models Wanted]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Adult_Models_Wanted_43</link>
	<description><![CDATA[If you're beautiful we want to work with you to start webcasts. Must be over 18 with photographs and information. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Adult_Models_Wanted_43</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Model Wanted]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Model_Wanted_184</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Looking for a male model who would be interested in modeling our costumes and mascots for online catalogs. 

The candidate must be in between 5'9" to 5'11"' in height, 150 lbs-170 lbs and with nice personality!

Would like to have the model come over once or twice a week to model the new costumes.

Will pay same day and all pictures would be posted online. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Model_Wanted_184</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Promo Models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Promo_Models_163</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Female Promotional Models Needed for promotional modeling jobs coming up throughout the next few months all around the greater Seattle area and areas North and South of. All models must be at least 18 or older no past modeling exp. is required. Females interested in this please email in a photo of yourself and include info. stats such as height-weight be sure to mention any experience you do have and leave a contact phone number to call you at. All models need to have a good personality an attractive look and a nice smile. Thanks for taking the time and thanks for your interest in this posting. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Promo_Models_163</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Car Show Models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Car_Show_Models__2</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Car Show Models Wanted for upcoming Summer Car Shows which will be held around the Tacoma/Seattle areas. Models must be at least 18yrs of age. No modeling experience is required. Tattoos are OK and models do not have to be tall. Ladies interested please submit photo of yourself as well as some general info. about yourself as well such as height, weight and age. Please be sure to mention any modeling or promotional modeling experience you do have and please be sure to give a good contact number to reach you at. Thanks for your interest. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Car_Show_Models__2</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Models Wanted]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_Wanted_3034</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Please be between 18-25, respond with pics and stats. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_Wanted_3034</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Female Models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Female_Models_301514</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Casting Female Models for paid assignments. 
You must have valid ID and be open minded...
Paid assignments up to $1500.00, per assignment. 
If interested please send recent photos, and a contact number to reach you easier.
We will respond with more details on the projects available. 
You must be eighteen or older 
Must be 18+ to apply! ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Female_Models_301514</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Models Needed]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_Needed_4860</link>
	<description><![CDATA[My schedule has changed and have the week open. Need to fill my times this week. Will offer TFP for portfolio building. Send your stats, content ideas, wardrobe thoughts and available times. I have attached my Model Mayhem account link below. I have several open projects as well needing specific types. Please respond soon.]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_Needed_4860</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Adult Film Actress]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Adult_Film_Actress_22</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Looking for an Adult Female Actress to fill a Supporting Role in a Local Film. Experience not required. Must be 18 years of age, 5'4'' - 5'9", Caucasian (preferably blond), voluptuous and in good physical shape, and be comfortable with being nude in front of others.]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Adult_Film_Actress_22</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Boys and girls sm-med]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Boys_and_girls_smmed</link>
	<description><![CDATA[-boys and girls sizes small and medium for local clothing line fitting/promotional shoot
-boys 6 to 12 years old
-girls 8 to 14 yeasr old


-Parents: email recent images and contact number. There will be a fitting day and a shoot day in Mid-June
*Adult must accompany child AT ALL TIMES. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Boys_and_girls_smmed</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[amateur videos]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/amateur_videos_1</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Up and coming amateur adult video production company based in SKC is looking for sexy female models ages 18-35 for amateur, real-life adult videos. All shoots are local and compensation is cash on hand at shoot. No experience necessary, but willingness to learn, take direction and perform is! We do weekly or bi-weekly shoots so we are always looking for fresh or new talent to work with!
We strive to create fun, "reality-based," multi-camera videos that are sexy, exciting and get across the model's personality! Come join us and have fun while making $ ! ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/amateur_videos_1</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[WEDDING SHOOT]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/WEDDING_SHOOT_4</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Need a few nice and fun loving models to do a wedding shoot, we need everyone from a bride and a groom as well as a flower girl and ring bearer for a new up and coming line of wedding apparel for summer and fall. 

Descriptions: 

*Bride: between 21-35 with long beautiful hair and a small build. 
*Groom: between 24-40 with a clean cut and fresh new look 
*Brides maids between 19-30 need various height, weight and hair lengths 
*Flower girl and ring bearer between 5-12 with an adorable look and is comfortable with being in front of the camera 

The shoot is going to be on June 16th with a fitting date on June 15th in order to make sure that the clothes fit properly. 

In order to apply please send some photos, a short description of why you think you are good for this shoot and contact info so that I may reach you about specific things like clothing size, waist size, etc. As for compensation each person will receive $150 plus images for the shoot and be featured in a few local magazines. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/WEDDING_SHOOT_4</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Actors/Actresses]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/ActorsActresses__16</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Male and Female needed for training videos:
Asian Gentleman 50ish playing policeman
Caucasian male 30's Shopper
African American Female 20's Sales Associate

Please respond with Resume and Headshot, no inquiries will be answered without them!]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/ActorsActresses__16</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[photo shoot]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/photo_shoot_978</link>
	<description><![CDATA[-Seeking Child Models, ages 1-3, African American, Asian, Latin/Hispanic and Caucasian.

-Outdoor afternoon photo shoot on Monday, June 25 near the Seattle waterfront.

-Photos will be for professional commercial use and the shoot will last 2-3 hours.

-Please submit with a photo and contact information for details and specific requirements.

-We will not hold a casting date. Pay will be flat rate.


Thank you!
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/photo_shoot_978</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[ACTRESS/ACTORS]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/ACTRESSACTORS_</link>
	<description><![CDATA[I'm looking to cast for a dramatic short film that will begin filming in the next few weeks. Filming will take place over the span of 2-5 days, your presence will not be required on all days.

This is a low budget, independent short that will be submitted to film festivals in the Fall and Winter of this year. All performers will be credited for their contributions. Very good opportunity to gain exposure.

Again, prior experience is only preferred for the Lead Actress and not required for any of the roles offered. 

ROLE 1
Actress - female, early to late 20's, some acting experience preferred but not required, the role is of an actress and love interest to our lead actor


ROLE 2
Supporting Actress - female, late 20's to mid-30's, the role is a mother waiting at a bus stop with her child, no experience required at all, this is non-speaking role

ROLE 3
Supporting Child - boy or girl, age 5-11, this is a non-speaking role, no experience required 


Auditions will be held in Seattle on June 8th. More information about location and time will be given to those who submit their info.

Email 2 head shots and contact information as well as basic info (name, age).

Pay will be discussed with each individual with an assigned role.]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/ACTRESSACTORS_</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[female models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/_female_models_2040</link>
	<description><![CDATA[GF Photography is looking for four models to shoot on the 8th of June
the ad is for athletic wear and we will be focusing on leggings and tank tops.
it will be relased in July in a series of magazines.
keep in mind we are looking for models with slender/slim bodies for this ad,

to apply please email your portfolio including
-2 full body shots
-2 head shots
-Full name and contact information

All models must be reliable and be 18-24 years old to participate (previous modeling experience is not required)

Pay will be $300 for full day ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/_female_models_2040</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Model needed]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Model_needed_501</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Urban Eclectics is expanding! We are looking for two females to model our clothes for our online clothing store. Looking for size 4 or size 6 to shoot in multiple pairs of shorts. Preferably 5feet 3 inches or taller. 



This is not a paying gig, it is a trade you will receive a disc of edited photos and a pair of our amazing shorts which retail anywhere from 50-79 dollars. Will be shooting in mid-June



If interested please email 1 head shot and 2 full body shots! They do not need to be professional just recent and clear enough to see the detail of your body because you will be modeling shorts.
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Model_needed_501</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[exotic dancers]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/exotic_dancers_65</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Looking to hire one or two male exotic dancers/strippers for a gay mens bachelor party.

The gig would last for about an hour on Saturday night June 9th

Please respond with rates, services, and photos ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/exotic_dancers_65</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Model casting call]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Model_casting_call_61</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Up in coming lingerie company needs models for brand launch party!

June 9th 11pm-2pm Line will be shown from about 12-1 No modeling experience is required

Please send pictures along with measurements ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Model_casting_call_61</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[2013 photo shoot]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/2013_photo_shoot</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Local custom musical instrument company is now looking for models for our 2013 calendar. Models will spacificly be in mixed locations with our new line of custom drummsets. Indoor and outdoor. Please respond with a photo portfolio and a little about yourself. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/2013_photo_shoot</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[documentary]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/documentary_960</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Documentary on filmmaking in post seeking Japanese actors/models and/or Asian talent that can speak (at least some) Japanese. Shooting a fun short sequence that would represent contemporary Japanese experimental filmmaking. Sort of a mix of original elements perhaps with nods to Michael Gondry or Rampo Noir. 
Micro/no-budget production, no pay, finishing in HD and film. 
Please send links to pics/resume and email any questions. Thank you.
copy, credit, cast&crew book ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/documentary_960</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Performers]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Performers__7</link>
	<description><![CDATA[I am looking for unique, family friendly acts for a space themed festival this summer August 17-19. I am looking for a performance that will really stand out. Free entry + promotion + possible opportunities after. Also looking for unique features such as palm reading, dancing, and comedians. Please respond with information, contact, website links, pics, videos, etc. Thank you ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Performers__7</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[female models needed]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/female_models_needed_3362</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
I am looking for a reliable female model for photoshoot Hair and Make-Up will be done by a Professional Hairstylist/ Make-Up artist.This shoot will be taken by a Professional Photographer. Date to be set sometime end of june. Will be meeting w/ models over the next 2 weeks or so. If interested please send measurements along with a couple photos. This will be a great opportunity to help build your portfollio, you will receive several photos for your participation. must be willing to cut/color hair ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/female_models_needed_3362</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Photoshoot models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Photoshoot_models_1</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Female models needed for photoshoot in june must be willing to cut and/or color your hair if interested please email me with your name, height, measurements and atleast 2 photos and I'll get back to you as soon as possible ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Photoshoot_models_1</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Seeking Attractive Women]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Seeking_Attractive_Women_2</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Top Internet Modeling Agency is currently hiring attractive models. 

Earn high pay working part time at home. 

To apply or get information please e-mail. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Seeking_Attractive_Women_2</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Models needed]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_needed__241</link>
	<description><![CDATA[NO EXPERIENCE NECESSARY!!!
Female owned looking for 18 to 50 year old women, thin or BBW or anything in between. Students, stay-at-home Mom's or anyone looking to make some extra money.

HOURLY WAGE plus great commissions.

Email for the dates and details ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_needed__241</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[live models needed]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/live_models_needed</link>
	<description><![CDATA[NO EXPERIENCE NECESSARY!!!
Female owned agency looking for 18 to 50 year old women, thin or BBW or anything in between...looks are not important as long as your comfortable with yourself! Students, stay-at-home Mom's or anyone looking to make some extra money.
I need 4 people for June...and could extend thru the summer months!

Guaranteed HOURLY WAGE plus commission, bonuses and incentives!! FLEXIBLE HOURS!

Email for the dates and times and all the other important info for this gig!!]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/live_models_needed</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Short Film]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Short_Film_3938</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
CASTING ACTORS FOR SHORT FILM

Adapted short film script- Option owned -Serious project

Seeking for non-professional or professional actors.

We are looking for:

MALE LEAD - Latino / African-American / Caucasian: 25-35 years old- average height and weight.

FEMALE LEAD - 20 to 30 years old --slim to average build.

Looking to begin production in late June or July- Must be available for read through.

Examples of previous work a plus.

HEAD SHOT & RESUME REQUIRED


More info and script will be provided to serious inquiries. 

Low budget short- Fair compensation, food/ drink and copy will be provided
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Short_Film_3938</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Adult Film]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Adult_Film_248</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Starting a new adult film agency. Looking for young beautiful talent. 21 to 26 . Earnings potential is great. Only serious inquiries will be contacted. Thanks ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Adult_Film_248</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Hairs & Eyewear Models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Hairs__Eyewear_Models</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Need women ages 18-30 to model for article on fashionable hairstyles and eye glasses, mostly latest eye glasses and some sunglasses. Send headshots with your contact number. $875 for feature on both subjects ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Hairs__Eyewear_Models</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Lusty Ladies Wanted]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Lusty_Ladies_Wanted_1</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Pro photographer seeking adventurous female models in their prime of life. We will have fun doing erotic and art nude photography.
Total comfort with your body and sexuality is a requirement.
TFP - You pick your favorite 20 images for your own portfolio immediately following the shoot. 
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Lusty_Ladies_Wanted_1</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Alternative Models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Alternative_Models_5</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Looking for models who would like to freshen up their portfolios with a creative photographer or for those who would like to get their portfolios started in the industry. Tattoos, piercings, all forms of uniqueness welcome. We could do a few different themes during our shoot. You would get your disc of high definition images.]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Alternative_Models_5</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[girl next door models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/girl_next_door_models_14</link>
	<description><![CDATA[females aged 18-24 required for photo shoot 
no modeling experience is needed casting fresh faces will train
each photo session will required about one hour of your time

submit a photo for more details
compensation 350 per shoot ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/girl_next_door_models_14</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Attractive younger couple needed]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Attractive_younger_couple_needed</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Attractive, energetic younger couple (MF) with a passion for video games needed for adult-oriented Internet start-up project. Paying opportunity with potential for ongoing work.

Contact us with face photos for a response. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Attractive_younger_couple_needed</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[looking for model]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/looking_for_model_44</link>
	<description><![CDATA[looking for a new model (female) payed please send photo ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/looking_for_model_44</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[female promo models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/female_promo_models_16</link>
	<description><![CDATA[i need some females in the seattle area that can handle some events that are going on in the area, please send bio, pics and contact information ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/female_promo_models_16</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Calendar Model Shoot]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Calendar_Model_Shoot_2</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Casting for new fresh faces 18+ sexy indivduals who are confident and would like to try out for our model photo shoot, whether your an amateur or one with experience and looking to model for a Luxury Car Collection Shoot as well as Vintage collectible cars. No exp necessary as long as you have the look were looking for. Must be 18+, gig pays 100-150 per shoot and this would be a great shoot to build or enhance ones portfolio especially if your new.
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Calendar_Model_Shoot_2</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Makeover Video]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Makeover_Video_7</link>
	<description><![CDATA[We are currently looking for a couple of ladies to participate in a haircut makeover video. We are looking for ladies who have long hair and are willing to go short. We will work with you to pick your style, but we are looking for shorter styles for this program. If you just want a trim, this is not the program for you. 

We will pay you in cash at the time of your session. 

If you could use some extra holiday cash and would like a new style, please contact us. Your hair will be cut by someone who has been doing these sessions for many years. 
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Makeover_Video_7</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Model Amatures]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Model_Amatures</link>
	<description><![CDATA[seeking a petite sized female fashion model for underwear, fetish and fantasy wear fetish themed

you must be 18-27yrs old and size 4/5 or less petite size 

very comfortable in your skin, open minded and easy going attitude.
i am amature photographer seeking a special amature only for my subject. 
****will supply all outfits and you may keep select number of items

be on time, reliable and good attitude 
if you love lingerie, swimwear, fantasy wear and fetish wear etc. this is strictly a fun project, but you still need to respect time 

then please send age with clothed pic and your waist size. be able to prove age of 18 + 

small breasted is a plus 32/34 A is perfect 

Limited number of tattoos 

No Pros !! 

Non Paid as ad clearly states

No Links 

Non nude !!

Have transportation to Renton area ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Model_Amatures</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Photo-shoot]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Photoshoot_1928</link>
	<description><![CDATA[I am looking to get out in todays wonderful weather and shoot some photos... Are you a Model whom wishes to showcase your talents? Need Photos for your company promotions? Have a cool idea but no camera gear? Get ahold of me asap and lets make something happen... 
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Photoshoot_1928</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Photoshoot]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Photoshoot_1927</link>
	<description><![CDATA[We are looking to hire a few models on June 16th, 
Must be available 7:45am-4pm.
This is a workshop so you will be shooting with around 60 photographers! 
Its a great way to add images to your portfolio & network yourself. 
Compensation for the shoot with be $100 
SERIOUS inquires only!! 

MUST submit: stats & professional images. 
Thank you & Good Luck ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Photoshoot_1927</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Asian Females]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Asian_Females_14</link>
	<description><![CDATA[I need an attractive ASIAN female to 
model some Asian Outfits.
Model should be slender with s feminin
figure, long hair preferred.
Please reply with picture.
This is a Time For Picture offer. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Asian_Females_14</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Models needed]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_needed_4859</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Gals between the ages of 18 & 35 needed for shoots. Great pay & flexible scheduling. If you are interested, please send your photos and contact info! ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_needed_4859</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Looking for models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Looking_for_models__164</link>
	<description><![CDATA[I'm looking for male or female models {preferably female but I won't be picky ;) }-heavily tattooed {If you have less than 10 tattoos please do not email me}, MUST be in good shape. I'm a professional photographer looking to expand some areas of my portfolio. I'm based out of Everett-willing to travel up to 15 miles from my doorstep. Or you can come to me. This will be an on-location photo shoot and you will receive a High-Res disc with 10-15 re-touched/edited images. This is a TFCD. Please send me a photo or 2 of tattoos that you have and any modeling experience. I'm not looking for pro models, but it would help if you are already great at posing. I'm looking to do 30-45min photo shoot. 

I will send you a link to my work once I receive an email, thank you very much~
I am a female photographer {I know that matters to some people/models}

Have a great day! 
And I'm not doing anything wrong by posting this so STOP flagging me!!! If you have an issue with this post then look somewhere else....simple enough ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Looking_for_models__164</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Model Attractive]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Model_Attractive_</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Model for events and promos. Good personality.
Cruise/ Hospitality some travel maybe required
Do reply with bio/ pics
Compensation is aro. 350.00 ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Model_Attractive_</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_301771</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Female Models Wanted for upcoming Fashion Show this Summer to be held in the Tacoma area this July. Models must be at least 18yrs of age or older no height requirements Tall or short welcome to apply. To be considered for this event please e-mail over a photo of yourself something that shows your look inclide with your e-mail your stats such as your weight-hight and your age and tell about any expeience in modeling that you do have. Please also be sure to give contact info. phone number you can be reached at is preferred. Thanks for your interest. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_301771</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Models]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_301770</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Female Model Wanted for Small Businesses in need of print models for various marketing materials such as but not limited too Fliers, Brochures and Web Design. In addition to the print opportunities models can also get opportunities to work as promotional models as well. All models must be at least 18yrs of age or older no experience in required but can be real helpful. Ladies interested please submit photos via email of yourself photos do not have to be professional. Please include your age height and weight with all submissions and a good contact number to call you at.]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/Models_301770</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[MUSIC VIDEO]]></title>
	<link>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/MUSIC_VIDEO_2561</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Looking For Females for This Major UpComing Music Video For Our UpComing Hip Hop Recording Artist, Please Email Name age and Pictures, THis is a Serious Video and Need Some Good And Trustful people...
Please Contact Us ASAP
Thanks ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 22:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://starsearchcasting.com/auditions/MUSIC_VIDEO_2561</guid>
</item>

	
</channel>
</rss>