<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Cancer Newsline</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/Departments/newsroom/dIndex.cfm?pn=E2AD1A8D-7A8A-11D4-AEC700508BDCCE3A" />
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www2.mdanderson.org/feeds/cancer_newsline/atom.xml" />
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2009-01-05:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10</id>
    <updated>2012-05-21T18:57:33Z</updated>
    
    <generator uri="http://www.sixapart.com/movabletype/">Movable Type Pro 4.25</generator>

<entry>
    <title>Health care reform and the effect on cancer prevention services</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2012/healthreform-cnl.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2012:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2335</id>

    <published>2012-05-21T18:55:13Z</published>
    <updated>2012-05-21T18:57:33Z</updated>

    <summary>Lewis Foxhall, M.D., vice president for Health Policy at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, explains ways health care reform supports cancer prevention. This includes health insurance affordability and lower or no-cost cancer prevention services and screenings....</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="cancer" label="cancer" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    <category term="prevention" label="prevention" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[<p style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 10pt" class="MsoNormal"><font size="3"><font color="#000000"><font face="Calibri">Lewis Foxhall, M.D., vice president for Health Policy at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, explains ways health care reform supports cancer prevention. This includes health insurance affordability and lower or no-cost cancer prevention services and screenings. <o:p></o:p></font></font></font></p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>The connection between genes and colon cancer</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2012/genetic-colon-cancer-cnl.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2012:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2308</id>

    <published>2012-05-08T16:13:54Z</published>
    <updated>2012-05-08T16:15:29Z</updated>

    <summary>About 20% of colon cancer cases are related to a strong family history of colon cancer. Eduardo Vilar-Sanchez, M.D., Ph.D., Assistant Professor in the Department of Clinical Cancer Prevention at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, focuses his...</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="coloncancer" label="colon cancer" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    <category term="genetics" label="genetics" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[<p style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 10pt" class="MsoNormal"><font size="3"><font color="#000000"><font face="Calibri">About 20% of colon cancer cases are related to a strong family history of colon cancer. Eduardo Vilar-Sanchez, M.D., Ph.D., Assistant Professor in the Department of Clinical Cancer Prevention at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, focuses his discussion on the main types of genetic colon cancers including hereditary nonpolyposis colorectal cancer syndrome or HNPCC (also called Lynch syndrome) and familial adenomatous polyposis (FAP). <o:p></o:p></font></font></font></p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Tips to Help Kids Avoid Adult Cancers</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2012/kids-avoid-cancer.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2012:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2284</id>

    <published>2012-04-23T20:31:26Z</published>
    <updated>2012-04-23T20:32:35Z</updated>

    <summary>Beverly Gor, Ed.D., postdoctoral fellow in the Center for Health Equity and Evaluation Research at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, discusses healthy lifestyle choices you can make for your children to help prevent the development of certain...</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="prevention" label="Prevention" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[<p>Beverly Gor, Ed.D., postdoctoral fellow in the Center for Health Equity and Evaluation Research at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, discusses healthy lifestyle choices you can make for your children to help prevent the development of certain adult cancers; such as prostate, breast and colon. Gor stresses the importance of healthy nutrition and exercise to reduce the risk of developing cancer later in life.</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Bone Cancer Surgery Options for the Adult Patient</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2012/bonecancersurgery-cnl.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2012:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2269</id>

    <published>2012-04-10T20:12:45Z</published>
    <updated>2012-04-10T20:14:13Z</updated>

    <summary>Valerae Lewis, M.D., Associate Professor in The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center Department of Orthopaedic Oncology, discusses the many surgery options for bone cancer patients. Limb salvage surgery replaces the cancerous bone with either a bone graft from...</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="bonecancer" label="bone cancer" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        Valerae Lewis, M.D., Associate Professor in The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center Department of Orthopaedic Oncology, discusses the many surgery options for bone cancer patients. Limb salvage surgery replaces the cancerous bone with either a bone graft from another person (allowgraft), a metal implant or a combination of the two (allo-prosthetic). After amputation of the lower leg, rotationplasty moves the ankle joint to where the knee once was to function as the knee joint. MD Anderson is highly experienced in treating bone cancer specializing in less invasive procedures that have minimum impact on your body&apos;s appearance.
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Brain Cancer Basics and Hope through Research</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href=" http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2012/brain-cancer-research-cnl.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2012:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2248</id>

    <published>2012-03-26T19:31:06Z</published>
    <updated>2012-03-26T19:32:29Z</updated>

    <summary>Amy Heimberger, M.D., Associate Professor in the Department Neurosurgery at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, discusses the basics, history and the incidence of brain cancer. She is joined by Gail Goodwin, MD Anderson employee and brain cancer...</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="braincancer" label="brain cancer" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        Amy Heimberger, M.D., Associate Professor in the Department Neurosurgery at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, discusses the basics, history and the incidence of brain cancer. She is joined by Gail Goodwin, MD Anderson employee and brain cancer survivor, and Lanie Rose, founder of Run for the Rose (annual run raising funds for brain cancer research) for an engaging discussion about new advances in brain cancer research and how there is hope for more long-term brain cancer survivors.
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Bile Duct Cancer - Rare but Numbers are Growing </title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2012/bile-duct-cancer-cnl.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2012:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2224</id>

    <published>2012-03-12T19:03:05Z</published>
    <updated>2012-03-12T19:04:57Z</updated>

    <summary>Bile duct cancer (cholangiocarcinoma) is rare. There are 4,000 - 5,000 newly-diagnosed cases in the United States each year, and the numbers are growing. It&apos;s important to get the disease treated at a multidisplinary facility that specializes in bile duct...</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="bileductcancer" label="Bile duct cancer" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    <category term="cholangiocarcinoma" label="cholangiocarcinoma" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[<p style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 10pt" class="MsoNormal"><font size="3"><font color="#000000"><font face="Calibri">Bile duct cancer (cholangiocarcinoma) is rare. There are 4,000 - 5,000 newly-diagnosed cases in the United States each year, and the numbers are growing. It's important to get the disease treated at a multidisplinary facility that specializes in bile duct cancer. Thomas Aloia, M.D., Assistant Professor in Surgical Oncology; Boris Blechacz, M.D., Assistant Professor in the Department of <span style="mso-ansi-language: EN" lang="EN">Gastroenterology, Hepatology and</span><span lang="EN"> </span>Nutrition; and <span style="mso-ansi-language: EN"><span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span></span>Milind Javle, M.D., Associate Professor in the Department of Gastrointestinal (GI) Medical Oncology, all at The University of Texas MD Anderson, <span style="mso-spacerun: yes">&nbsp;</span>discuss the basics including treatment, and surgery options for bile duct cancer patients.<o:p></o:p></font></font></font></p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Cancer Research for Stage 1 Lung Cancer </title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2012/cnl-lung-cancer-clinical-trials.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2012:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2209</id>

    <published>2012-02-29T14:22:25Z</published>
    <updated>2012-02-29T14:23:51Z</updated>

    <summary>New cancer research for stage 1 lung cancer is being investigated at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, led by Jack Roth, professor in the Department of Thoracic and Cardiovascular Surgery. This clinical trial called STARS (Stereotactic Radiation...</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="clinicaltrial" label="Clinical Trial" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    <category term="lungcancer" label="lung cancer" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[<p>New cancer research for stage 1 lung cancer is being investigated at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, led by Jack Roth, professor in the Department of Thoracic and Cardiovascular Surgery. </p>
<p>This clinical trial called STARS (Stereotactic Radiation Therapy Verses Surgery), compares a new type of radiation treatment with a traditional surgery approach. Roth describes this promising new treatment and explains how lung cancer patients may get involved.</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Skin Cancer of the Eye - Uveal Melanoma</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2012/uvealmelanoma-cnl.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2012:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2207</id>

    <published>2012-02-28T14:55:37Z</published>
    <updated>2012-02-28T14:56:38Z</updated>

    <summary>Uveal melanoma is a very rare cancer that forms on the eye&apos;s skin tissue, usually in the back part of the eye under the retina (choroid). Sapna Patel, M.D., Assistant Professor in the Department of Melanoma Medical Oncology at The...</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="uvealmelanoma" label="uveal melanoma" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[<p>Uveal melanoma is a very rare cancer that forms on the eye's skin tissue, usually in the back part of the eye under the retina (choroid). Sapna Patel, M.D., Assistant Professor in the Department of Melanoma Medical Oncology at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, discusses the causes, symptoms and treatment of uveal melanoma. Patel also explains why it is important for everyone to have their eyes examined, even if your vision is 20/20.</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Fertility Issues for Parents to Consider before Child&apos;s Cancer Treatment</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2012/fertilitychildcancer.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2012:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2163</id>

    <published>2012-01-30T17:41:14Z</published>
    <updated>2012-01-30T17:42:33Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[The best way to preserve your child's fertility during cancer treatment depends on age, sex &nbsp;and if the child has reached puberty. This concern is best addressed before cancer treatment starts. Anna Franklin, M.D., Assistant Professor, and Donna Bell, Advanced...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="childhoodcancer" label="Childhood Cancer" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    <category term="pediatric" label="pediatric" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[The best way to preserve your child's fertility during cancer treatment depends on age, sex &nbsp;and if the child has reached puberty. This concern is best addressed before cancer treatment starts. Anna Franklin, M.D., Assistant Professor, and Donna Bell, Advanced Nurse Practitioner, both in the Department of Pediatrics Patient Care at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, discuss ways to preserve your child's fertility and offer helpful resources.]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Proton Therapy Treatment for Liver Cancer </title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2012/protontherapylivercancercnl.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2012:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2143</id>

    <published>2012-01-13T18:48:59Z</published>
    <updated>2012-01-13T18:50:05Z</updated>

    <summary>Proton therapy has several advantages in treating liver cancer over traditional radiation therapy. Since the proton beam is so exact, larger dosages of radiation can be applied to the affected area, while sparing surrounding healthy tissue. Proton therapy also successfully...</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="livercancer" label="liver cancer" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    <category term="protontherapy" label="proton therapy" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[<p style="MARGIN: 0in 0in 10pt" class="MsoNormal"><font size="3"><font color="#000000"><font face="Calibri">Proton therapy has several advantages in treating liver cancer over traditional radiation therapy. Since the proton beam is so exact, larger dosages of radiation can be applied to the affected area, while sparing surrounding healthy tissue. Proton therapy also successfully addresses technical challenges, including liver movement during treatment when the patient breathes. Christopher Crane, M.D., Professor in the Department of Radiation Oncology at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, discusses proton therapy as well as other options available to liver cancer patients.<o:p></o:p></font></font></font></p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>CYCORE - Information Technology Tools Helping With Clinical Trials </title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2012/cycore-information-technology-tools-helping-with-clinical-trials.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2012:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2133</id>

    <published>2012-01-03T14:26:19Z</published>
    <updated>2012-01-03T14:27:15Z</updated>

    <summary>CYCORE (Cyberinfrastructure for Comparative Effectiveness Research) was a clinical trial conducted by The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, University of California-San Diego and University of Alabama at Birmingham, that studied the use of sensing devices to wirelessly send...</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="clinicaltrial" label="Clinical Trial" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[<span style="LINE-HEIGHT: 115%; FONT-FAMILY: 'Calibri','sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 11pt; mso-fareast-font-family: Calibri; mso-bidi-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-ansi-language: EN-US; mso-fareast-language: EN-US; mso-bidi-language: AR-SA"><font color="#000000">CYCORE (Cyberinfrastructure for Comparative Effectiveness Research) was a clinical trial conducted by The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, University of California-San Diego and University of Alabama at Birmingham, that studied the use of sensing devices to wirelessly send health-related data from the patient's home to the cancer research facility. The purpose of this study is for other researchers to use CYCORE's technology to gather more detailed information in their own clinical trials. Susan Peterson, Ph.D., M.P.H., lead investigator on the study and associate professor in the Department of Behavioral Science at MD Anderson, discusses the results.</font></span>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Childhood Leukemia: Most Common Childhood Cancer </title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2011/childhood-leukemia-most-common-childhood-cancer.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2011:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2107</id>

    <published>2011-12-12T20:09:03Z</published>
    <updated>2011-12-12T20:10:34Z</updated>

    <summary>Childhood leukemia is the most common childhood cancer with more than 3,500 children in the U.S. diagnosed each year. Patrick Zweidler-McKay, M.D., Ph.D., Assistant Professor at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center Children&apos;s Cancer Hospital, talks about symptoms,...</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="leukemia" label="leukemia" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    <category term="pediatric" label="pediatric" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        Childhood leukemia is the most common childhood cancer with more than 3,500 children in the U.S. diagnosed each year. Patrick Zweidler-McKay, M.D., Ph.D., Assistant Professor at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center Children&apos;s Cancer Hospital, talks about symptoms, diagnoses and treatment of this blood disease. Zweidler-McKay also discusses health problems that may occur decades after treatment and encourages long term follow-up doctor visits.
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Alarming Increase in Throat Cancer Due to HPV</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2011/hpv-throat-cancer.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2011:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2083</id>

    <published>2011-11-28T17:33:51Z</published>
    <updated>2011-11-28T17:35:45Z</updated>

    <summary>The number of new throat cancer cases in the United States has jumped by 125% in the last two decades. The main reason for this alarming increase in throat cancer HPV (Human Papillomavirus), the same virus that causes cervical cancer....</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="throatcancer" label="Throat Cancer" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[<span style="LINE-HEIGHT: 115%; FONT-FAMILY: 'Calibri','sans-serif'; FONT-SIZE: 11pt; mso-fareast-font-family: Calibri; mso-bidi-font-family: 'Times New Roman'; mso-ansi-language: EN-US; mso-fareast-language: EN-US; mso-bidi-language: AR-SA"><font color="#000000">The number of new throat cancer cases in the United States has jumped by 125% in the last two decades. The main reason for this alarming increase in throat cancer HPV (Human Papillomavirus), the same virus that causes cervical cancer. Floyd Christopher Holsinger, M.D., Associate Professor of Head and Neck Surgery at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, discusses this topic as well as other causes, diagnoses, and treatment options for throat cancer, including the minimally invasive surgical technique called robotic thyroidectomy. </font></span>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Targeted Drug Melts Fat in Obese Monkeys</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ybbVHTnmI4A" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2011:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2078</id>

    <published>2011-11-18T13:58:42Z</published>
    <updated>2011-11-18T14:01:09Z</updated>

    <summary><![CDATA[More info: http://bit.ly/sDYG2D An anti-obesity drug that homes in on and destroys blood vessels that support fat reduced the weight of obese rhesus monkeys by 11 percent in one month.&nbsp; It also trimmed their waistlines by eradicating 27 percent of...]]></summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[<p>More info: <a href="http://bit.ly/sDYG2D">http://bit.ly/sDYG2D</a> An anti-obesity drug that homes in on and destroys blood vessels that support fat reduced the weight of obese rhesus monkeys by 11 percent in one month.&nbsp; It also trimmed their waistlines by eradicating 27 percent of their abdominal fat.</p>
<p>Obesity raises a person's risk for developing breast, ovarian, prostate, colon and other cancers and also hinders treatment for cancer patients.</p>
<p>Scientists at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center who developed the drug discuss results of the study published in Science Translational Medicine.</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Old Age and Cancer - the Focus of This Doctor</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.mdanderson.org/newsroom/cancer-newsline/cancer-newsline-topics/2011/oldagecancer.html" />    
    <id>tag:www2.mdanderson.org,2011:/feeds/cancer_newsline//10.2073</id>

    <published>2011-11-15T13:45:49Z</published>
    <updated>2011-11-15T13:47:45Z</updated>

    <summary>Old age is the main focus of a geriatrician, a doctor who is board certified in medicine and in geriatrics. Patients faced with old age and cancer have a lot to deal with, especially managing drug intake. Holly Holmes, M.D.,...</summary>
    <author>
        <name></name>
    </author>
    
    <category term="support" label="support" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us">
        <![CDATA[<p>Old age is the main focus of a geriatrician, a doctor who is board certified in medicine and in geriatrics. Patients faced with old age and cancer have a lot to deal with, especially managing drug intake. Holly Holmes, M.D., Assistant Professor in the Department of General Internal Medicine and a certified geriatrician at the University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, states her main focus is to help the senior cancer patient remain as functional and independent as possible. Being old in years does not mean you are old mentally and physically, so Holmes works with each patient individually.</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

</feed>

