<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>1 MHz Apple II Podcast</title>
<link>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle>8-Bit Apple News and 2-Bit Apple Reviews</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>News and reviews about vintage Apple II computers, software and retrocomputing</itunes:summary>
<description>1 MHz is a podcast for lovers of vintage 8-bit Apple II computers including the Apple II, II+, IIe, IIc.  We even show the original Apple 1 and that newfangled IIgs some love. The latest in Apple retrocomputing news plus vintage software and retro computer hardware reviews</description>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Carrington Vanston</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>feedback@monsterfeet.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/images/itunes.jpg" />
<itunes:category text="Technology">
<itunes:category text="Tech News" />
</itunes:category>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>

<item>
<title>1 MHz episode 14</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 14: Bureaucracy</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>1 MHz is back to shout a quick hello before KansasFest 2011. Meanwhile, Anthony Martino and Henry Courbis say their goodbyes as UltimateApple2 and ReactiveMicro both go on hiatus. But then Henry Courbis says hello again almost immediately by scanning the Apple Service Technical Procedures Manuals and tossing them to apple2scans.net for hosting. I also take a quick gander at AppleIIGo, a new Apple II emulator written in Java that can run on (among other things) mobile phones and modern web browsers. Then I go in search of the poetic and lyrical in video games with Chris Lepine's Artful Gamer. Finally, I get tangled in hilarious red tape with Douglas Adams and Infocom's oh-so-funny and oh-so-difficult game Bureaucracy.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_014.mp3" length="13103395" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_014.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>27:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,KansasFest,Apple Service Technical Procedures Manuals,apple2scans,AppleIIGo,emulator,Infocom,Bureaucracy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz episode 13</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 13: In Search of the Most Amazing Thing</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>There's a new Apple II podcast on the block, as well as a new podcast for vintage computer enthusiasts: I lend my ear to Open Apple, and lend my voice to the Retro Computing Roundtable.  KansasFest 2011 registrations kick off with the announcement of a cool hands-on session to build your own Apple II MP3 card with the help of Vince Briel. Ewen Wannop reclassifies his aptly named NiftySpell NDA as freeware. And finally, I go In Search Of The Most Amazing Thing...twice!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_013.mp3" length="15252750" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_013.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>31:41</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,KansasFest,Vince Briel,NiftySpell,In Search Of The Most Amazing Thing</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz episode 12</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 12: Wasteland</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Krue releases the TreeHugger GS/OS Printer Port driver, but will you dare to install version 0.0? The daredevilry continues as you risk blowing your mind when you view the Visual 6502 emulator. For less risky but no less enjoyable online ogling, check out Dr. Matt Barton's book excerpt about LucasArts adventure games called The Maniac in the Mansion. And then come with me on a journey to the post apocalyptic world of Wasteland where we'll fight mutants, build robots and learn to repair toasts. Finally, I track down the rare and elusive Wasteland Survival Guide for the Apple II, which just makes me want to play Wasteland one more time.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_012.mp3" length="25415986" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_012.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 14:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>35:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,TreeHugger,GS/OS,Matt Barton,LucasArts,Wasteland Survival Guide</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz episode 11</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 11: The Curse of Crowley Manor</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>How much is a new, unopened IIc worth...and would you open it once you got it home? For Dan Budiac the answers are "more than $2,600" and "yes" respectively, which is why his purchase (and unboxing) of an Apple IIc made headlines this month. Also in this episode, a web server hosted on an Apple IIe, plus a list of servers on other ancient Apple hardware. Also, I reminisce about the AppleCat modem, and point you to a pair of Apple II articles by Ken Gagne for Computerworld. And just as I recorded this episode Reactive Micro announced a new service to upgrade your Transwarp GS to as fast as 18.75 MHz. Finally, I play the graphical adventure game The Curse of Crowley Manor, and I do indeed feel cursed while I play it.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_011.mp3" length="14900818" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_011.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>30:58</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,Dan Budiac,AppleCat modem,Transwarp GS,The Curse of Crowley Manor</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz Episode 10</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 10: Apple Panic</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>A brief (for me) show this month as I rush to get ready for KansasFest. In this episode, I take a look at the announcement of two new ways to transfer disk images from a 'modern' computer to an Apple II: ADTPro software, which finally hits version 1.0.0 after a year in beta, and the BlueFlash card, which is vaporware at the moment but looks tremendously exciting. I also take a look at a way to make an Apple II act as a dumb terminal for Mac OS X.  After that, I listen to some modern music made on a vintage Apple. Finally, I review the game Apple Panic, which gets a big thumbs down. Then it's time to pack up my new two wheeler and head towards Kansas City...slowly.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_010.mp3" length="9424251" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_010.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2007 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>19:33</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,KansasFest,ADTPro,BlueFlash,Apple Panic</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz Episode 9</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 9: Hollywood Hijinx</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Another extended break, but now I'm back, I'm bad, I'm nation-wide. In this episode, I try to sort out when the Apple II really turned 30...and whether Retro Thing and Retrocomputing Times are going to have to wrestle shirtless to Star Trek fight music. Also, I take a gander at the new Apple ][ Incider game review column before giving a highly professional analysis (read: big bunch of made up nonsense) of the Jobs and Gates interview at the recent All Things Digital conference. The review this month is of a classic Infocom text adventure, Hollywood Hijinx, whose author was put on trial by his fellow employees for goldfish homicide. Finally, I ask your advice about what I should drive to Kansas next month.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_009.mp3" length="13513188" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2007 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>28:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,Retro Thing,Retrocomputing Times,All things Digital,Infocom,Hollywood Hijinx</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz Episode 8</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 8: Black Magic, and Undiscoverd Galaxy</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>February's episode brings the usual batch of news and reviews, but this time from a different location: a hotel room in Vancouver. I do my best to put together a show from my notes alone without internet access to lean on. I also mix some hotel recordings with at-home stuff from both before and after the trip, just to see if you can tell which is which. In the Apple II news section, I talk about Juiced.GS's call for both new scriveners and new subscribers, as well as Device Side Data's pending release of a drive that will let you mount vintage computer floppies on modern Macs and PCs. I also watch a 1984 video of Woz walking through the Time Tunnel of the Apple Historical Collection. As for reviews, I finally tell you about Black Magic, the action-adventure-RPG game by Peter Ward that's been kicking my butt for months. I also rip the shrinkwrap off another sealed vintage game, this time Undiscovered Galaxy from K-TEK Video Software (AKA K-TEL, the guys and gals behind Hooked on Classics and the Mini Pops). Finally, I wrap up the first episode of 2007 with 5 predictions for the Apple II in the coming year.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_008.mp3" length="18571461" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2007 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>38:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,Juiced.GS,Device Side Data,Apple Historical Collection,Black Magic,Undiscoverd Galaxy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz Episode 7</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 7: No Reviews is Good Reviews</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>After skipping a month, 1 MHz returns with a vengeance. Well, maybe not a vengeance so much as an determined scowl. In addition to the scowl, I've also got a theme: failure. Failure to podcast, failure to review new software, and failure to mail out some overdue packages. But there's also some success to report on, even if it's not my own. A2Central has successfully launched both a new web site and a new BBS, and InTrec has successfully kept it's award winning ProTERM software alive for decades (now at a new low price with a spiffy new web site on the way). There aren't any software reviews in this episode (remember the theme?) there are a few Apple II related videos I can point you toward. You'll learn about a new fad called Electronic Mail (I remain unconvinced), brace your ears against Irene Cara singing the Apple theme song, and even see an Apple II up for grabs on the Price is Right.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_007.mp3" length="14157648" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>29:25</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,A2Central,ProTERM,Apple II Forever,Apple II on the Price Is Right</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz Episode 6</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 6: Apple II DiskGuide, and Portal</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>It's another end-of-the-month episode, with the October podcasting fun delayed a bit due to food poisoning. In this episode I share the tale of how I learned I was nigh invulnerable (like The Tick!), and I discuss both the storied past of the Replica 1 ROM and how you can build your own Replica 1 in an upcoming VCF workshop. Two dot-org domains offer up a wealth of vintage Apple goodies: 1,100 disk images at VirtualApple.org, and dozens of complete books at AtariArchives.org (don't be fooled by the Atari name: there's Apple II gold in them thar hills). David Szetela is announced as the keynote speaker for KansasFest 2007, while back here at 1 MHz HQ I announce the winners of the first Cartoon Head Cookie Jar software give-away. Finally, I review the minimalist but handy Apple II DiskGuide, and the unique computer novel Portal.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_006.mp3" length="16849928" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>35:01</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,VCF workshop,VirtualApple.org,AtariArchives.org,Cartoon Head Cookie Jar,Portal</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz Episode 5</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 5: Jam Session; Transylvania; Ballyoo</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In this long delayed episode I watch a pair of online videos that relate to the Apple II: one about clones, and one about hacking. I also find out there were once over 200 clones of the Apple II, while there are now two clones of the Apple 1. I also summarize--and muse about--the recently announced changes with Syndicomm Online and A2Central.com. This month's reviews include Jam Session for the IIgs, and a pair of adventure games: Transylvania and Ballyhoo. Also, I announce the Cartoon Head Cookie Jar software give away contest so you can take these boxes of Apple II software off my hands. </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_005.mp3" length="27172481" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_005.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>56:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,Apple II clones,Jam Session,Translyvania,Ballyhoo,Infocom</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz Episode 4</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 4: Dondra</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In this episode I announce a new podcast by somebody whose name is suspiciously like my own, and discuss another upcoming Apple II podcast. I also lament my non-attendance at KansasFest while pointing you to the field reports of those who were lucky enough to attend this year. A new universal binary Apple emulator for Mac OS X called Sweet16 makes the news, as do upgraded versions of CiderPress, SAFE 2, the tiny Contiki operating system, and a USB-equipped Replica 1.  Reviews include a look  at the Sudoku Solver, but do not include the promised Infocom game. But I do take the wraps off a brand new Apple II game...literally! After a 19 year wait, I RIP THE SHRINKWRAP OFF a pristine, sealed game from 1987. (The screams of collectors can be heard all across the land from a thousand parents' basements.) And what does any of this have to do with a mysteriously disappearing computer store? Tune in and find out!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_004.mp3" length="15894918" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_004.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 6 Aug 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>33:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,KansasFest,CiderPress,Contiki,Dondra</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz Episode 3</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 3: Micro Adventure #1 Space Attack; Escape!; Head On</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>I jealously look on as everyone else prepares to attend fun events like KansasFest and the Vintage Computer Festival Midwest, while at the same time the Big 8 Management Board prepares to pull the plug on two Apple II newsgroups. Apple emulation goes walkabout with the announcement of AppleIIGo for MIDP 2.0 compatible mobile phones, and Apple hackers go thinkabout with the announcement of the A.P.P.L.E 2006 Programming Contest. In the reviews, the fun first stage of Escape! is compared to the unplayable later stages, and the search is on for an accelerator button in the arcade port of Head On. This month's big find, though, is Micro Adventure #1: Space Attack, a terrific introduction to computer programming in the form of young adult novel.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_003.mp3" length="17225032" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_003.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 2 Jul 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>35:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,Vintage Computer Festival Midwest,Micro Adventure,Space Attack,Head On,Escape!</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz Episode 2</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 2: Lode Runner; Jungle Safari</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Apple II news this month includes a pair of updated emulators as both AppleWin and Virtual ][ get new features. The Replica 1 prepares an update of its own with an announced Special Edition model coming soon. GSE-Reactive announces an Apple IIe enhancement kit, and the Uthernet card from A2RetroSystems sells out. Rounding out the news is the release of the Apple Game Server, and Steve Wozniak becomes a co-author with his forthcoming book iWoz. This month's episode also has a glowing review of Lode Runner, and a less than glowing review of Jungle Safari.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_002.mp3" length="13722734" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_002.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 4 Jun 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>28:31</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,Steve Wozniak,iWoz,Lode Runner,Jungle Safari</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>1 MHz Episode 1</title>
<itunes:author>Carrington Vanston</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Episode 1: Introduction; Tass Times in Tonetown</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Welcome to very tip of "the long tail." In the inaugural episode of the 1 MHz podcast, I introduce myself and ramble on about my own 8-bit Apple history. There's also a review of what was I believe was the first commercially available game for the IIgs: a graphical text adventure game called Tass Times in Tonetown. Also in this show: Joy Of Tech celebrates Apple's 30th anniversary with an edible Apple 1, a IIgs Internet Starter Kit from Syndicomm makes it easy to get online, and the Vintage Computer Festival East rolls into New Jersey.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_001.mp3" length="13671033" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://monsterfeet.com/1mhz/shows/1mhz_001.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>28:25</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Carrington,Vanston,Apple II,retrocomputing,vintage,computers,8bit,Tass Times in Tonetown,Infocom,text adventure games,interactive fiction</itunes:keywords>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
