<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!--ACCF data feed by Del Olds on 6/6/2012 2:00:02 AM-->
<rss version="2.0">
  <AtheyChannel>
    <title>ACCF Recent Messages</title>
    <link>http://www.atheycreek.com</link>
    <description>complete library of online messages</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>(C) 2006 Athey Creek Christian Fellowship</copyright>
    <docs>http://www.atheycreek.com/rss</docs>
    <lastBuildDate>Wednesday, June 06, 2012</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Through the Bible Study - 1 Timothy 5 | #M1-600 | 5/30/2012 | Wednesday</title>
      <description>In 1 Timothy 5, Paul talks about how we are to treat others, specifically how we are to treat the elderly and young women in the church. Brett discusses the importance of purity as it relates to relationships with single men and women.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/M1-600.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>fathers, defense, self-defense, purity, widows, stay at home moms, homemakers, working mothers, dating</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let No Man Despise Thy Youth - 1 Timothy 4:12 | #S1-580 | 5/27/2012 | Sunday</title>
      <description>Today, we look at 1 Timothy 4:12, where we see Paul encourage the youth of Timothy's church. Pastor Brett talks about the importance of both the youth and the elderly in the church.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/S1-580.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>youth, ministry, kids, youth ministry, young people, elderly people, Joseph, Daniel</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Through the Bible Study - 1 Timothy 3:8-4 | #M1-599 | 5/23/2012 | Wednesday</title>
      <description>Last week we studied the role of the elder in the church.  In the latter half of 1 Timothy 3, Paul discusses the role of a deacon, and Brett talks about how we utilize Paul's words to Timothy at Athey Creek.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/M1-599.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>church leadership, leadership, deacon, ministry, volunteering, alcohol, drinking, finances, accountability, sound doctrine, deaconess</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctrines of Devils - 1 Timothy 4:1-6 | #S1-579 | 5/20/2012 | Sunday</title>
      <description>In 1 Timothy 4, Paul warns Timothy to look out for three things that could break up a church: demonism, relativism, and legalism.  Pastor Brett elaborates on these three things, how they are seen in our culture today, and what we as Christians can do to combat them.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/S1-579.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>the devil, Satan, hell, last days, demonism, relativism, legalism, spirituality, conscience, tolerance, abortion, homosexuality, Catholocism, alcohol, smoking</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Through the Bible Study - 1 Timothy 3:1-7 | #M1-598 | 5/16/2012 | Wednesday</title>
      <description>Tonight, we study 1 Timothy 3, where Paul takes a closer look at the importance of having elders in the church, what the role of an elder should look like, and the qualifications of being an elder.  Pastor Brett talks about how the elders at Athey Creek are appointed, and how we use this section of scripture to go about that process.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/M1-598.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>creation, bishop, pastor, elder, minister, leadership, alcohol, drinking, qualifications</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother's Day 2012 - 1 Timothy 2:15 | #G-185 | 5/13/2012 | Sunday</title>
      <description>This morning we continue to look at 1 Timothy 2, where Paul discusses women's roles in the church.  We pay particular attention to verse 15, where Paul says that women will be "saved in childbearing", and we take a closer look at what that really means.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/G-185.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>Mother's Day, women, Mary, childbirth, sin, roles of women, salvation</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Behave In Church - 1 Timothy 3:14-15 | #S1-578 | 5/12/2012 | Sunday</title>
      <description>As we continue our study through 1 Timothy, we take a closer look at chapter 3, where Paul talks to Timothy about how (not if) we are to go to church. Pastor Brett talks about the importance of preparing to receive the Word before going to church.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/S1-578.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>church, tradition, denominations, organized religion, humility</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Through the Bible Study - 1 Timothy 2:9-14 | #M1-597 | 5/9/2012 | Wednesday</title>
      <description>We take some time to see what Paul has to say about women's roles in the church.  It can be really easy to take something out of context in the Bible.  Tonight, we focus on what Paul's words to the women of the church mean, and how they apply to the women of the church today.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/M1-597.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>women, women's roles, men's roles, church, modesty, clothing, Dorcas, salvation, women's liberation</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True Godliness - 1 Timothy 2:2 | #S1-577 | 5/6/2012 | Sunday</title>
      <description>There are many interpretations of what the word "godliness" means.  In 1 Timothy 2, Paul talks about what it means to be godly as a Christian.  Today, Pastor Brett talks about godliness and how we can be godly in this day and age.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/S1-577.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>godliness, ministry, holiness, Catholicism, salvation</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Through the Bible Study - 1 Timothy 1:17-2:15 | #M1-596 | 5/2/2012 | Wednesday</title>
      <description>As we continue our study through Paul's letter to Timothy, we see Paul talk to Timothy about some of the issues Timothy was having with his church.  These are issues that are definitely applicable to the way things are today, and Pastor Brett discusses how we can relate these things to our lives.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/M1-596.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>praise, faith, salvation, baptism, Mormonism, mediator, prayer, women in ministry, women's roles</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First of All…Prayer - 1 Timothy 2:1-3 | #S1-576 | 4/29/2012 | Sunday</title>
      <description>Today, we take a moment to talk about prayer.  Paul talks with Timothy about prayer, and we see an excellent Old Testament depiction of how we are to pray in Daniel 6.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/S1-576.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>prayer, lifting hands, supplication, intercession, thanksgiving, thankfulness, Daniel</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Through the Bible Study - 1 Timothy 1:1-18 | #M1-595 | 4/25/2012 | Wednesday</title>
      <description>Tonight, we delve further into Paul's first letter to Timothy.  We discover that the intent of Paul's letter was to encourage Timothy, but also to instruct him in the ways of the Lord.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/M1-595.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>doctrine, Micah, church, apostle, hope, Timothy, legalism, vain jangling, the law</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Sinner - 1 Timothy 1:12 | #S1-575 | 4/22/2012 | Sunday</title>
      <description>This Sunday, we begin our study in 1 Timothy.  Here, we see Paul discuss with Timothy the magnitude of salvation and what it means to be saved.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/S1-575.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>sin, salvation, saints, humility, judgment, comparing, legalism</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Through the Bible Study - 2 Thessalonians 2-3 | #M1-594 | 4/18/2012 | Wednesday</title>
      <description>As we wrap up our study through Paul's second letter to the church at Thessalonica, we learn about the importance of avoiding bitterness.  We also continue to learn about end times, predestination, and salvation.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/M1-594.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>justice, vengeance, rapture, salvation, predestination, sin, homosexuality, bitterness</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The End: Description of the Antichrist - 2 Thessalonians 2:1-12 | #S1-574 | 4/15/2012 | Sunday</title>
      <description>This morning, we delve further into 2 Thessalonians as it relates to end times.  We turn our attention to what the Bible says about the antichrist, a man of sin and a son of perdition.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/S1-574.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>end times, antichrist, world leaders, Iran, Mahdi, tribulation, perdition, pride</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Through the Bible Study - 2 Thessalonians 1 | #M1-593 | 4/11/2012 | Wednesday</title>
      <description>Tonight, we begin our study through Paul's second letter to the church at Thessalonica.  Pastor Brett gives us a little history as to why this letter was written.  Additionally, we see Paul encourage the Thessalonians in praise, in promise, and in prayer.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/M1-593.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>hell, heaven, false teaching, false prophets, correction</keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easter Sunday 2012 - Acts 17:16-34 | #G-184 | 4/8/2012 | Sunday</title>
      <description>On this Resurrection Sunday, we celebrate Jesus' incredible gift of salvation that He gave us on the cross.  Pastor Brett spends this morning discussing the mockers of the Christian faith, the procrastinators, and those who believed.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.atheycreek.com/media/G-184.lq.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <author>Brett Meador</author>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <keywords>death, resurrection, crucifixion, Easter, Paul, communion</keywords>
    </item>
  </AtheyChannel>
</rss>