<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
 
<channel>
<title>Necromancers of the Northwest</title>
<link>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/podcast.html</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<itunes:subtitle>A Gaming Podcast</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Every Friday, Necromancers of the Northwest puts out a half-hour-long podcast devoted to gaming and entertainment. With reviews of various gaming products, discussion of game design, tips and tricks on anything from how to make your characters more effective to how to run a campaign, and a little dash of humor and fun as well.</itunes:summary>
<description>Reviews, humor, and tips and tricks for tabletop roleplaying.</description>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Alex Riggs</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>ariggs@necromancers-online.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image 
href="http://www.necromancers-online.com/img/itunesbanner.jpg" />
<itunes:category text="Games &amp; Hobbies">
<itunes:category text="Other Games"/>
</itunes:category>

<item>
<title>June 1st, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>The Wyrm Turns</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In a slightly-delayed Dragon Week installment, this podcast features a review of Mongoose Publishing's "A Slayer's Guide to Dragons," as well as a discussion on ways to make using dragons a more fun, memorable, and above all easy thing for GMs to do.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120601.mp3" length="30388739" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120601.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 1 June 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:31:39</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, Gygax, drake, chromatic, metallic</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>May 25th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Speculative Horizons</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We celebrate the beginning of the D&D Next playtests by taking a look at some of the design goals that Wizards of the Coast has been putting out regarding the upcoming edition, and providing our own commentary and insight about them.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120525.mp3" length="44441781" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120525.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:46:17</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, speculation, design, goals, 5th, edition, next</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>May 18th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Encounters and Enchantments</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In this week's podcast, Alex reviews a product that might very well finally put an end to the debate about whether or not to use random encounters in your game. After that, we spend some time examining different approaches a GM can take when it comes to letting his party purchase magic items, and the pros and cons of each.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120518.mp3" length="29822822" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120518.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:31:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, random, magic, item, encounter, treasure, merchant, route</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>May 4th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Servants of Chaos</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In the first of our new, sleeker, more compact, travel-size podcasts, we focus on bringing you the random, in the form of a special, feature-length Seed to Story, where, with a little random inspiration, we create not just an adventure hook, but also a magic item, and an NPC. It's a triple threat!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120504.mp3" length="34720049" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120504.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 4 May 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:36:09</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, random, magic, item, seed, story, plot, adventure, hook, NPC, character, backstory</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>April 27th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Visions of the Future</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This week's podcast begins with a review of Encyclopaedia Arcane: Divination, a book by Mongoose Publishing devoted entirely to divination magic, and Alex will walk you through it and let you know whether or not the stars are right for you to pick it up. After that, we take a look into the future and give you the inside scoop on some upcoming products coming from the Necromancers of the Northwest workshop.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120427.mp3" length="61734844" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120427.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:04:18</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, magic, divination, mongoose, diviner, crystal ball, foretell, demon, summoning, gun, pistol, firearm, bandito, ring, ebon, vault</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>April 20th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Mad Magics</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This week's podcast kicks off like so many with a review, this time of a book by Alderac Entertainment Group, entitled "Magic." This book attempts to provide well over a dozen new types of magic and put the wonder and excitement back into spellcasting, and Alex takes a closer look and lets you know how well they fared. After that, Josh continues the Bestiary Breakdown segment, continuing through the Bestiary 3 one monster at a time. This podcast also sees the return of Optimal Options as Josh takes a look at some of the fighter archetypes from Ultimate Combat and lets you know which ones to take and which ones to pass up. Finally, we both take a look at our most recent release, A Necromancer's Grimoire: The Wonders of Alchemy, and talk about why it was designed the way it was and what has us so excited about it.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120420.mp3" length="60063843" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120420.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:02:33</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, magic, alchemy, wonders, AEG, fighter, archetype, potion, serum, infusion</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>April 13th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Mount Week</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We begin the Mount Week Podcast with a review of one of the few mount-centered books for Pathfinder/3.5, entitled In the Saddle: Fur and Feather Volume I, and our final verdict may surprise you. Next we move on to Best Beasts, where we determine once and for all whether or not the nightmare is cool. Then we give some tips and tricks on how to use mounts in your game, from ways to make them more interesting and memorable, to how to get your PCs excited about them, and so on. Then, in Optimal Options, Alex takes a look at the Mounted Combat feat, and its related feats, and tries to dispel a few myths about what you need to do to make an effective mounted character. Finally, Josh wraps things up with 10 interesting mounts with character.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120413.mp3" length="57667265" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120413.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:00:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, horse, camel, mount, knight</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>


<item>
<title>April 6th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Podcast Ascension</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This week's podcast kicks off with a review of the book Bits of the Boulevard, a flavorful product by Tabletop Adventures. Then the ongoing saga of John the Grinning Skull Morgan continues to unfold, followed by a continuation of Bestiary Breakdown, as Alex takes a look at the ahuizotl, the akhlut, and the alraune. Then Josh gives a preview of Mount Week, discussing some ways to make mounts more interesting in your game. Finally, Alex takes a look at the Magic: the Gathering set Dark Ascension, discussing some general design lessons that can be learned by examining its contents.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120406.mp3" length="55661478" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120406.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 6 Apr 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:57:58</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, magic, mtg, dark, ascension, boulevard, city</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>March 30th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>The King of Podcasts</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>For Nobility Week, Alex takes a closer look at Pendragon, a different kind of tabletop system that allows you to play as a knight of the round table, build a dynasty, and perform chivalrous and heroic deeds. Then we take a closer look at preconceptions and stereotypes about nobles, and how you can use those in your game. The Best Beasts segment returns, with a look at whether or not the king of dinosaurs is really as cool as he claims. Alex then introduces a new segment, Bestiary Breakdown, where he takes a closer look at each of the monsters from the Bestiary 3, giving useful information for GMs who might be interested in using such monsters. Then Josh provides 10 interesting ideas for noble NPCs that you can drop into your game. Finally, in Seed to Story, some treants are in trouble, or so it seems.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120330.mp3" length="61069452" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120330.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:03:36</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, noble, knight, king, arthur, pendragon, treant</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>March 23rd, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Mage's Digest</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Considering adding some cheap magic to your game? This week's podcast is your friend, as it focuses primarily on reviews, from Ronin Arts' 101 Arcane Material Components to several installments of Super Genius Games' Loot for Less series. Also included is the next installment in the ongoing series of John "the Grinning Skull" Morgan, and a Seed for Story revolving around a strange mist causing havoc in a large city.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120323.mp3" length="64340818" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120323.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:07:01</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, magic, component, loot, review</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>March 16th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Conjuring Excitement</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>For our Conjuration Week podcast, we begin with a couple of magic-themed reviews, as Josh takes a look at both Ars Metamagic and 101 Spell Variants. Then, in Best Beasts, we debate the merits of the succubus. The bulk of the podcast is an in-depth breakdown of the various monsters available with the summon monster spells, with a view at getting the most bang for your spellcasting buck. Finally, we provide descriptions for 10 interesting and unique outsiders with personality, which can help to spice up your next casting of lesser planar binding, or any other outsider-themed encounter.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120316.mp3" length="57892126" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120316.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:00:18</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, conjuration, summon, demon</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
</item>
 
<item>
<title>March 9th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>General Outfitters</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This week's podcast begins as the froghemoth gets the Best Beats treatment, and we determine whether it's cool or not. From there, Josh reviews 101 Legendary Treasures of Medieval Europe, and lets you know whether this product is a holy grail, or just another fake sword in a stone. Then, Josh and Alex compete head-to-head, equipping an NPC with what they think is the best array of gear, and then putting him through a series of challenges, with hilarious results. In the latter part of the podcast, we give advice on how to deal with rules lawyers, and our Seed to Story involves lizardfolk mercenary madness.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120309.mp3" length="60044615" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120309.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 9 Mar 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:02:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>March 2nd, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Maidens and Monsters</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>It's Maiden Week at Necromancers of the Northwest, so naturally our podcast starts out as an examination of the cost-effectiveness of the figurines of wondrous power, and a literal look at what's the biggest bang you can get for your 3,000 gp buck. From there, we naturally review the Pathfinder Bestiary 3, determining whether or not this menagerie of monsters is worth your time and money. Eventually we do get around to damsels, providing 10 different interesting distressing situations for your damsel, and then end with a Seed to Story involving a maiden, a wizard, a map, and a magic forge. </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120302.mp3" length="55931479" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120302.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 2 Mar 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:58:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, damsel, maiden</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>February 10th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Sword Week</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In this week's podcast, we take the opportunity to honor everyone's favorite fantasy weapon: the sword. Josh takes a look at a book devoted to magic weapon properties, and we discuss the design behind on of our own sword-themed books, The Ebon Vault: Swords of Legend. Further, we discuss 10 ways to make magic swords more fun and interesting, as well as how to be most effective with your sword in game. It's not all about swords, though, as we begin a short story about a skeletal pirate captain, and our Seed to Story produces a plot where PCs act as guerilla resistance against an invading army. </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120210.mp3" length="69893409" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120210.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:12:48</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, sword</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>

<item>
<title>February 3rd, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>On Villainy</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In this week's podcast, Alex reviews two witch-related 3rd-party books, and both Alex and Josh look at optimal options for ambushes, and the great usefulness of illusory wall. Later on, we examine the ins and outs of villainy, and how to make a good villain. Finally, a look at 10 tips for great evil strongholds, and the podcast wraps up with a Seed to Story about an arcane cold war. </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120203.mp3" length="52918832" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120203.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 3 Feb 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:55:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, evil</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>
 
<item>
<title>January 27th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Abjuration Week</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In honor of Abjuration Week, this week's Necromancers of the Northwest podcast takes a look at magic, defenses, and the places that those two meet. Josh reviews the book 101 1st-level Spells, we take a closer look at the design of Ancient Warriors: Sons of Sparta, and give some insight on some abjuration spells that may have escaped your notice. </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120127.mp3" length="56447661" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120127.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:58:47</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon, abjuration, magic, wizard</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item>
 
<item>
<title>January 20th, 2012</title>
<itunes:author>Alex Riggs and Joshua Zaback</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Grand Beginning</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In the very first Necromancers of the Northwest podcast, among other things, Alex reviews the first adventure of the Jade Regent adventure path, we talk about the recent changes to our production schedule, and give an inside look at the production of Advanced Arcana II.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120120.mp3" length="94797478" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.necromancers-online.com/articles/Podcast/2012/20120120.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:38:44</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>D&amp;D, Pathfinder, roleplaying, rpg, tabletop, dice, gaming, hobby, dungeon, dragon</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</item> 

<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>  
</channel>
</rss>

