<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:cf="http://www.microsoft.com/schemas/rss/core/2005">
<channel>
<title>Gary Revel Martin Luther King Jr Assassination Investigation News</title>
  <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news2.xml</link> 
  <description>News of Martin Luther King Jr Assassination Investigation by Gary Revel and more.</description> 
  <language>en-us</language>
  <docs>http://www.garyrevel.com/news2.xml</docs>
  <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2006 14:15:00 PST</pubDate> 
  <lastBuildDate>THU, 28 MAY 2012 16:15:00 CST</lastBuildDate> 
   <generator>Gary Revel</generator> 
  <managingEditor>gary@garyrevel.com (Gary Revel)</managingEditor> 
  <webMaster>gary@garyrevel.com (Gary Revel)</webMaster> 
- <image>
  <title>News of The Gary Revel Investigation of the Assassination of Martin Luther King Jr.</title> 
  <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news2.xml</link> 
<url>http://www.garyrevel.com/images/gr_logo5.JPG</url> 
  </image>
 - <item>
<title>Letter to the Editor, May 28, 2012, New York, NY USA From Bob Wilson</title>  <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/BobWilsonLettertoEditor.htm</link><description>The last U. S. Government "official" investigation of the murders of JFK and MLK by the House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA) found a probable conspiracy in their deaths. The recommendation of the committee was to have the Dept. of Justice pick up the trial. Their only official undercover investigator, Special Investigator Gary Revel, over the years has continued to bring attention to the facts of the cases and followed up the links he found to the assassination of Robert F. Kennedy. He further found that, like Oswald was a patsy in the JFK assassination and James Earl Ray was a patsy in the MLK assassination, Sirhan Sirhan was also a patsy and not guilty of the murder of RFK.
.</description>  <pubDate>THU, 28 MAY 2012 16:15:00 CST</pubDate><guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/NEWS</guid>
</item> - <item>
<title>Conspired to Kill an opinion and commentary by Gary Revel</title>  <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/conspiredtokill.html</link><description>All the major news organizations in the United States and beyond helped in establishing the lone gunman theory and a cover-up of the conspiracy. One of the methods used by them was to paint anyone who didn't go along with the lie that a lone gunman was the killer as some kind of half witted conspiracy theorist. Many of the major magazine and book publishers worked together with the conspirators and their chosen authors/journalists to publish works that were simply propaganda and used to convince sensible people that anything but the lone gunman scenario was wayward thinking even possibly lunacy. It is sad to say that the operations worked very well because in spite of the facts continuing to make the case that the killings could not have been lone gunman operations many people are still convinced of the lies published and still being promoted by the conspirators' comrades and supporters.</description>  <pubDate>SAT, 26 MAY 2012 14:15:00 CST</pubDate><guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/NEWS</guid>
</item> - <item>
<title>Historical Perspective and Commentary by Gary Revel</title>  <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/perspective1.html</link><description>As I stand on the edge of time that seems to be an arrival of great change and life meaning such as hinted at in times before but not remarkably realized as yet, I am humbled.
My love for America will not die with me. My love for my fellow human being, where-ever and whoever they may be, will never fail regardless of the beat or non-beat of my heart. My love for the beauty and sometimes coarseness of words shall not pass away as they enlighten, encourage, bolster and sometimes discipline our lives. The sound of music, like the stars that shine in the night sky, could only diminish but for the comfort, warmth and brightness of the orchestrations in heaven itself. </description>  <pubDate>SAT, 26 MAY 2012 14:00:00 CST</pubDate><guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/NEWS</guid>
</item> - <item>
<title>MLK Assassination Truth Petition Launched</title>  <link>http://signon.org/sign/face-up-to-the-truth</link><description>The assassination of Martin Luther King Jr. on April 4, 1968 has never been satisfactorily adjudicated. The US Government along with many in the private sector have used murder, threats and financial means to cover the truth up about it and to continue that cover up. We petition the US Government to face up to the truth and admit that high government officials including FBI Director J. Edgar Hoover and President Lyndon Baines Johnson were part of this criminal conspiracy that included members of organized crime and contract agents of the Central Intelligence Agency. </description>  <pubDate>WED, 7 SEP 2011 19:00:00 PST</pubDate><guid>http://www.garyrevel.com</guid>
</item> - <item><title>JFK Assassination Truth Petition Launched</title>  <link>http://www.garyrevel.com</link><description>The assassination of President John F. Kennedy on November 22, 1963 has never been satisfactorily adjudicated. The US Government along with many in the private sector have used murder, threats and financial means to cover up the truth and to continue that cover up. We petition the US Government to face up to that truth and admit that high government officials including FBI Director J. Edgar Hoover and then Vice-President Lyndon Baines Johnson were part of this criminal conspiracy that included members of organized crime and contract agents of the Central Intelligence Agency. </description>  <pubDate>WED, 7 SEP 2011 19:00:00 PST</pubDate><guid>http://www.garyrevel.com</guid>
</item> - <item><title>RFK Assassination Truth Petition Launched</title>  <link>http://www.garyrevel.com</link><description>The assassination of Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy on June 6, 1963 has never been satisfactorily adjudicated. The US Government along with many in the private sector have used murder, threats and financial means to cover up the truth and to continue that cover up. We petition the US Government to face up to that truth and admit that high government officials including FBI Director J. Edgar Hoover and President Lyndon Baines Johnson were part of this criminal conspiracy that included members of organized crime and contract agents of the Central Intelligence Agency.</description>  <pubDate>WED, 7 SEP 2011 19:00:00 PST</pubDate>  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com</guid>
</item> - <item>  <title>Wesley Snipes to do MLK movie based on Code Name Zorro</title>  <link>http://www.cinemablend.com/new/Wesley-Snipes-Planning-A-Film-About-J-Edgar-Hoover-And-Martin-Luther-King-Jr-21340.html</link>  <description>Lately Wesley Snipes is better known as a punchline on NBC sitcoms than for any of his own work-- both 30 Rock and Community have taken gentle jabs in recent episodes  at the actor, who is currently battling the IRS thanks a big pile of unpaid taxes. He's still due to serve a three-year prison sentence for that crime, but he's also got big plans to produce and star in films-- including, as explained to Deadline, a feature about J. Edgar Hoover's smear campaign against Martin Luther King Jr.  Yes, you're reading that right. Even as Clint Eastwood is developing his own biopic about the former FBI chief, Snipes wants to tackle a different side of Hoover's long and storied career, his efforts to tarnish King's reputation through wiretapping and trying to ruin his marriage. There's plenty of documentation about the effort. COINTELPRO was exposed in a book called "Code Name Zorro".  After MLK's "I Have A Dream Speech," the FBI'S COINTEL director William Sullivan wrote to Hoover that "We must mark [King] now, if we have not done so before, as the most dangerous Negro of the future in this nation." Sullivan eventually tried to blow the whistle on the project, but was shot and killed in a so-called "hunting accident" before his book about Hoover could be published.  Snipes is producing under his Maandi Media Productions banner and hopes to play a role of some kind in the Justin Stamm-scripted project, entitled Code Name Zorro based on the book Co-authored by Mark Lane and Dick Gregory.</description>  <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 12:00:00 PST</pubDate>  <guid>http://www.garyreve.com/</guid>
  </item> - <item>
 <title>A Prince and a Gentleman AKA Jack Kershaw</title>   
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/jack_kershaw.html</link>
<description>My friend and associate Jack Kershaw is dead. His role in The Fugitives and the representation of James Earl Ray set a mark for other patriots to reach for.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2010 21:00:00 EST</pubDate>  <guid>http://www.garyreve.com/</guid>
  </item> - <item>
 <title>New York Times-Jack Kershaw is Dead</title>   
<link>http://www.nytimes.com/2010/09/24/us/24kershaw.html</link>
<description>Jack Kershaw, who represented James Earl Ray as he fought to overturn his conviction in the assassination of the Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., arguing that Ray was an innocent participant in a conspiracy led by a mysterious figure named Raul, died Sept. 7. in Nashville. He was 96.  By Douglas Martin</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 5:00:00 EST</pubDate>  <guid>http://www.nytimes.com/</guid>
  </item>
 - <item>
 <title>CNN-James Polk Mistaken on MLK Assassination</title>   
<link>http://garyrevel.wordpress.com/</link>
<description>Pulitzer Prize Winner and Senior Producer for CNN, James Polk makes mistakes in his articles and CNN Specials about the assassination of Martin Luther King JR.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 5:00:00 CST</pubDate>  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/</guid>
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>Final Report - Martin Luther King Jr Assassination Investigation</title>   
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/final_report.html</link>
<description>The final report of the Gary Revel investigation of the assassination of Martin Luther King JR.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 8:00:00 CST</pubDate>  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/final_report.html</guid>
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>Martin Luther King Jr Assassination and the Music of Gary Revel-Commentary</title>   
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/musicandmlkassassination.html</link>
<description>As negotiations for the making of a movie about my investigation of the assassination of Martin Luther King Jr. proceed I have taken a moment to do some reflection. I ask myself, Just how did I get entangled in this highly controversial and emotionally impacting subject?</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 6:00:00 CST</pubDate>  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/musicandmlkassassination.html</guid>
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>Obama and Assassination</title>   <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/Obama%20and%20Assassination.html</link>
<description>Gary Revel opinion on the possibility of an assassination of Senator/Presidential Candidate Barack Obama</description> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2008 9:00:00 CST</pubDate>  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/Obama%20and%20Assassination.html</guid> 
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>Martin Luther King Jr. Assassination the US Government and Hoover's FBI</title>   <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/leutrell_16.html</link>
<description>Leutrell Osborne, Sr., has interviewed Ray Kohlman, Mike Ruppert, former Congresswoman Cynthia Mc Kinney, Catherine Austin Fitts, Gary Revel and more to shape this news commentary-opinion about the MLK assassination. </description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 5:00:00 PST</pubDate> 
  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/leutrell_16.html</guid> 
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>Jongleur Music Pictures to make JFK MLK RFK Assassination Trilogy</title>   <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/press_release_14.html</link>
<description>The Assassination of JFK, MLK, and RFK will be the subjects of 3 motion pictures planned by Jongleur Music Pictures. The feature length pics will be based on the investigation of the assassinations by Special Investigator Gary Revel. </description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 5:00:00 PST</pubDate> 
  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/press_release_14.html</guid> 
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>Senator Christopher Dodd and the Continuing Coverup of the JFK/MLK Assassinations</title>   <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/press_release_13.html</link>
<description>Although I have found it to be disconcerting over the years and even now, the reality that Congressman Christopher Dodd was a part of the HSCA for the purpose of limiting it's investigation and preventing the truth from being made known is clear to me. </description> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 10:15:00 PST</pubDate> 
  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/press_release_13.html</guid> 
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>JFK Assassination Bullet Fragment Analysis Prove Second Shooter</title>   <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/press_release_11.html</link>
<description>A December 2007 report on a scientific analysis of the 5 bullet fragments from the JFK assassination finds that more than one shooter had to be involved. </description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 11:15:00 PST</pubDate> 
  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/press_release_11.html</guid> 
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>Santo Trafficante And The Business Of Murder With The CIA</title>   <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/press_release_10.html</link>
<description>An Executive Session of the House of Representatives Subcommittee on the Assassination of John F. Kennedy began it's meeting. HSCA Chairman Louis Stokes, Representative L. Richardson Preyer, Representative Walter E. Fauntroy, Christopher Dodd and Stewart B. McKinney were there to hear the testimony of Mafia Boss/CIA Assassination Contractor Santo Trafficante regarding his knowledge of the assassinations of President John F. Kennedy and Nobel Peace Prize Winner Martin Luther King Jr. </description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 12:15:00 CST</pubDate> 
  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/press_release_10.html</guid> 
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>President Lyndon Baines Johnson Statue With Gary Revel</title>   <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/lbj_mlk.html</link>
<description>Photograph of Gary Revel standing with the statue of President Lyndon Baines Johnson. The Martin Luther King Jr. Assassination Investigation has found that President Johnson was a criminal associate of those who planned, executed and covered up the assassination of Martin Luther King Jr.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2008 7:15:00 PST</pubDate> 
  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/lbj_mlk.html</guid> 
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>CNN Once Again Tries To Convict James Earl Ray Of MLK Jr. Assassination</title>   <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/press_release_9.html</link>
<description>On April 3, 2008 a CNN Special presented by Soledad O'brien on the assassination of Martin Luther King Jr. tried in vain to convince us that James Earl Ray singularly escaped from Missouri State Prison and tracked MLK from coast to coast before finally miraculously having MLK come out on the balcony of the Lorraine Motel at just the exact moment that Ray was in the bathroom window taking aim to shoot and kill him.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 3 Apr 2008 10:30:00 PST</pubDate> 
  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/press_release_9.html</guid> 
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>Killing of Martin Luther King Jr and the 40th Anniversary</title>   <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/press_release_8.html</link>
<description>40th Anniversary of the MLK Assassination Commentary by Gary Revel. 40 years after the killing of Martin Luther King Jr. and still the disturbing realities of his murder and cover-up plague the American consciousness.</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 12:30:00 EST</pubDate> 
  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/press_release_8.html</guid> 
  </item>
 - <item>
  <title>TO LIVE OR MAYBE NOT on sale at AMAZON dot COM</title>   <link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/press_release_7.html</link>
<description>TO LIVE OR MAYBE NOT is the book that assembles and brings stories of the life of Gary Revel to the public for the first time ever.  It is published and for sale today atamazon dot com.  The stories include events related to the Gary Revel investigation of the assassination of Martin Luther King Jr.</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 12:25:00 CST</pubDate> 
  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/press_release_7.html</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
  <title>THEY SLEW THE DREAMER music video released</title> 
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/Music%20Videos/They%20Slew%20The%20Dreamer.wmv</link> 
  <description>Martin Luther King assassination uncovered in this music video by Gary Revel.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2007 10:30:00 PST</pubDate>  <guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/Music%20Videos/They%20Slew%20The%20Dreamer.wmv</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>Martin Luther King Jr. (JFK, RFK) Assassination Investigation</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/index.html</link>
<description>The Investigation of the assassination of Martin Luther King Jr., President John F. Kennedy and Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy.</description>
 <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2006 11:47:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/index.html</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>Podcast Richard Sprague Introduces Himself to James Earl Ray</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/audio/hscaid2_march_22id.mp3</link>
<description>Richard Sprague, Chief Counsel of HSCA Introduces Himself to James Earl Ray March 22, 1977. The meeting was in a conference room behind the walls of Brushy Mountain Prison. Deputy Chief Counsel-HSCA Robert Lehner, Chief MLK Assassination Investigator-HSCA Ed Evans, James Earl Ray Attorney Jack Kershaw, James Earl Ray Attorney Mary Kershaw and Special Investigator on Assassinations Gary Revel were also present.  Gary Revel officially began his investigation of the JFK and MLK assassinations at this time.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2006 11:47:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/audio/hscaid2_march_22id.mp3</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>New Questions About The 3 Tramps of Dealy Plaza November 22, 1963 JFK Assassination</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/JFK/tramps.htm</link>
<description>The so-called 3 tramps were photographed in Dealy Plaza November 22, 1963 shortly after President John F. Kennedy's assassination.  They were identified as being CIA agents or at least
back pocket agents that had CIA credentials at one time or another. The most convincing have been the identities of Frank Sturgis or Daniel Carswell as the first tramp in line and Carswell or Sturgis as the 2nd tramp. Most who have studied these photos at length are quite convinced that the 3rd tramp is E. Howard Hunt.</description>
 <pubDate>MON, 24 Apr 2006 8:25:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/JFK/tramps.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>The Leutrell Osborne Interview of Gary Revel</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/Leutrell_interview1.htm</link>
<description>The exclusive interview of Gary Revel by Leutrell Osborne related to Gary's investigation of the assassination of Martin Luther King Jr. and how his song THEY SLEW THE DREAMER became an important part of it.</description>
 <pubDate>WED, 19 Apr 2006 8:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/Leutrell_interview1.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>James Earl Ray Pleads Guilty to King Assassination-Kind Of</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/ray_court1.htm</link>
<description>Shelby County Register of Deeds Posts Court Documents Proving King Murder Case A Judicial Nightmare (James Earl Ray Pleads Guilty-Kind Of)</description>
 <pubDate>TUE, 18 Apr 2006 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/ray_court1.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>News Advisory:  An Interview of Gary Revel by Leutrell Osborne</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/pre_leutrell_interview1.htm</link>
<description>News Advisory:  An Interview of Gary Revel by Leutrell Osborne.  Gary Revel has agreed to an exclusive interview with Leutrell Osborne related to his investigation of the assassination of Martin Luther King Jr. and how his song THEY SLEW THE DREAMER became an important part of it.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2006 18:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/pre_leutrell_interview1.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>Jack McNeil's MLK Sing For King Brings 1965 Voting Rights Act To Mind</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/mcneil1.htm</link>
<description>He has been a Tennessee State Legislator, a Memphis City Councilman and is a practicing attorney.  His name is Jack McNeil and juxtaposed to his legal profession writes poetry and recently has written a play about the greatest of our Civil Rights Leaders, Martin Luther King Jr.  He produced a trial run of the play last year and was intrigued to hear some suggest that he use it as a platform for advancing the Anti-War agenda that had become part of MLK's public stand before his death.  Mr. McNeil says that he is not anti-war and does not believe the Anti-War stance is the importance of King's legacy</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2006 08:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/mcneil1.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>New Questions About E. Howard Hunt And MLK Assassination</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/a_mlk_investigate2.htm</link>
<description>Veteran Central Intelligence Agency Case Officer Leutrell Osborne Has New Questions About E. Howard Hunt And MLK Assassination</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2006 08:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/news/a_mlk_investigate2.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>Leutrell Osborne Finds Disturbing New Details Investigating Martin Luther King Jr. Assassination</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/a_mlk_investigate1.htm</link>
<description>When Leutrell Osborne learned about the deaths of people associated with the investigation of the assassination of Martin Luther King Jr. such as the two judges and six FBI Special Agents, he said "There has to be fire where there is smoke."</description>
 <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2006 15:30:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/a_mlk_investigate1.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>Secret Files That Would Have Proven James Earl Ray Not Guilty</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/secret_files.htm</link>
<description>Secret Files That Would Have Proven James Earl Ray Not Guilty were asked for during the 1977 investigation of the MLK assassination but never released.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2006 10:15:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/secret_files.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>Sirhan Sirhan Utterly Useless Parole Hearing March 15, 2006</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/sirhan.htm</link>
<description>Sirhan Sirhan in prison for shooting Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Utterly Useless Parole Hearing March 15, 2006</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2006 16:15:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/sirhan.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>HR 2554: Submitted to House Government Reform Committee by Congresswoman Cynthia McKinney </title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/hr_2554.htm</link>
<description>HR 2554: Submitted to House Government Reform Committee by Georgia Congresswoman Cynthia McKinney to bring about release of MLK life and death files.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2006 13:25:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/hr_2554.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>A Pro Per Legal Petition to the US Government from Gary Revel</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/congressional_petition.htm</link>
<description>A Pro Per Legal Petition to the US Government from Gary Revel related to his work as a special investigator on the investigation of the Martin Luther King Jr. assassination.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2006 05:25:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/congressional_petition.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>Mystery Helicopter Disrupted Memphis Police Helicopters' Efforts to Prevent Rioting in Memphis</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/mystery_helicopter.htm</link>
<description>On March 28, 1968 while Martin Luther King Jr. was marching in support of the garbage workers Memphis Police Helicopter 201 reports a 3rd helicopter interfering with police helicopters 'came within 100 feet of us.' This indicates that the 2nd police helicopter was in the air by the time this 3rd mystery helicopter interfered with the Memphis Police.</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2006 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/mystery_helicopter.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>The Deadly Business of a King's Murder</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/deadly_biz.htm</link>
<description>New Release: An analysis of the Martin Luther King Jr. assassination written by Leutrell Osborne and Gary Revel</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2006 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/deadly_biz.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>Congresswoman Cynthia McKinney Introduces Legislation to House Government Reform Committee for New Martin Luther King Jr. Assassination Investigation</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/mckinney.htm</link>
<description>Congresswoman Cynthia McKinney Introduces Legislation to the House of Representatives Government Reform Committee for a New Martin Luther King Jr. Assassination Investigation</description>
 <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2006 19:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/mckinney.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>President George Herbert Walker Bush Used CIA For Personal Gain</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/bush1.htm</link>
<description>Political Analysis: President George Herbert Walker Bush Used CIA For Personal Gain.</description>
 <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2006 19:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/bush1.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>CIA Veteran Case Officer Associates With Gary Revel MLK Assassination Investigation</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/Leutrell2.html</link>
<description>CIA Veteran Case Officer and Counter Intelligence Expert Associates with Gary Revel Martin Luther King Assassination Investigation.</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2006 24:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/Leutrell2.html</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>United States Government Stole Private Martin Luther King Assassination Investigation Interviews</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/US_Government_Stole_Assassination_Investigation_Interviews.htm</link>
<description>The United States Government stole and published tape recorded private interviews of James Earl Ray as he was being questioned about the murder with the promise by the government that the recordings were private.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 08:10:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/US_Government_Stole_Assassination_Investigation_Interviews.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>CIA Intelligence Officer Offers Help In Gary Revel MLK Assassination Investigation</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/Leutrell.html</link>
<description>26 year CIA Intelligence (Case Officer) Officer Offers His Expertise To Gary Revel.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 08:10:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/Leutrell.html</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>The Gary Revel Martin Luther King Jr Assassination Investigation</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/index.html</link>
<description>Gary Revel renews his investigation of the Martin Luther King Jr. assassination with new facts about the United States Government's interference and hampering of the case since 1977.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 08:10:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/index.html</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>The DOD, CIA's DOD, ECHELON, CIFA and TALON opinion by Gary Revel</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/DOD.htm</link>
<description>United States Government departments and agencies have been used illegally in assassination and other crimes in this opinion by Gary Revel.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 08:10:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/DOD.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>DEEP THROAT Was The Foil For High Level US Government Criminality Opinion by Gary Revel</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/deep_throat_surfaces.html</link>
<description>Gary Revel opines that DEEP THROAT was a covert operation that kept the American people from going after the real story which was the continued coverup of the United States Government's role in the assassinations of Martin Luther King Jr., President John F. Kennedy and Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 08:10:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/deep_throat_surfaces.html</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>Excerpts From US Govt Book HSCA Investigation of Assassination Martin Luther King Jr</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/hsca_ray_interviews/1979_book_HSCA_Excerpts.htm</link>
<description>Excerpts from United States Government 1979 book are prima facie evidence that investigation story of Gary Revel is true.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 08:10:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/hsca_ray_interviews/1979_book_HSCA_Excerpts.htm</guid> 
  </item>
- <item>
<title>Congressman Brad Sherman Asked to Investigate the US Governments Illegal Interference and Tampering with the HSCA MLK Assassination Investigation</title>
<link>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/congressaskedtoinvestigate.htm</link>
<description>Congressman Brad Sherman has been asked to investigate the United States Government's illegal interfernce and tampering with the investigation of the assassination of Martin Luther King Jr.</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 08:10:00 PST</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.garyrevel.com/News/congressaskedtoinvestigate.htm</guid>
  </item>
  </channel>
  </rss> 

