<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Hailing Frequency - Star Trek Gaming Podcast 'The Internets Only Podcast Dedicated to Star Trek Gaming'</title>
<link>http://www.hailingfrequency.co.uk</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Hailing Frequency</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle>The Internets First Podcast Dedicated to Star Trek Gaming!!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>The Internets First Podcast Dedicated to Star Trek Gaming!! Each week we bring you the latest news and happening in the Star Trek Gaming world! From Clan Wars to Massivly Multiplayer Trek Games, we cover it all in an exciting, entertaining and leading format!</itunes:summary>
<description>Started in 2005, Hailing Frequency is the ONLY podcast on the internet dedicated to Star Trek Gaming. Covering all aspects, from official games such as Star Trek Online to semi-official games such as Star Trek Excalibur, your hosts, Zach, Kinneas, Nova and our Vulcan-Like Newsgirl K'suan'indra present you all of the current events in this genre in an entertaining and leading format. We have one several awards over the years and to date have had over 10 million downloads!</description>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Zach Nicodemous</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>zach@hailingfrequency.co.uk</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:category text="Games &amp; Hobbies">
<itunes:category text="Video Games"/>
</itunes:category>
<itunes:image href="http://www.hailingfrequency.com/podcast.jpg" />
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - A Brief History of Star Trek Gaming for StarTrek.com</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
In our first in a series of special podcasts for StarTrek.com, we take a journey through time and give you a brief history in Star Trek Gaming!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-08102010.mp3" length="19672534" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-11072010.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:20:18</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Interview with Daniel Stahl - The New Executive Producer of STO!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Following the recent announcement by Craig Zinkevich that he was stepping down as executive producer of Star Trek Online, we contacted the new one, Daniel Stahl and sat down with him for a 30 minute interview to talk about various aspects of the game and ask a number of community submitted questions.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-11072010.mp3" length="32896143" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-11072010.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:27:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item><title>Hailing Frequency #75 - STGN, Excalibur Interview, BC2, STO and more!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Episode 75 has arrived and its another fun filled, jam packed show.

K'suan'indra gets us up to date on all of the latest Star Trek Gaming News and then later in the show, Mark Ward joins us to talk about the latest developments in the upcoming fan game, Star Trek Excalibur.

Jigallypuff also joins us to talk about some mod plagurism issues that have been occuring in the Birth of the Federation community, plus Zach and Nova discuss all of the latest Star Trek Online happenings as well as the recent announcement of the fan game, Bridge Commander 2
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-75-29062010.mp3" length="73295646" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-75-29062010.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:27:02</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Interview with Craig Zincevic, Executive Producer of STO!!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Our first interview with Craig Zincevich since the release of Star Trek Online in February, this interview focuses on upcoming new features and includes tonnes of cool information!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-14062010.mp3" length="34098868" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-14062010.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:47:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item><title>Hailing Frequency #74 - STGN, Mod Weekly Returns, ST Freelance, Star Trek Online, more!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Hailing Frequency returns for its first episode since February 2010 and does not disappoint.  In this one hour show, we talk about all of the latest Star Trek Online updates that have hit the game since its launch in February, including the Season 1 updates, the upcoming Season 2 updates and beyond.

Later on in the show, we sit down with Griffin Endurance, lead developer of the Freelance Mod for Star Trek Elite Force 1 - a very exciting upcoming mod that promises to add a forking storyline to the game, flight controls, and a full RPG system!

Most excitingly - this edition of Hailing Frequency sees the return of the highly popular and critically acclaimed segment - "Mod Weekly".   Mod Weekly is a long-time Hailing Frequency segment that was with the podcast from its roots back in 2005, until late 2008 when the segment presenter, Croesus, retired to focus on his real life work.

Now, the segmenth as been revived by community member and modder - Max Loef.   Max has produed mods for a range of Star Trek Games, including Legacy and Bridge Commander.   He is also an experienced ship modeller, and is a perfect new host for Mod Weekly!.

Rounding out the show, K'suan'indra brings us the latest Star Trek Gaming News, and we have a fantastic edition of Fleet Radio!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-74-09062010.mp3" length="55479675" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-74-09062010.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:17:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency Interview - Craig Zinkevich, Executive Producer Star Trek Online</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
On the evening of Wednesday 27th Jan (2010) we sat down with Craig Zinkevich for a final audio interview before Star Trek Online releases next week on February 2nd!

We asked a tonne of community submitted questions on subjects ranging from the genesis system to social planets, along with some retrospective questions on the last 2 years of development and all in all, its a great interview with a cargo-bay full of information!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-28012010.mp3" length="33056512" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-28012010.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:34:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Star Trek Online Q and A #2</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
On Saturday 9th January 2010, we broadcast a second live show where myself and my team members, Nova and Kinneas, answered literally dozens of your questions about Star Trek Online, Live.

If you missed the live show, the good news is that the MP3 is now ready to download for your listening pleasure

Many thanks to all who had questions during this show, especially to those who actually called in!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-09012010.mp3" length="76643359" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-09012010.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:46:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Star Trek Online Q and A #1</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
On Sunday 3rd January 2010, we broadcast a 100 minute live show where myself and my team member, Nova, answered literally dozens of your questions about Star Trek Online Live.

If you missed the live show, the good news is that the MP3 is now ready to download for your listening pleasure

Many thanks to all who had questions during this show, especially to those who actually called in!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-03012010.mp3" length="98177586" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-03012010.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:40:45</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #72 - Christmas 2009 Special - STO Interview, Closed Beta Competition, Video, Screenshots and more!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous. Tony Tuthill, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
The Hailing Frequency 2009 Christmas Special is upon us and we have a truly awesome show for you!

During the show, we take a look back at what 2009 has brought to us and look forward to what 2010 has in store.  Ksuan brings us all of the latest Star Trek Gaming News, and at approximatly 30 minutes into the show, our special guests join us

Craig Zinkevich, Christine Thompson, Dan Griffis and Joe Blancato from Cryptic Studios spend a whopping 40 minutes with us talking about Star Trek Online and answering our questions along with a tonne of community submitted questions.

Following on from that - perhaps the only thing in the world that could be better than an interview with those 4 - we launch the Hailing Frequency Star Trek Online Closed Beta Competition where you have a chance to win one of 150 closed beta keys we have to giveaway for Star Trek Online!  Details for the competition are below.

After that, Mindwipe, a popular figure from the Star Trek Gaming Community gives us his thoughts about 2009 and his outlook for 2009 and ending the show, we have a 3 minute compilation of christmas greetings from the Star Trek Gaming Community
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-72-22122009.mp3" length="81462983" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-72-22122009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:36:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #70 -  Tonnes of STO News, Zinkievich Interview and more!  </title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
We are very happy to announce that Episode Number 70 of Hailing Frequency is hereby released, recorded to a live audience on Sunday 6th September 2009.

This episode sets both a record and milestone for Hailing Frequency - it is our 100th Audio Production since 2005, meaning we have released a total of 70 full length podcasts and 30 shorter special episodes such as interviews, road reports, etc.  This is also possibly the longest episode of Hailing Frequency which will ever occur, running a whopping two hours and ten minutes.

You might be asking yourself - what could they possibly have spent two hours and ten minutes talking about and the answered lies in the fact that we have just had the busiest period of Star Trek Online News - EVER!.

Cryptic Studios attended Penny Arcade Expo in Seattle this weekend, taking with them the first ever publicly playable demo of Star Trek Online and Hailing Frequency (with the help of Tamgros and Vmann from AoA) were there to cover it.  We released almost thirty high def photos of Star Trek Online, an 8 minute gameplay video and a 20 minute video interview with Craig Zinkevich.

In addition, information about Star Trek Online was coming from dozens of other sources, so we discuss everything we have learnt over the past two weeks about Star Trek Online in this bumper show.

Other than Star Trek Online, K'suan'indra brings us all of the latest Star Trek Gaming News from across the franchise and we bring you Episode 2 of Fleet Focus where this week, we speak to Fleet Admiral Fyasko of The Risen Phoenix Fleet!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-70-06092009.mp3" length="93564436" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-70-06092009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:09:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #69 -  STGN, Fleet Focus, Khyrons Korner, STO News, more!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Episode 69 of Hailing Frequency is hereby released.  Recorded to a live audience on Saturday 22nd August, this episode runs approximatly 1hr 26mins.

Kinneas and K'suan'indra are currently on a well deserved shore leave on Risa, so filling in for them this week, we have Jatal Khyron and Soulful Latina respectivly, who both do excellent jobs in their temporary positions!

The show starts as always with the Star Trek Gaming News and we then descend into a conversation about the latest Star Trek Online Video Trailer which was released at GamesCon in Germany.  Later on in the show, we also talked about the hypercool UI screenshot that Craig Zinkievich released on his Twitter Account.

Launching in this show, we have two great new segments.  The first, entitled "Fleet Focus" is a new regular segment where each week, we will sit down and interview a different Star Trek Gaming Clan so that members of our audience can get to know some of the wide selection of fleets out there.

The second is a new Star Trek Online Opinion Segment from Jatal Khyron entitled "Khyrons Korner".   Jatal is embedded in the Star Trek Online Forums and each week he will tackle a different hot topic.  This time around, its the subject of Microtransactions - Friend or Foe?!.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-69-26082009.mp3" length="62184897" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-69-26082009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:26:19</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item><title>Hailing Frequency #68 - STGN, STO news, Interview with Craig Zinkievich and more!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This is episode 68 of Hailing Frequency, our first "normal" episode since our stream of specials over the past few weeks as we covered the New Jersey and Las Vegas Star Trek Conventions.  Episode 68 was recorded on Saturday August 8th and our interview with Star Trek Online's Executive Producer Craig Zinkievich was run during this show for the first time.  I am sure you have all heard it already, but how can you ever get tired of it?

Ksuan brings us all of the latest Star Trek Gaming and Star Trek Online news as usual and we talk about some of the Star Trek Online screenshots that were released at Kotaku.  Another great show and well worth the download as usual! Enjoy Folks!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-68-12082009.mp3" length="62276743 " type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-68-12082009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:26:27</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Interview with Craig Zinkevich, Executive Producer of Star Trek Online!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Here it is folks, this is what you have been waiting for all this time.  Hailing Frequency's 25 minute telephone interview with Star Trek Onlines Executive Producer, Craig Zinkievich.  

There is a tonne of information in this interview ranging from subjects such as space and ground combat, to other things such as gameplay and economy.  Its a truly amazing interview, so download it right away folks and don't forget to post your comments after you have listened to it!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-CZ-10082009.mp3" length="36365885 " type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-CZ-10082009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:34:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Road Report #4 from Las Vegas Trek Con!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Mike Crowl</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Our fourth and final road report from the Las Vegas Trek Con 2009.  Athos joins us to give us his report on all of the happenings there, some funny stories, but unfortunatly no videos today as Creation Entertainment were really pushing the "no video" rule today.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-09082009.mp3" length="13715005 " type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-09082009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:37:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Road Report #3 from Las Vegas Trek Con! STO Info!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Mike Crowl</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This is our third audio road report from the Las Vegas Star Trek Convention and this report covers the convention for Saturday 8th August. The first 8 minutes of the report focus on the convention in general and then the last 25 minutes or so focus specifically on the STAR TREK ONLNE panel which had a playing demo of Star Trek Online! He also recalls how he was elected to dish out the TRIVIA questions for the BETA KEY GIVEAWAY!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-08082009.mp3" length="33547586 " type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-08082009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2009 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:34:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Road Report #2 from Las Vegas Trek Con!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Mike Crowl</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This is our second audio road report from the Las Vegas Star Trek Convention and this report covers the convention for Friday 7th August.  Our reporter Athos is on the floor meeting Trek Fans and Trek Stars and already has some funny stories to tell us!

Accompanying this audio report, we have photos and video from the convention on Thursday and there is some fun stuff to see there!

Check out photos in our gallery at     and videos are on our official YouTube channel at

Another Road Report will follow tomorrow, so until then folks, keep it Hailing Frequency!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-07082009.mp3" length="17857398 " type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-07082009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2009 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:18:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Road Report #1 from Las Vegas Trek Con!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Mike Crowl</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This is our first audio road report from the Las Vegas Star Trek Convention and this report covers the convention for Thursday 6th August.  Our reporter Athos is on the floor meeting Trek Fans and Trek Stars and already has some funny stories to tell us!

Accompanying this audio report, we have photos and video from the convention on Thursday and there is some fun stuff to see there!

Check out photos in our gallery at     and videos are on our official YouTube channel at

Another Road Report will follow tomorrow, so until then folks, keep it Hailing Frequency!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-06082009.mp3" length="16184308" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-06082009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:16:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Road Report #2 from the New Jersey Trek Con!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This is the second and final special report from Hailing Frequency for August 1st 2009 covering the New Jersey Star Trek Convention which is being run by Creation Entertainment and that is tagged as the Largest Star Trek Convention on the East Coast.

On the floor, is our Hailing Frequency Technical Director and Co-Host, Ryan L White aka Nova, who has been hard at work all day capturing HD Video, taking Photos and conducting interview after interview with folks such as Barry Jenner (Admiral Ross of DS9).

In this second road report, Nova lets us know everything thats been happing in the last 5 hours and its sounds like an aweful lot of fun, so if you arnt lucky enough to be there, this is the next best thing.  

<a href="http://www.podcastalley.com/"> My Podcast Alley feed!</a> {pca-170d6eafa86445543c48b70e7bb6cfb4}
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-01082009-P2.mp3" length="10383662" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-01082009-P2.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:08:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Road Report #1 from the New Jersey Trek Con!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This is a Hailing Frequency Special. We are on the floor today at the New Jersey Trek Con, ran by Creation Entertainment. It is the largest Trek Convention on the East Coast, and our Technical Director Nova is milling around, meeting folks and getting tonnes of interviews!  This is the first of two audio road reports we will release today.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-01082009.mp3" length="6134062" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-RR-01082009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:05:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item><title>Hailing Frequency #67 - STGN, State of Franchise, KM1.0, STO News and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This is our second show since our 8 week break for updates and reformatting and the changes continue in this show with a selection of new segment and backing music provided by our talented musician,  Tim Reinink.  K'suan'indra once again brings us the Star Trek Gaming News, in two parts and our special guest on this show is Victor1st from startrek-gamers.com who opens our discussion into the current state of the Star Trek Gaming Franchise, with a 10 minute recording of his thoughts and predictions for the next 12-24 months.

Later in the show, we discuss the latest Star Trek Online Updates including the new Klingon Ship which can only be described as a behemoth and following on from this, Napalm006 joins us once again to discuss mods - last week it was Fleet Operations 3, this week it is Kobayashi Maru 1.0 for Bridge Commander.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-67-29072009.mp3" length="61574258" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-67-29072009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:25:28</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #66 - Excalibur Interview, News, UFP Media and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Old is mixed with new in this show, as the hosts, Zach, Kinneas and Nova discuss all of the latest happenings in the world of Star Trek Gaming.  As usual, K'suan'indra brings us the Star Trek Gaming News, though in a new two-part format which focus on Modding/Fan Games and Star Trek Online, respectivly.

During the show, we interview Mark Ward, Lead Artist of ST: Excalibur and we find out some amazing information about what future updates they have planned, plus their newtonian physics system and what this means for ship control and playability.

Kinneas bring us the first new segment pilot, for something we call UFP Media which envisions how an "in-character" radio station might work in Star Trek Online and during the show, we premiere several new adverts from various Star Trek Guilds including Zeta Fleet who will soon be celebrating their 1 year anniversary.

We also disscus how the closure of StarTrek-Games.com is affecting the community and the most recent screenshots to come out of Cryptic Studios for Star Trek Online.

New Voice Talent in this show is provided by Napalm006 and new music sections in this show are produced by our talented new composer, Tim Reinink.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-66-15072009.mp3" length="64841863" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-66-15072009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:30:01</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #64 - STGN, Star Trek Online, Star Trek DAC, ST Excalibur Updates and more!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
During this Episode, Hosts Zach, Kinneas, Nova and Athos discuss all of the latest updates from the past four weeks to Star Trek Online - including discussion on the most recent screenshots, new video footage, new timeline updates and much more.

K'suan'indra brings us a 16 minute roundup of Star Trek Gaming News from all around the community and in addition, we discuss DAC Updates, Star Trek Excalibur Updates and more!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-64-25042009.mp3" length="91861357" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-64-25042009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:07:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Interview with George Takei!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
We are happy to release the interview which we conducted with the legendary "George Takei" on April 14th 2009. 

In this truly amazing 25 minute interview, we speak about Mr Takei's experiences with The Original Series and the Original 6 movies, as well as his hopes for the future and more!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-15042009.mp3" length="23146673" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-15042009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:32:06</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #63 - STGN with Ksuan, DAC Updates, STO Updates and More!!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This show sees a temporary return to the original crew of Zach, Kinneas and K'suan with Nova and Athos both incapacitated in sickbay with the Tarquelian Flu.

In the show, we talk about all of the latest Star Trek Online Updates, plus some Star Trek DAC Updates which have been quietly filtering out in past weeks including some screenshots.  K'suan brings us a 15 minute Star Trek Gaming News Update and we also talk about the pending collapse of Filefront (or so we thought at the time!) 
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-63-29032009.mp3" length="83239695" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-63-29032009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:55:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #62 - Excalibur Update, Star Trek Online News and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
n this show, we discuss all of the latest Star Trek Online news, screenshots, storyline updates, et cetera. 

Mark Ward of Star Trek Excalibur also joins us with a 30 minute update on the status of their upcoming fan game.

Amira brings us the latest Star Trek Gaming News this week, and Athos joins us as a third co-host once again.   
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-62-07032009.mp3" length="85935529" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-62-07032009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:59:19</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #61 - STO News, Interviews w/ Nano (NanoFX) and Klogd (TrekWars)</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
In this show, we cover the latest STO news from the last 2 weeks including an Ask Cryptic Update and 4 new screenshots.

We also have two interviews in this show, the first one is with the legendary Nano - who created NanoFX for Bridge Commander and is currently working on the NanoFX-Evolved Game Engine which is powering Star Trek Excalibur.

As always, we have the latest Star Trek Gaming News Roundup however this week we have an Orion Slave Girl called Amira standing in for K'suan.

Athos joins us once again as a guest host in this show.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-61-21022009.mp3" length="94749290" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-61-21022009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:11:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #60 - Tons of STO News, Live Report from Comic Con and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Ryan White</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
In this show, we cover a ton of Star Trek Online News that has been released since the last show including the first tid-bits of information to come out of the New York Comic Con.

Half way into the show, we bring our field reporter into the show live from the floor of the New York Comic Con where he gives us some STO Updates and an idea of the incredible atmosphere there.

As always, K'suan'indra brings us the latest Star Trek Gaming News Roundup and towards the end of the show we talk briefly about the new fan game TrekWars and about some rumours surrounding Bethesda Softworks hold over the Star Trek Gaming License.

Athos joins us once again as a guest host in this show.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-60-07022009.mp3" length="94247792" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-60-07022009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:10:52</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #59 - Cryptic Interview, STGN, STO News and More!!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
In this episode, we feature an EXCLUSIVE Interview with Cryptic Studio's Head of Community Relations, Nicole Hamlett. (This was released as a separate file a few days ago.)

In the interview we discuss the how the community of STO will be handled inside and outside of the game post launch, upcoming website features, videos and much much more.

K'suan'indra also brings us the latest Star Trek Gaming News and myself, Nova and Kinneas are joined this week by Athos who joins our discussions about the latest STO Updates.

Athos also talks to us in detail about the Lotus Fleet Academy in the last 15 minutes of the show.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-59-24012009.mp3" length="90655087" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-59-24012009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:05:53</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency Special - Interview with Nicole Hamlett (Cryptic Studios Community Manager)!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
You all know her as Awen and those of you who pay attention to the Star Trek Online website probably know her by her real name too - Nicole Hamlett.

In this 30 minute interview, she joins us to talk about many aspects relating to the Community in Star Trek Online, Fleets/Clans/Guilds,  the STO Forums, how community will be handled post launch, and much much more.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-Interview-Awen-22-01-2009.mp3" length="28694743" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-Interview-Awen-22-01-2009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:29:52</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #58 - STGN, 5 Star Trek Online Updates, SFA, The Trek License and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Here is Episode 58 of Hailing Frequency which was broadcast live on Saturday January 10th 2009.

In our first show of 2009 we discuss in detail the multiple updates that have been posted on the Star Trek Online Website since our Christmas show.

We gauge the communities opinions on the topics from the updates which include the ship specs in the new ship of line updates, owning multiple ships and ship physics from the new Ask Cryptic Update and we discuss the new screenshots in detail and analyze how the graphics have improved since the first batch of screenshots and hopefully how they will continue to improve.

We also talk about what might happen to the Star Trek Gaming License once Bethesda's tenure with it expires in 2010/2011 and we check out the Interplay Classic "Starfleet Academy" to see if it still holds up on today's computers.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-58-10012009.mp3" length="87202135" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-58-10012009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:01:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item><title>Hailing Frequency #57 - Christmas 2008 Special - STGN, Fleet Radio, Majel Roddenberry Dies, A Look Back at 2008, Players Choice 08 Coverage</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Here is the 2008 christmas special of Hailing Frequency which was broadcast and recorded live on December 20th 2008.

In this show, we talk about the hard hitting impact the death of Majel Roddenberry has had on the community.  After this, we discuss the latest Star Trek Online Timeline updates and we reveal that we have 2 interviews lined up with Cryptic Studios in January - The first one with Nicole Hamlett aka Awen and the second one which will be with Craig Zinkevich - Dates for both of these will be announced very soon.

Following on for this - we give a little bit of coverage on the 2008 Players Choice Awards from StarTrek-Games.com and discuss some of the nominations to date - voting for this opens on January 1st at http://www.startrek-games.com

We take a look back at the events of 2008 and reveal the full details of how and when exactly Hailing Frequency found out that Cryptic Studios had taken over development of Star Trek Online and we look forward to what we can expect in 2009.

Finally - we remind folks that Hailing Frequency will be going down on December 30th for some major upgrades and refits to upgrade our forum, design and launch some exciting new features for 2009.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-57-20122008.mp3" length="59886738" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-57-20122008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:23:09</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #56 - STGN, Star Trek Online, Bethesda and more</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Episode 56 is here after a 7 week break in Hailing Frequency broadcasts. This episode was broadcast live on Saturday 13th December 2008 and released as a podcast on Sunday 14th December.

K'suan brings us a bumper edition of the Star Trek Gaming news this week, bringing us fully up to date on all of the news from the last 7 weeks.   

Then we talk about the hot topic - Atari's purchase of Cryptic Studios.  Following on from that, we touch briefly on the latest Storyline updates and Ask Cryptic updates. 

Later on in the show, we discuss the latest updates from the fan project - Star Trek Excalibur - we speak to Bethesda Softworks to see if they intend to release any more Star Trek Games, and we review the latest Beta Version of Fleet Operations 3 for Armada 2.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-56-13122008.mp3" length="81539445" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-56-13122008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:53:13</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #55 - STGN, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Mods for X3 and more!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Episode 55 is here, almost 2 weeks on from the last show, and once again this show was recorded live on Saturday October 4th. Its slightly rougher than our past shows have been, but its much cleaner than last weeks show.

K'suan returns this week with the Star Trek Gaming News for the last couple of weeks and we discuss some of the latest things out of Cryptic Studios relating to Star Trek Online.  Following on from that, Max Loef join us to talk about a Star Trek Mod he discovered for the Space Simulator X3: Reunion.

Fleet Radios on this show are all from the Brand New Brad Sucks album and Kinneas provides some excellent news updates from around the UFP and Beyond!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-55-04102008.mp3" length="65399577" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-55-04102008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:30:48</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency #54 - Vegas Debrief, STGN, STO Roundup, Lotus Fleet and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This is the first actual show we have done since we got back from Vegas, so we begin the show with a 30 minute de-brief with Kinneas and Nova who give us some of their experiences and feedback from Vegas including a rather touching story from Kinneas toward the end of the de-brief.

We then launch into the Star Trek Gaming News - K'suan was unable to join us to read this live, so it was read out by myself, Kinneas and Nova and was far from smooth - but all of the important news is there which is what matters. K'suan will return in the next show.

After that, we get caught up on all of the latest STO News from the last couple of months and boy has there been alot and finally at the end of the show, Nova tells us about some of the exciting things going on at Lotus Fleet Lately.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/Live/HF-Live-20092008.mp3" length="84061722" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/Live/HF-Live-20092008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:07:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency - Meet Razor | Interview with Your Star Trek Online Community Manager</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
We got a chance at the Las Vegas to sit down with your STO Community Manager Razor, also known as JR Sutich in real life.  This is his very first interview ever in his career at Cryptic, so we were very nice to him.  Its a great chance for you to meet the man behind the name, so we hope you will all enjoy this interview.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://hailingfrequency.co.uk/shows/vegas/HF-Razor-10082008.mp3" length="8846786" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://hailingfrequency.co.uk/shows/vegas/HF-Razor-10082008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:09:11</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Jack Emmert, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency - Star Trek Online Interview with Jack Emmert | Part 2</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
We are now able to release part 2 of our video interview with Jack Emmert, CCO at Cryptic Studios.

In this part of the interview, we cover things like the economy, starbases, and much more.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.hailingfrequency.co.uk/vegas/HF-Emmert-P2-10082008.mp3" length="8100696" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://www.hailingfrequency.co.uk/video/HF-Emmert-P2-10082008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:08:26</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Jack Emmert, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency - Star Trek Online Interview with Jack Emmert | Part 1</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
We have been given the go ahead by Cryptic Studios to release PART ONE of our EXCLUSIVE VIDEO Interview with Jack Emmert, Chief Creative Officer at Cryptic.

In this interview, we discuss a wide range of topics surrounding Star Trek Online and Jack reveals a good amount of new information about Star Trek Online, and while we are only able to release PART ONE at the moment, its definetly a revealing segment.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/vegas/HF-Emmert-P1-10082008.mp3" length="7000503" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/vegas/HF-Emmert-P1-10082008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:07:16</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Jack Emmert, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency in Vegas - August 6th and 7th | TrekCon Review Days 2 and 3</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Previously, we posted an audio review of the first day of the convention and we now have an audio review of days 2 and 3 of the convention hosted by HF Co-Host Kinneas, Lotus Fleet Admiral Athos and Star Trek Writer Derek Chester.

We hear TONNES of news from the convention including the fact that Chase Masterson wants "in" on Star Trek Online and we hear about a new Remote Controlled flying 4 ft Enterprise, plus Anthony Montgomery, Garret Wang, Jolene Blalock, George Takei and MORE!.

This is a jam packed review weighing in at around 45mins folks - so be sure to download it and have a listen!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/vegas/HF-SE-VegasD2-3.mp3" length="38357932" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/vegas/HF-SE-VegasD2-3.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:39:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency in Vegas - August 5th | TrekCon Review Day 1</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Broadcasting from Quarks Bar, we have a 15 minute audio review of the first day of the Las Vegas Star Trek Convention.  Hailing Frequency Co-Host Kinneas and Lotus Fleet Admiral Athos talk about their experiences on day one of this amazing convention and we also hear from a Klingon D'har Master who wanders up to Kinneas and Athos asking about podcasts!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/vegas/HF-SE-VegasD1.mp3" length="14061722" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/vegas/HF-SE-VegasD1.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:14:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency Live - July 27th - Cryptic Countdown Show</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
After 36 hours of editing and post production, here we finally have the recorded sound file from our Cryptic Countdown show which was broadcast on Sunday July 27th for around 5 hours.

Key Highlights:

Interview with Rick Sternbach - Senior Illustrator and Technical Advisor on Star Trek since 1979 - We talk to him about a range of things including his thoughts on STO, his thoughts on the NASA Space Program and much much more!

Derek Chester - Co-Writer of Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Tactical Assault, Star Trek Bridge Commander and the IDW Year 4 comic books, Derek Chester is DC Fontanas writing partner and a huge gamer. He joins us throughout the live show discussing his views on Star Trek Online and much much more.

A huge array of guests throughout the entire show including-

    -DIF-Josh who is leader of Consortium Ultimate Gamers
    -Chris Jones who is head of Chris Jones Gaming
    -GamerGlo from OnTheAirTV
    -Pestalance from Dynaverse.net
    -Lotus Fleet Members Raven, Lrd Nova, Random Redshirt and Admiral of Starfleet
    -Gemini Fleet
    -and many many more folks joined us throughout the evening.


We talked about all things Star Trek Online as the Cryptic Countdown edged towards zero and at the end of the evening we provided coverage of the new Cryptic Website and Forums!

We were on the air for well over 5 hours with our main show and we have done our best to edit out any long periods of silence or pauses caused by technical glitches.

For those who only want to listen to the interview we did with Rick Sternbach, I have encoded that section of the show as a standalone file running around 90 minutes.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/Live/HF-Live-27072008.mp3" length="249665946" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/Live/HF-Live-27072008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 July 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>5:46:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency 53 ft KA2 Interview, All Crew Reporting Announced for Wii and DS, STGN and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>

In this weeks show, we talk about the continuing trek towards the big "zero" on the Cryptic Countdown Timer and we also talk about the Cryptic Hints that have been dropped on the Hailing Frequency Forums.

K'suan'indra gives us a 12 minute roundup of the Star Trek Gaming News, covering the first two weeks of July and following that, we hear the second segment from Random Redshirt - "Thoughts of a Random Redshirt". 

About half way into the show, we interview Robert Palfrey about his acclaimed total conversion for Star Trek Armada 2 - Klingon Academy.

Lastly, Nova of Lotus Fleet comes to us with another segment about Star Trek Online.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-53-13072008.mp3" length="41348268" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-53-13072008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 13 July 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:57:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item><title>Hailing Frequency 52 - STO Confirmed, Derek Chester Interview, Thoughts of a Random Redshirt, Fleet Radio and More</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Here it is - the much waited for next episode of Hailing Frequency - and our longest show this year - Episode 52 of Hailing Frequency.

In this weeks show, the hot topic is of course the mysterious countdown timer that appeared on the Cryptic Website and how it pretty much confirms that Cryptic Studios are developing Star Trek Online.

We cover the facts and take a look at some of the comments folks have been making about the subject.

K'suan'indra brings us a roundup of the Star Trek Gaming News headlines as always, and at the end of the show, she gives us an amazing 35 minute interview with Derek Chester - veteran Star Trek Writer.

We also have two new pilot segments in this show - Thoughts of a Random Redshirt takes a look at other major MMOs on the market today and how elements of them could be applied to or used in Star Trek Online.

Lord Nova brings us an as yet unnamed segment (Called STO-Zone v2 in this show only) which attempts to take over where MrJuliano left of - covering all of the latest news and facts to come out about Star Trek Online. He also takes a look at some of the hot topics of the week on the Hailing Frequency STO Forums.

Thats all until the next show, see you in a couple / few weeks!

</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-52-22062008.mp3" length="63180200" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-52-22062008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 June 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:27:43</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency 51 - STGN, Fleet Radio + SFC4 and More! Sorry for the Delay!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
First of all, I would like to apolagise for the huge delay in the release of this show - this was meant to be released on June 8th, but due to the fact that i am in Serbia at the moment, on my laptop, i have experienced problems uploading the show. This is now resolved.

In this show, we do not have a Mod Weekly due to Croesus's hectic schedule, however rest assured, there will be another few episodes of Mod Weekly before he disembarks the ship.

In addition, we do not have a STO-Zone due to the departure of Mr Juliano from the crew after Episode 50. We are taking applications for a new host for the STO-Zone Pod Segment, and for a replacement host for Mod Weekly. If you are interested, e-mail zach@hailingfrequency.co.uk

In this show, we get caught up on the last 4 weeks of Star Trek Gaming - The announcement of Starfleet Command 4 and Erik Bethes statements about Star Trek Online make the key headlines of the show.

There is a ton of content in this show so its well worth a listen!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-51-08062008.mp3" length="34987662" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-51-08062008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 08 June 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:48:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency 50 ¦ STO-Zone, Mod Weekly, Fleet Radio, STGN and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>

Welcome to our 50th Hailing Frequency Episode. Given the relative quietness in the community as of late, we didnt really have alot to celebrate with, so this is a fairly typical show.

K'suan'indra brings us the latest Star Trek Gaming News roundup as always, and following that we talk about the Current State of the MMO Devlopment world and how risky it is at the moment in MMO Development. With Star Trek Online struggling to be developed, the everchanging devlopment world could see the project shelved!

In Mod Weekly this week, we hear about a Star Trek Mod for the Hit RPG, Neverwinter Nights 2, and we get an update on the DJ Galaxy Class for Bridge Commander.

Kinneas had a chance to play a 2 week free trial on EVE-Online - We hear from a long time trek gamer how EVE shapes up. Does it have good gameplay and what would work in STO?

STO-Zone gets a revamp this week and has a fresh new audio bed. Juliano talks about Ship Models this week! Great Stuff!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-50-04052008.mp3" length="37089475" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-50-04052008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:51:29</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency 49 ¦ Keys of Legacy Interview, Rockstar, DARPA + STGN and more!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Sorry for the one day delay in the release of this show. A number of coinciding factors caused some technical hitches and delays that unfortunatly could not be avoided. Some of the audio in this show is a little bit off - we are not sure why, however there was some bugs with our recording equipment this week. While its nothing major, i think most of you will notice that this is not up to our usual quality of sound.

However, in terms of quality of content, we have another great show for you. Alexraptor takes 10 minutes to sit down with us and chat about Keys of Legacy, a hit mod for Star Trek Legacy designed to show folks what the game should of been at launch. Also in this weeks show, we talk about the Rockstar takeover of Mad Doc Software and some of the potential options this could open up for trek gaming.

Mr Juliano presents us with the final part of his "Perfect STO" series in STO-zone this week, and following that, Kinneas tells us about how the U.S Department of Defense contacted him to say they are interested in STO!

Unfortunatly, Croesus has had a bit of a family emergency in the past week, so he has had to shoot of to another part of the country to help deal with that, therefore, we do not have a Mod Weekly in this show. It will however be back with an extended edition next show.

Again, we apolagise for the touchy audio in this show, but rest assured the issues will be tracked down and resolved in time for the big 5-0!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-49-13042008.mp3" length="37458098" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-49-13042008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:52:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Special - Spring Break 2008 </title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Hey Folks,

We are happy to announce that the much anticipated Spring Break Special of Hailing Frequency, is now released!

Following the demise of Perpetual and STOnet Bases, Captain Zach decides that his crew needs some shore leave, so he sets a course for Risa, however, the Devilfish can never go very far without the Evil Alter Ego popping up!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SB-07042008.mp3" length="40616919" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SB-07042008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:42:17</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency 48 ft Captain Source, BOTE, Trek CCG, Mod Weekly and More!!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
In this weeks show, we sit down with Captain Source to get the latest news from Enterprise TCW.

We also talk about the recently released star trek fan game Birth of the Empires, and discuss the demise of the Star Trek CCG. Plus, the latest STO rumours.

In STO-Zone, we hear part three of Mr Julianos "Perfect Star Trek Online" series, and in Mod Weekly, we hear about Media Release 20 for Temporal Cold War, plus some news regarding the Delta Quadrant pack for Bridge Commander.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-48-30032008.mp3" length="458394740" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-48-30032008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:54:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency 47 ft Fleet Radio, Mod Weekly, STO-Zone, Star Trek Gaming News!!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>

In this weeks show, we get the latest gaming news roundup from around the quadrant from our sexy vulcan, K'suan'Indra, we also hear about the latest mods for Bridge Commander in Mod Weekly. On STO-Zone, we hear part 2 of MrJulianos perfect Star Trek Online.

We also talk about the Animated Series Mod Project for the popular Source Game  Engine, and we delve into the latest rumours surrounding Star Trek Online.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-47-16032008.mp3" length="34906116" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-47-16032008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:48:27</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency 46 ft Gamemaster of Aftermath + STOnet Closes, Fleet Radio!!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>

Episode 46 of Hailing Frequency is here. In this show, we feature an interview with Gamemaster of Star Trek Legacy: Aftermath where we get some information on their mod and hear about their latest 1.7 release. We also talking about the closure of STOnet and how a new website, STO-Zone, created by the team behind Hailing Frequency, has launched to save the day.

In Mod Weekly this week, Croesus talks about 2.5 Patch Project for Star Trek Armada 2, and on Fleet Radio this week, SheriffNL, leader of Aries Fleet gives us an amazing rendition of the classic song - "Hurt". We also get the latest update on those all important Civil Spaceways.

In STOzone this week, Mr Juliano talks about what he believes the perfect Star Trek Online would be.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-46-02032008.mp3" length="39230458" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-46-02032008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:54:27</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency 45 ft Mark Ward of ST: Excalibur plus Mod Weekly, STOZone and More! </title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Greetings Trek Fans,

Hailing Frequency 45 has arrived, and in this episode, we feature an extensive thirty minute interview with Mark Ward, who is lead artist and chief publicist for Star Trek: Excalibur. (See our recent news article on Excalibur at http://www.hailingfrequency.co.uk/boards/index.php?topic=259.0)

In the interview, we cover many aspects of what Star Trek Excalibur is and some of the features it will have. This is a truly exciting game that is designed to be the spiritual sequal to Bridge Commander, so it is well worth having a listen to this interview.

We also have all of our usual segments - In Mod Weekly this time around, Croesus talks about the recently released Bridges and Crew Pack from 3rd Era Productions, and in STO-Zone, Juliano talks about the theories surrounding the downfall of Star Trek Online.

Brad Sucks returns in Kinneas' Fleet Radio, and K'suan'indra brings us the Star Trek Gaming News roundup for the last two weeks.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-45-17022008.mp3" length="47112939" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-45-17022008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:05:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency 44 ft STGN, Armada 1 Dead? P2 / Kohnke Settlement and an Enterprise TCW Exclusive!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Hailing Frequency 44 has arrived - sorry it is a day late folks, my internet died yesterday and only just came back on.

Quite a short show for you this week as there has not been a whole lot going on, but as always we have strived to bring you a quality production.

K'suan'indra brings us a roundup of all the latest star trek gaming news, and Juliano brings us another great and informative edition of the STO-Zone.

Additionally, we get an exclusive look at the Enterprise Temporal Cold War internal Beta - Check out the hyper-cool screenshots and video file below!

Croesus is on shore leave this week to Delta IV, visiting a luxury deltan spa, so unfortunatly we have no Mod Weekly this time round.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-44-03022008.mp3" length="23683846" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-44-03022008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:32:52</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency 43 ft STO Cancellation, Kingworld, The Alter Ego Show and More!! (Video Version)</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Good Morning, Good Afternoon and Good Evening Trek Gamers,

Please ensure your seats are in their upright and locked position and prepare for a ride - Hailing Frequency 43 is here.

In this episode, we return to normal programming for the first time in 2008 - and you may notice some changes. While the overall feel and format of the show has not changed - we have attempted to further promote the idea and feel that Hailing Frequency is broadcast from a ship - the UFP Devilfish - this is something we have always attempted to convey with varying success. One large step we have taken towards this is the implementation of an "in character" scene at the begining and end of each show lasting no more than a minute each - i think you will find them pleasing!

In an attempt to improve audio quality ever further this year, we have begun using a new method of recording - i think you will all notice the higher clarity and quality!

And now - Kickstarting things this show we have the Star Trek Gaming News from the ever popular and super sexy K'suan'indra.

Following on from the news, we talk about the recently announced bombshell that has affected trek gamers worldwide - Perpetual Entertainment has ceased development on Star Trek Online. We gauge the communitys response too this terrible news and we are later joined by Chris "ChessMess" Koerner of Star Trek Games, Victor "1st" Mullin of Star Trek Gamers, and for the first time ever on Hailing Frequency - the world famous Star Trek Writer Derek Chester.

Mod Weekly returns in this show where we hear about a new mod for Bridge Commander by DJ Kurtis - and on the first fleet radio of 2008 - we here the musical genius Arthur Yoria with "Something Must be Wrong".

Ever heard of KingWorld? Hailing Frequency reveals details of an investigation into the rumours about a new high budget star trek game in 2008 - we left no leaf unturned in our search for information in our attempts to confirm or debunk these rumours.

Lastly - we have STO-Zone episode eleven - with a twist - it seems that we have accidently recieved a transmission from an alternate universe, and the STO Zone has become...."The Alter Ego Show!"
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-43-20012008.mp3" length="245588968" type="video/mp4" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-43-20012008.mp4</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:12:47</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency 43 ft STO Cancellation, Kingworld, The Alter Ego Show and More!! (Audio Version)</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Good Morning, Good Afternoon and Good Evening Trek Gamers,

Please ensure your seats are in their upright and locked position and prepare for a ride - Hailing Frequency 43 is here.

In this episode, we return to normal programming for the first time in 2008 - and you may notice some changes. While the overall feel and format of the show has not changed - we have attempted to further promote the idea and feel that Hailing Frequency is broadcast from a ship - the UFP Devilfish - this is something we have always attempted to convey with varying success. One large step we have taken towards this is the implementation of an "in character" scene at the begining and end of each show lasting no more than a minute each - i think you will find them pleasing!

In an attempt to improve audio quality ever further this year, we have begun using a new method of recording - i think you will all notice the higher clarity and quality!

And now - Kickstarting things this show we have the Star Trek Gaming News from the ever popular and super sexy K'suan'indra.

Following on from the news, we talk about the recently announced bombshell that has affected trek gamers worldwide - Perpetual Entertainment has ceased development on Star Trek Online. We gauge the communitys response too this terrible news and we are later joined by Chris "ChessMess" Koerner of Star Trek Games, Victor "1st" Mullin of Star Trek Gamers, and for the first time ever on Hailing Frequency - the world famous Star Trek Writer Derek Chester.

Mod Weekly returns in this show where we hear about a new mod for Bridge Commander by DJ Kurtis - and on the first fleet radio of 2008 - we here the musical genius Arthur Yoria with "Something Must be Wrong".

Ever heard of KingWorld? Hailing Frequency reveals details of an investigation into the rumours about a new high budget star trek game in 2008 - we left no leaf unturned in our search for information in our attempts to confirm or debunk these rumours.

Lastly - we have STO-Zone episode eleven - with a twist - it seems that we have accidently recieved a transmission from an alternate universe, and the STO Zone has become...."The Alter Ego Show!"
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-43-20012008.mp3" length="52261640" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-43-20012008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:12:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title> Hailing Frequency Special "The Peoples Choice Awards 2007 - Results!"</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Hailing Frequency, in association with startrek-games.com is proud to present special toonshow coverage of this years peoples choice awards, as well as the much anticipated results!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://video.hailingfrequency.co.uk/HF-PCA-05012008.mp4" length="55670778" type="video/mp4" />
<guid>http://video.hailingfrequency.co.uk/HF-PCA-05012008.mp4</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2008 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:20:02</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title> Hailing Frequency Presents "When the Borg Assimilated Christmas"</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Greetings Trek Gamers and Pod Fans - And a Belated Merry Christmas!

This year, Hailing Frequency wanted to do something truly special for our christmas special - looking back at our christmas shows in 2006 and 2005 - there was'nt really a whole lot about them that was special - so this year, we got together and came up with the idea of doing a fully featured audio and TOONSHOW story - and thus, "When the Borg Assimilated Christmas" was born.

Penned by our very own Dominic Ervolina (aka Mr Juliano) - When the Borg Assimilated Christmas is our first major audio story, set aboard our virtual media ship, the devilfish (Which we would like to have in Star Trek:Online :)  ).

The entire Hailing Frequency cast is present - Zach, Kinneas, K'sua'indra, MrJuliano, Croesus, and STO-Zones new co-host, Julianos brother David - (who's voice we had to digitally alter as he sounds so damn similar to juliano)

"When the Borg Assimilated Christmas" is our gift to you all - and we hope you will find it funny and exciting to listen too and watch - and yes, you read right - we said watch.

Kinneas - wanted to do a toonshow version of this special  (( He would like ALL our shows to be Toonshows and move away from audio only.   Any opinions?)) - as I am sure you can imagine, this was quite an undertaking which is why we are making this release a few days late - Though he is not done with all six scenes (damn, Romulan Ale) ...the show must go on...and so we are releasing the full audio version and the first five toonshows now.

There are some major differences between the two experiences - so we recommend that you check them both out!

(( P.S.  Kinneas' 'Fleet Radio Toonshows' on YouTube were chosen as the best Star Trek fan videos on YouTube on the seventh day of 'The Twelve Days of Trek Christmas over at the TrekUnited web site!   Check out Kinneas' other toonshows! ))
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-42-25122007.mp3" length="119673002" type="video/mp4" />
<guid>http://video.hailingfrequency.co.uk/HF-42-25122007.mp4</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:34:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title> Hailing Frequency Presents "When the Borg Assimilated Christmas"</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Greetings Trek Gamers and Pod Fans - And a Belated Merry Christmas!

This year, Hailing Frequency wanted to do something truly special for our christmas special - looking back at our christmas shows in 2006 and 2005 - there was'nt really a whole lot about them that was special - so this year, we got together and came up with the idea of doing a fully featured audio and TOONSHOW story - and thus, "When the Borg Assimilated Christmas" was born.

Penned by our very own Dominic Ervolina (aka Mr Juliano) - When the Borg Assimilated Christmas is our first major audio story, set aboard our virtual media ship, the devilfish (Which we would like to have in Star Trek:Online :)  ).

The entire Hailing Frequency cast is present - Zach, Kinneas, K'sua'indra, MrJuliano, Croesus, and STO-Zones new co-host, Julianos brother David - (who's voice we had to digitally alter as he sounds so damn similar to juliano)

"When the Borg Assimilated Christmas" is our gift to you all - and we hope you will find it funny and exciting to listen too and watch - and yes, you read right - we said watch.

Kinneas - wanted to do a toonshow version of this special  (( He would like ALL our shows to be Toonshows and move away from audio only.   Any opinions?)) - as I am sure you can imagine, this was quite an undertaking which is why we are making this release a few days late - Though he is not done with all six scenes (damn, Romulan Ale) ...the show must go on...and so we are releasing the full audio version and the first five toonshows now.

There are some major differences between the two experiences - so we recommend that you check them both out!

(( P.S.  Kinneas' 'Fleet Radio Toonshows' on YouTube were chosen as the best Star Trek fan videos on YouTube on the seventh day of 'The Twelve Days of Trek Christmas over at the TrekUnited web site!   Check out Kinneas' other toonshows! ))
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-42-25122007.mp3" length="48733712" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-42-25122007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:40:35</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title> Hailing Frequency Episode 41 ft ST Supremacy, STO Zone, Fleet Radio and More! </title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Hey Hey Everybody
Its that time again - and we are proud to announce the release of Episode 41 of Hailing Frequency.
Normally, we only release two shows per month - one every two weeks, however, Hailing Frequency was invited to take part in Trek Uniteds "Twelve Trek Days of Christmas" project - and here we are.
Kicking of the show once again this week, we have K'suan'indra with the Star Trek Gaming News - Sandwiches can be sent to fleetradio@gmail.com.
Hot on the heels of the STGN, Zach and Kinneas chat about the recently released ground combat screenshot from Perpetual Entertainments Star Trek Online.
Mr Juliano returns this week to bring us another excellent edition of STO ZOne, and immediatly after that, we feature an advert for "st-online.nl"
In Fleet Radio this week, Kinneas brings us his Traffic Report concept along with another excellent song choice from a london based band - and following this, i sit down and chat with Mike Strobel, Executive Producer for Star Trek Supremacy, and representative of the BOTFII Project. He updates us on all four projects currently underway over there, and he also clears up some of the misconceptions currently surriounding the development of Birth of the Empires.
Finally, Zach and Kinneas discuss the recently released article from Eric Heinburg - A Former systems designer from the STO Dev Team and Zach brings us all another Fan Game review segment.
Show Summary:
00.00 - 02.30 - Introduction
02.30 - 13.37 - Star Trek Gaming News from K'sua'indra
13.37 - 13.52 - Advertisements
13.58 - 15.45 - Hailing Frequency / Enterprise Temporal Cold War Competition! Win 4 Amazing Prizes!
15.46 - 20.17 - Zach and Kinneas discuss the STO Ground Combat Screenshot
20.20 - 22.00 - The Twelve Trek Days of Christmas
22.00 - 34.30 - Mr Jullianos STO Zone Episode 10
34.30 - 36.00 - ST-Online.NL Advertisement
36.00 - 37.36 - Zach and Kinneas discuss the STO Promo Video from the TOS Remastered DVD Set
37.36 - 42.53 - Fleet Radio featuring The Northern Electrics with Electric Superhighway
42.53 - 43.43 - Enterprise Temporal Cold War Advertisement
43.43 - 45.15 - Zach and Kinneas Misc
45.15 - 59.15 - Interview with Mike Strobel
59.15 - 1.04.00 - Zach and Kinneas discuss the recent article from Eric Heinburg
1.04.00 - 1.13.52 - Somethings Missing! The Best Free Trek Fan Games
1.13.52 - 1.15.00 - Ending</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-41-16122007.mp3" length="54012712" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-41-16122007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:15:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title> Hailing Frequency Episode 40 ft STO, Conquest, Enterprise TCW and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Greetings and Salutations Trek Gamers
Its been a little while since we the last edition of Hailing Frequency – I am sure allot of you thought we had kicked the bucket – but never fear – Hailing Frequency will always persevere.
There has been a lot going on recently, but do not worry as we have been keeping tabs on all of it. During this show, K’sua’indra gets us all caught up on the Star Trek Gaming News for the last couple of months.
Following this, we sit down for a chat with Captain Source of the Enterprise Temporal Cold War Project who is able to update us on everything going on over there. We also get to hear samples of TCW’s music which is layered into the background throughout the interview – and some of their voice acting talent!
Additionally, we also announce details of a competition in association with Lightspeed Design Studios.
We also discuss and review the recently released ‘Star Trek Conquest’ before moving onto a brilliant episode of Mod Weekly from Croesus.
After Mod Weekly, we talk in detail about the recently released screenshot from perpetual entertainment – be aware that portions of this discussion may offend the STO-Lovers out there.
Finally – Just before we end the show, we run a segment compiled by myself as a response to a cry from community member “RonaldRabbit” – detailing the best free star trek games out there!
Show Notes:
    * Introduction by Hosts Zach and Kinneas
    * Star Trek Gaming News by K’suan’indra
    * Interview with Captain Source of Temporal Cold War
    * Competition Launch! Win Copys of Half Life 2 Episode 1 to play upcoming mod Enterprise: Temporal Cold War
    * Star Trek Conquest Review by Zach and Kinneas
    * Mod Weekly 18 from Croesus – Featuring a Review of RPG-X V2.0
    * Fleet Radio – Brad Sucks with Bad Attraction. Fleet Radio promotes the idea of radio and media within Star Trek Online.
    * Star Trek Online Screenshot Discussion by Zach and Kinneas
    * “Something is Missing” – Free Fan Games Segment by Zach
    * Hosts Zach and Kinneas say “Goodbye” and End the Show.
As always - we appreciate any comments and suggestions that you may like to make about Hailing Frequency. To that end, if you do have any comments to make, please visit our forums at http://www.hailingfrequency.co.uk/boards/
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-40-09122007.mp3" length="46291001" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-40-09122007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 02:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:04:16</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode 39 - Star Trek Conquest and More!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Summer break is over, and Hailing Frequency is back. I hope you all had a fun summer - the team here at Hailing Frequency have certainly been busy - I myself have been transitioning to a new job here in the UK, as well as moving - croesus has been working hard at hs place of work, as well as testing a whole bunch of new mods, and kinneas has been slogging away producing tons of new artwork for various projects.
So, without further ado, we give you, Episode 39 of Hailing Frequency. This one was meant to be released on sunday, but due to some issues with my ISP (talktalk) not letting me upload, it was delayed until today, so sorry for that - send your complaints to TalkTalk, part of the Carphone Warehouse.
Show Notes:
Star Trek Gaming News with K'sua'indra (Tons of New News!)
Star Trek Conquest Discussion! Wiiiiiiii
Mod Weekly covering Kobayashi Maru 1.0, DS9FX and Ultimate Universe
Fleet Radio featuring Arthur Yoria
Tons More!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-39-160907.mp3" length="32250984" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-39-160907.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2007 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:54:17</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode 38 ft Starfleet Command and The Sacawegea in Second Life</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This week, we start out the show as always, with the Star Trek Gaming News, before moving swiftly into discussing that old trek gaming classic - starfleet command one.

Additionally, we also have all of our usual segments, including a VERY informative STOzone from Mr Juliano, and an action packed Mod Weekly from our amazing Croesus, who this talks about DS9:FX for Bridge Commander, Ultimate Universe for Legacy, and The Legendary Generations also for Legacy!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-38-080707.mp3" length="47991891" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-38-080707.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:54:17</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode 37 ft The Crew of Enterprise TCW</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This week, we start out the show as always, with the Star Trek Gaming News, before moving swiftly into discussing the current state of Bethesda Softworks, with the Trek Gaming Franchise. Will there be more Trek Games, and will they be a success - Or are we doomed for the next 3½ years?

Additionally, we also have all of our usual segments, including a VERY informative STOzone from Mr Juliano, and an action packed Mod Weekly from our amazing Croesus, who this week reviews sits down with three guys from the Enterprise Temporal Cold War Mod.

On Fleet Radio this week, Hailing Frequency supports one of its long term contributing artists, Arthur Yoria, who is currently vying to win a competition over at ZigZagLive.com

Head on over and cast your vote for him!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-37-27052007.mp3" length="47991891" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-37-27052007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2007 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:04:17</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode 36 ft Brice Campbell, Commander of Second Life Starfleet</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
First of all folks, an apology - it has been three weeks since the last episode of Hailing Frequency, this was due to some personal issues in both mine, and Kinnea(s) life - however all has past now, and we're back on track.

This week, the show is predominantly focused around Star Trek in Second Life. We sit down and speak to Admiral Brice Campbell, Leader of Starfleet in Second Life. On top of this, we hear from a number of the members of SL Starfleet, and we also launch a 4 part report entitled "7 days in Starfleet" - which is based around my experiences over seven days, in Second Life.

Additionally, we also have all of our usual segments, including a VERY informative STOzone from Mr Juliano, and an action packed Mod Weekly from our amazing Croesus, who this week reviews the Ultimate Universe Mod for Star Trek Legacy.

Not forgetting the Star Trek Gaming News, and Fleet Radio, all of this adds up to another amazing episode of Hailing Frequency.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-36-06052007.mp3" length="77991891" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-36-06052007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:48:17</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode 35 ft Mike Strobel, Developer of Star Trek Supremacy</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Hard to believe its been two weeks since the last episode of Hailing Frequency - but i guess the saying "time flys when your having fun" is true.

Its been a rollar coaster ride here on Hailing Frequency over the last couple of weeks, with over 300 new members registering at a rate of 20 per day - and with all these new members, the forums have burst to life!

This week, we sit down and speak to Mike Strobel, who is the genious behind the independant game project, Star Trek Supremacy! During this interview we not only cover the basic frequents, we talk about some more in depth topics, so that new comers and long time fans of Supremacy, can all get something from the interview.

Additionally, we also have all of our usual segments, including a hilarious STOzone from Mr Juliano, and an action packed Mod Weekly from our amazing Croesus.

We also feature a number of shoutouts directed at Perpetual Entertainment, thanking them for all their hard work on Star Trek Online!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-35-15042007.mp3" length="57879944" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-35-15042007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2007 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:20:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode 34 ft Ryan Denning, Lead Artist for Stsr Trek Online</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
We are very happy to release Episode 34 of Hailing Frequency.

In this Episode, we sit down with Ryan Dening, Lead Artist for Perpetual Entertainments Star Trek Online, and chat about the various
aspects of the project for almost 90 minites.

The interview is chocked full of interesting little tid-bits of information, as well as some fairly large chunks of info too!

On top of all this, our hit cast return with their usual segments - K'suan'indra brings us the Star Trek Gaming News, Croesus brings us Mod Weekly, Kinneas brings us Fleet Radio, and Mr Juliano brings us STOzone!

Coinciding with the release of this podcast, we have also launched the new Hailing Frequency Website and Forum designs - The website is designed now to by simplistic, yet high impact and attention grabbing, and the forums first the first time, match the site design!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-34-01042007.mp3" length="77696806" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-34-01042007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:47:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode 33</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
In this show, we feature all of the usual segments, including Fleet Radio, Mod Weekly, and the Star Trek Gaming News, as well as a new STOzone, where Mr Juliano speaks about Combat in Star Trek Online, and of course, Faxxers Fleet Gossip.
On top of all of this, Zach sits down with Mr Dan "Devil" Jones, Leader of Red Squadrens - A Star Trek Gaming Clan thats been around for almost 9 years - we discuss what exactly it takes to keep a clan going for such a long time.
Additionally, Zach and Kinneas chat about all of the latest Star Trek Online information thats been released over the past few weeks at the Game Developers Conferance.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-33-25032007.mp3" length="45773758" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-33-25032007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:03:33</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode 32</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Episode 32 covers a variety of different topics, from the latest Legacy Mods, too what will be needed to entice older people to play Star Trek Online - be sure to check it out!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-32-18022007.mp3" length="40518014" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-32-18022007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2007 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:56:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Breaking News Dated Feburary 9th 2007</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
This is a breaking news podcast regarding the upcoming announcement from Bethesda Softworks.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-BN-09022007.mp3" length="2034839" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-BN-09022007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:00:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #31</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
The moment i am sure alot of you have been anticipating and looking forward too has arrived.
Hailing Frequency 31 is now released - first of all i would like to apolagise for the delay and explain - we have tried out a new recording and ost prodction tecnique in this show, which involved recording each participant on an individual channel - seperatly editing each of those channels, then syncing them up and merging them to produce the final audio stream - this has all taken a bit of time, however we hope you will notice an increase verbal audio quality.
Anyway folks, onto the show.
We have taken up a dominantly STO theme in this show (Star Trek Online) with only a little bit of Legacy stuff, so Legacy Lovers please forgive us. Myself and Kinneas talk alot about various recent developments in the Star Trek Online world, whilst K'sua'nindra our sexy vulcan, gives us the latest Trek Gaming News from accross the board.
Croesus comes to us with a 10min Mod Weekly about all things Legacy, and a status report on Victor1sts roof, so be sure to check that out, and once again, Mr Juliano joins us with another STOzone segment, focusing on the Ecomony in Star Trek Online.
Topping off the show, Faxxer brings us a Valentines Special of Fleet Gossip
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-31-07022007.mp3" length="40268753" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-31-07022007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2007 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:00:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #30 - Welcome to 07</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Episode Number 30 of Hailing Frequency is hereby released, and features Myself, Kinneas, K'sua'nindra, Croesus, Faxxer and Mr Juliano.
K'suanindra brings us the latest Star Trek Gaming News, featuring all the latest tid-bits from the Trek gaming World, and Croesus brings us an Interview with CaptainSource, of the Enterprise Temporal Cold War project for Half Life 2. Kinneas brings us Fleet Radio, while Mr Juliano hosts Star Trek Online 101. Finally, Faxxer brings us Fleet Gossip, Exploring the Lighter side of STO Life.

Show Notes:

Hosted by Zach21uk and Kinneas
Star Trek Gaming News by K'suanindra
News Addon by Zach21uk
Mod Weekly with Croesus Interview with CaptainSource
Fleet Radio with Kinneas - Kookoon
Star Trek Online 101 by MrJuliano
Faxxers Fleet Gossip
Fleet Radio with Kinneas - The Ultimate Showdown of Ultimate Destiny by Lemon Demon


M-Peg-Layer 3 at 96kbps Stereo
Filesize: 41.3mb
Running Time: 1 hour and 5 seconds
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-30-21012007.mp3" length="43268753" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-30-21012007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2007 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:00:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #29 - The Christmas Special</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Hey Folks!
After a short delay, i am finally happy to release Episode 29 of Hailing Frequency, the Christmas Special. This episode is back dated to the 25th of December for continuity, and features myselfs, kinneas, croesus, and dr photon as the hosts of the show.
During the show we chat about various things, Legacy, the Last 1 year in reflection, what we hope to see next year, as well as having our normal line up of in show segments.
Be sure to visit our forums at www.hailingfrequency.co.uk/boards/ and comment on the show.
Hope you all enjoy the show, and we will see you in the new year.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-29-25122006.mp3" length="47821540" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-29-25122006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2006 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:06:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #28</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Hey Folks,
I am happy to announce that after a two day delay, Episode 28 of Hailing Frequency is finally released.
We start out with the Star Trek Gaming News from Kinneas, and we then move on to have a 15min discussion about our experiences with the Legacy Multiplayer
Next we have Croesus with the Latest Mod Weekly, where he discusses the upcoming "Star Trek 3D" game, and theres also something a little funny at the beginning of the segment
We then all go on too discuss the mods that have been released for Legacy thus far, and the potential for various upcoming mods.
Next we have another hilarious Looney Trek from Dr Photon, including the top ten ways a klingon expresses love!
This show also features two editions of Fleet Radio, the first called "Too Little to Late" and dedicated to Bethesda, and second called "Goodbye to you" dedicated to Argus Array from Kinneas.
As always, we ask you to visit our forums at http://www.hailingfrequency.co.uk/boards/ - register, post, click our ads, etc. Clicks from Our Ads help us pay for our servers to please click once or twice - we would really appreciate it.
From the Entire Hailing Frequency Team, we hope you enjoy the show, and we hope too see many of you entering into our newest Legacy Competition.
Best Wishes
The HF Team
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-28-17122006.mp3" length="45757604" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-28-17122006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2006 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:03:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #27</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Hey Folks,
I am happy to announce that after a two day delay, Episode 27 of Hailing Frequency is finally released.
The delay was due to our good friend, the Flu Virus, which saw fit to declare war on me, and it turn, caused me to loose my voice for a short period, the battle was lost, however the overall war was won, the germs defeated, and here we are.
Episode 27 of Hailing Frequency is yet another milestone and step forward for us, as it sees the most community contributions and segment varietys ever.
We start out the show with a thank you to the developers from the entire community, with new music provided by our sound engineer, faxxer. If you wish too add your audio shoutout to this segment, you can record and e-mail your shout in any format to zach@hailingfrequency.co.uk
We then go on to the Latest Star Trek Gaming News from Acidrain, who is making a special guest appearance in this episode.
Myself and Photon then go on too discuss the recently released Legacy Video showcasing a complete mission from Legacy, and we then listen to the Latest Mod Weekly from Croesus, Hallelujah!.
Later on in the show, we hear from Mindwipe, who brings us all the latest Buzz at CUGS, Dr Photon who brings us another hilarious edition of Looney Trek, Kinneas who brings us anothe Fleet Radio, Faxxer who brings us Fleet Gossip, and to top all of that off, we launch a brand new Legacy Competition where you, the community, get a chance to win a brand new copy of the soon to be released Star Trek Legacy, for the PC.
As always, we ask you to visit our forums at http://www.hailingfrequency.co.uk/boards/ - register, post, click our ads, etc. Clicks from Our Ads help us pay for our servers to please click once or twice - we would really appreciate it.
From the Entire Hailing Frequency Team, we hope you enjoy the show, and we hope too see many of you entering into our newest Legacy Competition.
Best Wishes
The HF Team
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-27-05122006.mp3" length="52020516" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-27-05122006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2006 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:07:43</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Special - Interview #3 With Rantz Hoseley (Quicksilver Software)</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Hey Folks,
You get an extra episode of Hailing Frequency this month, as we are releasing this special edition of Hailing Frequency featuring a 45 minite (edited down from 84mins) interview with Rantz Hoseley, Creative Director for Tactical Assault.
During the interview we chat about Sales Figures, Alcohol, Modding, the Playstation 3, and the general reaction to Tactical Assault from the gaming world.
We also have another interesing episode of Fleet Radio, Featuring Weird Al Yankovic's "Your Pitiful"
Hope you all enjoy the show!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-26112006.mp3" length="41604458" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-26112006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2006 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:57:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #26</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
Hey Folks
That time has come again, hard to believe its been two weeks already since the last Hailing Frequency, but i guess thats just the way of the world, time flys  when your having fun, or working a full time job.
This week we once again have a jam packed show for you, starting off, kinneas gives us all the latest trek gaming related news, and following on from that, we hear Dr Photons latest Looney Trek.
After Looney Trek, We go on to talk for a couple of minites about a new service that Hailing Frequency is offering, Free Community Web Hosting, on either a sub-domain or properly registered domain. For more info on this you can check out our forums.
Following on from this, we hear the latest Mod Weekly from Croesus, where he has exclusive access to a brand new DS9 mod for Bridge Commander. Details on this mod are again, on our forums, along with some screenshots.
After Mod Weekly, we have the latest Fleet Radio from Kinneas, featuring a guy called Weird Al, who has been around since about 1979 doing parodys of various mainstream songs. This particular one is called "White and Dirty" and is a parody of Chamillionaires "Ridin' Dirty"
Going into the last 25mins of the show, we have a long chat with RMoore about the Legacy Stratergy guide, and manage to get loads of new information about Star Trek Legacy - definetly the most information about Legacy to date! Dr Photon joins me and Kinneas for this part of the show.
Finally, we annouce the winner of the Star Trek Legacy Signed Poster Competition.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-26-19112006.mp3" length="52020516" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-26-19112006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2006 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:12:27</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #25</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Hey Folks,

The moment you have all been waiting for is at hand, the next exciting episode of Hailing Frequency has been released.

I think you are all going to love this weeks show, we start off with the latest edition of the Star Trek Gaming News, where the sexy K'Sua' Nindra, Vulcan Love Slave....Well Ok Just Vulcan, Returns to her usual position hosting the news, We then go into latest Hilarious Edition of Looney Trek from Dr Photon, which recieved high praise last show.

This is followed by a 5 minite chat about Star Trek in Second Life from myself, and we then go into the latest Mod Weekly from the man that everyone loves, Croesus!

Following that, we chat to RMoore about the difficulties of moderating a forum such as this, and about his experiences with Star Trek Tactical Assault, which we go on to briefly review. Croesus join Zach and Kinneas for this interview.

Fleet Radio comes up next, featuring Warp 11's award winning song, Red Alert (Explicit Language Warning in Effect for this Segment)

After fleet radio we reveal the Poster Competition results, and go on to launch another Competition.

Bringing up the rear of the show, we have a special 8min segment for you, however we are keeping this classified top secret, you will have to listen to find out what it is, i think you will all be suitable pleased with it though. Remember, Imitation is the Highest Form of Flattery.

Show Notes:

Hosted by Zach and Kinneas!
Star Trek Gaming News from K'sua'nindra
Looney Trek from Doctor Photon
Star Trek in Second Life
Mod Weekly from Croesus
Interview with RMoore
Fleet Radio ft Warp 11 with Red Alert (www.warp11.com - show your support!)
Competition Results
New Competition
Secret Segment!

Technical Info:

M-Peg Layer 3 at 96kbps Stereo
Filesize: 47.7mb</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-25-05112006.mp3" length="50007606" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-25-05112006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2006 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:09:27</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Special and Argus Array Halloween Special</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous, Tony Tuthill, Victor Mullin, Rhein Buskirk and Scott Murphy</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>This week Hailing Frequency, and Argus Array, the two biggest star trek gaming podcasts on the internet team up to release this halloween special, featuring exclusive news on Tactical Assault, as well as a review of Tactical Assault, we also talk about the Legacy requirements, and launch another Legacy Competition!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-AA-311006.mp3" length="23837746" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-AA-311006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:43:29</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>



<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Special: Warp 11 Interview!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>This weekend Hailing Frequency in association with Fleet Radio, we're able to sit down with Captain Karl Miller of Warp 11 to chat about the band, some of their songs, and a few other things.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-FRS-W11-23102006.mp3" length="25161544" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-FRS-W11-23102006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2006 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:34:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #24</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Starting the show off, Dr Photon brings us a new showly segment that will have even the most stern and most emotionally controlled people, laughing their asses off.

After this, Kinneas and Croesus speak about Star Trek Encounters, and give us a brief rundown and review of the game.

We later feature a 40 minite interview with CaptainSource, Lead Producer of the Enterprise Temporal Cold War Project, and to top of the show, we launch a competition in association with Bethesda, where you have a chance to win some signed Legacy Posters!

Its a long show this week, clocking in at almost 1 hour and 30 minites

Shows Notes:

Hosted by Zach and Kinneas
Dr Photons "Looney Trek" (working name)
Mod Weekly Episode 2 - Croesus talks Bridge Commander
Max Loefs Bridge Commander Mod
Fleet Radio - I Love Star Trek by Micheal Roth
Interview with CaptainSource of Enterprise: TCW
Legacy Competition!
And Much Much More!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-24-22102006.mp3" length="60853322" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-24-22102006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:24:30</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #23</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>In this show, we welcome Croesus, from the Startrek.Bethsoft Boards to our team - who has taken over the popular Mod Weekly Segment and Breathed new Life into It!
Additionally, we feature a 5 minite preview of Legacy's Soundtrack, and Kinneas launchs the first in a new series of G4 TV's Interactive Spock Market updates.
Show Notes:
Hosted by Zach
Fleet Radio - Emmasmini - Figure it Out
Mod Weekly - Hosted by Croesus - Armada 2 Fleet Operations 3.0
Learn to Speak Klingon Episode 1
Faxxers Fleet Gossip (but where is faxxer?!)
5 Minite Preview of Legacys Soundtrack
Exclusive Spock Market Updates from Kinneas
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-23-08102006.mp3" length="42074921" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-23-08102006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 8 Oct 2006 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:43:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #22 ft Rantz Hoseley (Quicksilver Software)</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Episode 22 features a 65 minite  interview with Quicksilver Softwares Rantz Hoseley, Creative Producer for Star Trek Tactical Assault
We chatted for an hour about the projects current status, attempted to get a release date, talked about possible future trek projects for Quicksilver, and heard some funny anecdotes from the San Dieago Trek Convention that Rantz Attended a short while ago. We also got answers to a few of the communitys questions.Show Notes:
Hosted by Zach and Kinneas
Interview with Rantz Hoseley
Fleet Radio - Fire by John Jackson
Technical Info: M-peg Layer 3 Encoded at 96kbps
Filesize: 46.4mb
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-22-24092006.mp3" length="48707813" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-22-24092006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:07:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #21 ft Pete Calabria (Mad Doc Software)</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Episode 21 features a 55 minite  interview with Mad Doc Softwares Pete Calabria, Senior 3D Artist for Star Trek Legacy
In this hour long interview, we chatted about various aspects of Legacy, such as what makes legacy next-gen, we chatted about Legacys long and bumpy history, and we get in depth information about the games Modding Tools and Features. On top of this we get answers for dozens of community submitted questions.!
Show Notes:

Hosted by Zach and Kinneas
Interview with Pete Calibria
Fleet Radio - Fountain of Life by Artimus
Technical Info: M-peg Layer 3 Encoded at 96kbps
Filesize: 34.6mb
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-21-23092006.mp3" length="36332398" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-21-23092006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2006 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:50:27</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #20 ft Daron Stinnett (Perpetual Entertainment)</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Episode 20 features a 70 minite long interview with Perpetual Entertainments Daron Stinnett, Executive Producer of Star Trek Online!
Show Notes:
* Hosted by Zach and Kinneas
* 70 minite interview with Daron Stinnett!
* Fleet Radio - Kill Kill Kill Kill Klingons by Warp 11 from their Album Boldy go Down on Me
Technical Info: M-peg Layer 3 Encoded at 112kbps
Filesize: 61.4mb
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-20-170906.mp3" length="64897207" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-20-170906.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2006 23:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:17:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>


<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Special: The Bits you don't Hear!</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Show Notes:
* Hosted by Zach Nicodemous
* Features Kinneas, K'sua'nin'dra, Victor1st and More
Technical Info: M-peg Layer 3 Encoded at 96kbps
Filesize: 9.5mb
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-Bloopers-170906.mp3" length="9899155" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-SE-Bloopers-170906.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2006 23:21:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:13:44</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #19</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Episode 19 is flagged as the comeback episode, and is filled with lots of content, featuring OppdDay2001 who talks about the latest Star Trek Online update, and Mike Strobel speaks about his game, Star Trek Supremacy. We also feature the first in a limited series of fleet radio's, featuring music from trek tribute band, Warp 11!.
Show Notes:
    * Hosted by Zach Nicodemous
    * Special Dev Shoutout - Thank You!
    * Star Trek Gaming News (read by our Soong Type B-4 Android)
    * Fleet Radio 1 - Here to Stay by Arthur Yoria
    * OpdDay2001 speaks about Star Trek Online
    * Update on Community Created Trek Games
    * Interview with Mike Strobel on Star Trek Supremacy
    * New Hailing Frequency Competition Launched
    * Fleet Radio 2 - She Make it So by Warp 11 from their Album Boldy go Down on Me
Technical Info: M-peg Layer 3 Encoded at 96kbps
Filesize: 37.4mb</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-19-170906.mp3" length="39274093" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-19-170906.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2006 22:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:54:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Special: The Best of Fleet Radio</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>To celebrate the re-launching of Hailing Frequency after a period of 2-3 months of the air, we are launching 4 new episodes of Hailing Frequency today.
To that end, Here is Number 1 in this 4-episodes marathon for today, Sunday 17th September 2006.
Over 18 Episodes of Hailing Frequency, we have featured apoximatly 25 Fleet Radios, each of them featuring great music as chosen by Kinneas.
We we decided it was about time that we did a "Top 10 Best of Fleet Radio" show - and to that end, that is what we have produced for the first release in the 4-episode marathon.
Show Notes:
    * Hosted by Zach and Kinneas
    * 10 to 1 Countdown Best Fleet Radios
    * Advertisments for our new sponsor CUGs are also Featured.
    * Number 1 "winner" celebration featuring fireworks display!
Technical Info: M-peg Layer 3 Encoded at 96kbps
Filesize: 43.9mb</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-BOFR-170906.mp3" length="46134880" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-BOFR-170906.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2006 21:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:04:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #18 ft Gary Conti and Rantz Hoseley (Mad Doc Software and Quicksilver Software)</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Hailing Frequency Episode #18! Featuring interviews with Mad Doc Software and Quicksilver Software
Again i would just like to remind everybody to check out the Hailing Frequency Website, along with the Hailing Frequency ONLINE SHOP @ http://cafepress.com/hfpodcast
Hope everyone enjoys it - And remember - this is a community podcast - So do not hesitate to Send in audio clips
and submissions to submisssions@hailingfrequency.co.uk</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-18-20060721.mp3" length="8727310" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-18-20060721.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 July 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:12:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #18 Teaser</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Here is a teaser for Episode 18 of Hailing Frequency, which features an interview with Mad Doc's Gary conti, and Quicksilver's Rantz Hosely.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/Ep18Promo.mp3" length="8727310" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/Ep18Promo.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:02:17</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #17</title>
<itunes:author>Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Featuring: Star Trek Legacy video from the greatest web-site in the universe, 'TOM'S HARDWARE', WILDCARD from Trek-Online.com, A Fleet Radio Slideshow with the music of BRAD SUCKS (an homage to GENE R!), STOnet's Fleet Gossip (by Faxxer), STAR TREK ONLINE's COMPLETE 'Deck 7' gallery drawings by legendary TREK artist, Andrew Probert...
...also includes v.2 of the Fleet Radio slideshow of Arthur Yoria's 'Strange Grin'

Zach21UK is on shore leave, so Kinneas was in charge of putting this episode all together by himself.
( maybe Zach will hurry up and come back now. )
-Kinneas</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-17-20060601.mp3" length="8727310" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-17-20060601.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 1 Jun 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #16</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Here it is folks, finally, Episode 16 of Hailing Frequency is out!

Apolagies for the long delay (6weeks) since the last show, ive been busy moving homes so everything has been a bit hectic.

Show Notes:

    * Hosted by Zach and  Kinneas
    * Star Trek Gaming News [05:00]
    * Hailing Frequency Competition Results [07:12]
    * The Victor1st Zone [09:25]
    * Fleet Gossip Episode 5 from Faxxer of STOnet [27:45]
    * Fleet Radio - Lemondemon - Telekinesis [29:45]
    * Interview with DIf-Josh, Founder of Consortium Ultimate Gamers [35:20]
    * New Competition [42:40]
    * Mod Weekly - Armada 2, 2.5 mod [45:15]
    * Closing Music [50:20]

Another excellent show if i do say so myself, i know its been a long time since the last one, but i think everyone will agree this has been worth the wait.

Fleet Gossip is just SOOO Hilarious this week, even though its so short.

The Interview with Josh from CUGs is short but very sweet, and Mod Weekly is also cool this week.

by far my favorite this week though, Fleet Radio - that song is just so damn good, catchy too, i cant stop listening to it!!!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-16-300406.mp3" length="39914113" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-16-30042006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 1 May 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:55:25</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #15 ft Perpetual Entertainment</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Here it is folks, finally, Episode 15 of Hailing Frequency is out!

Show Notes:

    * Hosted by Zach and  Kinneas
    * Interview with Daron Stinnett- Executive Producer of Star Trek Online
    * Fleet Gossip Episode 4 from Faxxer of STOnet
    * Fleet Radio - Arthur Yoria - Just Like You
    * Danos Commentary
    * Hailing Frequency Competition!

All i Can say is WOW!

What a Fun time everybody had making this week's episode!

Chatting with Daron was such an honour, and a laugh too! He is a funny guy!

Add on too all that a Rap-Tastic episode of Fleet Gossip from Faxxer, and another fantastic arthur yoria fleet radio, and we have a hit!!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-15-20060312.mp3" length="55819242" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-15-20060312.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:17:31</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #14</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Here it is folks, finally, Episode 14 of Hailing Frequency is out!

Show Notes:

    * Hosted by Zach and  Kinneas
    * Opening Music - EF Trance
    * Interview with ChessMess about his New Job
    * Star Trek Gaming News from Ksuaindra
    * Fleet Gossip Episode 4 from Faxxer of STOnet
    * The Victor1st Zone - Clans BEWARE!
    * Fleet Radio - Breech: Holiday
    * Stylsy Speaks on Legacy!
    * Closing Commentary from Zach and  Kinneas

Community Submissions have gone through the roof lately, and to that end, there was
not time to play ALL the submissions on this weeks show!
But Never Fear, if it wasnt played this time, it will go out on the next show!

I have too say thanks though, the community has been great! All these submissions,
without them it would not have been possible to get another show out so quickly!

As always, Me and Kinneas had a real good time doing the show, and we look forward to reading all of your comments on the show!

Hope everyone enjoys it - And remember - this is a community podcast - So do not hesitate to Send in audio clips
and submissions to zach@hailingfrequency.co.uk</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-14-20060226.mp3" length="49243307" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-14-20060226.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:08:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Breaking News 22nd Feburary 2006</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary></itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/BreakingNews/HFBN-022206.mp3" length="4227310" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/BreakingNews/HFBN-022206.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:03:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #13</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Here it is folks, finally, Episode 13 of Hailing Frequencys is out!

Show Notes:

    * Hosted by Zach and  Kinneas
    * Opening Music - Robert Picardo and Jeri Ryan a.k.a Seven and the Doctor - You Are my Sunshine
    * ....Perhaps Not
    * Real Opening Music - Elite Force Frag
    * Fleet Gossip - Episode 2 of this Exciting new Segment from STO-net's Faxxer
    * Community Submission - ZTrike Talks Star Trek Online!
    * Fleet Radio - The King: by C. Lane
    * Interview with Chris Jones - Famed Modder in the Star Trek Gaming Community (Conducted by Zach, Kinneas, and Victor1st from Star Trek Gamers
    * Closing Commentary from Zach and  Kinneas

Two weeks since the last show, and hardly enough time!

Community Submissions have gone through the roof lately, and to that end, there was
not time to play ALL the submissions on this weeks show!
But Never Fear, if it wasnt played this time, it will go out on the next show!

I have too say thanks though, the community has been great! All these submissions,
without them it would not have been possible to get another show out so quickly!

As always, Me and Kinneas had a real good time doing the show, and we look forward
to reading all of your comments on the show!

Hope everyone enjoys it - And remember - this is a community podcast - So do not hesitate to Send in audio clips
and submissions to zach@hailingfrequency.co.uk</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-13-20060207.mp3" length="50642709" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-13-20060207.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 2 Feb 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:12:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #12</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill and Victor Mullin</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Show Notes:

    * Hosted by Zach and  Kinneas
    * Special Guest Host - Victor 1st of Star Trek Gamers
    * Opening Music - Robert Picardo a.k.a The Doctor - La Donne Imobbile
    * Opening Commentary from Zach, Kinneas and  Victor
    * The Victor1st Zone
    * Fleet Radio - Arthur Yoria - Strange Grin
    * Commentary from Zach, Kinneas and  Victor - Discussing Legacy, and Tactical Alert
    * Advertisement Break
    * Commentary from Zach and  Kinneas and  Victor - A Goodbye to Harry Lang!
    * Fleet Gossip - A New Segment from STO-net's Faxxer
    * Closing Commentary from Zach, Kinneas and  Victor

Almost a Month since the last show - but hey, you know what they say, Quality is Better than quantity....Right?

Well Quality is definetly one word to descirbe the show this week.

With the announement of the new trek games, we decided to bring in Victor this week to do the show with us - and i have to say - it was a laugh - Contrary to what everyone thinks - and although Victor probably wont admit it - He's a very nice guy at heart!

After several hours, multiple bloopers, and some laughs on the top, this show was the result!

To top it off, we have a new segment this week from Faxxer of STO.net - and, although i personally had no clue what he was talking about, I found his on-air attitude and demeanor very refreshing - he is the type of guy who, even if you have no clue what on earth he is talking about - you can still follow him, and laugh with him!

Additionally, this show, Kinneas has worked hard, and has once again produced a wonderful video accompniment for this show - definetly worth checking out folks!

Hope everyone enjoys it - And remember - this is a community podcast - So do not hesitate to Send in audio clips and submissions to zach@hailingfrequency.co.uk</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-12-20060122.mp3" length="43136546" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://www.shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-12-20060122.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2006 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:59:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #11</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Special XMAS Edition!

Show Notes:

* Hosted by Zach and  Kinneas
* Opening Welcome and  Opening XMAS Music!
* Opening Commentary from Zach and  Kinneas
* The Victor1st Zone
* Commentary from Zach and  Kinneas
* Fleet Radio
* Commentary from Zach and  Kinneas
* Interview With Leia Fortain of Destinys Wind
* Commentary from Zach and  Kinneas
* Star Trek Gaming News by K'suanindra
* Commentary from Zach and  Kinneas
* Segment from Stylsy
* Closing Commentary from Zach and  Kinneas

Its a long one this week, clocking in at 68 minutes, and it is also 47.3 megabytes - sorry dialup users!!!
Enjoy!!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-11-20051225.mp3" length="49649162" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-11-20051225.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:08:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #10</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Some of you may be wondering why i pulled the MP3 version of Hailing Frequency earlier this week.

The answer is, our main man Kinnea's has been working his butt of for the last two weeks to produce a VIDEO PODCAST of Hailing Frequency 10!!

So as not to limit our audience, we are releasing several versions of the show to accomadate all people.

There shall be the standard standalone audio show, an apple quicktime version which is optimised for video ipods and viewable in quicktime or itunes, and later on, there will be a .avi.

Low and Behold, it is HERE!

Show Notes:

    * Hosted by ChessMess and Zach!!!!
    * Opening Welcome and  Opening Music!
    * Opening Commentary from Zach and  Chess
    * Fleet Radio
    * Commentary from Zach and  Chess
    * Segment From Victor1st from Star Trek Gamers
    * Commentary from Chess and  Zach and  Holly (chessmess's baby)
    * Star Trek Gaming News by Kayswanindra
    * Closing Commentary from Chess and Zach
    * Outro Song - Star Trekking (oh no!!)
    * Video by Kinneas

Its a long one this week, clocking in at 71 minutes, and it is also 50 megabytes - sorry dialup users!!!

Sorry about not having any new shows for almost a month, but we have more than made up for it this one! This show has it all, including many laughable moments!!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-10-2005-11-28.mp3" length="50421888" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-10-2005-11-28.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 2 Dec 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:10:01</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Breaking News 2nd November 2005</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary></itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/BreakingNews/HFBN-110205.mp3" length="1727310" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/BreakingNews/HFBN-110205.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 2 Nov 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:02:26</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #9</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Show Notes:

* Opening Welcome
* Star Trek Gaming News
* Fleet Radio
* Interview with Kresimir Spes of TNZ2
* Closing Comment
* Outro Song

Its a Short one this week, only 30mins long, its been a quiet two weeks since the last show, not alot to talk about.

Anyway, i hope you all enjoy the show.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://hailingfrequency.co.uk/shows/HF-09-20051031.mp3" length="21908689" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://hailingfrequency.co.uk/shows/HF-09-20051031.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:30:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #8</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous and Tony Tuthill</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Show Notes:

    * Opening Welcome
    * Segment from Victor from the STG
    * Star Trek Gaming News
    * Fleet Radio
    * Segment from Demosthenes from STO.net

    * Mod Weekly - Koyasyashi Maru mod for Star Trek: Bridge Commander
    * Closing Comment
    * Outro Song</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-08-20051016.mp3" length="23934640" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-08-20051016.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:49:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #7</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Another Excellent Podcast From Mua - Zach21uk

The Longest one Yet at 59mins!!

If your not listening then your missing out!

SPECIAL ON THIS WEEKS EPISODE!

Interview with Gavin Turfrey - Lead Dev of BOTFII !!!!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-07-20050925.mp3" length="41485792" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-07-20050925.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:57:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #6</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Another Excellent Podcast From Mua - Zach21uk

If your not listening then your missing out!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-06-20050911.mp3" length="28146408" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-06-20050911.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:39:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #5</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Starring guest host Zach21uk! Fetures include guest commentary, new mod weekly coverage, and lots more! Check it out, you don't want to miss it!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-05-20050828.mp3" length="282612340" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-05-20050828.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:33:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #4</title>
<itunes:author>Zach Nicodemous</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Starring guest host Zach21uk! Fetures include guest commentary, new mod weekly coverage, and lots more! Check it out, you don't want to miss it!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-04-20050702.mp3" length="30241182" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-04-20050702.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 2 July 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:42:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #3</title>
<itunes:author>ChessMess</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Episode #3 clocks in at 38mins!

Its a great episode, hope you like it!

Because the server isn't the normal location I'm not going to update the Blog and thus the RSS feeds, so you'll have to download it via the link below manually. Sorry!

I'm going to be unable to make a cast next week, so it'll be two weeks until the next one.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-03-20050615.mp3" length="27358824" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/HF-03-20050615.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 16 June 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:37:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #2</title>
<itunes:author>ChessMess</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/startrek-games_podcast_02.mp3" length="14504919" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/startrek-games_podcast_02.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:30:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

<item>
<title>Hailing Frequency Episode #1</title>
<itunes:author>ChessMess</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>It is with great excitement that Star Trek Gaming Universe brings you another first in the world of Star Trek gaming! We'd like to officially announce Hailing Frequency, the first and only podcast created for Star Trek Gamers!!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/startrek-games_podcast_01.mp3" length="15996103" type="audio/x-mp3" />
<guid>http://shows.hailingfrequency.com/startrek-games_podcast_01.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2005 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:33:19</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Star Trek, Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Podcast, Star Trek Gaming Podcast, Star Trek Games, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Online News, Star Trek Gaming News, Cryptic Studios, Perpetual Entertainment, Star Trek Gaming, STGU, Sci Fi, Games, Sci Fi Games, Science Fiction, Legacy, Tactical Assault, Star Trek Online, Star Trek Legacy, Star Trek Encounters, Encounters</itunes:keywords></item>

</channel>
</rss>