<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>AMStunes Alt Podcast</title>
<link>http://www.amstunes.co.uk/radio/podcast/</link>
<description>Best new original alternative music from all over the globe, including Electric Fan Death as DJs.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>AMStunes.co.uk 2009</copyright>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 09:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<webMaster>info@amstunes.co.uk (Steven Wilson)</webMaster>
<ttl>800</ttl>
<atom:link href="http://www.amstunes.co.uk/radio/podcast/tracks/AMStunes_Alternative_podcast.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<itunes:author>info@amstunes.co.uk</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>AMStunes Alt Podcast: The best new original alternative music from all over the globe, including Electric Fan Death as DJs.
</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>
The AMStunes Alt Podcast is a selection of original alternative music including many genres; indie, alternative, rock, grunge, punk, post punk, folk, dance, electronica, electro, soundscape and more. Featuring Ste and Ollie from Electric Fan Death as DJs sometimes with special guests. Listen to Ste Wilson and Ollie Philpott chat about life, whilst playing a selection of some of the best alternative music around.
Enjoy. 
</itunes:summary>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Steven Wilson</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>info@amstunes.co.uk</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:image href="http://www.amstunes.co.uk/radio/podcast/images/itunespodcastimage.png"/>  
<itunes:category text="Music">
</itunes:category>
<item>
<title>AMStunes Alt Podcast 2 - Eat Our Music</title>
<description>Eat Our Music You Greedy People - Some more great new alternative music from Myspace and beyond with Electric Fan Death (EFD) as DJs. Featuring an exclusive play of Shooting Shadows from Electric Fan Death's Debut EP - Yeosu Dangerous. Loads of great bands and artists including Veto, Popolo, Longwave, Vox Equinox, Greg Whalen and more. Some druncken banter from the lads about climbing lamp-posts to listen to music, Ollies American dream, their time in Thailand and Ollies first Korean Scottish kiss.
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.amstunes.co.uk/radio/podcast/tracks/AMStunes_Alternative_Podcast_Real2.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.amstunes.co.uk/radio/podcast/tracks/AMStunes_Alternative_Podcast_Real2.mp3" length="68186112" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:author>info@amstunes.co.uk (Steven Wilson)
</itunes:author>
<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>
The second AMStunes Alt Podcast - listen in for some great original tunes for free. 
</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary> Electric Fan Death's Ollie Philpott and Ste Wilson return for the second AMStunes Alternative Podcast. Playing loads of great artists and bands including Popolo, Longwave, Vox Equinox, Siegfried Sassoon and loads more. AMStunes artists in the playlist include Electric Fan Death with an exclusive first play of their track Shooting Shadows from their Yeosu Dangerous EP, John S Wilson and Tear Down The Lies! </itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>01:11:01</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>AMStunes, alt, music, alternative, indie, ste, wilson, ollie, philpott, electric fan death, podcast, Popolo, Vox Equinox, Longwave, Greg Whalen, Siegfried Sassoon, yeosu dangerous, john s wilson, tear down the lies, veto </itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
<title>AMStunes Alt Podcast 1 - Listen Or Die</title>
<description>Best new original alternative music including Electric Fan Death as DJs. Playing tracks from AMStunes artists with an exclusive play of Books On Buildings from Electric Fan Death's Yeosu Dangerous EP, Tear Down The Lies! and John S Wilson's dark electro sound. Cuba Cuba, The Areola Treat, Miss The Occupier, Get In Get Out and Be A Familiar are just a few of the great artists we have in store for you.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2009 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid>http://www.amstunes.co.uk/radio/podcast/tracks/AMStunes_Alternative_Podcast_Real.mp3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://www.amstunes.co.uk/radio/podcast/tracks/AMStunes_Alternative_Podcast_Real.mp3" length="76201984" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:author>info@amstunes.co.uk (Steven Wilson)
</itunes:author>
<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>
Welcome to the AMStunes Alt Podcast hosted by Ste and Ollie from Electric Fan Death. 
</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary> Ste and Ollie from Electric Fan Death talk about music the world and everything whilst playing a selection of some of the best alternative music around. From the alternative indie of EFD and Cuba Cuba to live tracks from Be A Familiar and Endor to alternative electro from John S Wilson and Tear Down The Lies.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>01:19:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>AMStunes, alt, music, alternative, indie, ste, wilson, ollie, philpott, electric fan death, podcast, the poems</itunes:keywords>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>