<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
<channel>

		<title>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Podcasts from The Hub</title>
		<link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub</link>
		<copyright>&#xA9; 2008 Yamaha Corporation of America </copyright>
		<image>
	  			<url>http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/podcasts_icon_keys.jpg</url>
	  			<title>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Podcasts from The Hub</title>
				<link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub/</link>
		</image>
		<itunes:image href="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/podcasts_icon_keys.jpg" />
		<description>Hear it from the experts. From product announcements to artist clinics and exclusive concerts, the Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Podcasts are your connection to the very latest information about all Yamaha keyboards and pianos. Video and audio podcast episodes focus on digital pianos, portable keyboards, Arius, YDP, entry-level portables, lighted instruments, arranger workstations, contemporary, professional stage pianos, music labs and educational keyboards, pianos, Clavinovas, pianos for worship and more in the jazz, world music, pop and classical idioms.</description>
		<language>en-us</language>

		<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
      <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 08:00:00 PDT</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<itunes:owner>
		<itunes:name>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Podcasts</itunes:name>

		<itunes:email>thehub@yamaha.com</itunes:email>
		</itunes:owner>
		<itunes:category text="Music" />
		<managingEditor>thehub@yamaha.com</managingEditor>
		<webMaster>thehub@yamaha.com</webMaster>	
		
	<item>
		<title>Yamaha Artist Services, Inc 'Best of' Piano Performances Part 2</title>
		<link>https://www.yamaha.com/thehub/default.html?CNTID=5008074</link>
		<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
		<description>Since its establishment in April, 1987 in New York City, Yamaha Artist Services, Inc. (YASI) has gained widespread recognition for its professional service and devotion to the global performing arts community. Experience a few of the spectacular performances from the Piano Salon in Part 2 of this exclusive 5-year anniversary episode on The Hub. Visit www.yamaha.com/yasi to learn more about Yamaha Artist Services, Inc. Check out www.yamaha.com/thehub to see more exclusive content from this very special concert and recital facility. You can also follow us at www.twitter.com/theyamahahub.</description>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2009 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

		<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/YASI_2_0509.m4v?rssid=5008074&amp;et=Scott_Krippayne_Alive_Again&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fYASI_2_0509.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="186440" type="x-video/m4v" />
s
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Scott Krippayne Alive Again</title>
		<link>https://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5008074</link>
		<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
		<description>Check out Scott perform one of his many hits on the Yamaha Clavinova. Over 150 of his songs have been recorded by artists including Point of Grace, John Tesh, Avalon, Jaci Velasquez, FFH, True Vibe and Sandi Patty. Enjoy the song Alive Again. From The Hub of all things Yamaha. www.yamahahub.com.</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

		<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/scott_krippayne_0808.m4v?rssid=5008074&amp;et=Scott_Krippayne_Alive_Again&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fscott_krippayne_0808.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="44724224" type="x-video/m4v" />

	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Yamaha P85 Digital Piano</title>
		<link>https://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5008003</link>
		<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
		<description>Authentic, natural sound, remarkable expressiveness and full Yamaha quality in a compact, affordable piano. This short overview video demonstrates the streamline design of the Yamaha P85 Contemporary Piano. From The Hub of all things Yamaha. www.yamahahub.com.</description>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		
		<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/dp_p85_010108.m4v?rssid=5008003&amp;et=Yamaha_P85_Digital_Piano&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fdp_p85_010108.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="22458368" type="x-video/m4v" />

	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Yamaha Arius Digital Pianos</title>
		<link>https://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5008002</link>
		<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
		<description>This short overview video provides an overview of the YDP140 and YDP160 Arius Digital Pianos. From The Hub of all things Yamaha. www.yamahahub.com.</description>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2008 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

		<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/dp_arius_010108.m4v?rssid=5008002&amp;et=Yamaha_Arius_Digital_Pianos&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fdp_arius_010108.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="24391680" type="x-video/m4v" />

	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Modus Product Video</title>
		<link>https://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5020303</link>
		<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
		<description>The Modus H01 combines true piano sound in a modern, attractive cabinet that evokes the beauty of an acoustic grand piano - adding sophistication and musical expressiveness to your living space. A futuristic appearance, supreme sonic power and audio quality combined with meticulous attention to detail will ensure that the H01 is an instrument which defines the player - and makes a bold statement of contemporary living. Presented by Peter Baartmans. On The Hub of all things Yamaha, www.yamahahub.com.</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

		<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/MODUS_0908.m4v?rssid=5020303&amp;et=Modus_Product_Video&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fMODUS_0908.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="96008973" type="x-video/m4v" />

	</item>
				
	  <item>
         <title>Music at the Disneyland Resort - 2008</title>
         <link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5021543</link>
		 <itunes:author>Yamaha Winds Instrument Department</itunes:author>
         <description>Learn about the talented Disneyland ® cast members who depend on Yamaha instruments every day, helping to take your special celebration to a new level and enhance the overall Disneyland ® experience. From Main Street to Innoventions to Tom Sawyer Island to Sleeping Beauty's Castle, hear these unique individuals share their favorite Disneyland ® musical memories. From The Hub of all things Yamaha. www.yamahahub.com  -- Feel free to send your comments and suggestions to thehub@yamaha.com.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 08:30:00 PDT</pubDate>

		 <enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/winds/musicians_1008.m4v?rssid=5021543&amp;et=Music_at_the_Disneyland_Resort-2008&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2Fpodcasts%2Fwinds%2Fmusicians_1008.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="163008512" type="x-video/m4v" />
      </item>
	  
	  <item>
         <title>Disneyland All-American College Band – 2008</title>
         <link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5023885</link>
		 <itunes:author>Yamaha Winds Instrument Department</itunes:author>
         <description>Learn about the talented Disneyland ® cast members who depend on Yamaha instruments every day, helping to take your special celebration to a new level and enhance the overall Disneyland ® experience. From Main Street to Tomorrowland, hear these unique individuals share their experiences as part of the All-American College Band. 

From The Hub of all things Yamaha. www.yamahahub.com  -- Feel free to send your comments and suggestions to thehub@yamaha.com.
</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 08:30:00 PDT</pubDate>

		<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/winds/Disneyland_AA_College_Band_1108.m4v?rssid=5023885&amp;et=Disneyland_All-American_College_Band–2008&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2Fpodcasts%2Fwinds%2FDisneyland_AA_College_Band_1108.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="194882999" type="x-video/m4v" />

      </item>
	  
	  	<item>
			<title>Yamaha Music Education System</title>
			<link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5024278</link>
			<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
			<description>Find out about the Yamaha Music Education System - its history, programs and events. But most of all, find out why YMES is so wonderful for children. From The Hub of all things Yamaha. www.yamahahub.com.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2008 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

			<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/ymes_intro_1208.m4v?rssid=5024278&amp;et=Yamaha_Music_Education_System&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fymes_intro_1208.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="102771082" type="x-video/m4v" />
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>AvantGrand</title>
			<link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5028033</link>
			<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
			<description>At Yamaha, our desire is to craft pianos that bring a little more joy to as many people as possible.
This is a treasured ideal that we have long held dear and one we have now transformed into a new piano. Meditating on those hours of happiness, those indescribable moments of joy experienced at a piano, we decided to do our best to respond to your desires and aspirations for this instrument. AvantGrand. A new identity for the piano, born from the fusion of twenty-first century technology and more than a century of piano-crafting experience. The blissful moment when you and the piano resonate as one ... is here. From The Hub of all things Yamaha. www.yamahahub.com.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

			<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/avantgrand_0109.m4v?rssid=5028033&amp;et=AvantGrand&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2favantgrand_0109.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="42360832" type="x-video/m4v" />
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Kakegawa Piano Factory Tour</title>
			<link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5029381</link>
			<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
			<description>Join us for this exclusive tour through the ‘birthplace of Yamaha Pianos', the Kakegawa factory in Japan. From soundboard gluing to sideboard assembly through stringing and regulation – see the process from fine materials to finished work of art. From The Hub of all Things Yamaha, www.yamaha.com/thehub.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

			<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/kakegawa_factory_tour.m4v?rssid=5029381&amp;et=Kakegawa_Piano_Factory_Tour&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fkakegawa_factory_tour.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="75504663" type="x-video/m4v" />
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Disklavier E3 Overview</title>
			<link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5029960</link>
			<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
			<description>The E3—which stands for Easy Enjoyment with Yamaha Elegance — is a new series of Disklavier performance reproducing pianos offering streamlined features and powerful functionality. Compatible with a range of Yamaha audio products, the E3 represents a breakthrough not only from a value and performance perspective, but also because of its simpler user interface. Get an overview of the main features in this informative video with Sue Downs. From The Hub of all Things Yamaha, www.yamaha.com/thehub.</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

			<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/E3_overview_0309.m4v?rssid=5029960&amp;et=Disklavier_E3_Overview&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fE3_overview_0309.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="151191552" type="x-video/m4v" />
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Yamaha Artist Services, Inc 'Best of' Piano Performances Part 1</title>
			<link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5037700</link>
			<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
			<description>Since its establishment in April, 1987 in New York City, Yamaha Artist Services, Inc. (YASI) has gained widespread recognition for its professional service and devotion to the global performing arts community. YASI is dedicated to meeting the needs of artists, artists' managers, performing arts organizations and educational institutions worldwide. At its current quarters on Fifth Avenue and East 54th Street, Yamaha Artist Services occupies two separate floors, which include the Piano Salon and the Band and Orchestral Atelier. Encompassing the entire third floor, the Piano Salon features an elegant performance venue seating up to 150 and houses a large selection of performance-ready CFIIIS concert grand pianos and Disklavier® reproducing grand pianos The floor also features an artists' lounge, a green room (practice studio), a stage which can accommodate multiple pianos, business offices and a workshop for concert piano technicians. The Piano Salon provides artists with a cutting-edge sound environment which is known as Yamaha Active Field Control (AFC). The sound processing technology of AFC can shape and correct room acoustics with amazing results—even creating authentic simulations of other performing arts venues. The Piano Salon's main room, equipped with a Yamaha projection system, wide screen, and surround sound, can be used to showcase activities such as concerts, master classes, press events and webcasts. Experience a few of the spectacular performances from the Piano Salon in this exclusive 5-year anniversary episode on The Hub. Visit www.yamaha.com/yasi to learn more about Yamaha Artist Services, Inc. Check out www.yamaha.com/thehub to see more exclusive content from this very special concert and recital facility.</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2009 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

			<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/YASI_1_0509.m4v?rssid=5037700&amp;et=Yamaha_Artist_Services,_Inc_'Best_of'_Piano_Performances_Part_1&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fYASI_1_0509.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="166573173" type="x-video/m4v" />
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Yamaha Disklavier Sync - Animusic</title>
			<link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5118735</link>
			<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
			<description>Animusic is a content creation company focused exclusively on computer animation of music. Animusic creates original content, such as "video album" DVDs, but have also produced animations for corporate clients such as HP, Disney, and Texas Instruments.
Animusic graphics and music are entirely digitally synthesized. They "invent" imaginary Virtual Instruments by building computer graphics models of objects that appear to create the sound of the corresponding synthesized music track. Virtual Instruments range from being reminiscent of existing instruments to arbitrarily abstract.  Check out an actual 'live' Disklavier being triggered and performed in sync with 'Starship' from Animusic 3. From The Hub of All Things Yamaha, The Hub. www.yamaha.com/thehub</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

			<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/Animusic_Starship.mov?rssid=5118735&amp;et=Yamaha_Disklavier_Sync_-_Animusic&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fAnimusic_Starship.mov&amp;type=mov" length="47561792" type="video/quicktime" />
		</item>

		 <item>
         <title>Yamaha at NAMM 2011 - Booth Overview</title>
		 <link>http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/namm2011_reel.m4v</link>
		 <itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
         <description>Check out the birds-eye view of the expansive Yamaha exhibit at NAMM 2011. For booth performances (featuring George Shelby, Chris Minh Doky, Don Alder, Lee Ritenour and more) and demos (Tyros4, KARMA Motif and more) - visit yamaha.com/namm. Get all of the Hub content on-the-go by downloading the free Yamaha Hub iOS app on the App Store. http://4wrd.it/hubapp.</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 08:30:00 PDT</pubDate>

		<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/namm2011_reel.m4v?rssid=5162686&amp;et=Yamaha_at_NAMM_2011_-_Booth_Overview&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2Fpodcasts%2Fkeyboards%2Fnamm2011_reel.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="10447379" type="x-video/m4v" />

      </item>

			<item>
			<title>Gordon Goodwin's Big Phat Band Part 1</title>
			<link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5162905</link>
			<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
			<description>Even for a successful composer and arranger in Hollywood, Gordon's numbers are impressive: A 2006 Grammy Award for his Instrumental Arrangement of "Incredits" from the Pixar film "The Incredibles," three Emmy Awards, and eight Grammy nominations. Here's another impressive number to add to the list: Eighteen. As in the number of musicians in Gordon Goodwin's Big Phat Band, one of the most exciting large jazz ensembles on the planet.  Populated by L.A.'s finest players, the Big Phat Band takes the big band tradition into the new millennium with a contemporary, highly original sound featuring Gordon's witty, intricate, and hard-swinging compositions in a veritable grab bag of styles: swing, Latin, blues, classical, rock and even an homage to Looney Tunes. Watch them perform live from Disneyland in this exclusive Yamaha Hub podcast episode. Want to Connect with Yamaha on the go? Make sure to grab the free Yamaha Hub iPhone app - http://4wrd.it/hubapp for the Hub of all things Yamaha.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2011 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

			<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/Big_Phat_Band_1.m4v?rssid=5162905&amp;et=Gordon_Goodwin's_Big_Phat_Band_Part_1&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fBig_Phat_Band_1.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="1086746970" type="x-video/m4v" />
		</item>
		
				<item>
			<title>Gordon Goodwin's Big Phat Band Part 2</title>
			<link>http://www.yamaha.com/thehub/home.html?CNTID=5162906</link>
			<itunes:author>Yamaha Keyboards and Pianos Department</itunes:author>
			<description>Even for a successful composer and arranger in Hollywood, Gordon's numbers are impressive: A 2006 Grammy Award for his Instrumental Arrangement of "Incredits" from the Pixar film "The Incredibles," three Emmy Awards, and eight Grammy nominations. Here's another impressive number to add to the list: Eighteen. As in the number of musicians in Gordon Goodwin's Big Phat Band, one of the most exciting large jazz ensembles on the planet.  Populated by L.A.'s finest players, the Big Phat Band takes the big band tradition into the new millennium with a contemporary, highly original sound featuring Gordon's witty, intricate, and hard-swinging compositions in a veritable grab bag of styles: swing, Latin, blues, classical, rock and even an homage to Looney Tunes. Watch them perform live from Disneyland in this exclusive Yamaha Hub podcast episode. Want to Connect with Yamaha on the go? Make sure to grab the free Yamaha Hub iPhone app - http://4wrd.it/hubapp for the Hub of all things Yamaha.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2011 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate>

			<enclosure url="http://www.yamaha.com/podcasts/keyboards/Big_Phat_Band_2.m4v?rssid=5162906&amp;et=Gordon_Goodwin's_Big_Phat_Band_Part_2&amp;source=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yamaha.com%2fpodcasts%2fkeyboards%2fBig_Phat_Band_2.m4v&amp;type=m4v" length="648272397" type="x-video/m4v" />
		</item>

</channel>
</rss>
