<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
 <rss version="2.0">
	 <channel>
	 	<title>The Speed Scene</title>
	 	<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/</link>
	 	<description>
 A talk radio show that is all about Sportsman Racing. 
 This is the show where you, the local racer, is the star. 
 Race results, schedules, interviews, and product reviews,
 this is the place to hear all about what's going on with
 racing today.
	 	</description>
	 	<language>en-us</language>	
		<image>
			<title>The Speed Scene</title>
			<url>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/images/RSS-Speed-Scene-Logo-live.gif</url>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/</link>
			<width>144</width>
			<height>68</height>
		</image>
<!--begin-->
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 12/27/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Roger Norman from the HDRA with news and big announcements about 2012 race series, with Bryant Layton on the Slime Off Road Report, Chuck Lipka from Geezer Gassers and Hot Rod Bob talks about Slot Car drag racing, We give away a cool T. Nichols artwork.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio12-27-11.mp3" length="14657306" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 12/20/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Lee Boy Pro Mod racer Quain Stott, Les Morris and his S &amp; W racecar, Go Cart racing with Shannon Parks and the Indy Karting Classic, Bryant Layton with the Slime Off Road Report and Lucas Oil Off Road Champion Corry Weller, &amp; last week to sign up for Giveaway!
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio12-20-11.mp3" length="14620469" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 12/13/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Courtney Force talks about racing, her family, and her nomination for the ESPN Next award, Vote for Courtney at www.johnforce.com, Koby calls us from Israel and gives
us an update on the racing scene there. Sprint cars at Perris Auto Speedway, sign up for free T. Nichols Christmas giveaway.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio12-13-11.mp3" length="15384385" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 12/06/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Ed Justice Jr. talks about the history of the Justice Brothers company, Hot Rod Bob with G.A.A.S. talks with Gary Smith about A/FX &amp; B/FX racecars and the upcoming Mooneyes show and race, Bryant Layton with Justin Fantz on the Slime Off Road Report, Chris Kurtis talks about Kurtis Midget racecars, Sign up now for the T. Nichols free giveaway!
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio12-6-11.mp3" length="15065587" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 11/29/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Team Purple Motorsports live in studio with Melanie and Ron,
Learn how to insure your racecar with Mike Flake at 1 855 DragCar, New Burma Shave Christmas giveaway from T. Nichols. Check out latest issue of Drag Illustrated, and 2012 racing schedule review.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio11-29-11.mp3" length="14895060" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 11/22/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Shayna Texter gets in the history books on her motorcycle in Grand National Flat track racing,
Mike Halstead and his Junior Dragster, Bryant Layton reviews the Baja 1000 on the Slime Tire 
Treatment Off Road Report, and Currie Nova bodywork update. 
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio11-22-11.mp3" length="13980735" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 11/15/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
NHRA Top Fuel Funnycar driver Robert Hight, Super Gas &amp; Super Comp racer 
Tommy Phillips, Hot Rod Bob talks about the John Force early days, and Bryant 
Layton with the Slime Off Road Report gives a Baja 1000 preview.

			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio11-15-11.mp3" length="14512731" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 11/08/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Legendary Dave McClelland live and in studio, Newhouse Cagle Modified Roadster Fuel Altered recreation with Dave and Joel Gruzen and Franny Sanger. Hot Rod Bob with G.A.A.S. and the 53 to 56 Ford F150 custom trucks,
Bryant layton and the Slime Off Road Report talking Glamis.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio11-8-11.mp3" length="15924245" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 11/01/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Jungle Pam talks about her past with Jungle Jim, Kris Krabill drives his Pedaler Nitro funny car in the finals at CHRR, Retro truck and trailer, Sam Auxier Jr., Kevin Sargensen, Dave McClelland and Bob Beck with G.A.A.S. talking 50&#39;s custom show cars.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio11-1-11.mp3" length="12480470" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 10/25/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
JT Taylor from TorchMate racing talking about desert racing, hill climbing, and Pikes Peak, Chip &quot;the Legend&quot; Johnson talks about his IHRA world championship, Bob Beck with Conrad Cavallero and the historic Nor Cal Hardtops. CHRR racing video. Bryant Layton and Over-Revv industries motosports apparel.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio10-25-11.mp3" length="14809378" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 10/18/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
California Hot Rod Reunion show with Tony Thacker and Monique Valadez from the NHRA Museum,
Great American Auto Scene with Robin Millar of Pete Millar&#39;s Car Toons, Slime Off Road Report 
with Lucas Oil Super Lite racer Jessie Johnson.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio10-18-11.mp3" length="14440947" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 10/11/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Radial Revolution &quot;No Mercy&quot; race at SGMP with &quot;The Mayor&quot;,  
Bob Beck talks about the legendary Dart,  
Slime Tire Treatment Off Road Report covers the Powder Puff charity race. 

			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio10-11-11.mp3" length="14580193" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 10/04/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Lucky on the road to SSL nationals, BOB Beck and the Corvair on GAAS, Bryant Layton with Jason Johnston from Mercy Air on Slime off road report, and Bobby Murty.
Sent from my HTC on the Now Network from Sprint!
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio10-4-11.mp3" length="14607399" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 09/27/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
We announce the winners of the Speed Scene Live Nationals entry and the R. Tillery giveaway,
How to get Sponsored tips, Randy Folk with the Million Dollar Drag race, Bryant Layton with 
Ana Cody on the Slime off Road Report, Alex Barrett races a airplane with his Funnycar.

			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio9-27-11.mp3" length="14117760" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 09/20/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
How to get Sponsored tips, Bob Beck visits the legendary GM FuturLiner, Speed Scene Live Nationals preview, TV Tommy Ivo, and Dominic Cardoza at the NHRA Museum Twilight Cruise.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio9-20-11.mp3" length="14316918" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 09/13/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
How to get sponsored tips, stock racer Jeanne Linke, Hot Rod Bob with vintage USAC midgets, Bryant Layton with Dirt Sports magazine driver of the year, David Caspino on the Slime off road report. Sent from my HTC on the Now Network from Sprint!
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio9-13-11.mp3" length="14685976" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 09/06/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
How to get sponsored tips, winner of free racer entry to Speed Scene live nationals, hot rod Bob and GAAS viewers first cars, drag racing 201 book author Ike Hecklet Jr. King Kong race team, Bryamt Layton and the Slime off road report.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio9-6-11.mp3" length="14383373" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 08/30/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Dan Warner from the SCTA live in studio talking about Bonneville Speed Week, John Beck talks about his  
Bonneville experience, We have a Free ticket giveaway to Famoso Night of Nitro Sept. 10th, Bob Beck and 
G.A.A.S. Talking about the AMC pony car that never was manufactured, the Rambler Tarpon and which car 
was its replacement.

			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio8-30-11.mp3" length="14500924" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 08/23/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Debbie from Crusin for A Cure Car show, Rocky Mountain SuperChargers, Brett Wagner talks about new PassTime TV shows, Slime Off Road Report With Bryant Layton and Sean Mecham and Vegas to Reno race, Bob Beck with Woodward
dream cruise, More free stuff to give out at Speed Scene Live Nationals. 
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio8-23-11.mp3" length="14704679" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 08/16/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Bruce Penhall, world famous Speedway racer and TV / Film star, Rocky Mountain SuperChargers, Dan Warner &amp; John Beck report from the salt flats at the beginning of Bonneville Speed Week, Zack Langley, from COPS TV show talks to Bryant Layton about his Off Road racing team on the Slime Off Road report, Bob Beck with Big Bear car show coverage.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio8-16-11.mp3" length="14694866" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 08/09/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Top Alcohol Dragster driver Brandon Greco talks about his crash with Monroe Guest, Phil and Mary from Extreme Automotive in studio talking about their restoration shop, 
and Prolong products. Bob Beck and the Great American Auto Scene talks about the Ford Maverick. Slime Tire Treatment Off Road report will be back next week.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio8-9-11.mp3" length="14816170" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 08/02/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Monroe Guest talks about the crash in his Top Alcohol Dragster, his suspension from NHRA, and the tires that caused it all, We give away a free racer entry to the Speed Scene Live Nationals, Artist T. Nichols and his great art, Frantic Ford Funny Car, and Bob Beck and G.A.A.S.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio8-2-11.mp3" length="15573730" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 07/26/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Geezer Gassers bring back nostalgia race action, Dave McClelland at the NHRA Museum Twilight cruise, NMRA racecars at Fontana, Industry Hills Speedway with Brett Wagner, Hot Rod Bob with G.A.A.S., and Bryant Layton and the Slime Off Road Report with Josh Daniel.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio7-26-11.mp3" length="14999131" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 07/19/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Stephen Pullin from Pullin TV talking about the movement to bring back  Pinks All Out, Brett Wagner from PassTime, Industry Hills Speedway Winners, Bryant Layton and the Slime Off Road Report and Bob Beck with the Great American Auto Scene.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio7-19-11.mp3" length="16184464" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 07/19/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Stephen Pullin from Pullin TV talking about the movement to bring back  Pinks All Out, Brett Wagner from PassTime, Industry Hills Speedway Winners, Bryant Layton and the Slime Off Road Report and Bob Beck with the Great American Auto Scene.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio7-19-11.mp3" length="16184464" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 07/12/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Industry Hills Speedway show with Brett Wagner from PassTime, Darrell Gwynn, Barrett Jackson, and Donnie Couch from West Coast Funnycar Factory. Lots of Speedway racing, interviews, and thrills and spills. Bryant Layton with the Slime Tire Treatment Off Road Report.
			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio7-12-11.mp3" length="14816065" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>The Speed Scene for 07/05/2011</title>
			<link>http://www.speedsceneracing.com/arch.shtml</link>
			<description>
Kevin Sarginson with his Mustang Funny Car and his back up girl Sharon, Ed from Rocky Mountain SuperChargers talking about July 16th race at Pueblo Motorsports Park, Bob Beck with the Great American Auto Scene Fontana car show.

			</description>
			<enclosure url="http://www.speedsceneracing.com/Audio/SpeedSceneAudio7-5-11.mp3" length="14927660" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
	</channel>
 </rss>

