<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/DTDs/Podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
    <itunes:author>Wireless Tech Radio</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Wireless Tech Radio is a weekly technology news and information talk show focused exclusively on the wireless industry.  Each week Wireless Tech Radio explores wireless technologies, companies, markets, newsmakers, or provides informative and instructive tutorial segments. The show is hosted by Jim Sutton, Marlon Schafer, and Steve Stroh. http://www.wirelesstechradio.com</itunes:summary>
<itunes:subtitle>Listen LIVE Wednesdays at 3PM GMT (London), 10AM ET (New York), 7AM PT (Los Angeles).</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:owner> <itunes:name> Jim Sutton </itunes:name>    <itunes:email> jim@wirelesstechradio.com </itunes:email> </itunes:owner>
<category>Technology</category>
<itunes:category text="Technology">
   <itunes:category text="News" />
   <itunes:category text="Smart Phones" />
</itunes:category>
<itunes:link rel="image" type="video/jpeg" 
href="http://www.wirelesstechradio.com/images/WTR-ITMS-logo.jpg"> Wireless Tech Radio Podcast </itunes:link>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <title>
            Wireless Tech Radio
        </title>
        <description>
            Technology Talk Radio for the wireless industry: manufacturers, WISP, enthusiasts, analysts, owners, and more.  Streamed LIVE every Wednesday at 10AM Easter, 7AM Pacific, and 3PM GMT (London) from www.WirelessTechRadio.com.
        </description>
        <link>
            http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
        </link>
        <language>
            en-US
        </language>
        <webMaster>
            Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
        </webMaster>
        <copyright>
            2004, 2005 Waterford Media All Rights Reserved.
        </copyright>
        <pubDate>
            Sun, 10 Jul 2005 15:34:27 -0400
        </pubDate>
        <image>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <url>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com/images/wtr_live.jpg
            </url>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio
            </title>

        </image>
        <item>
            <title>
                February 2, 2005 Wireless Tech Radio Show
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Industry News: Steve Stroh and Marlon Schafer&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;The merger
of AT&amp;amp;T and SBC - One wireless angle is that AT&amp;amp;Ts announced plans to
offer AT&amp;amp;T Wireless as a MVNO running on Sprint is likely dead, dealing a
small blow to Sprint/Nextels planning. Apple is shipping (the first) Bluetooth 2.0 in its refresh of its PowerBook line. Koreas SK Telecom and Earthlink are
have announced SK-Earthlink, which will do an MVNO running on Sprint/Nextel and
Verizons networks. The Associated Press reports that RADAR systems at Eglin Air
Force Base in Florida are experiencing false targets, possibly as a result of
the use of Wireless systems that operate in the 5.6 - 5.8 GHz
range.www.bwianews.com&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;VOIP for WISPs : Is This Sticky Enough - Tony
Surak&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Voice Over IP is shaping up to be the next killer Internet
application.&amp;nbsp;Wireless ISPs everywhere are looking to add voice calling and
enhanced feature capabilities , its sticky, adds value and brings them
additional revenue.&amp;nbsp;Tony Surak of Newforth Partners joins us to discuss
VOIP technologies and the important choices ISPs and WISPs need to consider.
Tony explains not only why wired and wireless ISPs should offer VOIP services
(customer stickiness &amp;amp; retention, higher ARPUs), he will also discuss the ways
to implement them.&amp;nbsp;Should you build, it, buy it or partner up&amp;nbsp;Each
has its costs and advantages.&amp;nbsp;Mr. Surak is Senior Director of Newforth
Partners, an M&amp;amp;A advisory firm which also provides business &amp;amp; technology
consultancy. He was a cofounder of TalkingNets, one of the first all VOIP based
CLECs, which was later acquired by DSLnet. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;A
href="http://www.newforth.com"&gt;www.newforth.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Wireless Remote Rebooting Product - Myron Anduri&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Marlon
Schafer has been fascinated with this unique variant of rebooting equipment that
uses paging services instead of dedicated lines or IP addressing. He met Myron
Anduri of Nighthawk Systems first at WISPCON and recently at EXC EXPO in Denver. So now you have an untethered way to reboot a digital camera in your deep-in-the-woods deer blind or jumpstart recalcitrant equipment at the most inaccessible tower location. &lt;A
href="http://www.nighthawksystems.com"&gt;www.nighthawksystems.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If you have any questions you want to ask the guests or you have any of
your own comments about a topic, please Instant Message us at AIM: JimSuttonVA,
Marlonoffice, or SteveStroh2.. &lt;BR&gt;Hope you get a chance to listen in! &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;If You Missed The January 26th Show ... Check it out below! &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Industry News: Steve Stroh and Marlon Schafer&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Steves
picked out some interesting topics for this weeks wireless industry news and
developments. &lt;A href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;WiMAX: Can it live up to the Hype - Michael Young&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I
predict that WiMAX stories in 2005 will be the wireless industry equivalent to
National Enquirer articles on busty starlets. Everyones interested in them and
boy those covers sell! So heres our first bodacious cover story article on
WiMAX for 2005. The WiMAX interoperability plug fest has reportedly slipped
out to year end which suggests theyll not be official WiMAX gear until 2006.
Michael Young, founder and former CTO for YDI Wireless, joins us to suggest some
good points, bad points and some recommendations on what to BUY while were
waiting. "If you are ready to deploy now, do not wait for WiMax.&amp;nbsp;There are
several radio manufactures that make good outdoor OFDM P-P and M-MP systems that
are very effective. CAUTION: Do not buy systems that use straight 802.11a or g
WLAN cards that run the standard .11a/g protocols." &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Back to Basics - Mounting Antennas, Doing Cables &amp;amp; Connectors
Right, Weatherproofing - Marlon Schafer&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;"I bet 90% of WISP
equipment failures are mechanical in nature." says Marlon Schafer, WISP Owner,
Operator, and Consultant. "For example, an antenna installed with the weep holes
facing upward. We see it every day." Marlon brings us Back to Basics with tips
on smarter ways to mount antennas, how to construct cable and connectors
properly, and since its Winter - he cant pass up weatherproofing. Hes
suggested some excellent links from the Times Microwave website that offer
excellent streaming instructional videos. &lt;A
href="http://www.odessaoffice.com"&gt;www.odessaoffice.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                wtr@wirelesstechradio.com (Jim Sutton, Steve Stroh, Marlon Schafer)
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Wed, 02 Feb 2005 01:12:39 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{9BB5AFD1-BD1D-40BF-8959-4806EF3783BE}.38373.3837859491
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                First Anniversary Show - Wireless Tech Radio February 16, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Industry News: Tsunami Relief Efforts - Mike Outmesguine
&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;Steve Stroh is traveling to Chicago for &lt;STRONG&gt;WISPNOG&lt;/STRONG&gt;
that begins this week. Mike Outmesguine, Co-founder of SOCALWUG, joins us to
bring us up-to-date on Tsunami Relief Efforts. He has some thoughts on wireless
networking and wireless technologies as disaster relief platforms. &lt;A
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Part 1:&amp;nbsp; Consumer Wireless (WiFi) Equipment - Mike Outmesguine,
Matt Wilkinson&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;The first segment on relief planning status and
efforts continue in the second segment. Matt Wilkinson joins the discussion in
mid-segment as the relief effort updates are completed. Matt kicks off his
discussion of consumer router gear and choices aided by Mike Outmesguine who,
too, has considerable expertise in choosing and deploying consumer
equipment.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;My Favorite Consumer Wireless (WiFi) Equipment - Matt
Wilkinson&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;So you are headed out to BestBuy to get that wireless
router, finally, now that the new work laptop has its Intel branded wireless
networking embedded somewhere inside. Or, your latest customer hasnt even heard
of Wireless 101 and you need this advisor role like a hole in the head.
Lockergnome IT channel editor and creator of JustCallMatt.net, Matt Wilkinson,
joins us to discuss Linksys, Netgear, Belkin, Apple, SMC, D-Link and Hawking
Technologies gear hes used and installed recently. &lt;A
href="http://www.JustCallMatt.net"&gt;www.JustCallMatt.net&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Fri, 25 Feb 2005 09:32:23 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow021605.mp3" length="10941934" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{C2BF964E-3091-4EF9-9F7E-DBD018A55ED2}.38408.35583
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show - February 23, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Industry News: Wrap-up of the WISPNOG Conference in Chicago - Steve
Stroh &lt;BR&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;Steve Stroh has returned from Chicago where he attended the
first and highly successful &lt;STRONG&gt;WISPNOG&lt;/STRONG&gt; (Wireless ISP Network
Operators Group) conference last week. He has a report on WISPAs organizational
efforts and more. &lt;A href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000&gt;Incumbents Will Staunchly Oppose Municipal
Wireless Efforts- Jim Carlini&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Northwestern University
Professor and expert witness Jim Carlini says "there are MANY things going on
including the sudden defense of the "traditional phone companies" trying to BAN
municipally owned infrastructure (both fiber and wireless).". The &lt;STRONG&gt;bogus
NMRC report&lt;/STRONG&gt; is only one example of output from "White paper for hire"
firms paid directly by the incumbent telephone companies. &lt;A
href="http://www.carlinij.com"&gt;www.carlinij.com&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#006400 size=4&gt;IIndustry Leading Ultra-Wideband
Capabilities - John Santhofff&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;John Santhoff, &lt;STRONG&gt;CTO
&amp;amp; Co-founder of Pulse~LINK&lt;/STRONG&gt;, joins us to discuss the recently
announced availability of the worlds first UWB radio for Wireless Local Area
Networks (WLANs). The Pulse~LINK platform delivers wireless Gigabit data rates
at Personal Area Network (WPAN) ranges and data rates capable of supporting
multimedia and &lt;STRONG&gt;HDTV data streams&lt;/STRONG&gt; at WLAN ranges. Pulse~LINKs
technology is different than that of MB-OFDM and DS-UWB forms of Ultra Wideband
presently pursued by other groups. &lt;A title="John Santhofff"
href="http://www.pulselink.net"&gt;www.pulselink.net&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Thu, 03 Mar 2005 20:16:38 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow022305.mp3" length="11114028" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{A0598D6F-3455-46DB-9274-CC7D758E1BCD}.38414.8032261458
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show - March 02, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Industry News: All Signs Looking Good For Mesh Networks - Steve Stroh
&amp;amp; Marlon Schafer&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Firetide&lt;/STRONG&gt; has some new mesh
products, more evidence that mesh is really starting to take off. Biggest news
is that &lt;STRONG&gt;Aloha Partners&lt;/STRONG&gt; got their adjacent channel waiver to
start &lt;STRONG&gt;700 MHz&lt;/STRONG&gt; service in Tucson. Thats a big deal, and not
just for 700 MHz. Minor news is the paper LPTV mini-scandal. &lt;A
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Orthogon OS Spectra Product Launched - Phil Bolt&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;I
want to say the hot new OS Spectra product is &lt;STRONG&gt;like the Gemini on
steroids&lt;/STRONG&gt; - faster speeds, larger bandwidth, dual payload capability,
better ERA but Im not so sure thats the politically correct phrase anymore.
Orthogon Systems CEO, Phil Bolt, joins us again to discuss improvements in this
product platform and who its targeted to serve. There are some very interesting
and unusual applications the market is finding for the robust Orthogon products
that I hope well have time to explore. &lt;A
href="http://www.orthogonsystems.com"&gt;www.orthogonsystems.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Thu, 03 Mar 2005 20:24:27 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow030205.mp3" length="10953454" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{5E173F95-2A2F-4792-9361-0C526F6691E6}.38414.8086551157
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio - March 09, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Industry News: Clearwire/Bell Canada -
Steve Stroh&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;It may be too dramatic to opine that Telco execs
are going to have a rough nights sleep tonight with the multiple bombshell
announcements from &lt;STRONG&gt;Clearwire and Bell Canada&lt;/STRONG&gt;. But maybe not ...
Clearwire announced that Bell Canada will be their VoIP backend and that
&lt;STRONG&gt;Bell Canada is purchasing a $100 Million&lt;/STRONG&gt; stake in their
company. This leapfrogs Clearwire around any number of ILEC induced obstacles.
Steve Stroh will connect a lot of dots tomorrow as hes been watching Clearwire
closely for more than a year. Also, Sprint has committed to
&lt;STRONG&gt;1xEV-DO&lt;/STRONG&gt;, not the potentially faster variant that would have
taken a few more years. So, no leapfrogging Verizon. Two rival factions on UWB
are going to merge; finally some rationality on UWB. &lt;A
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;Broadband Wireless Innovation Lags
Technologys Pace - Scott Shamp&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Is there enough true
innovation in the wireless field Or are we just refining, rather than
revolutionizing its use &lt;STRONG&gt;Professor Scott Shamp&lt;/STRONG&gt;, Director of the
University of Georgia New Media Institute, joins Wireless Tech Radio Wednesday
to discuss innovation in the wireless Industry: The technical capability of
wireless has outstripped creative uses for the technology. Putting our advanced
technology to creative use will be the center of innovation. Many believe
&lt;STRONG&gt;VOIP&lt;/STRONG&gt; or adding voice services to broadband wireless &lt;STRONG&gt;is
the next killer application&lt;/STRONG&gt;. But is this innovation, voice is the
original use of telephony dating back more than a hundred years So what is
innovation and who will drive it “&lt;STRONG&gt;It will be content”&lt;/STRONG&gt; and “I
will argue that it has to be young people -- they are unencumbered by
restrictive paradigms -- they wont let existing models hold them back say
Shamp. This innovation [content] will not come from the commercial domain,
either. “There isnt room for radical experimentation here. Profit is too
crucial to these groups. Universities will play a major role. Professor Shamp
will discuss the Mobile Media Consortium and examples of types of innovative
projects that are underway. &lt;A
href="http://www.nmi.uga.edu"&gt;www.nmi.uga.edu&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;Anti-Municipal Broadband Legislation -
Rick Harnish&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;According to MuniWireless, 11 states had
legislation presented this Spring concerning this topic.&amp;nbsp;Five of those
states have avoided this legislation as it has died in committee, has been
pulled by the author or has been delayed.&amp;nbsp;The states of Colorado - SB
05-152, Florida   SB 1714 and HB 1325, Iowa  SSB 1136 and HSB Bill 182,
Nebraska, Tennessee  HB 1403 and SB 1760 and Texas - HB 789 are still active.
For the record, I am generally opposed to MuniWireless projects unless all
other options to partner with current private providers in the general area have
been exhausted say Harnish. As most WISPs know, what looks good on paper
today, in reality is a very challenging business. Our real world experience
should give us expertise to partner or offer to cooperate with the
municipalities that choose to move forward on wireless projects.&amp;nbsp;I look at
MuniWireless not so much as a threat but as an opportunity.&amp;nbsp; Rick
organized an email list of 40 WISPs in the state to keep them aware of the
legislation calendar and language and to urge them to contact their legislators.
He also worked directly with the Department of Commerce office in a series of
meetings to discuss the bills, language and possible solutions. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Concerning Legislation:&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;UL&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Beware of deceiving titles: Anti-Municipal Broadband Bill may mean
  PRO-RBOC Broadband Bill or Anti-Competition Broadband Bill &lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Content of the bills language is what is important. Read it once, then
  reread it again, speculate what each line can mean to your future in the
  business &lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Contact your State Department of Commerce or related agency that oversees
  broadband deployment, make a name for yourself with the people who count &lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Begin to organize with other WISPs and ISPs in your state to battle and
  amend legislation and even to formulate solutions for various MuniWireless
  projects &lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Sources of Information: State Legislation Websites, if you dont know it,
  Google it!, Muniwireless.com, Wispa.org, wispcentric.com. Most important point
  here is Get Connected, Get Reading, Get Active or Get Run Over! &lt;BR&gt;&lt;A
  href="http://www.oibw.net"&gt;www.oibw.net&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/LI&gt;&lt;/UL&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Fri, 11 Mar 2005 00:39:44 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow030905.mp3" length="14655344" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{9A4184A3-0815-4060-B62B-43A0D8E8C2A0}.38434.9859329745
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio - March 16, 2005 Show
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Industry News Marh 16, 2005: - Steve Stroh
&amp;amp; Marlon Schafer&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Verizon coughs up &lt;STRONG&gt;$100MM for
LEAP Wireless&lt;/STRONG&gt; spectrum, Motorola debuts MOTOMESH operating in 2.4ghz
and 4.9ghz, FCC &lt;STRONG&gt;creates new unlicensed "contention based" band&lt;/STRONG&gt;
from satellite earth station freqs (3.65ghz - 3.70 ghz), and &lt;STRONG&gt;Redline,
Airspan, and Alvarion&lt;/STRONG&gt; announce theyll do private interoperability
testing -- &lt;STRONG&gt;Can you say "first to market with interoperable
WiMAX&lt;/STRONG&gt;" And more in a big news week! &lt;A
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Brief History of Unlicensed Spectrum
Operation - Kenneth R. Carter&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;"Part 15 was established in
1938, only four years after the founding of the FCC," says &lt;STRONG&gt;Kenneth
Carter, Counsel in the FCCs Office of Strategic Planning&lt;/STRONG&gt;, "even then
the FCC anticipated experimentation at emission levels too weak to cause
interference. Its important to remember the Cardinal Rule: do not cause
interference; accept all interference when discussing unlicensed spectrum and
its use.&lt;STRONG&gt; "I think were entering the Golden Age of Unlicensed
Operation&lt;/STRONG&gt;, the most interesting technologies are emerging there, rather
than in licensed." Stay tuned because things are changing. &lt;A
href="http://www.fcc.gov"&gt;www.fcc.gov&lt;/A&gt; &lt;BR&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Thu, 24 Mar 2005 00:55:18 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow031605.mp3" length="15369950" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{D0AEB3C6-8B9B-45FE-A28F-5087FE23DFD8}.38434.9948169792
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show March 23, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Industry News: - Steve Stroh &amp;amp; Marlon
Schafer&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;WISPCON wrap-up; Progress on 802.11n; Airespace
joins MESH parade on the way to their Cisco buy-out; Proxim announces a Starter
Kit. &lt;A href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;Open Spectrum International - Robert
Horvitz&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Robert Horvitz founded Open Spectrum International
in 2004. It is an advocate organization for license-exempt spectrum
internationally. "We cant use the US style First Amendment argument in
international markets, its a more subtle process advocating free speech issues.
Robert indicated that its an interesting process to convince foreign governments
that they can avoid expenditures and still experience growth when a
license-exempt model is allowed. &lt;A
href="http://www.open-spectrum-international.org"&gt;www.open-spectrum-international.org&lt;/A&gt;
&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;Ultra-Wideband Is Not Just a PAN
Technology - John Santhoff&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Julie Knapp of the FCC, at a
WISPCON briefing Tuesday afternoon, indicated that UWB is not just a PAN
(Personal Area Network) technology - some companies envision HDTV and in-home
multimedia uses. Pulse~LINK is one of those firms as theyve demonstrated their
bandwidth carrying capacity. John Santhoff, Pulse~LINK CTO and Co-founder
discusses how UWB and software defined radios might blend capacities and what
applications that technology could serve. John was recently honored as Innovator
of the Year as we reported earlier in the Wireless Tech Log. &lt;A
href="http://www.pulselink.net"&gt;www.pulselink.net&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Sun, 27 Mar 2005 21:22:24 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow032305.mp3" length="35837962" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{09FB7AEB-1D4A-4F94-824E-37EADDF41E21}.38438.8488997338
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show for April 6, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Araya radios tested by
Marlon in his network. ISCWest coming up this week in Las Vegas. Steve announces
hell be &lt;STRONG&gt;a speaker at the WISPCON Pacific&lt;/STRONG&gt; conference coming up
in Auckland, NZ. Sprint PCS announces M-Spot radio - streaming music from their
CDMA network. &lt;STRONG&gt;Aircell to test new ground to air radio&lt;/STRONG&gt; system in
July for Internet access at &lt;STRONG&gt;300-500 Kbps&lt;/STRONG&gt;. NextWeb expanding
coverage to all of Los Angeles. &lt;STRONG&gt;Waverider announces MobileWan&lt;/STRONG&gt;
enhancement to 900mhz systems to offer mobility and nomadic services. XIRRUS
debuts enterprise wireless LAN AP product with array antennas and multiple
radios. IEEE 802.22 and 802.16 Committees create PR tug-of-war. Dishnet
Wireless, LTD announces &lt;STRONG&gt;2.5 Billion Rupees&lt;/STRONG&gt; investment to deploy
hybrid WiMAX/WiFi system in India - &lt;STRONG&gt;6000 WiFi Hotspots in 38
cities&lt;/STRONG&gt; by early 2006. More deployments in Zambia and St Petersburg
(Russia). &lt;A href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;WiMax - the 2005 Vision : Service
Providers, Equipments &amp;amp; Chips Conference - David Ahlgren&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;
&lt;BR&gt;The San Diego Telecom Council sponsored the event of WiMAX outlook for 2005
including markets forecasts of computers, chipsets, etc. for the near term.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Airspan - Eric Stonestrom&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;
&lt;BR&gt;Airspan, Alvarion, and Redline jumped the pack two weeks ago with their
announcement to conduct private interoperability testing of their WiMAX products
later this year. So we thought wed like to learn more about Airspan by inviting
CEO Eric Stonestrom to join us. Airspan, founded in 1992, has revenues now
approaching &lt;STRONG&gt;$100 Million with over 300 customers in 95
countries&lt;/STRONG&gt; and is a founding member and Board member of the WiMAX
Forum.With products poised to deploy WiMAX around the globe, Eric may tell us a
bit of their plans for WiMAX as he sees it evolving and, of course, what
differentiates their product today. &lt;A
href="http://www.Airspan.com"&gt;www.Airspan.com&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Wed, 13 Apr 2005 20:20:34 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow040605.mp3" length="21096458" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{5D57EA29-0B94-49C0-B253-42E87351CCA4}.38455.8476269444
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show for April 13, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;Wireless Tech Radio can now be found live on Wednesdays right here on the web
at &lt;A href="http://www.wirelesstechradio.com"&gt;www.wirelesstechradio.com&lt;/A&gt; at
10AM Eastern, 7AM Pacific and 3PM London/Madrid. But you dont have to hear it
live to hear it!&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;You can also listen to this or previous shows at the show archive. We make it
convenient for you! This show will be found archived at &lt;A
href="http://www.wirelesstechradio.com"&gt;www.wirelesstechradio.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Weve got some great guest segments lined up this week including:&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Philadelphias release
of its wireless plan and RFP dominates the news this week. And the opinions are
as varied as you could possibly imagine. Some observers suggest it will be the
poster child for failure as it appears not to follow any of the previously
successful models for municipal deployments.&lt;BR&gt; &lt;A
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;NeighborNode: What is it - John Geraci
&amp;amp; Mohit SantRam&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;"Neighbornode is a network of online
neighborhood bulletin boards that people access through open wireless routers.
Hosts of Neighbornode place an open router in their apartments window, and
anyone within wireless range (+/- 300 ft) can log on to discuss things with
their neighbors." It began as a class project by John Geraci at the Interactive
Telecommunications Program at NYU. It was started as a way of reintroducing the
notion of the Old Town Center into modern cities, which are mostly lacking in
common space for community members to meet and exchange ideas and get to know
one another. This seems to be an "out there" use of wireless connectivity but it
has a growing group of followers and just maybe youd enjoy hearing about it
too. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.neighbornode.net"&gt;www.neighbornode.net&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Sveasoft firmware for Linksys Routers -
James Ewing&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Perhaps most good start-up companies have unique
and interesting stories to tell in the pub over a few pints - Sveasoft is
certainly in that class. James Ewing, founder of Sveasoft, will tell us the how
and why of their start but explain the business model and what new developments
can be expected in 2005. "We currently produce firmware for just 3 models of
Linksys brand routers. We are expanding this to support models from three other
manufacturers right now and will expand support for other platforms and
manufacturers through Summer 2005. " Also look for specific application versions
to supports things like hotspots, VPN, mesh and VOIP. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;A
href="http://www.Sveasoft.com"&gt;www.Sveasoft.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Wed, 20 Apr 2005 13:13:22 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow041305.mp3" length="21948426" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{B32B1E10-8048-40A1-8A9A-E8E6B3288EFE}.38462.5476014468
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show April 20, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You might have thought
nothing else happened this week except &lt;STRONG&gt;INTEL &lt;/STRONG&gt;announcement that
they are shipping their &lt;STRONG&gt;Rosedale chips&lt;/STRONG&gt; with WiMAX - or in
Steves words: "Intel "legitimizes" the WiMAX industry with the introduction of
their PRO/Wireless 5116 chipset, until now known by Intels codename
Rosedale.".And &lt;STRONG&gt;NextWeb,&lt;/STRONG&gt; a Broadband Wireless Service Provider
based in California offers VOIP services by partnering with CommPartners.
&lt;STRONG&gt;BelAir Networks&lt;/STRONG&gt; is the vendor behind &lt;STRONG&gt;Cityspace, a large
Wi-Fi HotZone in London, UK&lt;/STRONG&gt;. An interesting partnership - GigaBeam
teams with Adaptix to offer complementary Broadband Wireless products.
&lt;STRONG&gt;Redline launches RedMAX&lt;/STRONG&gt;, their WiMAX product line &lt;A
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;UK/EU Wireless Market Update - Tony
Fish&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Tony is the Principal of AMF Ventures in London and
Chairman of the WiFi Community at Ecademy. Tony joins us for a discussion of the
latest developments in Wi-Fi in the UK and EU. &lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT
color=#0000ff&gt;wireless.ecademy.com&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;A Hackers Guide to Secure Wireless
Networks - Don Beetle Bailey&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Youve read it a dozen times
from every security pundit: 1) turn on WEP, 2) turn off your SSID broadcast, 3)
put tin foil over your windows - Shazaaam - youre SECURE. So what would a
hacker tell us about that  &lt;STRONG&gt;Don Bailey, security consultant by day, AKA
"Beetle by night &lt;/STRONG&gt;or when organizing &lt;STRONG&gt;ShmooCon&lt;/STRONG&gt; events,
joins us for a Hackers view of how NOT to secure your network and some how-to
tips from &lt;STRONG&gt;simple, cheap methods&lt;/STRONG&gt; for home networks to not
simple, not cheap, but effective ways to secure a corporate network. &lt;A
href="http://www.shmoo.com"&gt;www.shmoo.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Wed, 27 Apr 2005 23:12:27 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow042005.mp3" length="23263544" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{FFB19D90-5A7D-49C2-B864-C3A111CD9011}.38469.9655065394
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show for April 27, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;FCC authorizes
new 1.92GHz band&lt;/STRONG&gt; for digital telephone services using DECT standard
common in Europe, T-Mobile says that its pleased with &lt;STRONG&gt;Flarion
trial&lt;/STRONG&gt;, &lt;STRONG&gt;fSONA and Laserbit&lt;/STRONG&gt; join forces, &lt;STRONG&gt;Vonage
solves blocking&lt;/STRONG&gt; problem for at least one Clearwire subscriber, but the
battle is just begun. More .. &lt;A
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Open Architecture MESH products from
Qorvus Systems - Tom Sharples &lt;BR&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;Founded in 2002 sin Vancouver,
WA, Qorvus Systems provides an interesting array of &lt;STRONG&gt;single, dual and
triple radio wireless mesh products&lt;/STRONG&gt; including management software.
&lt;STRONG&gt;President and CTO, Tom Sharples&lt;/STRONG&gt;, will describe Qorvus products
and intended markets. &lt;BR&gt;(1) Flexible organic rollout in under served broadband
markets- can start with just two or three strategically placed nodes and easily
add more as customer demand warrants&lt;BR&gt;(2) Can easily be deployed to provide a
pervasive low-level wireless cloud, therefore cheap or no CPE, taking advantage
of existing installed base of wifi users&lt;BR&gt;(3) Low device and installation cost
allows service provision with modest capex&lt;BR&gt;(4) Available as software only
(runs on several commonly available embedded x86 platforms including mini ITX,
wrap, and legacy Soekris), or as fully-integrated hardware and software
solution, in one, two, or three radio versions&lt;BR&gt;(5) Open Linux software
environment in a continual state of improvement, with extensive standard and
custom engineering support available &lt;A
href="http://www.qorvus.net"&gt;www.qorvus.net&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Trango Broadband Wireless Product
Roadmap - John Seaman&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Trango Broadband Wireless products have
earned a strong reputation in the WISP community with their PTP systems.
Interesting things are coming! &lt;STRONG&gt;John Seaman&lt;/STRONG&gt;, Director of Product
&amp;amp; Customer Support, discusses the Trango Product Roadmap, a preview of PtMP
platform plans, and a view into their &lt;STRONG&gt;WiMAX product strategy&lt;/STRONG&gt; -
their first WiMAX product will be a &lt;STRONG&gt;3.5 GHZ band&lt;/STRONG&gt; used in
markets outside the US. &lt;A
href="http://www.trangobroadband.com"&gt;www.trangobroadband.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Wed, 27 Apr 2005 23:17:06 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow042705.mp3" length="21952944" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{D925A07B-D147-44A6-85C7-4619EEBF8690}.38469.97021375
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show May 4, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Canada allocates an
additional&lt;STRONG&gt; 255 MHz of license-exempt spectrum&lt;/STRONG&gt; in 5 GHz band;
&lt;STRONG&gt;US Wireless Online&lt;/STRONG&gt; juggernaut continues acquisition binge,
acquires iSkywire; &lt;STRONG&gt;Verizon Wireless decides to kill&lt;/STRONG&gt; free Wi-Fi
network; New product family of Wireless Mesh Network Routers from Tropos. And
from the &lt;STRONG&gt;If You Have More Money Than Good Sense Dept,&lt;/STRONG&gt; you ve
heard of the WiFi shielding house paint probably, now a company is claiming WiFi
shielding window film - Steve will rip this one. &lt;A
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;WISP Of The Month: Tampas Rapid
Systems - Dustin Jurman&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Rapid Systems founder, Dustin
Jurman, joins us to discuss building a carrier class ISP/WISP network. "I wont
do it any other way, I wont use consumer grade products in my network."
&lt;STRONG&gt;Rapid Systems is a Tampa, FL&lt;/STRONG&gt; area ISP that also uses wireless
technologies to serve customers. "I dont ever call myself a WISP, Ill use
dial-up, DSL, fiber, or wireless technologies to serve customers."&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Airaya Gets FCC Grant for Public Safety
Banded Products - Bill Pabst&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Bill Pabst, Co-founder and VP of
Engineering for Airaya joins to discuss the company and their products. .
&lt;STRONG&gt;Airaya was co-founded by Mike Nydam and Bill Pabst in 2001.&lt;/STRONG&gt;
Bill has spent the last 16 years developing Spread Spectrum wireless products
for Point of Sale, Pen Computers, access points and mesh systems. Currently,
Bill is responsible for the design and development of the AIRAYA&lt;BR&gt;Bridge
Products. The current products allow users to do pt-to-pt, pt-to-mpt, and
functions between Ethernet networks over a number of different frequency bands
world wide usage. The product functions as a MAC layer bridge. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;A
href="http://www.airaya.com"&gt;www.airaya.com&lt;/A&gt; &lt;BR&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Tue, 10 May 2005 22:10:01 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow050405.mp3" length="22233098" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{8E14FDF3-6164-4169-BD94-BD730D7A0D6D}.38482.9236290046
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                May 11, 2005 - www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;FCC broadcast flag rule is ruled illegal by court; &lt;STRONG&gt;Azulstar&lt;/STRONG&gt; (formerly Ottawa
Wireless) launches &lt;STRONG&gt;Metro VOIP over Wi-Fi&lt;/STRONG&gt; Service in Rio Rancho New Mexico; GPS indoors Well, kind of but not really. Would you believe
radiolocation using TV signals &lt;STRONG&gt;Ultrawideband takes on role new
roles&lt;/STRONG&gt;, posing as RFID and Bluetooth; &lt;STRONG&gt;Sprint and Intel&lt;/STRONG&gt;
will collaborate on speeding up the development of Mobile WiMAX; NextWeb and
MPower Communications commence broadband wireless service in Las Vegas;
TowerStream commences broadband wireless service in San Francisco. . &lt;A
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Mobile Broadband Public Safety Is Not Just
For Small Towns - Patrick Leary &lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;A
href="http://informationweek.com/story/showArticle.jhtml?articleID=160403766"&gt;http://informationweek.
com/story/showArticle.jhtml?articleID=160403766&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;The Fresno system provides &lt;STRONG&gt;greater than 95% coverage of the 50% of
the city&lt;/STRONG&gt; has chosen to roll out first, and does so at about 1/10th the
cost of mesh systems that the city trialed according to Alvarions Chief
Evangelist aka Patrick Leary. "Several other things make this project important:
it is an excellent example that demonstrates that wireless broadband for public
safety is no longer just for small, rural towns." Fresno has a population around
500k, so it is a major tier 2 city. Also, it is the first major public safety
network that converges BWA with WiFi, since each police vehicle will receive an
Alvarion SU-M with integrated 802.11b.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A
href="http://www.alvarion-usa.com"&gt;www.alvarion-usa.com&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Avalan 900 Mhz Products- Michael R.
Derby&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;"Why our 900MHz gear" Avalan CEO Mike Derby explains,
"Three reasons: 1)Ease of installation 2) Ease of configuration.&amp;nbsp;AvaLANs
AW900 radios have no IP addresses, no MAC addresses and no browser interface.
Simply take them out of the box and plug them in.&amp;nbsp;They are an installers dream by all accounts in the field.&lt;BR&gt;3) Security.&amp;nbsp;"The AW900 radios are not 802.11-based and do not employ the somewhat vulnerable WEP technology prevalent in off-the-shelf 802.11 Ethernet bridge components.&amp;nbsp;128-bit keys
are dedicated per pair, so radios only work with their matching mate. As a result, it is nearly impossible to dis-intermediate using a man-in-the-middle attack." &lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Sun, 15 May 2005 23:06:39 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow051105.mp3" length="21960714" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{8F8324C0-C3BA-4FF2-BCCE-3DE41D34B6EA}.38487.9629526505
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                May 18, 2005 Wireless Tech Radio show
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve 
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;BR&gt;New laptop from Sony 
with built-in GSM-based EDGE broadband wireless (with Wi-Fi and Bluetooth); 
&lt;STRONG&gt;Verizon Wireless reduces the price&lt;/STRONG&gt; of its 1xRTT NationalAccess 
service to $60/month for unlimited use with national coverage; &lt;STRONG&gt;MetroFi 
Emerges From Stealth Mode&lt;/STRONG&gt;, offers 1 Mbps metropolitan Wi-Fi service for 
$19.95/month, follows the Stroh model of no services, just access; Fierce 
Wireless names its 3rd Annual Fierce Fifteen companies for 2005.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;We rarely do personnel news on Wireless Tech Radio, but were making an 
exception today. Wireless Tech Radio and I 
personally&amp;nbsp;&lt;STRONG&gt;congratulate Charles Brown on being named CEO&lt;/STRONG&gt; 
of WaveRider Communications. Charles new position was just announced. Charles is 
a very good friend to the Broadband Wireless Industry, especially to smaller 
WISPs with their pioneering 900 MHz system, and Charles is also a friend to 
Wireless Tech Radio : you’re hearing Wireless Tech Radio over a WaveRider system 
graciously provided to WTR. &lt;A 
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;Wireless Broadband Access Task Force - 
Lauren Van Wazer&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;An exciting opportunity for the wireless 
community to hear from and speak to Lauren Van Wazer, &lt;STRONG&gt;Special Counsel to 
the Chief of the FCCs Office of Engineering and Technology&lt;/STRONG&gt; when she 
joins us for this special show. Its perfect timing to get a read from the 
person so intimately involved in the &lt;STRONG&gt;Wireless Broadband Access Task 
Force report &lt;/STRONG&gt;development. The official Comment period has closed, Reply 
Comments are due May 23rd, but the FCC maintains a policy of always being open 
to industry comments and suggestions. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;UL&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Discuss creation and purpose of FCC Wireless Broadband Access Task Force 
  &lt;LI&gt;Define wireless broadband and discuss attributes, including portability, 
  mobility, off-the-shelf 
  &lt;LI&gt;Discuss growth trends in wireless broadband 
  &lt;LI&gt;Focus on role of wireless broadband in rural areas 
  &lt;LI&gt;Review FCC role in wireless broadband over the last few years 
  &lt;LI&gt;Review recommendations of Task Force - unlicensed and licensed 
  &lt;LI&gt;View of the future - convergence; technological developments; seamless 
  connectivity; integration between services&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A 
  href="http://www.fcc.gov/wbatf/"&gt;www.fcc.gov/wbatf/&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/LI&gt;&lt;/UL&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Sun, 29 May 2005 18:11:54 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow051805.mp3" length="21915488" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{A6DBB468-AFA1-4869-B7E3-721C2496F280}.38501.7582676852
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show - May 25, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve 
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Marlons moving Odessa 
Offices office into town, Terabeams bringing &lt;STRONG&gt;Karlnet products back to 
market&lt;/STRONG&gt;, ISPCON Spring show update, &lt;STRONG&gt;FCC mandates E911&lt;/STRONG&gt; 
availability for all VoIP phones that connect to PSTN, Vonage bringing Wifi 
router with its service embedded to market, &lt;STRONG&gt;WIMAX.com information portal 
has launched&lt;/STRONG&gt; Michael Wellerben locates his new venture in Austin, TX; 
Clearwire announces service in Medford, OR, SUPERCOMM announces SuperQuests 
awards&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;UK / EU Wireless Market Update - Tony 
Fish&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Tony Fish, Principal at AMF Ventures in London and 
Chairman of the 3500+ member Wireless SIG at ecademy.com joins us to provide his 
monthly update on the Wireless Market in the UK and European Union. Its been 
conference season in Europe these past five weeks and Tonys got insights from 
several shows.&lt;BR&gt;wireless.ecademy.com &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;TechTalk Primer: ZIGBEE - Venkat 
Bahl&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Venkat Bahl, &lt;STRONG&gt;VP of Marketing at Ember&lt;/STRONG&gt; 
joins us for our first tutorial session on Zigbee technologies. Headquartered in 
Boston, Ember is a promoter of the ZigBee Alliance and was named one of 
&lt;STRONG&gt;Fortune Magazines top "Cool Companies&lt;/STRONG&gt;" for 2004. ZigBee is a 
proprietary set of high level communication protocols designed to use small, low 
power digital radios based on the IEEE 802.15.4 standard for wireless personal 
area networking. The relationship between IEEE 802.15.4 and ZigBee is analogous 
to that existing between IEEE 802.11 and the Wi-Fi Alliance. The ZigBee 1.0 
specifications were ratified on December 14, 2004, but are available only to 
members of the ZigBee Alliance. &lt;A href="http://www.ember.com"&gt;www.ember.com&lt;/A&gt; 
&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;More Information on Zigbee:&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;ZigBee is poised to become the global control/sensor network standard. It has 
been designed to provide the following features:&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;* Low power consumption, simply implemented&lt;BR&gt;o Users expect batteries to 
last many months to years! Consider that a typical single family house has about 
6 smoke/CO detectors. If the batteries for each one only lasted six months, the 
home owner would be replacing batteries every month!&lt;BR&gt;* In contrast to 
Bluetooth, which has many different modes and states depending upon your latency 
and power requirements, ZigBee/IEEE 802.15.4 has two major states: active 
(transmit/receive) or sleep. The application software needs to focus on the 
application, not on which power mode is optimum for each aspect of 
operation.&lt;BR&gt;* Even mains powered equipment needs to be conscious of energy. 
ZigBee devices will be more ecological than their predecessors saving megawatts 
at it full deployment. Consider a future home that has 100 wireless 
control/sensor devices,&lt;BR&gt;* Low cost to the users means low device cost, low 
installation cost and low maintenance.&lt;BR&gt;o ZigBee devices allow batteries to 
last up to years using primary cells (low cost) without any chargers (low cost 
and easy installation). ZigBees simplicity allows for inherent configuration 
and redundancy of network devices provides low maintenance.&lt;BR&gt;* High density of 
nodes per network&lt;BR&gt;o ZigBees use of the IEEE 802.15.4 PHY and MAC allows 
networks to handle any number of devices. This attribute is critical for massive 
sensor arrays and control networks.&lt;BR&gt;* Simple protocol, global 
implementation&lt;BR&gt;o ZigBees protocol code stack is estimated to be about 1/4th 
of Bluetooths or 802.11s. Simplicity is essential to cost, interoperability, 
and maintenance. The IEEE 802.15.4 PHY adopted by ZigBee has been designed for 
the 868 MHz band in Europe, the 915 MHz band in N America, Australia, etc; and 
the 2.4 GHz band is now recognized to be a global band accepted in almost all 
countries.&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Mon, 30 May 2005 15:01:20 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow052505.mp3" length="22095882" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{B9ABE534-8626-4469-9471-3A81185D1478}.38502.6259326157
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio show June 1, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve 
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Nokia&lt;/STRONG&gt; 
Introduces Web Browser Tablet… With Wi-Fi. Very cool! Details in Steves blog 
post at &lt;A href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;. A &lt;STRONG&gt;draft 
Bill Proposes To Sunset Analog Television Broadcasting&lt;/STRONG&gt; By December 31, 
2008 - proposed by House of Representatives Commerce Committee Chairperson, 
Representative Joe Barton of Texas. Highlights from Ernest Miller of Corante’s 
“The Importance Of…” weblog:&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;UL&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;FCC must finalize channel assignments by the end of 2006, appeals complete 
  by the following July&lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Cable must carry digital signals, but can continue to carry analog 
  signals. On cable, the signals have to be carried at the same resolution as 
  they are broadcast.&lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Portions of spectrum from Channel 52-69 that are actually slated for 
  auction (Channels 54/59 – “Lower 700 MHz Block C”, Channel 55 – “Lower 700 MHz 
  Block D”, and some portions reserved for public safety and guard bands) would 
  be auctioned by April 1, 2008&lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Warning labels on analog TV’s stating that they won’t work after 
  12/31/2007 without buying an additional adapter or a subscription service like 
  satellite or cable. Television broadcasters must air public service 
  announcements with this information.&lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;As of July 1, 2006, all television sets 13” and larger that have analog 
  tuners must include a tuner for receiving digital broadcasts&lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Sticking points are likely to be the broadcast flag included with the 
  bill, and the possibility of subsidies for digital television coverters for 
  analog televisions.&lt;/LI&gt;&lt;/UL&gt;
&lt;P&gt;A new product offers easy(er) migration From CDPD To CDMA Data Services CDMA 
- the iPORT EMIV from AnyDATA Corporation is now certified for Verizon’s CDMA 
data network. It offers easy migration from systems using CDPD, which was a 
low-speed, TCP/IP-based wireless data system that operated “on top of” analog 
cellular. &lt;A href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;Highlights from MuniWireless 2nd Annual 
Report - Esme Vos&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If you seriously follow market trends in 
municipal wireless, youre already a MuniWireless fan. To celebrate the second 
anniversary of the site, &lt;STRONG&gt;Esme Vos, founder&lt;/STRONG&gt;, is releasing on 
July 1st the &lt;STRONG&gt;Second MuniWireless.com Annual Survey&lt;/STRONG&gt; of cities 
and regions around the world that have deployed wireless broadband networks. 
(Think this will be a trend) The report will also discuss adoption of VoIP by 
wireless ISPs, the use of mesh and latest hype surround WiMAX. But you get to 
hear a preview here, first, on Wireless Tech Radio. &lt;A 
href="http://www.muniwireless.com"&gt;www.muniwireless.com&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;Continued Discussion of Pro/Cons 
Municipal Deployments&amp;nbsp;- Marlon Schafer&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;BR&gt;The 
discussion of the Pros and Cons of municipal backed broadband wireless 
deployments spilled over from the second segment.&amp;nbsp; Marlon continues his 
advocacy for non-interference with any operating WISPs.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;A 
href="http://www.odessaoffice.com"&gt;www.odessaoffice.com&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Sun, 12 Jun 2005 17:00:21 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow060105.mp3" length="21948426" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{39A6E1EE-3C25-4211-B0F0-7CA29D70B07A}.38515.708585787
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio show - June 8, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve 
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Supercomm press 
conference for &lt;STRONG&gt;Aperto Networks&lt;/STRONG&gt; announcement of WiMAX product 
portfolio called &lt;STRONG&gt;Packet MAX.&lt;/STRONG&gt; Steve will provide in-depth 
information of their product announcements.BellSouth announces yet another 
broadband wireless system trial in Athens, GA. more D-Link &amp;nbsp;&lt;A 
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;State of Wireless Broadband and 
Disruptive Technologies - Noah Elkin&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;eMarketers senior 
analyst for all things wireless, &lt;STRONG&gt;Noah Elkin&lt;/STRONG&gt;, joins us to share 
insights from his latest research on broadband Wireless technologies, likely 
adoption rates in US and international markets with a number of observations 
that product marketers and analysts will be interested in. eMarketers new 
report, &lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;U&gt;Wireless Broadband: The Future Around the Corner&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt; 
has just been published, check out this preview and you may need more. &lt;A 
href="http://www.emarketer.com"&gt;www.emarketer.com&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Dartmouth Colleges Wireless Operation 
Is One of the Largest - Brad Noblet&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Dartmouth College may be 
the smallest of the Ivy League schools, but it has one of the most advanced 
enterprise Wi-Fi networks in the country. They are in effect their own WISP. 
&lt;STRONG&gt;S. Bradley Noblet is the Director Of Technical Service&lt;/STRONG&gt;s at 
Dartmouth College. The college, nestled in the Connecticut River Valley in 
Hanover, N.H., was one of the first to deploy a campus-wide wireless network a 
few years ago. They &lt;STRONG&gt;began offering VoWLAN&lt;/STRONG&gt; services last Fall 
using Cisco softphones and PDA clients made by TeleSym. Ultimately, the school 
intends to extend IP voice service to the &lt;STRONG&gt;entire community of 13,000, 
including faculty and staff.&lt;/STRONG&gt; Interestingly, in addition to the 
softphones, Dartmouth will also Star Trek like communicators from &lt;STRONG&gt;Vocera 
Communications&lt;/STRONG&gt;. The Cupertino, Calif.-based startups wearable badges 
use speech recognition to allow for hands-free calling; users just say the name 
of the person theyre trying to reach -- no phone numbers required. "We felt it 
would be a real advantage for the kids to be able to communicate with their 
classmates no matter where they were. Say youre sitting in the library in the 
middle of January and its two degrees below. If you have a friend coming over 
to the library, rather than you having to walk back over and get a paper you 
forgot, you could call him up and ask him to bring it." &lt;A 
href="http://www.dartmouth.edu"&gt;www.dartmouth.edu&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelestechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Sun, 12 Jun 2005 17:07:49 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow060805.mp3" length="22233098" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{EE250F62-69B7-49F5-A5D3-C847C4A903A0}.38515.7137615741
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show - June 15, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;June 15th Show&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve 
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;BridgeWave 
60GHz&lt;/STRONG&gt; milimeter microwave products, Proxim Corp. declares bankruptcy 
but products continue with buyer, &lt;STRONG&gt;Aruba Wireless wins BIG!&lt;/STRONG&gt; 
displacing Cisco wireless gear at Microsoft for &lt;STRONG&gt;277 buildings in 60 
countries&lt;/STRONG&gt; supporting new applications; &lt;STRONG&gt;Microsoft 
&lt;/STRONG&gt;developing mesh technology in software; Intels 3rd Annual Most UnWired 
Cities List released and declares &lt;STRONG&gt;Seattle "Most UnWired" in the 
US&lt;/STRONG&gt;; Sprint squating on their 2.5 GHz frequencies in Seattle area; 
&lt;STRONG&gt;3rd Annual DEFCON WiFi Shoot-out&lt;/STRONG&gt; to be held July 29th; 
&lt;STRONG&gt;FCC 3650&lt;/STRONG&gt; Proceedings attract many comment filers - 
manufacturers position in opposition to WISPA interests. &lt;A 
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;UK / EU Wireless Market Update - Tony 
Fish&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Tony Fish, Principal at AMF Ventures in London and 
Chairman of the 3500+ member Wireless SIG at ecademy.com joins us to provide his 
monthly update on the Wireless Market in the UK and European Union. &lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT 
color=#0000ff&gt;wireless.ecademy.com &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Finding and Dealing With Interference - 
Marlon Schafer&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Odessa Office Equipment Owner, &lt;STRONG&gt;WISP 
Operator and WTR Co-Host, Marlon Schafer&lt;/STRONG&gt;, takes us through his 
recommended checklist and process for identifying interference. "First, believe 
it or not, you have to be sure youre really getting interference," says Marlon, 
"many times therell be another really weird problem like &lt;STRONG&gt;a faulty 
connector&lt;/STRONG&gt; that presents itself as interference." He plans to explain 
the use of spectrum analyzers to isolate real interference problems &lt;A 
href="http://www.odessaoffice.com"&gt;www.odessaoffice.com&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Sun, 03 Jul 2005 13:56:19 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow061505.mp3" length="20193290" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{ACAF3E32-342F-4ECA-A0EE-3A4F87FD7E1B}.38536.4931296875
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show - June 22, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;June 22nd Show - Looks like its a Conference Wrap-Up and Preview Show &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve 
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;ArrayComms 
iBurst&lt;/STRONG&gt; tested in Australia, ArrayComm and Intel make joint 
announcement; &lt;STRONG&gt;IPWireless&lt;/STRONG&gt; and TMobile announcement for 
&lt;STRONG&gt;Czech Republic&lt;/STRONG&gt;; &lt;STRONG&gt;Netgear Pre-N MIMO&lt;/STRONG&gt; product 
uses seven (7) internal antennas , &lt;STRONG&gt;WaveRider EUM 3005&lt;/STRONG&gt; indoor 
gear announcement &lt;A href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;WiFi Planet and ISPCON Wrap-up - Ken 
DiPietro&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Ken DiPietro&lt;/STRONG&gt; of New-ISP.net has 
been attending many of the Spring Wireless conferences and joins us to discuss 
last weeks WiFi-Planet and observations from the Spring ISPCON held in 
Baltimore. &lt;A href="http://www.new-isp.net"&gt;www.new-isp.net&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;WCA Spring 2005 Show Starts Next Week 
- Andrew Kreig&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Andrew Kreig, WCAI 
President&lt;/STRONG&gt;, joins us to discuss next weeks WCA conference in 
Washington, DC at the Marriott Wardman Park hotel, June 28-31. WCA 2005 Show 
highlights include:&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;UL&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Biggest WiMAX show of the year, and last before July launch of 
  certification&lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Key juncture in several regulatory efforts, including 3.6 GHz and 2.5- 2.7 
  GHz&lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Status of license exempt providers in post-Michael Powell era, including 
  merger of LEA into WCA&lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Policy debate on municipal wireless, include rare if not unique debate 
  between Verizon and Philadelphia CIO/Tropos&lt;/LI&gt;
  &lt;LI&gt;Heavy focus on applications, including those for broadband wireless in 
  public safety (U.S. and Iraq), transportation, enterprises&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A 
  href="http://www.wcai.com"&gt;www.wcai.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/LI&gt;&lt;/UL&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Tue, 05 Jul 2005 08:43:40 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow062205.mp3" length="22104074" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{2D4AC503-EF9F-47E0-BD06-0774FAE4C793}.38536.4988060532
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio Show - June 29, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve 
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Travels out to San 
Diego to visit &lt;STRONG&gt;Trango Broadband&lt;/STRONG&gt; and their manufacturing plant; 
extended discussion of the &lt;STRONG&gt;Supreme Court BrandX&lt;/STRONG&gt; decision &lt;A 
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;MetroFi : Wireless Dial-up Replacement 
- Chuck Haas&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Youve probably heard the introductory teasers 
on television: "Wireless broadband for $19.95 for three months!" But what if 
that was the model for your entire business &lt;STRONG&gt;MetroFi founder and CEO 
Chuck Haas&lt;/STRONG&gt; joins us to discuss this new start-up business that begins 
commercial services in the SF Bay area in August. &lt;A 
href="http://www.metrofi.com"&gt;www.metrofi.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Fill-in Segment: News Segment continued - 
Steve, Jim &amp;amp; Marlon &lt;BR&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;Steve gives Kudos to the 
&lt;STRONG&gt;NetNewsWire RSS reader&lt;/STRONG&gt; application (Mac OS only) and explains 
how he uses NetNewsWire to watch and collect news through RSS feeds; 
&lt;STRONG&gt;Frank Lautenberg&lt;/STRONG&gt; and &lt;STRONG&gt;John McLain&lt;/STRONG&gt; sponsor a new 
bill (&lt;STRONG&gt;Community Broadband Act of 2005&lt;/STRONG&gt;) to allow municipalities 
to deploy broadband networks; &lt;STRONG&gt;Dell and Texas Instruments&lt;/STRONG&gt; are 
working to oppose anti-competitive laws being proposed in Texas; Marlon provides 
comments on Software Defined Radio forum and impact on television braodcasters; 
&lt;STRONG&gt;Earthlink&lt;/STRONG&gt; is bidding to provide broadband services for NYCs 
broadband RFP; US Military apparently negotiating to use &lt;STRONG&gt;XM 
Satellite&lt;/STRONG&gt; for its battlefield communications 
purposes.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Tue, 05 Jul 2005 08:22:25 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow062905.mp3" length="19173386" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{FC82DBD4-E78A-4E63-B043-77448F40D098}.38538.344425625
            </guid>

        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Wireless Tech Radio - July 6, 2005
            </title>
            <description>
                &lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Latest Wireless Industry News - Steve 
Stroh, Marlon Schafer &amp;amp; Jim Sutton&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A 
href="http://www.bwianews.com"&gt;www.bwianews.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;MikroTik Routers and RouterOS - Arnis 
Riekstins&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Mikrotik routers are known known to WISPs and 
wireless hobbyist around the world. &lt;STRONG&gt;Co-founder Arnis Riekstins joins us 
from Riga, Latvia&lt;/STRONG&gt; to discuss the company and products. Also of note, 
Mikrotik was active in the Tsunami Relief efforts in Banda Aceh, Indonesia 
donating a 5GHz system and hotspot routers through their Indonesian 
distributor.&lt;BR&gt;MikroTikls [trade name MikroTik®] was founded in 1995 to develop 
and sell wireless ISP systems. MikroTikls now provides wireless ISP systems for 
Internet connectivity in many countries around the world - some locations are 
Iraq, Kosovo, Sri Lanka, Ghana and many others. MikroTikls is located in Riga, 
the capital city of Latvia. MikroTikls has more than 50 employees. &lt;A 
href="http://www.mikrotik.com"&gt;www.mikrotik.com&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#008000 size=4&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Speak Softly And Carry A Big Stick - Jim 
Snider&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Spectrum issues are most important to the wireless 
industry and one of the most entertaining and engaging Watchers of Spectrum 
Issues is &lt;STRONG&gt;J.H.(Jim) Snider&lt;/STRONG&gt;. Hes developed a number of 
publications that poke holes in the &lt;STRONG&gt;myth of spectrum scarcity&lt;/STRONG&gt; 
and broadcasters efforts to protect their ownership of Americas spectrum 
licensed to them for TV services. Why do broadcasters have the reputation for 
being one of the most powerful lobbies in Washington What implications does 
this have for spectrum policy What is going on with DTV legislation on the Hill 
and at the FCC&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Jims just published his latest book entitled &lt;STRONG&gt;&lt;U&gt;Speak Softly And 
Carry A Big Stick: How Local TV Broadcasters Exert Political Power&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;. 
If you want an inside look into how things work and what to anticipate, this is 
the book to read. &lt;BR&gt;Jim Snider is a Senior Research Fellow at the &lt;STRONG&gt;New 
America Foundation&lt;/STRONG&gt; in Washington, DC. His work has appeared in numerous 
publications including The Washington Post, U.S.A. Today, and Atlantic Monthly. 
He holds a Ph.D. in political science from Northwestern University and an MBA 
from Harvard University.communications purposes.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A 
href="http://www.spectrumpolicy.net"&gt;www.spectrumpolicy.net&lt;/A&gt; 
&lt;/P&gt;
            </description>
            <link>
                http://www.wirelesstechradio.com
            </link>
            <author>
                Jim Sutton jim@wirelesstechradio.com
            </author>
            <pubDate>
                Sun, 10 Jul 2005 15:31:25 -0400
            </pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://www.muppethouse.com/wirelesstechradio/WTRshow070605.mp3" length="21864458" type="audio/mpeg">

            </enclosure>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">
                tristana.writer.{A48132BD-EECB-43B3-8ECA-B7F42ADDE9A5}.38543.644372963
            </guid>

        </item>

    </channel>

</rss>

