<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
	<generator>Feed Editor (Unlicensed)</generator>
	<pubDate>5 Feb 2008 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<title>Brad Lansky</title>
	<description>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire by protophonic
    
     Brad and Alex spent two years exploring the Cygnus arm of the Milky Way when they received a classified message from the Sol Ambassador to the Trilux System. Fifty Earth-years have elapsed since they parted ways with Giri Null in Trilux, and much has happened since; Giri Null somehow managed to win over most of the Grefim and execute his plans for a new culture with alarming speed. Those who opted not to follow their new Lord promptly invaded planet Lithom, destabilizing all of Trilux. 

His latest intent, to equip the formidable Grefim with A.I. minds, was interpreted as a hostile act toward Sol by hawkish elements within G.A.I.A. Subsequent events only served to spiral the star systems into a technical state of war.  

Not knowing whom to trust, Giri Null insisted his old friends and the Full Advantage form the Sol ambassador's entourage in a last-ditch effort to negotiate a peace accord. 
  
Brad and Alex feel duty-bound to act as agents for peace, but are well aware that they are merely pawns in a deadly chess game between at least three mighty A.I. groups, and possibly two Grefim factions. 

Alex is quick to point out that a pawn's odds are never good, even with only two players. But if they can make it to the other side and survive until the end game, they might just be able to tip the scales for peace. Worth a try, and besides, they have the Advantage!

    
    </description>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/</link>
	<copyright>Copyright 2008</copyright>
	<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<webMaster>info@protophonic.net</webMaster>
	<image>
	<url>http://www.protophonic.net/pics/EternalFire-Page-1-150x150.jpg</url>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/pics/EternalFire-Page-1-150x150.jpg</link>
	<description>A new Science Fiction audio adventure by protophonic. Visit www.protophonic.net for details.</description>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire</title>
	</image>
	
<a href="http://www.podcastalley.com/"> My Podcast Alley feed!</a> {pca-3ee7c70cb4308251f60c13aa54c02b57}
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 2</title>
	<description>Ship's Log - The Full Advantage is parked in geostationary orbit above Shanghai Spaceport, waiting for Brad and Alex to return from the surface. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T2-128K.mp3" length="4934512" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 3</title>
	<description>Heat Sink - They sprint to Venus at the request of an important A.I. Ambassador. A chilly reception awaits them on a very hot planet. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T3-128K.mp3" length="3758793" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 4</title>
	<description>Aleph One - The Ambassador has shocking news on several fronts. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T4-128K.mp3" length="4804527" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 5</title>
	<description>Parallelogram - Giri Null insisted they visit an old acquaintance of his in a parallel universe, for reasons entirely unclear to all. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T5-128K.mp3" length="7055237" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 6</title>
	<description>Game Plan - Realizing they are pivotal figures in a power struggle between star systems, Brad and Alex try to understand their position as best they can. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T6-128K.mp3" length="2326447" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 7</title>
	<description>Rendezvous with Overdog - Planet Lithom is under siege by the Grefim. Solship Overdog is there to help them rescue Attos from his war torn city. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T7-128K.mp3" length="7078225" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 8</title>
	<description>Tokolosh & Devil's Pique - They cross paths with sinister ships of war. There is no reasoning with A.I.'s of this nature. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T8-128K.mp3" length="5298973" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 9</title>
	<description>Negotiations - Brad and Alex are pinned down in the lander on the surface of planet Grefim itself. Will they ever be allowed to leave after touching holy Grefim soil?  This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T9-128K.mp3" length="3138124" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 10</title>
	<description>Secret Ballot - The terms of the peace deal with Giri Null are announced. As always, the devil is in the details.... This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T10-128K.mp3" length="4381134" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 11</title>
	<description>The Face of Eternal Fire - Under armed escort to the Grefim star, their ultimate part in the peace deal is now abundantly clear, or is it?  This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T11-128K.mp3" length="4135374" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 12</title>
	<description>The Teslalites - They make contact with MARA. Are they in the hands of the fire, or those of a friend? This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T12-128K.mp3" length="3037396" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Face of Eternal Fire - Track 13</title>
	<description>Looking Back - The genius of Giri Null.  This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To enjoy the full-length feature in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 January 2010 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/Eternal-Fire-T13-128K.mp3" length="4843397" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	
	
	<!-- COMMENTED OUT
	-->

	
	</channel>
</rss>

