<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
	<generator>Feed Editor (Unlicensed)</generator>
	<pubDate>5 Feb 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer by protophonic</title>
	<description>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer by protophonic
    
    After their return from Planet X, Brad and Alex have a tough time trying to get their ship to pass its maintenance review. The alien's viral onslaughts have left the Full Advantage riddled with software mutations and there are suspicions of even more invasive alterations. Dieter, whom they'd rescued from the moon-swamp at Planet X, is alive but struggling to shake off his infection. 

Even though their mission had been highly successful by many standards, no sentient press agents on Earth have shown the slightest interest at their return. Surely their findings were newsworthy?!

Things take a turn for the worse when Dieter's condition deteriorates. Just then one of the most powerful A.I.'s in the world requests their immediate presence and offers compelling arguments for a risky mission to an unchartered system twenty thousand light years away. Could this A.I.'s theory about the origin of the alien they found at Planet X be right? If so, can they trust a fragment of this A.I. aboard the Full Advantage to have their well-being at heart, and for that matter, can they still rely on their own ship to bring them back safely? 

And as if this mission didn't have enough unknowns, Brad couldn't deny the wishes of a dying man and has allowed Dieter to come along!

    
    </description>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/</link>
	<copyright>Copyright 2005</copyright>
	<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<webMaster>info@protophonic.net</webMaster>
	<image>
	<url>http://www.protophonic.net/pics/AlienEngineer-Page-1-150x150.jpg</url>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/pics/AlienEngineer-Page-1-150x150.jpg</link>
	<description>A new Science Fiction audio adventure by protophonic. Visit www.protophonic.net for details.</description>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer</title>
	</image>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 1</title>
	<description>This is a music-only intro track. The story begins at Track 2. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>07 Apr 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T1-64K.mp3" length="1374963" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 2</title>
	<description>Ship's Log - The Full Advantage is parked in the AG dock above Shanghai Spaceport, anxiously awaiting her maintenance review.  This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien at Planet X. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>07 Apr 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T2-64K.mp3" length="971086" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 3</title>
	<description>Dieter's Dream Destination - Brad and Alex take the lander down to visit Dieter in the medizone. Sandy is there to greet them. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien at Planet X. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>07 Apr 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T3-64K.mp3" length="2056027" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 4</title>
	<description>Clement II - Clement's robotic brain was destroyed near Planet X. Brad and Alex put Clement II's new brain is to work on the Full Advantage. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien at Planet X. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>07 Apr 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T4-64K.mp3" length="2629632" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 5</title>
	<description>An Audience with Gaia - The crew receive notice that a high-ranking AI  would like to meet with them a.s.a.p. Alex is not amused. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien at Planet X. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>07 Apr 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T5-64K.mp3" length="329647" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 6</title>
	<description>Giri - The AI thinks he's located the home world of the alien they found at Planet X. He makes his case for a joint mission to learn what Earth is dealing with. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien at Planet X. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>07 Apr 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T6-64K.mp3" length="3858058" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 7</title>
	<description>Heading out - Zara and Alex voice their concerns about the mission.  Once again there are too many wildcards for a well-planned expedition. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien at Planet X. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>13 Apr 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T7-64K.mp3" length="986470" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 8</title>
	<description>Journey up the Spiral Arm - Zara interviews the Full Advantage, hoping to understand the psychological changes the ship's AI-mind has undergone since it's return from Planet X. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien at Planet X. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>22 Apr 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T8-64K.mp3" length="2041190" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 9</title>
	<description>The Trilux System - They arrive at the Trilux star system and soon discover planet Lithom. Brad decides to make contact by going down in the lander. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien at Planet X. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>27 Apr 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T9-64K.mp3" length="2434489" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 10</title>
	<description>The Engineer - Brad and Zara meet Attos. They have much to discuss, and very little time in which to plan their next move. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien at Planet X. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>6 May 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T10-64K.mp3" length="4410392" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 11</title>
	<description>Battle of the Mirrors - The Grefim attacks, and the crew race to reach the Full Advantage before it does. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien at Planet X. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>12 May 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T11-64K.mp3" length="2357167" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 12</title>
	<description>Giri Null - Giri Null explains his move and motives. This is a track from the sequel to Brad Lansky and the Alien at Planet X. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>20 May 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T12-64K.mp3" length="2774290" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	<title>Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer - Track 13</title>
	<description>Signing off - More questions.... This is the last track of Brad Lansky and the Alien Engineer. To get this adventure in Hi-Fi quality, please visit www.protophonic.net</description>
	<pubDate>27 May 2006 04:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
	<link>http://www.protophonic.net/script.php</link>
	<author>info@protophonic.net</author>
	<category>Podcasts</category>
	<enclosure url="http://www.protophonic.net/sound/ALIEN-ENGINEER-T13-64K.mp3" length="2026561" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	</item>
	
	
	
	
	
	<!-- COMMENTED OUT
	-->

	
	</channel>
</rss>

