<?xml version="1.0"?>
	<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Craig Terry Motors</title>
		<link>http://www.craigterrymotors.com</link>
		<description>Craig Terry Motors is committed to offer you the resources to make an informed decision when purchasing your next car. We pride ourselves on being the best used car dealership available to you and have been serving our customers since 1984.  Our credit specialists are here to help you and inform you on your best choice for any credit problem financing.  We specialize in credit challenged financing and have positioned ourselves to offer the public many tailored options for the financing needs.</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>Craig Terry Motors.com</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 03:45:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<generator>tdscripts.com Podcast Generator</generator>		<webMaster>craigterry12@gmail.com</webMaster>
		<ttl>1</ttl>
		<item>
			<title>Craig Terry Motors</title>
			<description>Welcome to the premiere Sudbury and area Car Buying Dealership serving all of Northern Ontario.   Craig Terry Motors.com; whether you are looking for a certified pre-owned vehicle or maybe you have credit issue and require on the lot financing to help rebuild your credit.   Craig Terry Motors.com can help.  You want a vehicle but have bad credit?  Do not let your bad credit circumstances stand in the way of securing your dream car.  Craig Terry Motors.com can help; our credit specialists are committed – they can help you get on the road and increase your credit.  Craig Terry Motors.com finances right on the lot and is connected to the most financial lenders and private banks available in Canada.  Either way you win.  Don’t think your credit problems will stop you from buying a car.  At Craig Terry Motors; we have the answers for all your concerns in Sudbury, North Bay, Timmins, Sault Ste. Marie and Barrie.  Our dealership can help you get a car even if your credit is not the best.  Relieve your stress and be happy again by getting a car you both want and deserve.  Craig Terry Motors.com can get you into a vehicle in under 24 hours.  Log onto our site and tell us what it is you are looking for.  One of our credit specialists will contact you, we deal with the best financing options available.  If we cannot help you – then no one can.  Our credit specialists can help you get into your car today.  Go on over to Craig Terry Motors.com and let us help you get a new car today.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 03:45:43 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="www.craigterrymotors.com" length="461136" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			</item>
		</channel>
	</rss>