<?xml version="1.0"?>
	<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Weight Perspectives</title>
		<link>http://www.allihcp.com/alliInAction.aspx</link>
		<copyright>2009, GlaxoSmithKline</copyright>
		<pubDate>Tue, 6 Oct 2009 11:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
		<itunes:author>Hosted By Shel Lustig</itunes:author>
		<itunes:category text="Health" />
		<itunes:image href="http://mediatracks.com/Weight%20Perspectives.jpg"/>
		<itunes:keywords>weight, weight loss, tips, health, overweight, weight loss advice, weight reduction</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:subtitle>A series providing practical advice on the topic of weight loss.</itunes:subtitle>
		<description>A series of three podcasts developed to provide healthcare professionals with answers and practical advice on the topic of weight loss. Topics explored include recommendations on how to provide patients with information, appropriate counseling, and behavioral support. The series also offers tips from pharmacists Cheryl Hartvigsen and Jann Skelton on how to counsel patients with small, sustained lifestyle modifications in an effort to achieve long-lasting results.</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:owner>
        <itunes:name>Sean Waldron</itunes:name>
        <itunes:email>swaldron@mediatracks.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
		<generator>tdscripts.com Podcast Generator</generator>		<webMaster>info@mediatracks.com (Sean Waldron)</webMaster>
		<ttl>1</ttl>
		<item>
			<title>Need for Onsite Counseling</title>
			<description>In the first podcast of our series, pharmacist Cheryl Hartvigsen discusses the importance of onsite weight loss counseling for those who are considering an over-the-counter weight loss aid. She also shares valuable tips that can be shared with patients who are seeking advice and counsel on how to lose weight and keep it off.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 8 Oct 2009 11:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://mediatracks.com/Weight%20Perspectives%201.mp3" length="4800000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Need for a Support Program</title>
			<description>In the second podcast of our series, pharmacist Cheryl Hartvigsen explains the health benefits of gradual weight loss and the beneficial effects of even modest changes in body weight.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 7 Oct 2009 11:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://mediatracks.com/Weight%20Perspectives%202.mp3" length="4400000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Achieving Modest Weight Loss </title>
			<description>In the third podcast of our series, pharmacist Jann Skelton talks about reshaping the way people think about weight loss and the importance of small, sustained lifestyle modifications as the key to successful weight control.</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 6 Oct 2009 11:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://mediatracks.com/Weight%20Perspectives%203.mp3" length="3400000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			</item>
		</channel>
	</rss>