<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Bah &amp; The Humbugs Christmas Eve Podcast</title>
<link>http://www.bahandthehumbugs.com</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>&#x2117; &amp; &#xA9; 2010 Bah &amp; the Humbugs</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle>Holiday Cheer with America's Premier Satiric Christmas Rock Band</itunes:subtitle>
<description>Bah &amp; the Humbugs, America's premier satiric Christmas rock band, presents their annual Christmas Eve podcast for your enjoyment.  Sit back with some eggnog and your favorite elf and enjoy the Humbugs' unique brand of holiday cheer and coal-in-your-stocking, laugh-until-you-hurt Humbugs songs.</description>
<itunes:author>Bah &amp; the Humbugs</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Bah &amp; the Humbugs, America's premier satiric Christmas rock band, presents their annual Christmas Eve podcast for your enjoyment.  Sit back with some eggnog and your favorite elf and enjoy the Humbugs' unique brand of holiday cheer and coal-in-your-stocking, laugh-until-you-hurt Humbugs songs.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Paul Nordquist</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>paul@fjordstone.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/images/podcast.jpg" />
<itunes:category text="Comedy" />
<itunes:category text="Music" />
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

<item>
<title>Bah &amp; The Humbugs Christmas Eve 2005 Podcast</title>
<itunes:author>Bah &amp; The Humbugs</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A Christmas Eve Spooktacular featuring the Tale of Dr. Frankincense</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>It's Aliiiive!!!  Bah &amp; the Humbugs - A Christmas Eve Spooktacular is the 2005 podcast from America's premier satirical Christmas rock band.  A brand-new spooky radio play and six coal-in-your-stocking Humbugs classics make this a must-listen on your Christmas Eve "To Listen" list.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2005.mp3" length="29214638" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2005.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2005 03:33:33 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>30:25</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>Christmas, humor, funny songs, satiric, Frankincense, monster, creature, snowman, tree, scary, Humbugs</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bah &amp; The Humbugs Christmas Eve 2006 Podcast</title>
<itunes:author>Bah &amp; The Humbugs</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A Very Commercial Christmas</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Bah &amp; the Humbugs is back with an hour of hilarious Christmas commercial parodies.  On Christmas Eve, slip off your shoes, relax by a warm, crackling fire...and tune in radio station WCOMMERCIAL, "All-Commercial Radio."  The DJ will be spinning all of your favorite Christmas commercials, to make the Yuletide bright.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2006.mp3" length="82640062" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2006.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2006 03:33:33 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>01:08:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>Christmas, humor, funny songs, satiric, snowman, tree, Bah, Humbugs, commercials, commercial, parody, Whining Christmas Babies, toyminator, WCOMMERCIAL</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bah &amp; The Humbugs Christmas Eve 2007 Podcast</title>
<itunes:author>Bah &amp; The Humbugs</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Big Jerry's Big Emergency Overstock Liquidation Bonanza Christmas Special</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Bah &amp; the Humbugs is back with an all new, all original comedy program to while away the hours while you're waiting for Santa.  This year, entrepreneur Big Jerry is podcasting live from his emergency overstock liquidation warehouse, where the big deals of the day are on Bah &amp; the Humbugs' new CD, "The 12 Symptoms of Christmas," surplus pharmaceuticals from the People's Army of Izbogustan, and piles and piles of misprinted higher math textbooks.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2007.mp3" length="59867034" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2007.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2007 03:33:33 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:49:53</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>Christmas, humor, funny songs, satiric, snowman, tree, Bah, Humbugs, satire, pop music, 12 Symptoms of Christmas</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bah &amp; The Humbugs Christmas Eve 2008 Podcast</title>
<itunes:author>Bah &amp; The Humbugs</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Yetis of Yuletide</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Bah &amp; the Humbugs take over Christmas once again, this year featuring the saga of Newton Figg's 'Backyard Astronomer Podcast.' Listen as Figg rails against his neighbor's elaborate Trans-Sylvanian Orchestra-backed light show that foils his attempts to view objects in space, and ultimately bringing ruin and mayhem to the neighborhood.  Enjoy this all-new original program, paired with the usual irreverent and festive Bah &amp; the Humbugs music, including the new songs Santa Hat and Mincemeat.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2008.mp3" length="31301643" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2008.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 12:25:08 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:32:36</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>Christmas, humor, funny songs, satiric, snowman, tree, Bah, Humbugs, satire, pop music, irreverent, mincemeat, Santa Hat, astronomy, astronomer, Trans-Siberian Orchestra, Wizards of Winter, space aliens, SETI, Bah and the Humbugs</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bah &amp; The Humbugs Christmas Eve 2009 Podcast</title>
<itunes:author>Bah &amp; The Humbugs</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Elfbook vs. Humbook</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>A merry band of elves are enjoying the social networking phenomenon, Elfbook, until one elf gets mad, and gets even.  Listen as Diesel the elf gets so annoyed, he quits Elfbook and joins Humbook, in order to take advantage of...anti-social networking.  Included are brand new Bah &amp; the Humbugs songs Mr. Big Christmas, Titanic Tannenbaum, No Free Lunch, Cease and Desist, and 2007 hit No Smoking in the Chimney.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2009.mp3" length="20539268" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2009.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 04:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:21:23</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>funny Christmas songs, humor, satiric, Santa, Santa Claus, Mr. Big Christmas, Titanic Tannenbaum, No Free Lunch, No Smoking in the Chimney, Elfbook, Humbook, social networking, Bah, Humbugs, satire, pop music, irreverent, Bah and the Humbugs</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Bah &amp; The Humbugs Christmas Eve 2010 Podcast</title>
<itunes:author>Bah &amp; The Humbugs</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Help! I Have A Celebrity Babysitter on Christmas!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Everyone's favorite Christmas reality show decks the halls on Christmas Eve when veteran rock star Phizzy Parker babysits for an ordinary American family.  Phizzy's bedtime tale tells the true story of the first Christmas, with help from the internet and TV friends.  Included are brand new Bah &amp; the Humbugs songs Authority Man, Christmas Beer, Merry or Die, Frostbite, and Perry T. Partridge (The Christmas Detective).</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2010.mp3" length="25893325" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2010.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2010 23:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:26:58</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>funny Christmas songs, humor, satiric, Santa, Bah, Humbugs, satire, pop music, irreverent, Bah and the Humbugs, authority man, christmas beer, merry or die, frostbite, flesh-eating snowman, perry t. partridge, christmas detective, celebrity babysitter</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bah &amp; The Humbugs Christmas Eve 2011 Podcast</title>
<itunes:author>Bah &amp; The Humbugs</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Ask Us Anything About Christmas with Stormin' Snoman and the Merry Morning Menagerie</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>The Arctic Circle's #1 morning radio show, The Merry Morning Menagerie with Stormin' Snoman on KPLR 90.0 'The Polar,' asks listeners to call in with their Christmas questions for experts visiting in the studio.  Included are a brand new recording of the Bah &amp; the Humbugs classic You Decorated My Tree, as well as Round and Round, Fahrenheit 12/25, The Christmas Zoo, Here Come the Christmas Zombies, Santa Cruise, Getting Christmas Off the Ground, and No Santa.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2011.mp3" length="31045090" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.fjordstone.com/bah/bahcast2011.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:32:20</itunes:duration>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords>funny Christmas songs, humor, satiric, Santa, Bah, Humbugs, satire, pop music, irreverent, Bah and the Humbugs, ask us anything about christmas, kplr, the polar, stormin' snoman, merry morning menagerie, santa cruise, you decorated my tree, round and round, fahrenheit 12/25, the christmas zoo, here come the christmas zombies, no santa, getting christmas off the groundåå</itunes:keywords>
</item>
 
</channel>
</rss>