<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>ALM CyberChurch Services</title>
		<link>http://livingsounds.org</link>
		<description>Services from the virtual reality world. Cutting edge worship experience with singing and Biblical preaching.</description>
	    <docs>http://livingsounds.org</docs>
	    <language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>Copyright 2006-2010 Living Sounds</copyright>
		<pubDate>Sun, 7 Sep 2006 14:10:00 EST</pubDate>
	    <lastBuildDate>{podcast_date}</lastBuildDate>
		<itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
	    <itunes:keywords>christian, christianity, church, bible, jesus, god, religion, religious, truth, doctrine, christian music, online church, internet church</itunes:keywords>
    	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:image href="http://livingsounds.org/podcast/almcyberchurch.jpg" />
	    <itunes:owner>
			<itunes:name>Living Sounds</itunes:name>
			<itunes:email>mail@livingsounds.org</itunes:email>
	    </itunes:owner>
	    <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
	    <itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">
			<itunes:category text="Christianity"/>
	    </itunes:category>

        <item>
             <title>Why Answers Are Delayed</title>
             <description>Why does it sometimes seem as though God isn't answering our prayers? Why does He sometimes wait so long to respond? And is it a lack of faith to pray more than once for the same thing? Today we look to the Scriptures for the answers to these questions, as we ponder Why Answers Are Delayed.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 3 June 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/06-03-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Our Vision</title>
             <description>"To break through religion and man-made traditions and doctrines so the Body of Christ can develop deep, intimate, unobstructed and unbroken fellowship with God, and to do so in an environment that breaks through physical distances and is engaging, immersive, personal, and as free from distractions as possible." Today we talk about the vision of this ministry, the direction in which we are going, the exciting changes that direction demands, and how important it is for you to discover and write down the vision God has for your life.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/05-27-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Neither Will I Tell You</title>
             <description>Most of us have heard the story of Jesus' encounter with the religious leaders when they asked Him by what authority He was doing these things. Is there something buried in that account that we can learn and apply to our lives? Today we dig a bit deeper into this passage, and listen for what the Spirit wants to teach us today through His word.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/05-20-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>What is the Flesh?</title>
             <description>We hear a lot about crucifying the flesh, not feeding the flesh, and walking according to the Spirit instead of the flesh. But what exactly IS the flesh? A closer look at God's word might surprise you. Today we look into the Scripture for the answer to this question, as we ponder what it means to feed the flesh, and how we can walk according to the Spirit instead.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/05-13-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>New Beginnings</title>
             <description>Today is our last service on Truth Island in Second Life. This is our "farewell" service. We talk about our move to OSGrid (we're not leaving ministry, just changing locations), and also talk about how when God closes a door, "somewhere He opens a window," and consider what closed doors really mean. Join us for this important message that could change your outlook on life for the better.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 6 May 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/05-06-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>The Armor of God, Part 7: Praying Always</title>
             <description>In this final part of this series on The Armor of God, and possibly the last service in our location in Second Life, we talk about how we can keep all the parts of the armor clean, polished, oiled, and strong -- Praying Always. Join us as we discuss this lifestyle we are all called to live -- a lifestyle that will change our lives and will transform the world around us.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 29 April 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/04-29-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>The Armor of God, Part 6: The Word</title>
             <description>What is the word of God? Does it include the "lost books of the Bible"? Is it relevant to us today? Has it changed and "evolved"? And what role should it play in our lives? Today we see what Jesus says about what the word of God is, and we examine the power of The Word.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 22 April 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/04-22-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>The Armor of God, Part 5: Salvation</title>
             <description>What is salvation? What does it mean to wear the helmet of salvation? And how important is it to make sure we have the whole thing? Today we search the Scriptures as we listen for what God says about Salvation, a vital part of the Armor of God.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 15 April 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/04-15-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>He Is Risen!</title>
             <description>Today, we celebrate the resurrection of Jesus. How important is the resurrection? And does it matter if we believe Jesus rose physically, or could He have risen only in the spirit as some in the Church claim? Today we open the Holy Scriptures and see what God has to say about these matters, as we celebrate the fact the He Is Risen!</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 8 April 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/04-08-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>The Armor of God, Part 4: Faith</title>
             <description>What is faith? Is it a strong belief? Is it blindly accepting something as true despite how things appear? Is it a strong conviction or certainty? Or is it something else, something much bigger and much more powerful? Today we look to the Scriptures to answer these questions, as we ponder what true faith really is, and as we consider the only way we can truly have faith.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 1 April 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/04-01-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>The Armor of God, Part 3: The Gospel</title>
             <description>For the past two weeks, we've been talking about the Armor of God, and how important every single piece is if we are to be able to stand against the deceitful trickery of the devil. What are the Shoes of the Preparation of the Gospel of Peace? And how can be make sure they are firmly in place? Today we open up the Scriptures and examine what is really meant by the Gospel of Peace.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 25 March 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/03-25-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>The Armor of God, Part 2: Righteousness</title>
             <description>What is righteousness? How important is it in the Christian's life? And how does it connect with the rest of the Armor of God to protect us from the deceitful trickery of the devil? Today we take an in-depth look at righteousness from the Holy Scriptures.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 18 March 2012 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/03-18-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>The Armor of God, Part 1: Truth</title>
             <description>What is the Armor of God? Is it really that important? And how do we "put it on"? Today we consult the Holy Scriptures for the answers to these questions, as we explore the Armor of God.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 11 March 2012 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/03-11-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Living in a Spiritual World</title>
             <description>What are demons? Are all bad spirits mentioned in the Bible referring to demonic entities? How can we live lives surrounded by light and life, while expelling darkness and the presence of the enemy? Today we look at the word of God and consider the answers to these questions, as we prepare ourselves for Living in a Spiritual World.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 4 March 2012 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/03-04-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Freedom and Desire</title>
             <description>Do you ever find yourself wanting to do the right thing, but falling short? We all do, and it can make us feel "unholy" or like we're not as "spiritual" as we should be. But is this really the case? Today we see what the Bible says about this issue, as we explore the topic of Freedom and Desire, and consider how we can move forward.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 19 February 2012 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/02-19-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Happy Valentine's Day 2012</title>
             <description>While many people love Valentine's Day, there are those who hate it for various reasons. What is the origin of this holiday? And how can we see God in this and every other day? Today we take a look at the history of Valentine's Day, and consider the love of God for us.</description>
             <itunes:author>Jennifer L. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 12 February 2012 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/02-12-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Dealing with Conflict</title>
             <description>If you've never had any sort of conflict with anyone, never had at least someone try to argue with you, and never said anything to someone you shouldn't have, then you probably haven't been born yet. We all deal with conflict. The question is how? Today we examine the causes of verbal attacks and arguments, and look to the word of God for direction in how to interact with others.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 5 February 2012 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/02-05-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Practical Miracles</title>
             <description>What exactly is a miracle? Do they happen today? And how can we see and recognize more miracles in our lives? Today we search the word of God for the answers to these questions, and consider what we can change in our lives so that our lives are filled with miracles.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 29 January 2012 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/01-29-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Miracles</title>
             <description>The Bible is full of miracles, especially those performed by Jesus. Does God still perform miracles today? Today we take a look at some of Jesus' miracles, including the most important one of all time.</description>
             <itunes:author>Jennifer L. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 22 January 2012 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/01-22-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>See Through</title>
             <description>What does it mean to be transparent? How can we allow the light of Jesus to shine through us? And how important is being "see-through" to the Christian? Today we explore the Scriptures and consider why and how we can become See Through.</description>
             <itunes:author>Jennifer L. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 15 January 2012 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/01-15-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Dissipated or Spirit Filled?</title>
             <description>What is dissipation? What does the Bible say about it? And is it just referring to getting drunk, or are there other ways we experience "dissipation"? What can we do about it? Today we consult the word of God for the answers to these questions we should all ask, and we explore the difference between being dissipated, and being filled with the Holy Spirit.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 8 January 2012 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2012/01-08-2012_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Christmas 2011</title>
             <description>During the Christmas Season, we celebrate the priceless gift God gave us on that first Christmas Day. But what gift can we give to God this Christmas? Today we sing some Christmas carols, read the Christmas story from Luke, and hear an inspirational Christmas story.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 25 December 2011 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/12-25-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Better to Give</title>
             <description>This Christmas Season, most of us will be giving and receiving gifts. Which one of these excites us the most? Is it wrong to be excited about receiving a gift? And how can be best connect with God's heart and share His love with those who need Him the most? Today we examine the verse in which Jesus says it is more blessed to give than to receive, and we consider what this really means.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 18 December 2011 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/12-18-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>The Box</title>
             <description>Have you ever felt as though there is something standing between you and happiness? Joy? Peace? Love? Throughout our lives, we build walls to protect us from pain, rejection, and disappointment. Join us today for a story that brings our building of walls into a new perspective, and learn how to be totally set free!</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 11 December 2011 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/12-11-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Making Disciples</title>
             <description>Are all Christians called to spread the Gospel? Is there anything we can learn from the business world to help us tell people the Good News? And what does Jesus say about using wisdom from the world? Today we talk about the subject of Making Disciples, and consider what we can learn from secular society.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 4 December 2011 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/12-04-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Our Plan vs. God's Plan</title>
             <description>We've all tried to live life according to our own plans, and in doing so, we miss out on the perfect things God has in mind for us. What examples does the Bible give of following God's plans instead of ours? And what difference does it make? Today we talk about the subject of God's Plan vs. Our Plan.</description>
             <itunes:author>Jennifer L. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 27 November 2011 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/11-27-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>God's Best vs. Man's</title>
             <description>Some believe that everything is up to them, while others believe that God doesn't really expect anything from us. Is either one of these true? Today we consult the word of God, take a look at Jesus' first miracle, and consider what that miracle teaches us today.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 13 November 2011 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/11-13-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Thanksgiving</title>
             <description>In a couple of weeks, we will be celebrating Thanksgiving. But what does giving thanks have to do with us right now? Today we look at what the Bible says about giving thanks.</description>
             <itunes:author>Jennifer L. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 6 November 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/11-06-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>From the Very First Day</title>
             <description>Have you ever felt as though God doesn't hear your prayers? As though heaven is made out brass? As though you don't know if God will ever answer your prayer? Today we learn from the Scriptures whether God hears you, when He hears you, and when He begins answering your prayers.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 23 October 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/10-23-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Intimacy with God</title>
             <description>What does "intimacy with God" mean? Is this something that only the pastors and evangelists should do? And what difference does it make whether you learn to be intimate with God? Today we take a look at what the Bible says about our intimacy with God, and consider what role intimacy should play in our lives.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 16 October 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/10-16-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Be Still and Know</title>
             <description>What does it mean to "be still and know"? In our fast-paced world, taking the time to be still is something most of us never learn to do. Is it important? If so, why? And how can we learn to be still and know? Today we search the word of God for the answers to these questions, as we learn to "be still and know."</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 9 October 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/10-09-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Strong Enough</title>
             <description>Do you ever feel as though you're just not strong enough to overcome an issue, or break an addiction, or do what you know you should do? Today we talk about our source of strength, whether we're ever given anything we can't handle, and who is Strong Enough.</description>
             <itunes:author>Jennifer L. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Thu, 2 October 1022 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/1022/10-02-1022_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Heaven Class</title>
             <description>For thousands of years, there have been different classes of people. Today we have the upper, middle, and lower class. These refer primarily to the amount of money each person has. But what type of class system is recognized in God's eyes? Today we talk about this issue from the perspective of God's word, and we explore what "Heaven Class" has to do with us.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 25 September 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/09-25-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Something About Jesus</title>
             <description>There have been a lot of popular men and women throughout history, from poets to warriors to philosophers to heroes. But there is one man who outshines them all. Today we talk about that man; because there is just Something About Jesus.</description>
             <itunes:author>Jennifer L. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 18 September 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/09-18-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Freedom</title>
             <description>Is freedom doing whatever you want? Are people who have no restraint really free? And how can we break free from the things that hold us bound? Today we take a look at what the word of God tells us about true freedom.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 11 September 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/09-11-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Emotional Worship</title>
             <description>Many Christians believe that getting too emotional during worship is a bad thing to do. Others believe that if you don't show great emotion, you're less spiritual. Which view is correct? And is there a balance? Today we talk about the issue of emotions in worship, and ponder the type of worship God desires from you.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 4 September 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/09-04-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Why?</title>
             <description>Have you ever asked God "why?" Have you ever wondered why God allows bad things to happen to you, those you love, and innocent people in the world? Today we go to the Scriptures to answer these questions.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 28 August 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/08-28-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>The Bereans and You</title>
             <description>Who are the Bereans? What did they do that caused them to be mentioned in Scripture as "more noble / fair-minded"? And would you fit in better with the Bereans or with those from Thessalonica? Today we explore this subject in the Scriptures, and ponder where we are, and how we can get to where we should be.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 21 August 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/08-21-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Joy, Part 2</title>
             <description>What exactly is joy? How can we find it? Can true joy be destroyed by our circumstances? And how long does it last? Today we take a look at what the word of God says, in this second of a two-part message on Joy.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 14 August 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/08-14-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Joy, Part 1</title>
             <description>What exactly is joy? How can we find it? Can true joy be destroyed by our circumstances? And how long does it last? Today we take a look at what the word of God says, in this first of a two-part message on Joy.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 7 August 2011 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/08-07-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Jesus Changes Lives</title>
             <description>Throughout history, many men and women have accomplished great things in the name of Jesus. But we often don't know anything about their lives BEFORE Christ. I think we'd all be amazed at how much Jesus really can change someone's life. Today, our women's pastor talks about some of the stories of those who came before us, and ends with an invitation to allow Jesus to change YOUR life too.</description>
             <itunes:author>Jennifer L. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 31 July 2011 12:10:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/07-31-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>God From The Beginning</title>
             <description>Many in the Church debate whether Jesus is God, whether there is only one path to God, and whether there is such a thing as the Trinity. Are these things spelled out clearly in Scripture? If so, where? Today we explore these questions, as we discover that, from even the first three verses in the Bible, the question of God's nature is answered, and from the word of God which follows, all the rest are made clear.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 24 July 2011 12:10:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/07-24-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>He Wants It All</title>
             <description>Most of us think of Solomon's wisdom as something that was given to him after he asked for it. This is natural, since we think of everything in terms of time and space. But God is not bound by time. Just as He preordained those who would come to Him before the beginning of time, could it also be possible that He has already put into motion the answers to your prayers and the gifts He has purposed for your life? Today we discuss this issue, and also consider that, out of everything He's put inside of you to become, He wants it all.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 17 July 2011 12:10:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/07-17-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Your Sin Will Find You Out</title>
             <description>We've all heard the words from Scripture, "Your sin will find you out." What does this mean if read in context? And how does it apply to us? Today we explore this issue a bit deeper, and discuss some possibilities which the Church seldom considers.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 10 July 2011 12:10:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/07-10-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Colors Of The Rainbow</title>
             <description>Tomorrow, in the United States of America, we will celebrate the 4th of July, rejoicing in the "red, white, and blue." Today, we discuss the deeper meanings of these and the other colors God has created.</description>
             <itunes:author>Jennifer L. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 3 July 2011 12:10:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/07-03-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>To Those Who Are Searching</title>
             <description>Sometimes it seems as though the truth is hidden, as though it is practically impossible to find. But Jesus said that whoever keeps on seeking will find. Who can find truth? And how? Today we turn to the Word of God to answer this question, and discover that the truth is revealed by God to those who are searching.</description>
             <itunes:author>Rev. Benjamin R. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 26 June 2011 12:10:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/06-26-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Father's Day 2011</title>
             <description>Today, as we celebrate fathers around the world, we have a time of sharing in the virtual world, talking about our earthly and our heavenly father. The in-world sharing time is not available on audio, but here is the introduction.</description>
             <itunes:author>Jennifer L. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 19 June 2011 12:10:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/06-19-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

        <item>
             <title>Such Love</title>
             <description>The world talks quite a bit about love. The radios are filled with songs about found and lost love. The movies and television shows are filled with love stories. And yet, the love we see presented to us by the world is unsure and unstable, and ends betraying us more often than not. Today we take a look at a different kind of love, God's love, a love that we cannot even begin to comprehend.</description>
             <itunes:author>Jennifer L. Faust</itunes:author>
             <pubDate>Sun, 12 June 2011 12:10:00 EST</pubDate>
             <enclosure url="http://livingsounds-media.org/sl/services/2011/06-12-2011_broad.mp3" length="70000000" type="audio/mpeg" />
        </item>

	</channel>
</rss>