<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Exploring the Frontiers of Assistive Technology</title>
        <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
        <description>A video podcast showing how people use assistive technology to communicate, express their creativity, play games and make so much more out of life. This podcast shows that there is no reason why people with physical, vision, speech or language impairments cannot use the same creative and educational software as every other Mac OS X user. There will be a few episodes per year, each starring a different person. Copyright AssistiveWare, all rights reserved.</description>
        <generator>Feeder 2.2.5(2.2.5); Mac OS X Version 10.6.8 (Build 10K549) http://reinventedsoftware.com/feeder/</generator>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>Copyright 2005-2008 AssistiveWare, all rights reserved.</copyright>
        <managingEditor>support@assistiveware.com</managingEditor>
        <webMaster>webmaster@assistiveware.com</webMaster>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 19:19:27 +0100</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 19:19:27 +0100</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://www.assistiveware.com/feeds/FrontiersOfAssistiveTechnology.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
        <itunes:subtitle>A video podcast showing how people use assistive technology to communicate, express their creativity, play games and make so much more out of life.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:keywords>disability, accessibility, handicap</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:image href="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/Frontiers-of-AT-artwork.png"/>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>David Niemeijer</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>d.niemeijer@assistiveware.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <itunes:category text="Education">
            <itunes:category text="Educational Technology"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Health"/>
        <itunes:category text="Kids &amp; Family"/>
        <item>
            <title>It really has become his voice</title>
            <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Max is nine years old and was born with Cerebral Palsy. The language area in his brain has been affected and he therefore has difficulty using his speech to communicate. He started using Proloquo2Go on an iPad about a year ago. He now uses it on a daily basis, at school and at home. His speech has made good progress and his frustration level has decreased. Max is more able to communicate, he spells and he can create sentences that he was not able to create before. He even helps with customizing the app's vocabulary. According to his speech therapist, Proloquo2Go has become his voice and has completely changed his life. Read more about Max at www.lovethatmax.com</p>

<p><i>Disclaimer: Note that this video presents an unscripted case study and any statements made in the video pertain to this particular case and are not intended as a comprehensive product evaluation or recommendation. Different people have different needs and it is always recommended to get an AAC evaluation from an expert.</i></p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 19:17:09 +0100</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/frontiersofassistivetechnology11.m4v" length="265460310" type="application/octet-stream"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">993CB1F0-BF4D-43A8-969B-53C7F57B8900</guid>
            <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Max is nine years old and was born with Cerebral Palsy. He started using Proloquo2Go on an iPad about a year ago. According to his speech therapist, Proloquo2Go has become his voice and has completely changed his life.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:duration>4:41</itunes:duration>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tell us, we want to know</title>
            <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Nick is ten years old and was diagnosed with autism. His progress in speech has been extremely slow. Picture symbols, picture exchange communication techniques and photos were tried but did not work out for him, as Nick was not really interested. When Nick started using an iPad, he immediately understood how it worked and really wanted to use it. The device was reinforcing and he sensed it was a powerful tool for him. Now that Nick is using an iPad with Proloquo2Go he no longer has to try to be what other people want him to be, because he can now initiate communication and say what he wants and needs. Nick lives in New Jersey, United States of America.</p>

<p><i>Disclaimer: Note that this video presents an unscripted case study and any statements made in the video pertain to this particular case and are not intended as a comprehensive product evaluation or recommendation. Different people have different needs and it is always recommended to get an AAC evaluation from an expert.</i></p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 14:15:51 +0100</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/frontiersofassistivetechnology10.m4v" length="297266505" type="application/octet-stream"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5243448C-A915-48EE-975F-14A20B685BE6</guid>
            <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Nick is ten years old and was diagnosed with autism. Now that Nick is using an iPad with Proloquo2Go he no longer has to try to be what other people want him to be, because he can now initiate communication and say what he wants and needs.
</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:duration>5:29</itunes:duration>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Blossoming as a child</title>
            <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><b>Vanessa</b> is three years old and was born with Pervasive Developmental Disorder (PDD), a form of autism. Her parents noticed that she was very to herself and knew right away that something was off. About three months ago, Vanessa started using <a href="http://www.proloquo2go.com/">Proloquo2Go</a> on an iPad. Even though her parents were concerned that using a communication solution might further delay her speech development, they trialed Proloquo2Go through the Young Autism Program of <a href="http://ddiny.org/">DDI</a>. Everyone has been amazed by Vanessa's approximations and increased attempts to communicate. The app has given her a voice. Now she can finally say what she wants, making more verbalizations and babbling more than before. Vanessa&rsquo;s speech is growing, and most importantly, she is blossoming as a child. Vanessa lives in New York, United States of America.</p>

<p><i>Disclaimer: Note that this video presents an unscripted case study and any statements made in the video pertain to this particular case and are not intended as a comprehensive product evaluation or recommendation. Different people have different needs and it is always recommended to get an AAC evaluation from an expert.</i></p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 21:51:00 +0100</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/FrontiersOfAssistiveTechnology9.m4v" length="276546144" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A4FD7132-6173-4688-8863-7A1EE30BF1B3</guid>
            <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Vanessa is three years old and was born with Pervasive Developmental Disorder (PDD), a form of autism. Vanessa started using Proloquo2Go on an iPad and her speech is growing, and most importantly, she is blossoming as a child.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:duration>5:19</itunes:duration>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Head-designed</title>
            <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<b>Giesbert Nijhuis</b> was a talented photographer and graphic designer when he had a spinal cord injury due to a car accident in December 1995. Left paralyzed from the neck down he took up his old professions again replacing his pencil with a computer. Now he does all his artwork with his head, using a <a href="http://orin.com/access/headmouse/">HeadMouse Extreme</a> from Origin Instruments to control his cursor. To write and control Photoshop and all those other applications that rely on keyboard shortcuts and modifier-key click combinations he uses AssistiveWare's <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/keystrokes.php">KeyStrokes</a> on-screen keyboard. He has a beautiful, head-designed <a href="http://www.laesieworks.com">web site</a> chronicling his "first" and "second" life and designs t-shirts, CD covers, film posters, application icons and much more using his head and his Apple Power Mac G5 Quad.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 17:41:46 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/FrontiersOfAssistiveTechnology8.m4v" length="31396593" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">headdesigned</guid>
            <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Giesbert Nijhuis is paralyzed from the neck down due to a spinal cord injury caused by a car accident. He now designs t-shirts, CD covers, film posters and much more using a head pointer and an on-screen keyboard.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:duration>3:05</itunes:duration>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Communication is the central thing</title>
            <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<b>Walter Pfrommer</b> was a pediatric surgeon when he was diagnosed with ALS in 1999. Despite losing his mobility and speech he continued to work: first as a project manager on a hospital IT project, later as consultant to another person who took over his role as project manager. Using his Apple laptop with AssistiveWare's <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/proloquo.php">Proloquo</a> augmentative communication software, AssistiveWare's <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/keystrokes.php">KeyStrokes</a> on-screen keyboard and an Origin Instruments <a href="http://orin.com/access/headmouse/">HeadMouse Extreme</a>, he communicated with co-workers, family, friends and other people through email, chat and an Acapela Group synthesized speech voice. Walter wanted to make the best of life. In the video, shot in November 2005 he takes us along to his work, to a museum and to cinema. After his condition worsened he died in February 2006.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 20:49:51 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/FrontiersOfAssistiveTechnology7.m4v" length="41757605" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">communication-is-the-central-thing</guid>
            <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Walter Pfrommer was diagnosed with ALS in 1999 and lost his mobility and speech. He uses an Apple PowerBook with augmentative communication software, an on-screen keyboard and a head pointer to communicate.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:duration>3:49</itunes:duration>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>We can because we think we can</title>
            <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<b>Leigh-Anne Tompkins</b> was born with cerebral palsy due to a lack of oxygen at birth. Inspired by a documentary of a young woman who painted with her feet, Leigh-Anne started drawing when she was 9 years old. Supported by her parents, teachers, college professors and other students she graduated magna cum laude in Fine Arts. She now has her own company: <a href="http://www.graphicsafoot.com/">Graphics Afoot Studio Design</a>. She draws with her right foot using a trackball on the floor. A head stylus, Sticky Keys and AssistiveWare's <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/keystrokes.php">KeyStrokes</a> provide her full keyboard access and word prediction. Using Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Flash, QuarkXpress and other print and web design software running on an Apple PowerMac G5 Quad she does design work for local, national and international companies. To communicate she uses AssistiveWare's <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/proloquo.php">Proloquo</a> software. Talent and technology have allowed her to make her dreams come true. Read more about Leigh-Anne's story in <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/newsletter.php">AssistiveWare Newsletter #2</a>. Leigh-Anne lives in Jacksonville, Florida, United States of America.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2007 12:44:18 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/FrontiersOfAssistiveTechnology6.m4v" length="31231886" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">we-can-because-we-think-we-can</guid>
            <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Leigh-Anne Tompkins was born with cerebral palsy. This did not stop her from making her dreams come true. She graduated magna cum laude in Fine Arts and now has her own company: Graphics Afoot Studio Design.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:duration>2:54</itunes:duration>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Me and my computer</title>
            <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<b>Elina</b> was born with athetoid cerebral palsy. About a year ago, when she was 9 years old, she got a computer and in this 4 minute video she demonstrates how it has revolutionized her life. The computer has given her independence as she can now draw and write by herself. She accesses her Apple iBook with an adapted joystick and uses AssistiveWare's <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/keystrokes.php">KeyStrokes</a> on-screen keyboard with word prediction for writing. She is also experimenting with <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/proloquo.php">Proloquo</a> and the <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/infovox_ivox.php">Infovox iVox</a> voices for speech feedback while she types. At home and at school her computer means life to her! Elina lives in California, United States of America.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2007 09:48:56 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/FrontiersOfAssistiveTechnology5.m4v" length="50350841" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">me-and-my-computer</guid>
            <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Elina was born with athetoid cerebral palsy. She is now 10 years old and her computer means life to her. Thanks to her computer she can write independently, correspond through email with her friends and express herself in school papers.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:duration>4:14</itunes:duration>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>One Thumb to Rule Them All</title>
            <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<b>Mike Phillips</b> is a gamer and freelance technology writer born with spinal muscular atrophy (SMA). In this 3.5 minute video, he explores the frontiers of accessibility, playing games such as <a href="http://www.insidemacgames.com/reviews/view.php?ID=541">World of Warcraft</a> and Unreal Tournament 2004 with just his thumb, a proximity switch, Origin Instrument's <a href="http://www.orin.com/access/swifty/">Swifty</a>&trade; switch interface and AssistiveWare's <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/switchaccess.php">SwitchXS</a><sup>&reg;</sup> software. Mike not only uses his Mac to play games, he also writes game reviews for <a href="http://www.insidemacgames.com/">Inside Mac Games</a>, presents at conferences, wrote chapters for several books, works on a novel and is active as a photographer and digital artist. <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/michael.php">Mike Phillips</a> lives in Tampa, FL, United States of America.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2007 10:44:20 +0200</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/FrontiersOfAssistiveTechnology4.m4v" length="40568547" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">one-thumb-to-rule-them-all</guid>
            <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Mike Phillips is a gamer and freelance technology writer born with spinal muscular atrophy (SMA). Using his thumb and a proximity switch to access his computer he is a prolific journalist and has contributed chapters to several books.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:duration>3:43</itunes:duration>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>It has made the world of difference</title>
            <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<b>Anne Robertson</b> became blind as a small child. She is now a professional French to English translator. In this short video, she shows how she uses <a href="http://www.apple.com/macosx/features/voiceover/">VoiceOver</a>, the latest Mac OS X screen reader from Apple, in combination with naturally sounding French and British English text-to-speech voices of Acapela Group's <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/infovox_ivox.php">Infovox iVox</a> to do her work. She explains how thanks to AssistiveWare's <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/visiovoice.php">VisioVoice</a>, which includes a French translation of VoiceOver, she has been able to speed up her translation work as she can now listen to text in one language while she is typing in another language. Anne Robertson lives in Orry la Ville, France.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2007 13:49:21 +0100</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/FrontiersOfAssistiveTechnology3.m4v" length="30942287" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">it-has-made-the-world-of-difference</guid>
            <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Anne Robertson became blind as a small child. She is now a professional French to English translator using the latest Mac OS X screen reader in combination with naturally sounding French and British English text-to-speech voices.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:duration>2:43</itunes:duration>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Everything I can't do in the real world I can do with my Mac</title>
            <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<b>Joe Barnick</b> was born with spinal muscular atrophy. In this 3.5 minute video he shows how, with an adapted trackball and AssistiveWare's <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/keystrokes.php">KeyStrokes</a> on-screen keyboard, he is able to do all those things with his computer that he cannot do in the real world. He explains how he uses his computer to design and edit the <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com/newsletter.php">AssistiveWare Newsletter</a> with Adobe InDesign, write college papers in Word, chat with family and friends with iChat, and buys exotic ingredients and Japanese anime figures on the internet. Joe Barnick lives in Charlton, NY, United States of America.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2006 11:45:59 +0100</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/FrontiersOfAssistiveTechnology2.m4v" length="37526299" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">everything-i-cant-do-in-the-real-world-i-can-do-w</guid>
            <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Joe Barnick was born with spinal muscular atrophy and cannot use a keyboard or mouse, yet thanks to assistive technology he can use his computer to do all those things he cannot do in real life.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:duration>3:24</itunes:duration>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>A Pivotal Role in the Household</title>
            <link>http://www.assistiveware.com/podcasts.php</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<b>Marie-France</b> has lost her voice and can only move a jaw muscle because of Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS), also known as Motor Neurone Disease (MND) or Lou Gherigs Disease. In this 4 minute video she shows how, with a single switch and <a href="http://www.assistiveware.com">AssistiveWare's</a> Proloquo, KeyStrokes and SwitchXS software, she accesses her Apple PowerBook computer and communicates with others. She explains how she continues to perform a pivotal role in the household by doing the shopping, managing the bank accounts and even designing her own <a href="http://www.als-testimony.org/">web site</a>. Marie-France lives in Paris, France.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2006 13:57:11 +0100</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://assistiveware.net/podcasts/frontiers/FrontiersOfAssistiveTechnology1.m4v" length="42718794" type="video/x-m4v"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">episode-1-a-pivotal-role-in-the-household</guid>
            <itunes:author>AssistiveWare</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Marie-France, has lost her voice and can only move a jaw muscle, but still plays a pivotal role in the household thanks to assistive technology.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:duration>3:55</itunes:duration>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>