<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>What is Judaism? A Conversation Between Rabbi Ismar Schorsch and Larry Josephson</title>
		<link>http://www.whatisajew.org</link>
		<description>
		Larry Josephson, a secular Jew who now wants to know more about the religion of his grandparents,
		asks Rabbi Ismar Schorsch, Chancellor of the Jewish Theological Seminary, to explain the meaning of the Jewish holidays. 
		These conversations along with their musical interludes are a free-flowing exploration 
		of the repertoire of Jewish festivals.  As such, they serve as an informal introduction to Judaism itself.  
		</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<copyright>Copyright 2005 The Radio Foundation, Inc.</copyright>
		<managingEditor>larryjo@radioart.org</managingEditor>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2005 08:25:53 GMT</pubDate>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2005 08:25:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<webMaster>graphicsmac@radioart.org</webMaster>
		<item>
			<title>Shabbat: Conserving the World</title>
			<link>http://www.whatisajew.org/</link>
			<description>
			Rabbi Ismar Schorsch, Chancellor of the Jewish Theological Seminary, talks with host Larry Josephson 
			about the Jewish Sabbath in celebration of Earth Day. Rabbi Schorsch esplains that the weekly observance 
			of Shabbat, a day without work, is a way of conserving the Earth's resources, and of renewing oneself. 
			Shabbat is a day of rest, reflection and prayer.
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 08:25:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure length="87031808" url="http://rf1.streamguys.net/content/Shabbat.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Passover: Why This Night?</title>
			<link>http://www.whatisajew.org/</link>
			<description>
			Larry Josephson, a secular Jew who now wants to know more about the religion of his grandparents,
			 asks Rabbi Ismar Schorsch, Chancellor of the Jewish Theological Seminary, to explain the meaning of Passover in a post-9/11 world. 
			Dr. Schorsch tells Larry the story of Passover - its history, rituals and foods, and the origins and structure of the Seder.
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 08:25:24 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure length="84095795" url="http://rf1.streamguys.net/content/passover06.m3u" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hanukkah: A Great Miracle Happened There</title>
			<link>http://www.whatisajew.org/</link>
			<description>
			A conversation between Rabbi Ismar Schorsch and Host Larry Josephson about the history, rituals and meaning of Hanukkah
			- and its importance in our time. Cantors David Lefkowitz and Elisheva Dienstfrey sing the music of Hanukkah.
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 03:00:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure length="84724941" url="http://rf1.streamguys.net/content/Hanukkah.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>High Holy Days: Remember Us Unto Life</title>
			<link>http://www.whatisajew.org/</link>
			<description>
			The Jewish High Holy Days are the most solemn time on the Jewish calendar. The ten-day period between Rosh 
			Hashanah (The Jewish New Year) and Yom Kippur (the Day of Atonement) are a period of renewal and reflection. Larry Josephson 
			talks with Rabbi Ismar Schorsch, Chancellor of the Jewish Theological Seminary, about the history, liturgy and customs of the 
			High Holy Days, and the value of these ancient rituals in the modern age. 
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 03:00:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure length="84829798" url="http://rf1.streamguys.net/content/HighHolyDays.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Purim</title>
			<link>http://www.whatisajew.org/</link>
			<description>
			Rabbi Ismar Schorsch talks with Larry Josephson about Purim, which celebrates the defeat of Haman's plot to destroy 
			the Jews during the reign of Ahasureus, king of Persia. The festival recalls an occasion when Jews were rescued from disaster.
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 03:00:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure length="86402662" url="http://rf1.streamguys.net/content/Purim.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Tish B'Av</title>
			<link>http://www.whatisajew.org/</link>
			<description>
			Larry Josephson talks with Rabbi Ismar Schorsch, Chancellor of the Jewish Theological Seminary, about Tish B'Av,
			 the ninth day of the month of Av. Tish B'Av is the saddest day on the Jewish calendar for it marks the destruction 
			 of the first and second Temples in Jerusalem. The destruction of the Second Temple in 70 CE, marked the end of the 
			 Jewish state and the beginning of the Diaspora where Jews were scattered throughout the known world.
			 </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 03:00:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure length="64277709" url="http://rf1.streamguys.net/content/Tishbav.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sukkot</title>
			<link>http://www.whatisajew.org/</link>
			<description>
			Larry Josephson talks with Rabbi Ismar Schorsch, Chancellor of the Jewish Theological Seminary, 
			about Sukkot, the festival of huts, how it evolved in Jewish history, how it's celebrated today, and its growing popularity.
			Rabbi Schorsch also discusses Sh'mini Atzeret and Simchat Torah, which come right after Sukkot on the Jewish calendar. 
			You will learn how a sukkah or hut is constructed to observe this holiday.
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 03:00:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure length="27053261" url="http://rf1.streamguys.net/content/Sukkot.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>S'Lihot - Part 1</title>
			<link>http://www.whatisajew.org/</link>
			<description></description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 03:00:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure length="81788928" url="http://rf1.streamguys.net/content/Slihot1.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>S'Lihot - Part 2</title>
			<link>http://www.whatisajew.org/</link>
			<description></description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 03:00:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure length="89443533" url="http://rf1.streamguys.net/content/Slihot2.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
