<?xml version="1.0"?> 
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/DTDs/Podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Aural Icebergs</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>Companion music cast to Intellectual Icebergs podcast</itunes:subtitle>
		<link>http://www.auralicebergs.org/index.html</link>
		<itunes:summary>Aural Icebergs is the musical companion podcast to Intellectual Icebergs (www.intellectualicebergs.org).  On this music cast, Tiffany plays the music from IntIce, without the interference of interview or spoken word tracks.  She also plays some other music she has found while searching for IntIce music, in this case songs that are inappropriate for IntIce because of vocals or non-derivative licensing.</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:image>
			<url>http://www.intellectualicebergs.org/aural/archives/rssear.jpg</url>
			<title>Aural Icebergs</title>
			<link>http://www.auralicebergs.org</link>
		</itunes:image>
		<description>Aural Icebergs is the musical companion podcast to Intellectual Icebergs (www.intellectualicebergs.org).  On this music cast, Tiffany plays the music from IntIce, without the interference of interview or spoken word tracks.  She also plays some other music she has found while searching for IntIce music, in this case songs that are inappropriate for IntIce because of vocals or non-derivative licensing.</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>2005, Tiffany Rapplean</copyright>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2005 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<webMaster>webmaster@auralicebergs.org</webMaster>
		<itunes:author>Ankh Infinity Productions</itunes:author>
		<itunes:owner>webmaster@auralicebergs.org</itunes:owner>
		<ttl>1</ttl>
		<itunes:category text="Music" />
		<itunes:link rel="image" type="video/jpeg" href="http://www.auralicebergs.org/aural/archives/rssear.jpg">Intellectual Icebergs</itunes:link>
		
		<item>
			<title>Aural Icebergs 11:  IntIce 11 and an Alternative Rock Set</title>
			<itunes:author>Tiffany Rapplean</itunes:author>			
			<description>For the first set today, I have the music we featured on the 2006 April Fool's day episode of Intellectual Icebergs:  All in a Night's Work by Steve Sinclair, Magnatune.com artist Shiva in Exile with Oriental Distortion, and Godspell by Single 7.
			Then I have an outstanding alternative rock set for you, featuring When Your Coming Home by Pralay, MD by the Peter Roy Project, and The One That Got Away by Id Guinness.</description>
			<pubDate>July 10, 2006</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>33:58</itunes:duration>			
			<enclosure url="http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/060708_AU_11.mp3" length="24457216" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Aural Icebergs 10:  IntIce 10 and the Long-Awaited Latin Set</title>
			<itunes:author>Tiffany Rapplean</itunes:author>			
			<description>Today I have an artist from Copenhagen, My Beloved, with After the Speechless Head, and more from Magnatune.com artist, Jami Sieber, with Undercurrent.  I finish the first set with Neon Macaw's Silver Cinema--all music we featured
			on the March 22, 2006 episode of Intellectual Icebergs.  For the second set, I'm playing a longer than usual set featuring Latin music.  I begin with Gregory Morris's acoustic guitar version of Bay Light Lullaby, followed by Havana Taxi by L.A. Carpool.
			Then I have Sinister Dexter's Morenita, followed by one of my favorite songs, Downtown La Paz, by Molasses.  Finally, I end this set near to where it began, with the entire Gregory Morris Group performing another version of Bay Light Lullaby.</description>
			<pubDate>April 11, 2006</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>49:53</itunes:duration>			
			<enclosure url="http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/060411_AU_10.mp3" length="35921920" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>	
		<item>
			<title>Aural Icebergs 9:  Frustration and Hope, and IntIce 9</title>
			<itunes:author>Tiffany Rapplean</itunes:author>			
			<description>Today I have the Italian artist Jontom, with Oceanica, and more Synthetic Movements: Sam Spade (None for the Better), and (Welcome) My Spirit Guide--all music we featured
			on the February 17, 2006 episode of Intellectual Icebergs.  Then, as we pass the third anniversary of the war in Iraq, I have three songs to reflect my mood of late:
			Anything at All by blind with rain, Bush, Bombs and Bin Laden by Green Man, and The Language of Light, by Magnatune.com artist iNTROSPEKT.</description>
			<pubDate>March 23, 2006</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>29:57</itunes:duration>			
			<enclosure url="http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/060322_AU_09.mp3" length="21567488" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>	
		<item>
			<title>Aural Icebergs 8:  Back to the Hard Sounds and IntIce 8</title>
			<itunes:author>Tiffany Rapplean</itunes:author>			
			<description>Today I have more Synthetic Movements, Spirits of the Spring (Japanese Folk Dance), More... by Mr. S, and Magnatune.com artist iNTROSPEKT with Knucklehead--all music we featured
			on the January 29, 2006 episode of Intellectual Icebergs.  Then it's back to some industrial and and metal, with Erasing the Lines by Broken Rain, Insekt/Angel by Brainclaw, and You Can't Hide From
			the Sky by Shadowjack.</description>
			<pubDate>February 25, 2006</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>33:05</itunes:duration>			
			<enclosure url="http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/060224_AU_08.mp3" length="23822336" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>	
		<item>
			<title>Aural Icebergs 7:  Femme Vox and IntIce 7</title>
			<itunes:author>Tiffany Rapplean</itunes:author>			
			<description>In this show I feature Electron Overflow and Pocket Orchestra NRG, both by Synthetic Movements, Flight of the Mongoose by Paul Vasey, and Last Flight (Heaven: Closed) by Mr. S--all music we featured
			on the January 1, 2006 episode of Intellectual Icebergs.  During the second set I feature songs with female vocals:  Universal Humans by Magnatune.com artist Version, disconnected by KSINE, and Goodbye by Mary Weldon.</description>
			<pubDate>January 4, 2006</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>45:54</itunes:duration>			
			<enclosure url="http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/060204_AU_07.mp3" length="33050624" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>	
		<item>
			<title>Aural Icebergs 6:  Final Show for 2005!</title>
			<itunes:author>Tiffany Rapplean</itunes:author>			
			<description>I play the music featured on the sixth episode of IntIce, December 7, 2005.  During the second part of the show I play Blue Hand's remix of Mr. S's Rainclouds of Thoughts, When You're Evil by Voltaire, and Waterfront Drive by Lord Wallace.</description>
			<pubDate>December 16, 2005</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>36:20</itunes:duration>			
			<enclosure url="http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/051216_AU_06.mp3" length="26171392" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>	
		<item>
			<title>Aural Icebergs 5:  Industrial, Electronic Reggae and Heavy Metal, oh my!</title>
			<itunes:author>Tiffany Rapplean</itunes:author>			
			<description>I play the music featured on the fifth episode of IntIce, November 15, 2005, followed by an interesting set featuring music by Patric Bakkenist, Dr. Kuch (an artist you can find on Magnatune), and Victor Olsson.</description>
			<pubDate>November 26, 2005</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>33:52</itunes:duration>			
			<enclosure url="http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/051126_AU_05.mp3" length="24393728" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>	
		<item>
			<title>Aural Icebergs 4:  Goth Indulgence</title>
			<itunes:author>Tiffany Rapplean</itunes:author>			
			<description>Tiffany plays the music featured on the fourth episode of IntIce, October 18, 2005, followed by a goth set featuring music by Blue Hand, Patric Bakkenist, and Self Delusion (an artist you can find on Magnatune)</description>
			<pubDate>November 06, 2005</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>30:04</itunes:duration>			
			<enclosure url="http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/051106_AU_04.mp3" length="21657600" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>			
		<item>
			<title>Aural Icebergs 3</title>
			<itunes:author>Tiffany Rapplean</itunes:author>			
			<description>Tiffany plays the music featured on the third episode of IntIce, September 18, 2005, followed by music from The Chillum Brothers, Curl, and beat&amp;path.</description>
			<pubDate>October 01, 2005</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>45:56</itunes:duration>			
			<enclosure url="http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/051001_AU_03.mp3" length="33081344" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>Aural Icebergs 2</title>
			<itunes:author>Tiffany Rapplean</itunes:author>				
			<description>Listen to the music featured on the second episode of IntIce, August 17, 2005, followed by music from Blue Hand, Green Man, and Joe Turley.</description>
			<pubDate>September 11, 2005</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>36:15</itunes:duration>			
			<enclosure url="http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/050911_AU_02.mp3" length="26103808" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Aural Icebergs 1</title>
			<itunes:author>Tiffany Rapplean</itunes:author>				
			<description>In this episode you can hear the music featured on the July 17, 2005 episode of IntIce, plus music from Cargo Cult, Komputadora, Mike Grebb, and Erica Cashman.</description>
			<pubDate>September 5, 2005</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>34:57</itunes:duration>		
			<enclosure url="http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/050905_AU_01_Final.mp3" length="25167872" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
		<images>
			<title>Aural Icebergs</title>
			<link>http://www.auralicebergs.org/index.html</link>
			<url>http://www.auralicebergs.org/archives/rssear.jpg</url>
			<width>88</width>
			<height>72</height>
		</images>
	</channel>
</rss>