<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>The Jersey Connect Show</title>
  <link>http://theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/jersey_connect.htm</link>
  <description>Hosted by Righteous Force and The Black M.O.B., we bring you the finest in New Jersey underground music on this monthly podcast.</description>
  <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 20:48:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  <generator>ListGarden Program 1.3.1</generator>
  <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
  <item>
   <title>March 2012 - The Original Crew</title>
   <description>Non-D is with us for another month and we're giving you more of that vibe when all 3 of us are in the studio.  Our guest this month is Producer, J-History.  He drops some beats on us and sits in with us for the whole show.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/March12Show.mp3" length="129398611" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 20:48:30 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>February 2012 - Our 6th Anniversary Show</title>
   <description>Really?  It's our 6th year already?  Damn!  Where does all the time go?  This month, we get a special visit from Jersey Connect host, Non-D.  He blows in from the windy city and talks to us about his latest project with Vic Royale.  We all catch up, celebrateand speak a bit on our Pioneer of the Month, Whitney Houston who died this month.&lt;br>&lt;br>Get comfortable and ready to kick back with us because this show is 5 hours long!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Feb12Show.mp3" length="313193952" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 19:50:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>January, 2012 - Just Music</title>
   <description>No talk whatsoever this month.  All music from beginning to end with DJ Cee Justice on the mix.&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Jan12Show.mp3" length="62539278" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 14:49:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>December 2011, Jersey Streets At Christmas</title>
   <description>In our last show of the year we don't do a whole lot of talking.  Just music to enjoy your holiday</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Dec11Show.mp3" length="131192072" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 20:20:11 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>November 2011 - Class Reunion - Open Mic Part 2</title>
   <description>The Teacher is back with us again this month.  Class is in session.  Be quiet, stop chewing that gum and listen up.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Nov11Show.mp3" length="130426629" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 20:04:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>October, 2011 - Class Reunion - Open Mic</title>
   <description>This month, we get a special visit from our teacher, Mr. Ash.  By now, you know how the intelltectual street talk cypher goes down.  Nothing particular, we just building and catching up with family.&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Oct11Show.mp3" length="127650632" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 20:06:48 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>September 2011 - On Simmer</title>
   <description>We're off this month but DJ Cee Justice leaves you with some goodies for your ears til we talk to you next month.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Sept11Show.mp3" length="77886843" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 23:06:24 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>August, 2011 - Rock Steady Wishlist</title>
   <description>Cee Justice tells us about the National Bodybuilding competition in Pittsburg he participated in this month.  We didn't get to attend the Rock Steady 34th Anniversary this year but we heard the turnout was great and the performances hot as usual. Since we didnt get to be there this year, DJ Cee Justice decided to hit you with a mix of what his dream line up of Rock Steady performances would be.  September is our vacation month, so we'll see you in October!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/August11Show.mp3" length="132037172" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2011 21:44:28 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>July 2011 - Fuel To The Fire</title>
   <description>It's a hot one this month with record breaking temperatures across the country and the Jersey Connect Show adding to the heat with hot music.  Cee justice puts together an inspirational mix for his oldest son CP who was incarcerated this month.  We talk about how things went down at the Bill Grant Bodybuilding and Figure Classic this year and the happenings at Shauno's new website, PolarCentric.com.  Keep your head up CP!&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/July11Show.mp3" length="145844854" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 20:49:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>June 2011 - The Summertime Opener</title>
   <description>This month we welcome the summer in with open arms.  We talk a little about the advertising campaign we recently completed fro Shabazz Fuit Cola's new energy drink, Shabazz Ultimate.  Cee Justice gives an update about the upcoming bodybuilding competitions he will be in.  He then hits the 1's and 2's to chef up a musical selection of some music we're feeling right now.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/June11Show.mp3" length="135811952" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 18:07:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>May, 2011 - The Ultimate</title>
   <description>Wahb Shabazz of  Shabazz Fruit Cola and  M.C. J-Crush sit in with us and we all go right into the intellectual street talk vibe.  DJ Cee Justice rocks out with an eclectic music selection for your summer kickoff.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/May11Show.mp3" length="142976522" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 22:02:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>April, 2011 - Playing What We're Feeling</title>
   <description>We got into this whole thing because we were tired of what is being offered as entertainment value these days.  So instead of complaining about it, we bring you Jersey Connect where we try to bring a different viewpoint on topics and what music we feel is hot.  This month,  Omar Spruell of Agape Love Productions and Jersey M.C. J-Crush hang out with us as we go in on some intellectual street talk on a number of items.  As usual, we're playing what we're feeling right now, so enjoy.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/April11Show.mp3" length="116102029" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 15:38:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>March, 2011 - The Art</title>
   <description>We just enjoy bringing you some music that hopefully uplifts your spirits in these trying times.  Artistic expression through whatever vehicle, has the power to help you reclaim your own happiness whether you create or enjoy someone elses creation.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/March11Show.mp3" length="103044445" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 23:08:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>February 2011 - 5 Years In!</title>
   <description>This month marks 5 years we've been doing the Jersey Connect Show.  Join us as we go into heavy celebration mode on our 5th anniversary.  We talk about the work it takes to keep the show authentic over the years and reminisce on guests and events that have occurred in the most recent couple of years.  We recap some of our favorite music we featured and give you a Pioneer of the Month mix strictly from the legends we've had on our show.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/February11Show.mp3" length="143542113" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2011 21:15:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>January 2011 - Better Late Than Never</title>
   <description>Yes we're putting the January show up in late February but there's been a lot going on and there was a lot of snow in January.  Okay, no more excuses.  You know we never leave you hanging for too long though.  Since we haven't touched base with you in the new year yet, we bring you some new music and talk about what 's been up.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Jan11Show.mp3" length="122874410" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:48:33 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>2010 Bonus Mix - DJ Cee Justice New Years Eve Party Part 2</title>
   <description>You thought it was over til the January show huh?  Not yet.  DJ Cee Justice was chillin' on New Years Eve and decided he was going to drop 2 house mixes before the year was out.  Now we're dropping them on you before the New Years celebration is over.  Happy New Year!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/DECEMBER_MIX_2010_PART_2.mp3" length="47911821" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 04:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>2010 Bonus Mix - DJ Cee Justice New Years Eve Party Part 1</title>
   <description>You thought it was over til the January show huh?  Not yet.  DJ Cee Justice was chillin' on New Years Eve and decided he was going to drop 2 house mixes before the year was out.  Now we're dropping them on you before the New Years celebration is over.  Happy New Year!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/DECEMBER_MIX_2010_PART_1.mp3" length="38175148" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 04:31:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>December 2010 - Holiday Nostalgia</title>
   <description>We wish everyone a Happy Holiday and and a prosperous joyful New Year.  We take you back in the day with Cee Justice's music selection and give you over 4 hours of quality soundtrack for whatever celebration or chilling you may be doing.  Merry Christmas and Happy New Year!  See you in 2011.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Dec10Show.MP3" length="167816299" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2010 17:18:16 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>November 2010 - Thankful</title>
   <description>Our guest this month is Fitness Professional and Event Planner,   Joyce Van Seters.  She talks with us about what she is doing for up and coming competitors that are lacking guidance on how to get started in competitive bodybuilding and fitness and what tips to success are.  We bring you some new music featuring The Lunch Break from their Reduced Lunch EP, KorElement, Skee da Substantial, Zodiac and Shauno all in the mix to enjoy with your holiday.  Happy Thanksgiving!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Nov10Show.mp3" length="82937330" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 19:55:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>October, 2010 - We're Back!!!</title>
   <description>Vacation is over.  It was nice while it lasted.  We're back in the lab and back to business.  We brought Non-D back from vacation with us and some new underground from around Jerz that we got blessed with while we were out.  New music from Espizito and La Union Del Barrio.  The Pioneer Artist of the Month is no other than The R.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Oct10Show.mp3" length="125025659" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 03:19:41 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>September, 2010 - R &amp; R</title>
   <description>You should know by now.  September is our month off but we never leave you completely hanging.  Enjoy this Cee Justice house mix and we'll get back to you in October.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Sept10Show.mp3" length="46163586" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 14:12:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>August 2010 - Rock Steady 33rd Anniversary</title>
   <description>We've been supporting the Rock Steady Anniversary every year since it was brought in by the Lincoln Park Music Festival and this year, we took the stage.  Cee Justice and Shauno reflect on the event as they play music from all of the artists that came out and represented at Newark's best yearly event.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/August10Show.mp3" length="101387741" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 14:34:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>July, 2010 - A Labor of Agape Love</title>
   <description>This month, we delve into the world of filmmaking with up and coming Screenwriter/Director,  Omar Spruell from  Agape Love Productions.  We talk about the projects he's done so far, new ones he working on, the American Black Film Festival that just went down in Miami and what it takes to sharpen your skills as a filmmaker. Non-D is Jersey side this month and picks up right where he left off.  As expected, we bring you some of the finest NJ underground for your summertime enjoyment.  It's blazing out here this month and the show is no different.  This month's pioneer artist is none other than Naughty By Nature.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/July10Show.mp3" length="102400296" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 18:26:22 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>June, 2010 - From NJ to AZ</title>
   <description>Shauno takes the show on the road out to Phoenix Arizona (during the show me your papers fiasco)  to visit longtime friend to the show,  The Zodiac.  They catch up on what he has been up to since 2006 when he was last on the show, discussing the re-launch of  Redline Designs and his weekly rant songs.  We also feature new music from 360 and NTelek.  Cee Justice hits you with a master mix the Pioneer Artist of the Month, KRS One.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/June10Show.mp3" length="96010714" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 23:06:12 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>May, 2010 - Inspired</title>
   <description>It's all about inspiration this month.    Wahab Shabazz of    Shabazz Fruit Cola shares the inspirational story of how his father, Frankie Shabazz started an independent soft drink company in the 60's that still thrives to this day.  We pay tribute to Guru whose music has inspired us all.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/May10Show.mp3" length="120682313" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 02:54:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>April, 2010 - Ether Utopia</title>
   <description>It's our 50th show and this month we sit with the brother who helped bring the Jersey Connect thing together in it's early stages.    IAM Riley aka Breeze talks about his book    Ether Utopia and discusses the inspiration behind it.  Cee drops a mix including some fire from the Ether Utopia soundtrack and we hit you up with our Old School Artist of the Month mix, PE!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/April10Show.mp3" length="104148401" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 02:50:56 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>March, 2010, For The Queens</title>
   <description>Not the borough, the Sistas.  March is Women's History Month, so whereas we would normally offer up a selection of female artists, we felt it would be a nice twist to do a mix of Men paying respect to Women.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/March10Show.mp3" length="71542410" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 02:08:34 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>February, 2010 - Celebrate Life</title>
   <description>We've been here for 4 years now, in support of good music and providing an alternative to trash radio rotation.  On our 48th show, we celebrate by playing some music from our previous guests over the years.  Our musical guests John Taglieri, Courtney Bryan, The Zodiac, Skee The Substantial, Tame One, NTelek, Minister Wes, El Da Sensai, Grandmaster Mele Mel, Commander Jesse &amp;amp; Loc Mass are all featured in that order.  Cee Justice reveals a funny find, the BS Button, which may make an appearance on the show from time to time.  We also celebrate the life of Apache who passed away last month.  Apache's music set trends, sparked the party, caused controversy and is a part of the rich culture of music in New Jersey.  We also give you an exclusive, unreleased, in-studio session with Apache &amp;amp; Lakim Shabazz from the Cee Justice vaults. Thanks to everyone supporting the show over the years.  We see you!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/February10Show.mp3" length="94939786" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2010 21:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>January 2010 - Free Thought</title>
   <description>Another year, a new decade and the Jersey Connect is still on the move!  Cee Justice and Shauno have a building session and give you some inspirational new music to start off your new year.  We are also introducing a new, monthly segment called the Old School Artist of the Month.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/January10Show.mp3" length="109600181" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 19:09:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>December, 2009 - The Holiday Party</title>
   <description>It's that time of year again...Time for the Jersey Connect to close out the year big.  This year, our gift to all of you is a 3 hour, that's right, 3 hour show!  Now we don't hit you with all talk,  Cee Justice  puts in overtime with R&amp;amp;B, House and Old School Hip Hop mixes in this holiday party we're throwing for the world.  Check the attitude and coats at the door, hit up the bar, come to the dance floor and party with us.  Happy Holidays!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Dec09Show.mp3" length="129936471" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 05:10:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>November 2009 - I'm Soooo Jersey!!!!</title>
   <description>Tame One and Mel-Ski come and wild out with the Connect crew in this funny ass episode.  Tame talks about his latest projects and Mel-Ski reminisces with us about some of his inspirations that led him to Hip Hop while growing up.  We feature music by Tame One, Slow Suicide Stimulus and Dusted Dons.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Nov09Show.mp3" length="59609237" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 18:09:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>October, 2009 - Strong Arms Of The Law</title>
   <description>This month,  Paul &amp;amp; Mike from Speed Weight Training sit in with us and explain the No Rest workout concept.  Paul tells us how his experience working in law enforcement inspired him to start this  weight training program.  We run some NJ underground Hip Hop as we go into the Fall season full throttle!  R.I.P. Mr. Magic, Sir Juice!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Oct09Show.mp3" length="40506830" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2009 17:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>September, 2009- We Out!</title>
   <description>September is our month off.  We leave you with some goods from the stash anyway though as we play a Ladies Of NJ mix crafted by DJ Cee Justice....Enjoy!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Sept09Show.mp3" length="61252377" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2009 16:19:10 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>August, 2009 - The Connect Family</title>
   <description>Non-D comes from the windy city back to NJ for a visit this month and Vagabond sits in too.  We wig out a little, reminisce and hit you with some Jersey R&amp;amp;B and Hip Hop.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/August09Show.mp3" length="40192000" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 17:06:47 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>July, 2009 - Summertime In Dirty Jersey</title>
   <description>We talk about corruption in Dirty Jerz poli-tricks after 44 people were taken down in a corruption sting including Mayors, Councilmen, Assemblymen and Rabbis.  We put you down with some underground NJ Hip Hop we're feeling right now.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/July09Show.mp3" length="40141597" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 01:27:45 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>June, 2009 - This One's For MJ</title>
   <description>This month, we celebrate the life and legacy of music by the King of Pop, Michael Jackson.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/June09Show.mp3" length="69577238" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 02:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>May, 2009 - What's Not Good Right Now?</title>
   <description>If you're familiar with the WhatsNotGood page, you know it often goes from positive to negative, funny to tragic, finding the funny in the tragic.  We're just hangin' out with That Nigga Jhamal and gettin' some of that shit off our chest this month.  No particular topic and some music we're feelin'.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/May09Show.mp3" length="50455287" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 02:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>April, 2009 - NJ Music History, Lesson 2</title>
   <description>New Jersey has a rich legacy of music in it's history.  It's like you can hear all of the sounds from the shores to the urban streets, up the mountains, into the burbs and feel the all those vibes through its music.  In part 2, we bring you up to the 70's and 80's with more artists hailing from the Garden State.  Get your soul, funk and club on!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/April09Show.mp3" length="42785962" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 23:43:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>March, 2009 - NJ Music History, Lesson 1</title>
   <description>New Jersey has a rich legacy of music in it's history.  It's like you can hear all of the sounds from the shores to the urban streets, up the mountains, into the burbs and feel the all those vibes through its music. In the 1st of this 2 part mix special, we take you into big band, jazz, standards and rock from the 50's through the 60's.  The artists were either born in or spent most of their careers residing in Jersey.&lt;br>&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/March09Show.mp3" length="35423820" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 02:09:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>February, 2009 - Time Flies....</title>
   <description>It's been 3 years already?  Where does all the time go?  This month, we're showcasing the music of...well, Us! - Shauno, Non-D and Black Sun Allah (aka Cee Justice).  After these few years of representing for many different genres from under and above ground, it feels good to put ours on blast.  Enjoy and thanks for all of the love worldwide.&lt;br>&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/February09Show.mp3" length="57315150" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 02:02:13 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>January 2009 - Ice Cold</title>
   <description>Bringing in 2009 with some ice cold music including a Cee Justice house mix to get your motivation maxed out for the new year.  </description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/January09Show.mp3" length="106892688" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 04:25:16 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>December, 2008 - Holiday Throwback Groove</title>
   <description>What a gift we got for the holidays this year when Mr. Ash dropped in on us!  it's been since 2006 when the teacher last held class with us and it was a pleasure as always building with him.  The intellectual street talk covers a number of topics and we take you back with some late 70's and 80's grooves from the soul.  Merry Christmas and Happy New Year!&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Dec08Show.mp3" length="101321230" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 01:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>November, 2008 - Yes We Can and What We Need To Do Now!</title>
   <description>This month we discuss the historic Presidential election of Barack Obama.  Haaniy sits in with us a we discuss the monumental event and go beyond to the hard work ahead for everyone who really wants change.  We also speak through a selection of music in the vein of this inspirational show in a way only Jersey Connect can.&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Nov08Show.mp3" length="79946442" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 02:55:32 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>October, 2008 - We Still Break That New Sh#t!</title>
   <description>We're back from vacation and hit the ground running.  Skee Da Substantial sits in with us this month and we preview tracks from his new mixtape, Vol. 2.  We cover a lot of ground from month to month but don't forget we're still about breaking new music from Jersey so check out this feature on one of the artists we've worked closely with over the years.&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Oct08Show.MP3" length="53151078" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 23:29:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>September, 2008 - Jersey Vacation</title>
   <description>This We're out this month with the &quot;will return&quot; sign up on the door but we never leave you hangin'.  Listen to the best Cee Justice mixes of 2008.  We'll be back in October with more of that fire.&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Sept08Show.mp3" length="48912823" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>August, 2008 - Collabo Zone</title>
   <description>This month's show is a blend of NJ Hip Hop collaborations with 3 or more MC's on the track.  Cee, Shauno and Non-D help you close the summer out right.&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/August08Show.mp3" length="60474730" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 00:55:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>July, 2008 - Lakim Shabazz</title>
   <description>This month, the God, Lakim Shabazz visits the show and drops 2 new tracks for the heads that have been wondering where he's been.  He and Cee Justice reminisce on how they got started in the 5% Nation and Hip Hop, later combining the two.  DJ Cee Justice blends a mix of classic NJ flavor for your BBQ/JerseyShore/Summertime soundtrack.&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/July08Show.mp3" length="75709221" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 21:39:12 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>June, 2008 - The Story Of Flowtown Part 2</title>
   <description>In Part 2, we take you into old and new projects of the many artists that have worked with Flowtown over the years.  First, hear the conclusion to last month's cliffhanger (if you listened to the end of the May show).  The connections continued to spread out and we realized we had so much talent, it needed to be showcased....somewhere.  Why not here?  So here we are over 2 years into the Jersey Connect Show and we've branched our connections to new talent way beyond Flowtown but the original story had to be told.  What better way than through our own music?</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/June08Show.mp3" length="57298874" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 03:47:16 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>May, 2008 - The Story Of Flowtown Part 1</title>
   <description>We try to take you many different places each month on the Jersey Connect, with a focus on creative, feel good music no matter the genre.  We realized we were yet to do a show featuring our own, original music, compositions and production.  Pack up the cooler and ride out with us as we give you music from all of the many MC's and singers that made up the collective known as Flowtown which was the inspiration for the Jersey Street Mix Tapes and that was the inspiration for the Jersey Connect Show.  There were too many songs for a single show so  this month we will focus on the original Flowtown Volumes which by the way are available at the STORE.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/May08Show.mp3" length="69553984" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 02:12:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>April, 2008 - Ride With The Commander</title>
   <description>This month Commander Jesse joins us as we do a feature on his music past and present.  Him and Pachino ride out with us for the entire show and let us know about upcoming shows, the new single and video for Spankin' and what Rednammoc Entertainment has been up to.&lt;br>&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/April08Show.mp3" length="58200363" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 17:15:14 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>March, 2008 - Jersey MC Divas</title>
   <description>March is Women's History Month, so we figured we would focus on the Female fire spitters of NJ's Hip Hop scene.  Some exclusive Cee Just remixes of some classic Queen Latifah, Digga, Lauren, Heather B and more are in the mix.  Respect to all the Queen's across the globe!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/March08Show.mp3" length="58625010" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 16:52:52 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>February, 2008 - That Jersey Fire!</title>
   <description>On our 2nd year anniversary, we're back to Jersey underground music in a strong way.  Ronnie Castellano tells us how his Nutrition Zone stores provide sound health and fitness advice and also sheds some light on how he got his start in acting.  For the past 2 years we enjoy bringing new insights, backgrounds, intellectual street talk and fresh talent.  We are proud to continue doing so.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/February08Show.mp3" length="81041704" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 03:07:42 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>January, 2008 - The What's NOT Good Show</title>
   <description>We're combining our show with the sites' What's Not Good page this month.  Dat Nigga Jhamal who is one of the posters on the Y'all Beefs section sits in with us and we talk about various topics, recent news and as the WNG slogan says, we get that shit off our chest.  Featuring music that co-signs the discussion with tracks by Kwanzaa, Grandmaster Mele Mel and more.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/January08Show.mp3" length="39986201" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 21:14:48 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>December, 2007 - Grandmaster Mele Mel</title>
   <description>On a truly monumental show,  the legend,  the G.O.A.T., the originator, the Hall of Famer, the Gun Show, Grandmaster Mele Mel joins us and gives us some unexpected insight into Hip Hop's present and past.  We hit you with some music from his new album &quot;Muscles&quot; and give you a master mix of GrandMaster Flash &amp;amp; The Furious 5 &amp;amp; Mele Mel classics.  Celebrate the holidays with Jersey Connect as we close the year out BIG!  See you in 2008!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Dec07Show.mp3" length="70386153" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 05:42:18 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>November, 2007 - Juice Crew &amp; Flavor Unit DJ's Connect</title>
   <description>Cutmaster Cool V comes through and blesses us this month.  He drops some jewels for the listeners, lets us know about him and Biz Markie's latest projects and drops an exclusive mix on us.   He and DJ Cee Justice get scientific regarding the element of DJing and how the art form has evolved as we vibe out.  All that and of course we've still got to hit you with some new and  classic music!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Nov07Show.mp3" length="68154626" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2007 04:09:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>October, 2007 - Definition of a Mix Show </title>
   <description>We define for you the art that is mixing as we continue out journey into the DJ and the many different aspects of the trade.  This month is a show demonstrating the true meaning of the mix.  We also send a tribute up to the NJ club scene of the 80's and 90's.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Oct07Show.mp3" length="58857536" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2007 07:27:53 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>September, 2007 The Sabbatical - Jersey Streets Vol. 1</title>
   <description>This month Cee Justice, Shauno, Non-D and Chellz are on vacation, kicking back.  While they do that, they didn't leave you hangin' as Jersey Connect presents you with the original inspiration for our show....DJ Cee Justice - Jersey Street Mix Vol. 1.  Don't say we never gave you anything!&lt;br>&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Sept07Show.mp3" length="56730126" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2007 04:11:32 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>August 2007, Rock Steady 30th Anniversary, Lincoln Park Music Festival</title>
   <description>It's time for a legendary master mix!  DJ Cee Justice hits you with a mix of some of the legends we encountered at the Rock Steady 30th Anniversary.  Jersey Connect was on location interviewing our hip hop heroes including Melle Mel, Soul Sonic Force, Just-Ice, Awesome 2,  Dana Dane, Biz Markie, Cool V, Craig G, Marley Marl, Chubb Rock, Naughty by Nature, Lords of the Underground, Tony Touch, Crazy Legs and EPMD .  Do your history (Your-story)!!!!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/August07Show.mp3" length="47648938" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 14:17:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>July, 2007 - The Summertime Cooker</title>
   <description>New music by Bungee, Mustajab, Minister Wes &amp;amp; Commander Jesse.  Our guest this month is Loc Mass who talks to Cee Just about his new educational music project,  what's going on over at Real-HipHop.com and drops some exclusive music on us.  We're hitting the pavement out there.  We'll see you at Sports Fest and Lincoln Park.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/July07Show.mp3" length="36161121" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2007 12:49:54 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>June, 2007 - Health &amp; Fitness Exclusive</title>
   <description>This month is all about Health &amp;amp; Fitness.  Not just on a physical but also a mental and spiritual level.  We are honored to present you  the legend, Bill Grant as he shares his experiences and spreads a positive, tough love message to today's youth.  We also feature Health and Fitness inspired music to get you moving with your workout.&lt;br>&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/June07Show.mp3" length="42496627" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2007 16:57:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>May, 2007 - Jersey Rocks!!!</title>
   <description>Special guest, John Taglieri joins us to talk about his new CD, &quot;Wide Awake &amp;amp; Dreaming&quot;, touring and living your dreams.  We bring you some classics and feature new music from Bungee &amp;amp; Socratic. Rock on Jersey!!&lt;br>&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/May07Show.mp3" length="32577121" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2007 16:38:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>April 2007 - The Preservation of Hip Hop Culture</title>
   <description>This month, we hit you with some straight fire, New Jersey Hip Hop.  New joints from Jerz Ali, Shauno feat. Skee Da Substantial, Wise Intelligent and more.  Ntelek drops in to for a serious building session on the state of our culture.&lt;br>&lt;br></description>
   <enclosure url="http://theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/April07Show.mp3" length="31864997" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2007 02:48:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>March 2007, Queen's Month</title>
   <description>March is Women's History Month, so it's only right that we honor the Queen's of NJ in this month's show.  Special guest Pianist, Composer and Arranger, Courtney Bryan graces our ears with music from her release, Quest For Freedom, talks about her creative process and gives us some info on her upcoming gigs.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/March07Show.mp3" length="40684745" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2007 20:48:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>February 2007 - The 2006 Recap Show</title>
   <description>It's our 1 year anniversary!!!! Hear some of our favorite music from last year and get a run-down of all of our 2006 interviews.  If you didn't get a chance to catch every show last year (we still hope you do), we'll get you all caught up on this one.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/February07Show.mp3" length="53078638" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 15:07:40 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>January, 2007 - Producer's Pick</title>
   <description>We're hitting the ground running and 2007 as we bring you legendary producer, 45 King.  This month's show is dedicated to the producer featuring beats by 45 King, Cee Justice, MDominance, Shauno, Chris Northan and more NJ composers.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/JanuaryShow.mp3" length="58872093" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 15:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>December 2006 - The New Jersey Education System Pt. 2</title>
   <description>Happy Holidays!  Meet the newest member of our team, Red, The Jamaican Goddess.  We get into the 2nd part of our compelling interview with Mr. Ashley and discuss what went down in Jersey City.  We're ending 2006 with a bang, featuring more political/conscious music.  It's the season for giving, so we're giving you double the show...2 Hours!!!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/DecemberShow.mp3" length="57537852" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 15:03:22 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>November 2006 - The New Jersey Education System Pt. 1</title>
   <description>In this 2 part show, we step outside of the NJ box (music-wise) to bring you some serious music and serious talk.  Veteran of the NJ education system, Mr. Ashley speaks with us about what many educators are reluctant to come forward with.  We had so much material we had to break the show into 2 parts.  Part 2 coming next month!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/NovemberShow.mp3" length="47041016" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 15:00:27 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>October 2006 - Spiritual, The Born Show</title>
   <description>Minister Wes joins our 9th show to discuss music, balance and spirituality as we play some inspirational music and words.  Featuring music by The Zodiac, NTelek, Sage and Black Sun,  as we get ready to wind up (not down) to the end of our  first year.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/OctoberShow.mp3" length="44622163" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 14:57:08 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>September 2006 - The No Trick Mix Show</title>
   <description>How can we represent Jersey music without taking you into the club and house music zone?  DJ Cee Justice takes off the gloves and burns it up on the 1 and 2's for a straight up master mix.  We're taking you back to when DJ's used to actually mix.  Less talk, no special guests, no tricks!!!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/Sept%20Show.mp3" length="31648833" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 14:54:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>August 2006 - Hip Hop State Of Emergency</title>
   <description>Special guest, Dashawn Taylor from BET's Ultimate Hustler drops in to talk about the show, what he's been up to since , his book, From Poverty to Power Moves and his many other projects. Get your Hustle on!!!!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/August%20Show.mp3" length="40416990" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 14:50:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>July, 2006 - THE NJ SHUTDOWN!</title>
   <description>Special guest, El Da Sensei sits down with us  to tell us what's been up and lay some fire tracks on us from his new CD, The Unusual.  We're going for an hour and 1/2 this month.  There's a lot going on!</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/July%20Show.mp3" length="45888703" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 14:46:18 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>June 2006 -Summer Cookout Anthems</title>
   <description>Special guest this month, The Zodiac!  We sit down with him and discuss his new release, June XIII while we sizzle some grub on the BBQ.  Playing some of our favorite New Jersey cookout grooves.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/June%20Show.mp3" length="52291786" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 14:43:08 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>May 2006 - The Memorial Day Show</title>
   <description>Special guest in the spot, Commander Jesse.  Music from the NJ youngin's and as usual, there's something you didn't expect.  Time to light up the grill and get it poppin' for the season.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/May%20Show.mp3" length="51764068" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 14:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>April 2006</title>
   <description>We keep the New Jersey musical variety alive.  Featuring Gospel, Spoken Word and Reggaeton. Cee-Just, Shauno and Non-D continue to rep Garden State Music.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/April%20Show.MP3" length="73438483" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 14:35:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>March 2006 Show</title>
   <description>Featuring new R&amp;amp;B, Reggae and Hip Hop.  Joints from Commander Jesse, Vercity, 1st Brigade and an exclusive premier from Shauno's new CD.  Special guest in the studio,  Non-D.</description>
   <enclosure url="http://www.theblackmob.com/Jersey%20Connect%20Podcast/March%20Podcast.mp3" length="49670750" type="audio/mpeg" />
   <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 14:32:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
