<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>ATTAC Report This Week</title>
		<link>http://www.attacreport.com</link>
		<description>A weekly five-minute, Hasidic analysis of world news by Boruch Ellison.</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<copyright>Copyright 2006, Bryan J. Ellison</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 08:00:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<item>
			<title>A Deadly Anthrax Hoax</title>
			<description>Public Health officials are warning about possible bio-warfare attacks. They're stockpiling medicines and developing emergency plans, but the cure may be worse than the disease. After hearing this, you might be more leery of the doctors than the anthrax.</description>
			<category>Podcast</category>
			<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2006 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.attacreport.com/ar_audio/pod_06_0910.mp3" length="1501780" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cuba Re-invades Central America</title>
			<description>Back in the 1980s, the tiny nation of El Salvador almost perished in revolution. When the tide turned the other way, the Communists saved themselves with a "peace treaty." But now the terrorists are armed and preparing to strike again.</description>
			<category>Podcast</category>
			<pubDate>Sun, 3 Sep 2006 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.attacreport.com/ar_audio/pod_06_0903.mp3" length="1501780" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sabotaging the War on Drugs</title>
			<description>The wars on drugs and terror intersect in Colombia, where America's cocaine is made by some of the world's most violent revolutionaries. The Bush Administration is on top of the situation -- protecting the terrorists and undermining the fight against their drug cartel.</description>
			<category>Podcast</category>
			<pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2006 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.attacreport.com/ar_audio/pod_06_0813.mp3" length="1501780" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A Surprise Behind the Hezbollah Mask</title>
			<description>Terrorists found a way to launch missiles at Israel while getting paid with your tax dollars. They're using the "Hezbollah" flag as a diversion, but they're killing Arabs along with Jews, and their sponsors are some of Bush's closest foreign allies.</description>
			<category>Podcast</category>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2006 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.attacreport.com/ar_audio/pod_06_0730.mp3" length="1501780" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The CDC's Cancer-Vaccine Fraud</title>
			<description>The virus doesn't cause cervical cancer and the vaccine doesn't work. But public health activists aren't letting science get in the way of their political agenda. Deals are being made, the money's flowing -- and your daughter is the next target.</description>
			<category>Podcast</category>
			<pubDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2006 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.attacreport.com/ar_audio/pod_06_0709.mp3" length="1501780" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Vodka-Tequila: Soviet Agents in Mexican Gangs</title>
			<description>Mexico's drug cartels are developing a nasty new streak of hard-core violence. They've come under the control of foreign Communists, and now they're gunning for the middle class, police, and top officials. A time bomb is ticking south of the Rio Grande.</description>
			<category>Podcast</category>
			<pubDate>Sun, 2 Jul 2006 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.attacreport.com/ar_audio/pod_06_0702.mp3" length="1501780" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Approaching PLO Holocaust</title>
			<description>The world's leading terrorist organization has been torturing and murdering thousands of palestinians, often in front of their own children. Now the PLO's announcing a new war of genocide against the helpless Arabs, and time is running out to stop the slaughter.</description>
			<category>Podcast</category>
			<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2006 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.attacreport.com/ar_audio/pod_06_0625.mp3" length="1502955" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Phantom Behind Iraqi Terrorism</title>
			<description>Recently, U.S. forces killed the "Al Qaeda" leader in Iraq -- or did they? Was he a terror mastermind or an intermediary? A Muslim or a Communist? There's a lot more to the murderous Al-Zarqawi than meets the eye.</description>
			<category>Podcast</category>
			<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2006 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.attacreport.com/ar_audio/pod_06_0618.mp3" length="1502955" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Revolutionary Flames in Rio</title>
			<description>Terrorists have launched a massive offensive in Brazilian cities. Police are under attack by urban guerrillas while Cuban-trained saboteurs run the government. If the U.S. doesn't intervene, we could soon be facing a new "Cuba" in South America.</description>
			<category>Podcast</category>
			<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2006 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.attacreport.com/ar_audio/pod_06_0611.mp3" length="1502694" type="audio/mpeg" />
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>