<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?> 
  <rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
  <title>The Frazer Guinness Show</title> 
  <link>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/</link> 
  <description>One Man, a few good friends, cheap karaoke mics, inspired music and amusing chit-chat.This podcast quite frequently has all of these.</description> 
  <language>en-us</language> 
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2010 18:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2010 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
 
  <item>
  <title>Series One Episode One: 15/12/07 with Cam Reynolds</title> 
  <description>Frazer and Cam open proceedings by playing some lovely tracks and crapping on about Frazer's flashy new flat, why Cam hates Christmas, Heather Mills, Nicholas Cage and Dog the Bounty Hunter.</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/FirstPodcast.mp3" length="77739282" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/FirstPodcast.mp3</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2007 16:36:19 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series One Episode Two: 26/12/07 with Cam Reynolds and Sarah Coombes</title> 
  <description>Frazer Cam and Sarah have a Boxing Day natter about family disputes at Christmas, Scientology, sexy dwarves, being a teenage rebel, and some of the mistakes of the first podcast.</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast02.mp3" length="57239220" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast02.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 15:36:19 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series One Episode Three: 03/01/08 with Cam Fry and Alan Vagenberg Feldman</title> 
  <description>In his first 2008 podcast, Frazer ropes in his new flatmate Alan as well as his good mate, another Aussie called Cam, to chat about unfunny cartoons Fred Bassett and Andy Capp, teenage Jesus, Cam's taste in music, and favourite deficating positions. In good taste? You be the judge. Luckily they also play some great tunes. Also, on long-distance telephone from Bulgaria, vanguard of the road less travelled DickCherry chats to Frazer about misheard song lyrics and TV theme tunes. Apologies for the low sound quality/mic technique throughout. Sorry also for loading up old Episode 2 instead of this one initially. Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast03.mp3" length="59346570" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast03.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2008 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>Series One Episode Four: 15/01/08 with Cam Reynolds</title> 
  <description>In a brilliant whirlwind of a show, Frazer and regular running partner Cam R attempt to sound more professional whilst they blab on about going back to work, bad wedding DJs, the difference between PE lessons in England and Australia, swimming pools, and the long list of people they've insulted in the past 3 podcasts. Along the way, they play some truly outstanding music, including another segment from Frazer Guinness: the musical, some avant garde German kook music and a contentious Play Something We Know track. Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast04.mp3" length="57589888" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast04.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>Series One Episode Five: 02/02/08 with Cam Reynolds and Sarah Coombes</title> 
  <description>Its a funky laid-back affair for number 5 as the Dynamic Duo Frazer and Cam R are back after a couple weeks of procrastination, and are joined late on by Cam's "girlfriend" Sarah. Together, they play some ace funky tunes and speak of American product names, Sarah's Book Club and difficulty of being positive, plus more irrelivences. Your regular funky features are here, such as a borderline Ballard of Johnny Foreigner, plus one song that encompasses Kook Music, Play Something We Know and Frazer Guinness: The Musical in one fell swoop. As well as a funky new segment called Frazer's Five Minutes, where your host rants uncontrollably about whatever gets up his nose during the week. Send your funky Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast05.mp3" length="58107739" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast05.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2008 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>Series One Episode Six: 10/02/08 with Cam Fry</title> 
  <description>Kick back and relax while Frazer visits Campbell "positive" Fry and discusses living in London, why Trendy=bad, "Fletch Lives" the film, Art and Commerce, K-Tel records, Nostalgic Britain, Post-Yoghurt Syndrome, Foreign Music, Free Sex Colonies, and Frazer's problem with foot-in-mouth disease. They also play some cracking tunes, including a double serving of the Ballard of Johnny Foreigner, a Play Something We Know (Do remixes count?), a Kook music track that's also from "Frazer Guinness: the musical" with a saucy story. This one runs a bit overtime, but it's still great entertainment, ok! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast06.mp3" length="60791873" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast06.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>Series One Episode Seven: 13/02/08 with Cam Reynolds</title> 
  <description>It's a bling-tastic Urban Affair on the eve of Valentine's Day as Frazer and Cam R reflect upon some famous white rappers' styles, The introduction of a "request line", a re-explanation of the music segments on this show, Sonic Mosquitoes, and Rick James. This ground-breaking episode also features an off-the-cuff rendition of "Ice Ice Baby" by Fraz and Cam rising up to bite the hand that feeds him as he metamorphosises into an offensive ego-driven Monster. Enjoy! (Apologies for annoying audio buzz in the first 30 mins, baby needs a new soundcard!) Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast07.mp3" length="57602008" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast07.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series One Episode Eight: 01/03/08 with Cam Fry</title> 
  <description>Back from the brink of a cold and Flu epidemic sweeping London Towne, Frazer journeys back to the West London abode of Cam Fry to play some 80's classics, a Sci-Fi Kook Music, a double shot of Play Something We Know, one of which is the show's first ever request, and a cheerful Ballard of Johnny Foreigner. Don't worry, they still find time to witter on about Watershed musical moments, the 80s vibe in elcectronics stores, being a DJ, the internet's effect on the the music industry, rubbish futuristic concepts, Scottish dancing, Merseybeat and moments of reality in novels. Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast08.mp3" length="57600754" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast08.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2008 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series One Episode Nine: 12/03/08 with Dave Richardson - TAKE TWO!WITH SOUND!</title> 
  <description>Yet another Aussie co-host Dave R pops his PodCherry and joins Frazer for some choice choons and chucklesome chat. This week, subjects dicussed include Wikipedia and public break-ups, Frazer and Dave's previous lives as local Rock-Gods, star signs in music, and bitchy comments about celebrities looks. Betwixt the mirth, you can listen to another Play Something We Know request, an OzRock episode from Frazer Guinness: The Musical, another Spanish language Ballard of Johnny Foreigner, and a smooth spiritual 70s Kook Music masterpiece. Gercha! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast09.mp3" length="57600754" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast09.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series One Episode Ten: 17/03/08 with Cam Reynolds</title> 
  <description>A travel-weary Cam R returns to the yellow mic as he regales Frazer with sparkling tales from The North. The old friends touch upon St Patrick and his day, unpaid holidays, the age-old comparison of Vegemite and Marmite, Frazer's dubious musical selection for the evening, Cam as a high-school musician, The Bryans of the houses of Adams and Ferry, the definition of a vest, and a preview of Cam's new Cooking Show "Ditch Dwelling". If that isn't enough for you, stay tuned for some music, including our now-regular Play Something We Know REQUEST, some 80's Kook Music, an African Ballard of Johnny Foreigner, and a song from a future episode of Frazer Guinness: The Musical. Hush now, no questions, just listen..Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast10.mp3" length="56773195" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast10.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>Series One Episode Eleven: 23/03/08 with Cam Reynolds</title> 
  <description>Frazer and Cam R celebrate the dregs of Easter Sunday by playing  bumper selection of music, including an Italian Ballard of Johnny Foreigner, a Play Something We Know request of a Dolly Parton song, plus "The Streets"-esque Kook Music and a slightly kooky song from Frazer Guinness: The Musical. Between the choons, the lads acknowledge the huge amount of feedback they've been getting, and attempt to have a serious discussion about the US Presidental Race, as well as the usual frivolous discussions about silly futuristic concepts, talkng animals, Easter Egg chocolate, and Druids. Once again, Frazer betrays his ignorance by confusing the origins of the names of the days of the week and months of the year and by not understanding the word "bionic", and then goes off on one about people who forward spam mail in Frazer's Five Minutes. Also, for the first time we present Cam's News Report, and an excerpt from Frazer's first forays into broadcasting, aged 13. Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast11.mp3" length="5781421" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast11.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series One Episode Twelve: 05/04/08 with Dave Richardson and Billy Styles</title> 
  <description>A laidback offering for the final episode of the maiden series as Frazer is joined by a couple of mates, Dave and Billy. They chat about The resuls of England's most popular and brutal horse race - the Grand National - 80's TV shows, Frazer's holiday in the South West of England, Pregnant Men and Clones of a Man-Cow, a teenage Frazer's unhealthy obsession with the Top 40 singles charts, and answers to the last week's feedback. In between all that nonsense, the lads listen to Some choice Aussie Rock, funk, 50's pop, an 80's episode of Frazer Guinness: The Musical, A double serve of Play Something We Know, one being a request and the other doubling as another bit of moog-y Kook Music and one of the best TV show themes of the last 25 years. How do we get all that quality into one hour? Find out by downloading this episode for Free!  Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast12.mp3" length="57069946" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast12.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode One: 31/05/08 with Cameron Reynolds and Campbell Fry</title> 
  <description>Feeling fresh after a two-month hiatus, Frazer's back on the road again with a twin-Cam and a brand new intro to bring in Series Two with a bang. Together, the underground stars of the Podosphere offer up all kinds of ill-informed tosh bound together with an eclectic mix of quality music. This week, the old pals return to the curious subject of the pregnant man, Campbell has a rant about a London landmark, the lads debate music to listen to when you've got a headache and read out their favourite Fundamental Christian quotes and in a new regular segment, Frazer goes head to head with the unmistakable poetry of Danielle Steele. Tunes include another TV classic, this time from the 70s, a Tamil Ballard Of Johnny Foreigner that doubles as a piece of YouTube-inspired Kook Music, a Play Something we know from a Doors hit. Find out more by downloading this episode for Free!  Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast13.mp3" length="58625172" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast13.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 01:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode Two: 08/06/08 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>In a celebration of the long-awaited summertime, Frazer and Cam R slip down a gear with some laid-back tunes including another Spanish-language Ballard Of Johnny Foreigner, courtesy of Señor Coconut, a jivetastic double bill, including a truly Righteous piece of Kook Music, as well as poems from John Cooper Clarke, Danielle Steele and Steele-esque efforts from Frazer and Cam. There's more wacky Christian Quotes, Pregnant Man Watch, now with added facts, stupid football chants, and more. Dare you miss it? Just download this episode now for Free!  Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast14.mp3" length="58557463" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast14.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode Three: 18/06/08 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>Another slice of fun with your usual hosts providing the kind of startling insights and sparkling entertainment that you've come to expect. This week, in "Tha Mixa" are yet more loony fundamental Christian quotes, some feedback, Cam's fledgeling segment Cameron On Cameron, where he highlights something funny about the UK's leader of the Conservtive Party, and general chat, plus of course our most popular segment so far, The still un-named Danielle Steele/Frazer Guinness poetry battle. In amongst all that are the musical segments you've come to love, including a early 90s episode of Frazer Guinness: The Musical, another Ballard of Johnny Foreigner from Cape Verde, a Jamaican take on a famous movie theme for Play Something We Know and an 80s shocker for Kook Music; dig those wimpy keyboard sounds! Still wondering if you should bother? Pffff! Just download this episode now for Free!  Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast15.mp3" length="5959438" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast15.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2008 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode Four: 28/06/08 with Campbell Fry</title> 
  <description>Summer japes galore in Casa del Frazer, as the ol' pals chew on why Cam doesn't like Sundays or fancy culinary descriptions, summer holidays, Frazer's anxiety dreams, as well as 2008's cult success story, The still untitled poetry duel with Danielle Steele. This episode's music includes more old-sounding new music, Gary Numan and Neil Young, an Arabic Ballard Of Johnny Foreigner, a disco Kook Music track, a couple of summery tracks including Santana's take on a Zombies classic for the Play Something We Know segment. Just download this episode now for Free!  Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast16.mp3" length="58824539" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast16.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2008 13:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode Five: 05/07/08 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>On the eve of his birthday, Frazer and his trusty dork Cameron enjoy another glorious Saturday afternoon playing some summer hits, including newer stuff from Roisin Murphy and MGMT, another winning 80s TV theme tune from Frazer Guinness: The Musical, some extra-kooky Kook Music and a few laid back soul tunes to help you shift down and feel the sun's love! Conversation ranges from modern marketing methods to Cambodian weather, from football to fundamentalism, from Australian homesickness to some terrible crisp flavours, and that's not even including Frazer's unrunning duel with romantic poetry genius Danielle Steele What's not to love? Put a deckchair in the back yard, put some sunscreen on and download this episode now for Free!  Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast17.mp3" length="58991305" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast17.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode Six: 15/07/08 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>The usual duo spend possibly the last sunny day of summer in Cam R's flat talking about such heady topics as Frazer's embarrassing spelling and pronunciation, Gordon Brown meeting youths, the ex-pregnant man's newborn baby girl, Cam's religious beliefs, Guitar Hero  the game, Hollywood creativity and Illegal Immigrants, and Frazer tries out his new Fox FM style but still staying true to his ameteurish bumbling announcing approah, whilst we also listen to an a couple of recent tracks from MGMT and Mystery Jets, Cam's first selection for Kook Music (which of course is jazz but don't worry, it's funny), another saucy song from Frazer Guinness: The Musical, a moog plays The Doors song for Play Something We Know and a mellow summery Brazilian Ballad of Johnny Foreigner. What's up in the Attic? Find out when you download this episode now for Free!  Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast18.mp3" length="58969153" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast18.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 19:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode Seven: 25/07/08 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>Another balmy Friday night sees our regular duo Fraz and Cam R roll out yet more intellectually stimulating discourse whilst playing some of their favourite music. This week topics of discussion include Frazer's recollection of a time he went a little crazy, Provocative installation art, The beginning of Campbell Fry's cultural awakening in Hungary, and an amazing story involving Van Halen, a Psychologist from the Central Coast of NSW Australia, and homosexuality. Oh yes, and our stunning competition in which Frazer and Danielle Steele battle it out for the most awful romantic poetry outside of a teenager's diary. Selected music includes an authentic Rock N Roll classic for this weeks scene from Frazer Guinness: The Musical, a funky Ballad of Johnny Foriegner from Ghana, and Kook Music doubling as Play Something We Know which is an 80s soft rock rendering of a Led Zep classic. Also included are another Sounds Old Is New track, this time from Alphabeat, a Faces tune and an rocking old bit of grunge/metal from Soundgarden, segueing nicely into a cruisy trip hop number. Like it? You'll love it! If you don't believe us then download this episode now for Free! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast19.mp3" length="63201408" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast19.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2008 16:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode Eight: 03/08/08 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>Back in Frazer's N1 Bachelor pad on Saturday night after a party, Cam R and Fraz hit the mics running for yet another hour of chat and music that could be described as "rad", "outstanding" or "thoroughly entertaining" depending on who you talk to. Hot topics this week include 80's fashions today and fashion/motor shows, vocabulary "issues", another story about someone hiding in someone's house, Tennants Special Brew, Mr Men,  Musicals based on famous bands, and our very first competition with PRIZES!! Also, this episode's battle with Danielle Steele features a poem with a different feel. Accompanying music includes a twin-Tom attack in the form of a ribald razzle-dazzle number from Tom Jones and a bluesy episode of Frazer Guinness: The Musical from Tom Waits, also a bit of funk, hiphop, an old Donavan track reworked for Play Something We Know and some Kook Music in the form of a Ballad of Johnny Foriegner from Falco. Unless you don't like any of the above, there is very little reason not to download this episode now for Free! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast20.mp3" length="57594067" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast20.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode Nine: 10/08/08 with Campbell Fry</title> 
  <description>Back from a day trip to the seaside, Frazer and Campbell spend Sunday night rather lethar9ically shootin' the breeze about all manner of thin9s, includin9 beach culture around the world, unnecessary train announcements, juvenile 9amblin9, Campbell's confusion about our favourite subject the Pre9nant Man, actors becomin9 musicians and vice versa, the horror of The Krankies and the rest of The Best Of British Variety Tour 2008, as well as Danielle Steele and Frazer 9oing head to head for the most rubbish romantic poetry. Also, we play a few tracks, includin9 some metaphorock from The Tin9s Tin9s, a couple of sample-tastic 80s numbers, a French Ballad of Johnny Forie9ner, a re99ae version of a Led Zeppelin in Play Something We Know, and freestyle hilarity from Lou Reed in the Kook Music se9ment, so do what more and more people are doin9 every week*, and download this episode now for Free! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!

*Claim based on no factual evidence</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast21.mp3" length="59046893" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast21.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode Ten: 20/08/08 with Cameron Reynolds and Glen Mutel</title> 
  <description>In front of an initially lively studio audience of more than one person, Cam and Frazer are joined by local pal Glen to run the voodoo down about topics such as eccentric neighourhoood characters, comically bad CVs including the infamous Aleksey Vayner, Cam's connection to the late great Isaac Hayes, name anagrams, terrible lyrics and more, as well as the latest stage of the endless battle of dreadful poetry between Frazer and Ms Danielle Steele. Between all that guff they listen to a couple of 80s mod revival hits, an indie pop tune from last year from The Klaxons, Mike Reid's tribute to Isaac Hayes, a Ballad of Johnny Foriegner from Frazer Guinness: The Musical supplied by Mr. J. Lo, a cockney novelty classic for Kook Music and Grace Jones doing Iggy Pop for Play Something We Know. Defy workplace guidelines and download this episode now for Free! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!
</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast22.mp3" length="62302377" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast22.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 18:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode Eleven: 25/08/08 with Campbell Fry</title> 
  <description>In the extended penultimate episode of the second series, Cam F and Frazer G get down to brass tacks, picking apart a small sample of the best and the worst song lyrics in modern music. They also touch on topics such as countries Frazer has no desire to visit, National Anthems, Paul McCartney and British newspapers' dirty tricks. In addition, the boys read out some of your letters and Frazer takes on shite love poetry merchant Danielle Steele in what has finally become known as "In The Style Of Steele". As if that wasn't enough, the music selection this week includes a pumping 80s funk track courtesy of The Godfather Of Soul, a Bulgarian 60s Ballad of Johnny Foriegner, the full version of the Led Zeppelin track discussed in the previous episode, a Phil Spector-Tina Turner classic for Frazer Guinness: The Musical, some more kook music from Michael "Jazzy-Wazzy" Franks, and a cover of a Joni Mitchell protest song for Play Something We Know by a collection of some of the biggest Nu-Mutal gurus of the last 15 years. For lovers of quantity over quality, download this episode now for Free! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast23.mp3" length="70404934" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast23.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 20:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Two Episode Twelve: 31/08/08 with Kevin Murphy Jnr TAKE TWO!</title> 
  <description>If this episode makes it to public access before 20th September, it will be a miracle! Under much self-made pressure to get a podcast on the internet before his holiday starts, Frazer had to forgo the usual format and create almost a new type of show. Music components are as usual, but he takes on the speaking by himself with no one to hold his hand or laugh at his daft jokes. Furthermore, he attempts his first ever outside broadcast from the streets of the city of Liverpool. He muses about the make up of the Liverpool nightlife and stupid nightclub names, and chats to the hostel proprietor about music and his hostels reputation as the most romantic hostel in Liverpool. Hiphop from Japan and the Just Say No-era US represent The Ballad of Johnny Foreigner and Kook music respectively, Gary Numan and Queen mix with The Knife and The Streets, who give us the final episode of Frazer Guinness: The Musical for this series, Leonard Cohen gets a soulful makeover in Play Something We Know, and we get a glimpse of some local Scouse talent. All this AND In The Style Of Steele?! Don't even think about delaying, you don't know what we went through to get this online! download this episode now for Free! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast24a.mp3" length="57594067" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast24a.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 22:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Xmas Special 2008 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>FINALLY! Only 4 months late, here for your curiosity is the long-lost Xmas 08 special! Yes, the FULL version, sorry about the technical difficulties with the last attempt. Here's the original spiel:

So this is Xmas and what have we got? A long awaited podcast from the undisputed king of ametuerish delivery and half-baked musings, Frazer Guinness, together with long-time running partner Cam R. Why watch another Queen's Speech when you can digest the turkey while you listen to Frazer's choice of Xmas number one singles including a Play Something We Know/Kook Music combo that is almost unlistenable, and an accapella track that could also fall into both segment categories, a smoooth sexy song about adultery and betrayal, a couple of hits from the 50s and absolutely no X-Factor contestants - that's our guarentee! As well as this, the fellas offer up yet more info about the story that just keeps on giving, the Pregnant Man, as well as a new segment called Shouldn't Laugh, this time involving a pensioner and mud, and for perhaps the last time, a poem In The Style Of Steele. Just because Christmas day has long finished, doesn't mean the festivities have to end, so go ahead; download this episode now for Free! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast25XmasSpecial.mp3" length="69534325" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast25XmasSpecial.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 15:20:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Three Episode One: 02/05/09 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>It's the first cab off the rank as Frazer and Cam R crack open another series. As usual, the presentation of fine music is tempered by thought-provoking debate on subjects ranging from Listeners letters, Cam's band, travelodge band tours, getting a full-time job and having kids, nom de plumes, 80s films about fallen rock stars, the current whereabouts of one hit wonder Rockwell, Now That's What I Call Music albums, and albums of cover versions British/Irish accents on US TV, US accents in British musical productions, tastless mourning souveneirs and Australians in the VietNam war,to the latest installment of the new Shouldn't Laugh segment, this week about a drunken stunt gone wrong. Music includes a Mexican Ballad of Johnny Foreigner which is also semi-Kook Music, Play Something We Know from a Cold Chisel hit, another 80's scene from Frazer Guinness: The Musical which again has an element of Kook Music about it. The re-start you've wanted is now here; download this episode now for Free! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast26.mp3" length="69534325" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast26.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Three Episode Two: 10/05/09 with Campbell Fry and John Falls</title> 
  <description>In a slightly rambley 2nd episode, Frazer goes over to the "West Side", (aaight?) to hang with Campbell Fry and Johnny "Mic Technique" Falls. After settling in to the luxurious surrounds of John and Angela's hotel room, the three blather on about a whole bunch of subjects including the new-look website, Winston Churchill, Pink Floyd and more London history, Aussie and Kiwi music, apologies for all the mistakes in episode one, the songs of Cold Chisel, Gary Glitter, a Frazer's 5 Minutes about Twitter and Get It Off Your Text, Barrack Obama's dog, and a Shouldn't Laugh segment about wildly irresponsible parents. They also flirt with the "Not Funny Alert" to talk illegal downloading, Music consists of tunes from modern era artistes such as The Kooks and Radiohead, together with 80's Aussie electro-pop, a house cover of a Cat Stevens classic for Play Something we know and realistically Kook Music also, an Italian version of one of Britain's biggest hits for The Ballad of Johnny Foriegner, and a poetic song for Frazer's dad for Frazer Guinness: The Musical. If you want to learn more, download this episode now for Free! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast27.mp3" length="68660790" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast27.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2009 16:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Three Episode Three: 20/05/09 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>Warning listeners! This episode was recorded under the influence of "drugs": Frazer decides to podcast while tripping out from a strong dose of Chai Tea and is joined by Cam Reynolds moaning like a flipping female dog; talk is of a couple of Rock n Roll Myths, the phenomenon of groupies, fellow-Twitterhater Kanye West, Frazer and Cam's extreme plans to deal with modern society and Frazer's growing Francophilea. This episode of Shouldn't Laugh is about bad kids and the latest controversy surrounding Britain's youngest Dad,  and the guys walk the entertainment boundary discussing British newspapers. The playlist includes a John Lennon cover for Play Something We Know, An uplifitng tune from Sheffield for Frazer Guinness: The Musical, a French Ballad of Johnny Foreigner and a couple  of Aussie tracks, one of which is Kook Music on account of the silly voice, pretentious metaphor and ridiculous CD cover, as seen on the website. If you can handle adult concepts and wild spaced-out tea parties, feel FREE to download this episode now for FREE! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast28.mp3" length="61705114" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast28.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Three Episode Four: 05/06/09 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>World Environment Day has never felt so good as Frazer and Cam R kick back with a smooth summery songlist which includes a cricket-themed Kook Music, a song from the Newcastle NSW scene of Frazer Guinness: the Musical, another Catalan fusion track as The Ballad of Johnny Foreigner, and the archetypal Play Something We Know track from Scissor Sisters. The lads also discuss their inadequacies with woodwork at school, some of the world's less attractive islands, the underrated Stevie Wonder and his eye fixation, the new Star Trek and Robin Hood films, the US idea of British Culture, the decline of songwriting, David Carradine and Kung Fu, WGWs, Sting miming, Bristol and Liverpool, and Shouldn't Laugh this week concerns a gay school assembly, gay criminals, and more bad parents. You know you're curious so don't delay; download this episode now for FREE! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast29.mp3" length="66189398" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast29.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2009 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Three Episode Five: 22/06/09 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>This week Frazer and Cam R celebrate the Summer Solstice not by getting naked, droppin acid and rolling around in a muddy field, but by getting together and recording their musings about bad School musicals, Free Jazz Festivals, da Breakzz, Frazer's witnessing of a crime, Trisha, Cam and Frazer's previous lives as unemployed bohemian musicians, mad laser show/classical concerts, Bobby McFerrin, pathetic fashion statements involving 18th century hats, and a Shouldn't Laugh segment about the sad state of Public Transport in London. This chitty-chat was augmented by a few summery tunes, including another Spanish language Ballad of Johnny Foreigner, a piece of Kook Music that may very well break your brain, a Latin American re-imagining of a Jean Michel Jarre classic for Play Something We Know, a dreamlike Led Zeppelin acoustic song for Frazer Guinness: The Musical. Summer's here and the time is right for downloading this episode now for FREE! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast30.mp3" length="61746492" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast30.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 07:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Three Episode Six: 24/07/09 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>After a bit of an unplanned "Summer" Hiatus, it's a beat-tastic show from the dynamic duo of FG and Cam R. They chuckle through various topics such as lack of free-time in blossoming relationships, the UK's relationship with Europe, boat trips along the waterways of London, Frazer's recent birthday party and the variety of presents he got, helicopters, Whitechapel culture (innit), Cam's previous life as a Government-sponsored Hiphop producer for Whitechapel street kids, Winnie the Pooh's Hiphop group and Hollywood blockbusters, Australian musical treasure Augie March, Aussie Rules Football and Cam's fickle relationship with sport. Shouldn't Laugh this week concerns a costly bit of spring cleaning and also Frazer drops an exclusive bombshell about his immediate future. Among all these golden moments listeners can enjoy a few musical gems including a couple of Hiphop tracks from either end of the quality spectrum - the rubbish end being this episode's Kook Music, a Greek Ballad of Johnny Foreigner, an acoustic Play Something We Know, as well as a sultry track from the 80s and a moody number from Tom Waits. You may indulge in long-awaited fun with the boys by simply downloading this episode now for FREE! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast31.mp3" length="64212451" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast31.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2009 21:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Three Episode Seven: 14/08/09 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description>Frazer and Cam R record this episode on the fly as they present a podcast with a vague flying theme, in tribute to Frazer's recent flight in a helicopter, starting with the most obvious song in the world by Bloc Party, then a couple of tracks -one for Frazer Guinness: The Musical- that he had playing on his iPod as he took to the skies imagining that he was in a VietNam war flick, a surprisingly meaty Roxy Music song, a disco space tune for Kook Music and Play Something We Know, a Rumba numba for the Ballad of Johnny Foreigner. They also discuss all manner of topics, including Her Majesty the Queen and the man who would be her corgi, fascist Wagner and Cam's theory of the link between music and politics, the helicopter ride, the lack of punctualility of Jimi Hendrix, the film "Flashback of a fool", the TV show "The Fall and Rise of Reginald Perrin", Frazer's memories of summer in Madrid, and his ridiculously inconvenient trip to France with cheap luggage. and a Shouldn't Laugh story about a man with permanent hiccups. To be a fly on the wall, download this episode now for FREE! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast32.mp3" length="
69317404" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast32.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 23:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Three Episode Eight: 31/08/09 with Cameron Reynolds</title> 
  <description> It's time for the penultimate London episode, Frazer being joined once more by Cam R. They talk about introducing one's self, Frazer's overuse of the word "exactly", the new sound of cosmic disco, the history of the Notting Hill carnival, the unexpected appearance of genuinely nice people in London, Cam's ideal festival, Soundsystem DJs' propensity to talk too much, dodgy steroetypes and racial profiling, wedding music, Thom Yorke's family get-together, house interviews, sad music reviewers, a Darwin Award-flavoured Shouldn't Laugh, and an introduction to the up-coming one-off episode of The Cameron Reynolds Show. Amidst all that, they enjoy the new and old sounds of disco, Kasabian's new single, some still sadly relevant anti-war anger from A Perfect Circle, a 80's German Ballad of Johnny Foreigner, an unspeakably awful Temptations cover for Play Something We Know and Kook Music as well as another Top Of The Pops childhood memory for Frazer Guinness: The Musical. Want a piece of the action? Download this episode now for FREE! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast33.mp3" length="
65472598" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast33.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>The Cameron Reynolds Show: 03/09/09 with Frazer Guinness TAKE TWO</title> 
  <description>To commmemorate the end of an era, the Dynamic Duo swap roles just this once and present a 150% jumbo-sized episode featuring a Stephen Stills cover for Play Something We Know Download and a hiphop tribute to the man who was Ghost Dog, a Malian Ballad of Johnny Foreigner, calypso and latin percussion party tracks, a freaky Gene Vincent wannabe who is a few flickknives short of a street fight, a funky tune for Cameron Reynolds: The Musical, some Liberacheese and more themed goodbye music. The departing friends also run overtime discussing the film The Crying Game, the totally lame reality show Celebrity Love Island, Cam quizzes Frazer on his London life, the nature of the nomad's life, living in the present vs living for the future, Cam's formative years as a musician, Parliament vs Funkadelic, and there is a Shouldn't Laugh concerning an acting school and Barbara Windsor and German confusion with the neighbours over sterility and surrogate fathering. It's a lot more than usual, but it is also the closest you will get to a collectors item, so don't wait for the rush on eBay years from now, download this episode now for FREE! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast34b.mp3" length="
175307127" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/Podcast34b.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 18:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Four Episode One: 11/02/10 pseudo-live in Nantes, France</title> 
  <description>Up up and away with the long-awaited forth series! Slightly different format as there is only one host, not two. No matter though, it doesn't prevent interesting topics being raised, such as French words that sound like swearwords or nocturnal birds in English, a strange and dreadful trend in French interior decorating, the Yacht Rock rockumentary series, hiphop pioneers Hall and Oates, French TV, the changing status of the Punk movement, French bolshie-ness, national hero Serge Gainsbourg, national villain Nicolas Sarkozy and his misleading campaign propaganda, the perils of being unemployed, the 'rude' French stereotype, French pop music and TV, as well as the regular segments of Shouldn't Laugh and Listener Feedback. As well as that, there's great music, including 2x Play Something We Know, 2x Kook Music, 2x Ballad of Johnny Foreigner, a classic punk hit, a bit of Yacht Rock and of course a French chanson; OOOOhh, look at him now, he's Mr Frog lover! Download this totally owl episode now for FREE! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/PodcastFR01.mp3" length="
66047710" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/PodcastFR01.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 11:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Four Episode Two: 14/04/10 pseudo-live in Nantes, France</title> 
  <description>It's the holidays in Frazer's world and you're all invited as he takes a well-needed break from demonic French children's ridicule to present you with some formidable music, including a new single from Hot Chip, some Saba, more Yacht Rock, a Afro-American French War Heroine and all the usual segments, including the best version of Spanish Flea you'll ever hear for Kook Music. As well as that, there is Listener feedback, some refreshing moaning about the new job, a brief review of Hot Chip's latest single, a description of Nantes and an insight into why their driving is so bad, how you can turn a misheard lyric into a room clearer, a few tips for wannabe procrastinators, French rocker legend Johnny Halliday and a rubbish advertisement, painful ringtones, and closure to Bastardgate and an amusing Good Ol' Fashioned American Beastiality for Shouldn't Laugh. Yeeeee-Haaahh!Download this totally owl episode now for FREE! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/PodcastFR02.mp3" length="
58698315" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/PodcastFR02.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 09:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Four Episode Three: 10/05/10 pseudo-live in Nantes, France</title> 
  <description>Frazer's back at work, but had just enough time to "squeeze out a poddy" as Brucey might have said. This celebration-friendly episode features the latest hip* music from THE Hot Chip, LCD Sound System and MGMT, as well as a German ballad of Johnny Foriegner/Play Something We Know combo, more from the buskeresque Harry Arms, some Italo Disco and 70s Aussie hippysurf musique. Between all that, Frazer uses the excuse that he's just bought a new mobile to go off on one about technology for Frazer's Five Minutes, breaks every taboo in the western world by discussing zoophilia, including some lovely quotes for Shouldn't Barf, also mentioning the depressing side of British culture, the art of French whinging, and tips for buskers. Sounds like a downer, so why bother? To find out and laugh, download this totally owl episode now for FREE! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!

(*hip for anyone in their 30s, which sadly is no longer fashionable)</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/PodcastFR03.mp3" length="
57197842" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/PodcastFR03.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>Series Four Episode Four: 26/05/10 pseudo-live in Nantes, France</title> 
  <description>Here's podcast no. 4, standing by the gateway to a seemingly beautiful Euro summer. In this super topical, mildly tech-themed and guaranteed Harry Arms-free episode, our host talks exclusively to anyone who will listen about his backtracking stance towards social networking, presents a Frazer's 5 Minutes about identity privacy and a Shouldn't Laugh story about identify fraud. He also covers the World Cup, the recent British political compromise from hell, our addiction to TV dramas, French TV and the apparently ever-dwindling amount of listener interest and still finds time to play tracks from Bloc Party, John Frusciante, The Rolling Stones, Cassetteboy, The Farm, Anaïs and Tokyo Ska Paradise Orchestra. All usual segments included. Download this totally OWL! episode now for FREE! You want to see a grown man beg? Pleeeeeeaaaaaase anyone with any kind of Advice, Complaints or Praise, pretty please with a cherry on top contact the desperados at podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/PodcastFR04.mp3" length="
58494769" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/PodcastFR04.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Series Four Episode Five: 09/09/10 pseudo-live in Nantes, France</title> 
  <description>After overcoming significant technical hurdles for the last few months, finally the fifth in the French series of The Frazer Guinness Show can be heard across the world, brought to you from the newly-aquired Frazer Guinness House. The full gamut of features are on display here, including a Japanese disco track for The Ballad of Johnny Foreigner, Senor Coconut a return for Play Something We Know, Michael Franks' cringeworthy lyrics qualifying him for a spot on Kook Music and a track from Aussie 90s legends Skunkhour for Frazer Guinness: The Musical. There is ample listener Feedback as you'd imagine after a four-month break. No Shouldn't Laugh, but we have a new more high-brow feature called English Puzzle where the intricacies and beguiling mysteries of the English Language are discussed. Also mentioned are my new property, great advertising and terrible product names, music festivals, mental people and their mobile phones, the many positive elements of Nantes and of France. You've been waiting for so long, now you can download this totally owl episode now for FREE! Advice, Complaints or Praise to podcast@frazerguinness.com and spread the word!</description> 
  <enclosure  url="http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/PodcastFR05.mp3" length="
69937656" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <guid>http://www.frazerguinness.com/audio/PodcastFR05.mp3</guid> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2010 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <atom:link href="http://www.frazerguinness.com/OReillyPoderator.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /> 
  </channel>
  </rss>