<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	
	<channel>
		<title>Bob Garner Audio Podcast</title>
		<link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/</link>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>&#xA9; 2012. bobgarneraudio.com</copyright>
		<itunes:author>Bob Garner</itunes:author>		
		<itunes:summary>Personal Success expert Bob Garner provides life-changing information with his free motivational audio podcasts, inspirational podcasts and spiritual podcasts. Bob Garner's message is about helping you change the way you think and create magic in your life. Bob offers two types of free podcasts - motivational and spiritual. The free motivational podcasts provide usable ideas and principles to help you turn your dreams into reality. The focus of the free spiritual podcasts is to amplify your spiritual beliefs, not change them. With a master's in religious studies, Bob Garner is known for his ability to simplify oftentimes complex teachings of New Thought and Universal Law and combine them with the wisdom found in the Bible, the Tao Teh Ching, the Bhagavad Gita and other religious texts. Those looking for Religious Science podcasts, Unity church podcasts, and New Thought podcasts will also discover empowering material.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Personal Success expert Bob Garner provides life-changing information with his free motivational audio podcasts, inspirational podcasts and spiritual podcasts. Bob Garner's message is about helping you change the way you think and create magic in your life. Bob offers two types of free podcasts - motivational and spiritual. The free motivational podcasts provide usable ideas and principles to help you turn your dreams into reality. The focus of the free spiritual podcasts is to amplify your spiritual beliefs, not change them. With a master's in religious studies, Bob Garner is known for his ability to simplify oftentimes complex teachings of New Thought and Universal Law and combine them with the wisdom found in the Bible, the Tao Teh Ching, the Bhagavad Gita and other religious texts. Those looking for Religious Science podcasts, Unity church podcasts, and New Thought podcasts will also discover empowering material.</description>		
		<itunes:owner>		
			<itunes:name>Bob Garner</itunes:name>
			<itunes:email>bob@bobgarner.com</itunes:email>
		</itunes:owner>
		<itunes:image href="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/images/itunes_cover.jpg" />
		<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">
		</itunes:category>
		<webMaster>bob@bobgarneraudio.com (Bob Garner)</webMaster>
<image>
  <url>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/images/itunes_cover.jpg</url> 
  <title>Bob Garner Audio Podcast</title> 
  <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/</link>
  </image>
  

          <item>
            <title>: Why Am I So Angry?</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Do you know someone who thinks they are a nice and pleasant person, but is actually quick to anger? Are you that way? Learn about diminishing anger on this free motivational audio podcast.</description> 
            <itunes:keywords>diminishing anger, how to diminish anger, are you angry, why are you so angry, dealing with anger, free motivational podcast, free spiritual podcast, free motivational podcasts, free spiritual podcasts</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Anger-WhyAmISoAngry.mp3" length="21520" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Anger-WhyAmISoAngry.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Thu, 3 May 2012 09:30:00 PST</pubDate>
  </item>

          <item>
            <title>Examining Needs vs Wants</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Before you make your next purchase listen to this free spiritual and motivational podcast on needs vs wants. Do you really need that thing or do you just want it? </description> 
            <itunes:keywords>needs vs wants, examining needs vs wants, abundance podcasts, free motivational podcast, free spiritual podcast, free motivational podcasts, free spiritual podcasts</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/ExaminingNeedsvsWants.mp3" length="21520" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/ExaminingNeedsvsWants.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 09:20:15 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
          <item>
            <title>Overcoming Business Uncertainty and Fear</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>More millionaires were made during the "Great Depression" then any time in US history. It was worse then, but today's business "thinks" it's worse. What traits did those millionaires develop then that can help you now. Listen and find out on this free motivational audio podcast.</description> 
            <itunes:keywords>millionaires great depression, traits of millionaires, free motivational podcast, free spiritual podcast, free motivational podcasts, free spiritual podcasts</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/OvercomingBusinessUncertaintyandFear.mp3" length="179556" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/OvercomingBusinessUncertaintyandFear.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 09:57:22 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
          <item>
            <title>Give Me Flowers While I'm Alive</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Is it that hard to be kind? Why are some people so ignorant? Learn about being kind to others while that person is alive on this free motivational podcast.</description> 
            <itunes:keywords>kindness, being kind to others, why are people ignorant, why are people mean, free motivational podcast, free spiritual podcast, free motivational podcasts, free spiritual podcasts</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/GiveMeFlowersWhileImAlive.mp3" length="20098" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/GiveMeFlowersWhileImAlive.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 10:02:01 PST</pubDate>
  </item>    
          <item>
            <title>The Starfish - It Made a Difference to That One!</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Bob smacks those who don't currently give to charities upside the head. It's not what you did in the past. It's about what are you doing today to relieve the suffering of other people or animals. Bob shoots straight from the hip on this free spiritual audio podcast.</description> 
            <itunes:keywords>the starfish story, giving to others, charity podcast, free motivational podcast, free spiritual podcast, free motivational podcasts, free spiritual podcasts</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/TheStarfish-ItMadeaDifferencetoThatOne.mp3" length="236542" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/TheStarfish-ItMadeaDifferencetoThatOne.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 14:30:24 PST</pubDate>
  </item>         
          <item>
            <title>Communication - Arguing Over a Donkey and Its Shadow</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Aesop shares a story on communication via a donkey and its shadow on this free motivational audio podcast.</description> 
            <itunes:keywords>Aesop story, Aesop donkey and its shadow, Aesop the donkey story, improving communication story, free motivational podcast, free spiritual podcast, free motivational podcasts, free spiritual podcasts</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Communication-ArguingOveraDonkeyandItsShadow.mp3" length="236542" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Communication-ArguingOveraDonkeyandItsShadow.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 16:55:02 PST</pubDate>
  </item>       
          <item>
            <title>Finding a Hero in Your Mirror</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Ever wonder where all the heroes have gone? Can you still find a hero today? Find out on this free motivational podcast by Bob Garner.</description> 
            <itunes:keywords>finding a hero, where have the heroes gone, be a hero</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Finding_a_Hero_in_Your_Mirror.mp3" length="245521" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Finding_a_Hero_in_Your_Mirror.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Wed, 8 Jun 2011 12:05:44 PST</pubDate>
  </item>     
          <item>
            <title>The Cave of Emptiness and Its Treasure</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Are you willing to give up your old ways, enter the emptiness and find your treasure? Learn how to face the darkness on this free spiritual podcast from Bob Garner.</description> 
            <itunes:keywords>how to change your life, improve your relationships, fear of change, free motivational podcasts, story of the cave and its treasure, how to improve your life, get rid of your old ways, change your old ways</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/The_Cave_of_Emptiness_and_Its_Treasure.mp3" length="254272" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/The_Cave_of_Emptiness_and_Its_Treasure.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 8:32:05 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
          <item>
            <title>Goals - The Power of Detachment</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Discover the power of detaching yourself from your goals.</description> 
            <itunes:keywords>Goals, detaching from goals, achieving goals, how to achieve your goals</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Goals_The_Power_of_Detachment.mp3" length="254272" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Goals_The_Power_of_Detachment.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 15:21:10 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
          <item>
            <title>Negative Emotions - Mental Burdens Can Weigh You Down</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Mental burdens of fear, worry, stress and other negative emotions can weigh you down. On this free spiritual audio podcast, discover how you can lighten your load by overcoming negative emotions and achieve peace.</description> 
            <itunes:keywords>negative emotions, overcoming negative emotions, negative thinking, diminish fear and worry, stop negative feelings, stop negative thoughts, achieving peace, negative emotions stress, negative emotions quotes, free spiritual podcast, free spiritual podcasts, center for spiritual living podcast, science of mind podcasts, unity church podcasts, free new thought podcasts, religious science podcasts</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/SearchingforHappiness.mp3" length="425117" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/NegativeEmotions-MentalBurdensCanWeighYouDown.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 07:21:10 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
          <item>
            <title>Searching for Happiness</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Tired of searching for happiness? Try letting happiness be revealed to you in 3 steps featured on this free spiritual audio podcast and free new thought podcast. </description> 
            <itunes:keywords>searching for happiness, looking for happiness, happiness quotes, happiness is revealed, free spiritual podcast, free spiritual podcasts, center for spiritual living podcast, science of mind podcasts, unity church podcasts, free new thought podcasts, religious science podcasts</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/SearchingforHappiness.mp3" length="425117" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/SearchingforHappiness.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Tue, 4 Jan 2011 21:46:22 PST</pubDate>
  </item>    
          <item>
            <title>Negative Thought Patterns - Stopping the Negative Mental Movies</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Negative thought patterns can sometimes take the form of negative mental movies. Learn how to control and diminish the negative thinking patterns of mental images. Another free spiritual audio podcast from Bob Garner. </description> 
            <itunes:keywords>negative thought patterns, change negative thought patterns, break negative thought patterns, stop negative images, stopping negative images, stopping negative mental thought patterns, stop negative thinking, negative thinking quotes, free spiritual podcast, free spiritual podcasts, center for spiritual living podcast, science of mind podcasts, unity church podcasts, free new thought podcasts, religious science podcasts </itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/NegativeThoughtPatterns-NegativeMentalMovies.mp3" length="36114" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/NegativeThoughtPatterns-NegativeMentalMovies.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Wed, 1 Dec 2010 11:12:05 PST</pubDate>
  </item>    
          <item>
            <title>Co-Worker Resentment</title> 
            <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
            <description>Dealing with problem co-workers is a situation that we've all had to deal with at one time or another. On this free motivational audio podcast, learn a few steps to help you handle problem co-workers.</description> 
            <itunes:keywords>dealing with problem co-workers, co-worker problems, handling difficult coworkers, coworker resentment, co-worker conflict, coworker problem, problem co-worker quotes, free motivational podcasts, free motivational podcast, free motivational audio podcasts, free motivational audio podcast</itunes:keywords>
            <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Co-WorkerResentment.mp3" length="59477" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
            <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Co-WorkerResentment.mp3</guid>  
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 18:23:11 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
        <item>
          <title>Moody Co-Workers</title> 
          <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
          <description>Dealing with moody co-workers can be a challenge. Learn how to not play the moody co-worker game on this free motivational audio podcast.</description> 
          <itunes:keywords>how to deal with moody co-workers, dealing with moody people, how to work with moody coworkers, moody co-workers, moody workers, moody worker, moody employees, moody free motivational podcasts, free motivational podcast, free motivational audio podcasts, free motivational audio podcast</itunes:keywords>
          <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/MoodyCo-Workers.mp3" length="57879" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
          <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/MoodyCo-Workers.mp3</guid>  
          <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 08:11:59 PST</pubDate>
  </item>     
        <item>
          <title>Comparing Yourself to Others</title> 
          <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
          <description>Comparing yourself to others - on this free motivational audio podcast, discover why we compare ourselves to others and how you can stop doing it.</description> 
          <itunes:keywords>comparing yourself to others, compare yourself to others, stop comparing yourself to others, comparing yourself to others quotes, free motivational podcasts, free motivational podcast, free motivational audio podcasts, free motivational audio podcast</itunes:keywords>
          <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/ComparingYourselftoOthers.mp3" length="80214" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
          <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/ComparingYourselftoOthers.mp3</guid>  
          <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 12:46:42 PST</pubDate>
  </item>     
        <item>
          <title>What a Psychic Taught Me About Success</title> 
          <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
          <description>In 1978, Bob interviewed a professional psychic for a college course. What this professional psychic taught Bob about success not only added to Bob's life, but can add to yours, as well. Listen to lessons on achieving success from a psychic on this free spiritual audio podcast.</description> 
          <itunes:keywords>psychic taught success, psychic success stories, psychic success story, lesson on success from a psychic, achieve success, tips on achieving success, professional psychic success, professional psychics, success stories, success quotes, psychic quotes, free spiritual podcast, free spiritual podcasts, center for spiritual living podcast, science of mind podcasts, unity church podcasts, free new thought podcasts, religious science podcasts</itunes:keywords>
          <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/WhataPsychicTaughtMeAboutSuccess.mp3" length="80654" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
          <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/WhataPsychicTaughtMeAboutSuccess.mp3</guid>  
          <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2010 12:41:10 PST</pubDate>
  </item>     
        <item>
          <title>15 Ways to Kill Creativity and 4 Steps to Keep Your Ideas Alive</title> 
          <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
          <description>This free motivational podcast is about how you can keep your ideas alive and combat negativity about creativity. 15 steps to kill creativity and 4 steps to keep your ideas alive.</description> 
          <itunes:keywords>15 ways to kill creativity, negativity in the workplace, how to deal with negative people, creativity quotes, stop negative thinking, free motivational podcasts, free motivational podcast, free motivational audio podcasts, free motivational audio podcast</itunes:keywords>
          <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/15WaystoKillCreativityand4StepstoKeepYourIdeasAlive.mp3" length="06247" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
          <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/15WaystoKillCreativityand4StepstoKeepYourIdeasAlive.mp3</guid>  
          <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 14:12:50:04 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
        <item>
          <title>Living In The Present</title> 
          <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
          <description>In this free spiritual podcast, Bob Garner shares information on living in the present.</description> 
          <itunes:keywords>free spiritual podcasts, free spiritual audio, free religious science podcasts, free unity church podcasts, free united centers for spiritual living podcasts, free new thought podcasts, living in the present podcast, free spiritual podcast, free religious science podcast, free unity church podcast, free united centers for spiritual living podcast, free abundance podcasts, abundance podcast free, new thought free podcast</itunes:keywords>
          <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/LivingInthePresent.mp3" length="06247" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
          <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/LivingInthePresent.mp3</guid>  
          <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 06:10:25 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
        <item>
          <title>Is It That Hard To Return Calls Emails?</title>
          <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link>
          <description>Don't you hate it when someone doesn't return your call or email? Send this audio file throughout your company to help reinforce the importance of professional courtesy. Another free motivational podcast from Bob Garner Audio and Bob Garner Online.</description> 
          <itunes:keywords>Free motivational podcasts, free motivational audio, motivational podcasts free, professional courtesy podcasts, not returning calls podcasts, why do people not return calls emails, free motivational podcast, free motivational audio podcast</itunes:keywords>
          <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/IsItThatHardToReturnCallsEmails.mp3" length="11247" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
          <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/IsItThatHardToReturnCallsEmails.mp3</guid>  
          <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 10:03:14 PST</pubDate>
  </item> 
      <item>
        <title>Why Are You Worrying</title> 
        <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
        <description>People worry all the time, but you don't have too. Examine worry on this free motivational podcast by Bob Garner. Another free motivational audio podcast from Bob Garner Audio and Bob Garner Online.</description> 
        <itunes:keywords>Free motivational podcasts, free spiritual podcasts, free abundance podcasts, free motivational podcast, free religious science podcasts, free united centers for spiritual living podcasts, free unity church podcasts, free spiritual podcast, free new thought podcasts, new thought org, affiliated new thought network, free abundance podcast, free religious science podcast, free united center of spiritual living podcast, free unity church podcast, podcast on depression, podcast on failure, podcasts on worry, united centers for spiritual living</itunes:keywords>
        <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/WhyAreYouWorrying.mp3" length="15245" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
        <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/WhyAreYouWorrying.mp3</guid>  
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 08:45:22 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
    <item>
      <title>Needing Security</title> 
      <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
      <description>Many feel they need more security. Discover the meaning of security and how to realize it in this free spiritual podcast from Bob Garner. Another free spiritual audio podcast from Bob Garner Audio and Bob Garner Online.</description> 
      <itunes:keywords>Free motivational podcasts, free spiritual podcasts, free abundance podcasts, free motivational podcast, free religious science podcasts, free united centers for spiritual living podcasts, free unity church podcasts, free spiritual podcast, free new thought podcasts, new thought org, affiliated new thought network, free abundance podcast, free religious science podcast, free united center of spiritual living podcast, free unity church podcast, podcast on depression, podcast on failure, podcasts on worry, united centers for spiritual living</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/NeedingSecurity.mp3" length="12004" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
      <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/NeedingSecurity.mp3</guid>  
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 08:30:22 PST</pubDate>
  </item>     
    <item>
      <title>What If I Fail?</title> 
      <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
      <description>Failure. Have you ever asked yourself, "What if I fail?" If so, Bob Garner may help you answer that question on this free motivational podcast. Another free motivational audio podcast from Bob Garner Audio.</description> 
      <itunes:keywords>Free motivational podcasts, free spiritual podcasts, free abundance podcasts, free motivational podcast, free religious science podcasts, free united center of spiritual living podcasts, free unity church podcasts, free spiritual podcast, free new thought podcasts, free abundance podcast, free religious science podcast, free united center of spiritual living podcast, free unity church podcast, podcast on depression, podcast on failure, podcasts on worry</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/WhatIfIFail.mp3" length="13834" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
      <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/WhatIfIFail.mp3</guid>  
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 010:45:22 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
    <item>
      <title>Depression - Understand It</title> 
      <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
      <description>Feeling Depressed? Bob Garner shares information on why you need to understand your depression as opposed to trying to get rid of it. Another free spiritual podcast from Bob Garner Audio.</description> 
      <itunes:keywords>Free motivational podcasts, free spiritual podcasts, free abundance podcasts, free motivational podcast, free religious science podcasts, free united center of spiritual living podcasts, free unity church podcasts, free spiritual podcast, free new thought podcasts, free abundance podcast, free religious science podcast, free united center of spiritual living podcast, free unity church podcast, podcast on depression, podcast on failure, podcasts on worry</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/DepressionUnderstandIt.mp3" length="13834" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
      <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/DepressionUnderstandIt.mp3</guid>  
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 010:42:12 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Jason Deitch Interviews Bob Garner on Branding, Success, and Becoming an Expert</title> 
      <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
      <description>Dr. Jason Deitch, Chiropractor and creator of the Discover Wellness Center, interviews Bob. In approx. 60 minutes, Bob answers questions dealing with branding your identity, building a business, becoming an expert, and diminishing lack. Even though the intended audience is chiropractors and wellness center experts, all can learn from this fun and engaging program.</description> 
      <itunes:keywords>chiropractor success, branding identity, Jason deitch, become a chiropractor, wellness center podcasts, chiropractor podcasts, success podcasts, discover wellness center, dr. Jason</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Dr.JasonDeitchInterviewsBobGarner.mp3" length="12752" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
      <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Dr.JasonDeitchInterviewsBobGarner.mp3</guid>  
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 010:12:04 PST</pubDate>
  </item>    
    <item>
      <title>Recorded Live at United Center of Spiritual Living - "Where Your Mind Goes, Energy Flows" Part 2</title> 
      <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
      <description>The 2nd part of this audio program was recorded live at the Church of Religious Science, now known as the United Center for Spiritual Living. What you focus on is what you will create in your life and in this empowering program, Bob shares 3 thought-provoking steps to help you redirect your mind (and energy) toward peace and happiness.</description> 
      <itunes:keywords> Free Religious Science podcasts, free united center of spiritual living podcasts, free new thought podcasts, free unity church podcasts.</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/WhereYourMindGoesPart2.mp3" length="53234" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
      <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/WhereYourMindGoesPart2.mp3</guid>  
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 08:12:04 PST</pubDate>
  </item>     
    <item>
      <title>Recorded Live at United Center of Spiritual Living - "Where Your Mind Goes, Energy Flows" Part 1</title> 
      <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
      <description>This two part audio program was recorded live at the Church of Religious Science, now known as the United Center for Spiritual Living. What you focus on is what you will create in your life and in this empowering program, Bob shares 3 thought-provoking steps to help you redirect your mind (and energy) toward peace and happiness.</description> 
      <itunes:keywords> Free Religious Science podcasts, free united center of spiritual living podcasts, free new thought podcasts, free unity church podcasts.</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/WhereYourMindGoesPart1.mp3" length="54234" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
      <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/WhereYourMindGoesPart1.mp3</guid>  
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 00:12:04 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
  <item>
    <title>Healing Hard Times (Part 2)</title> 
    <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
    <description>In the 2nd part of this free spiritual audio podcast, Bob shares ideas on how you can heal your hard times and turn your pains into gains.</description> 
    <itunes:keywords>forgiveness, religious science podcasts, unity church podcasts, new thought podcasts, free spiritual podcasts, podcasts on forgiveness, free motivational audio, free motivational podcasts, attracting abundance</itunes:keywords>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Healing_Hard_Times_Part2.mp3" length="87234" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
    <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Healing_Hard_Times_Part2.mp3</guid>  
    <pubDate>Thurs, 13 Nov 2008 13:57:04 PST</pubDate>
  </item>    
  <item>
    <title>Simple Steps To Reduce Stress</title> 
    <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
    <description>In this free motivational audio podcast, Bob shares a simple step to help you reduce stress when dealing with future events of which you are fearful. The "Simple Steps To Reduce Stress" DVD will be available soon. To be notified and receive a special pre-publication discount, sign up for Bob's free monthly ezine.</description> 
    <itunes:keywords>stress, anger management, free motivational audio, free motivational podcasts, podcasts on stress, podcasts on anger management</itunes:keywords>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Simple_Steps_To_Reduce_Stress.mp3" length="62156" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
    <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Simple_Steps_To_Reduce_Stress.mp3</guid>  
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2008 14:45:04 PST</pubDate>
  </item>     
  <item>
    <title>Healing Hard Times (Part 1)</title> 
    <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
    <description>In this free spiritual audio podcast, Bob shares ideas on how you can heal your hard times and turn your pains into gains.</description> 
    <itunes:keywords>forgiveness, religious science podcasts, unity church podcasts, new thought podcasts, free spiritual podcasts, podcasts on forgiveness, free motivational audio, free motivational podcasts, attracting abundance</itunes:keywords>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Healing_Hard_Times_Part1.mp3" length="872156" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
    <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Healing_Hard_Times_Part1.mp3</guid>  
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 15:05:23 PST</pubDate>
  </item>   
  <item>
      <title>Image - People Judge You Like a Book</title> 
      <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
      <description>Image - People judge you like a book, by the cover. Learn how to change your thinking and create the image that will help you achieve your goals with this free motivational audio podcast by personal success expert Bob Garner.</description> 
      <itunes:keywords>stress, anger management, free motivational audio, free motivational podcasts, podcasts on stress, podcasts on anger management</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Image-People_Judge_You_Like_A_Book.mp3" length="526415" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
      <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Image-People_Judge_You_Like_A_Book.mp3</guid>  
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 14:40:32 PST</pubDate>
  </item>  
  <item>
      <title>The Universal Law of Flow</title> 
      <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
      <description>Bob Garner shares with you the powers of the Universal Law of Flow on this free spiritual audio podcast.</description> 
      <itunes:keywords>stress, anger management, free motivational audio, free motivational podcasts, podcasts on stress, podcasts on anger management</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Universal_Law_of_Flow.mp3" length="523244" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
      <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Universal_Law_of_Flow.mp3</guid>  
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 13:20:15 PST</pubDate>
  </item>
<item>
    <title>Leadership-If You Want To Become A Better Leader Oil Yourself</title> 
    <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
    <description>If you want to become a better leader, oil yourself. Bob Garner shares the importance of trust and leadership in this free motivational audio podcast.</description> 
    <itunes:keywords>stress, anger management, free motivational audio, free motivational podcasts, podcasts on stress, podcasts on anger management</itunes:keywords>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Leadership-If You_Want_To_Become_A_Better_Leader_Oil_Yourself.mp3" length="6530240" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
    <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Leadership-If You_Want_To_Become_A_Better_Leader_Oil_Yourself.mp3</guid>  
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 11:20:15 PST</pubDate>
  </item>
<item>
    <title>Finite Thinking - Getting Water From a Rock</title> 
    <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
    <description>Learn about turning impossible situations into viable possibilities by diminishing your finite thinking and following your inner spirit. Listen to this free spiritual audio podcast from Bob Garner.</description> 
    <itunes:keywords>forgiveness, religious science podcasts, unity church podcasts, new thought podcasts, free spiritual podcasts, podcasts on forgiveness</itunes:keywords>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Finite_Thinking-Getting_Water_From_a_Rock.mp3" length="5530210" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
    <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Finite_Thinking-Getting_Water_From_a_Rock.mp3</guid>  
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 11:00:02 PST</pubDate>
  </item>    
  <item>
    <title>Stress - How Important Is Your Lemonade Stand</title> 
    <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
    <description>Stress-How important is your lemonade stand or your "to do" list. Personal success expert Bob Garner helps you change the way you think about how you view  your "to do" list on this free motivational audio podcast.</description> 
    <itunes:keywords>stress, anger management, free motivational audio, free motivational podcasts, podcasts on stress, podcasts on anger management</itunes:keywords>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Stress-How_Important_Is_Your_Lemonade_Stand.mp3" length="6530240" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
    <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Stress-How_Important_Is_Your_Lemonade_Stand.mp3</guid>  
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 02:25:02 PST</pubDate>
  </item>
<item>
    <title>Forgiveness - Unlock Your Prison Door</title> 
    <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
    <description>Discover the power of forgiveness. Bob Garner shows you how to move forward in life through the healing power of forgiveness.</description> 
    <itunes:keywords>forgiveness, religious science podcasts, unity church podcasts, new thought podcasts, free spiritual podcasts, podcasts on forgiveness</itunes:keywords>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Forgiveness-Unlock_Your_Prison_Door.mp3" length="5530240" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
    <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Forgiveness-Unlock_Your_Prison_Door.mp3</guid>  
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 02:00:02 PST</pubDate>
  </item>    
<item>
  <title>Ideas - Don't Look Like Old Cheese, Old Beer, and Old Whiskey</title>
  <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link>
  <description>Motivational speaker Bob Garner shares information on welcoming new ideas into your mind.</description>
  <itunes:keywords>free motivational audio, free motivational podcasts, free inspirational podcasts</itunes:keywords>  
  <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Ideas_Dont_Look_Like_Old_Cheese_Old_Beer_and_Old_Whiskey.mp3" length="3352576" type="audio/mpeg"/>
  <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Ideas_Dont_Look_Like_Old_Cheese_Old_Beer_and_Old_Whiskey.mp3</guid>  
  </item>  
<item>
  <title>It's Not Brain Surgery - Don't Strive for Perfection</title> 
  <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
  <description>Motivational speaker Bob Garner helps you release the need for perfection and instead focus on excellence and progress.</description> 
  <itunes:keywords>free motivational audio, free motivational podcasts, free inspirational podcasts</itunes:keywords>
  <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Dont_Strive_for_Perfection.mp3" length="3278848" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
  <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Dont_Strive_for_Perfection.mp3</guid>  
  </item>
<item>
  <title>Problems - Are You the Master or Slave of Your Problems? </title> 
  <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link>
  <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/</guid>
  <description>Motivational speaker Bob Garner helps you take control of your problems and take back your power. </description> 
  <itunes:keywords>free motivational audio, free motivational podcasts, free inspirational podcasts</itunes:keywords>
  <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Are_You_the_Master_or_Slave_of_Your_Problem.mp3" length="2400256" type="audio/mpeg"/>
  <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Are_You_the_Master_or_Slave_of_Your_Problem.mp3</guid>
  </item>
<item>
  <title>Understanding the Universal Law of Cause and Effect</title> 
  <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
  <description>Bob Garner explains how the Universal Law of cause and effect shapes your life. Discover the power of this Universal Law and change your life. </description> 
  <itunes:keywords>religious science podcasts, unity church podcasts, new thought podcasts, new thought speakers, spiritual podcasts</itunes:keywords>
  <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Universal_Law_of_Cause_and_Effect.mp3" length="4869120" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
  <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Universal_Law_of_Cause_and_Effect.mp3</guid> 
  </item>
<item>
  <title>The Universal Law of Desire and Expectation </title> 
  <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
  <description>Bob Garner illuminates the Universal Law of Desire and Expectation and shows you how to use it in your life to attract abundance, health, and peace of mind. </description> 
  <itunes:keywords>religious science podcasts, unity church podcasts, new thought podcasts, new thought speakers, spiritual podcasts</itunes:keywords>
  <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Universal_Law_of_Desire_and_Expectation.mp3" length="5183488" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
  <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Universal_Law_of_Desire_and_Expectation.mp3</guid> 
  </item>
<item>
  <title>Bob Garner Live at Unity Church </title> 
  <link>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com</link> 
  <description>Listen to a live recording of Bob Garner as he delivers a sermon at Unity Church. </description> 
  <itunes:keywords>religious science podcasts, unity church podcasts, new thought podcasts, new thought speakers, spiritual podcasts</itunes:keywords>
  <enclosure url="http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Live_at_Unity_Church.mp3" length="6538240" type="audio/mpeg"/>  
  <guid>http://www.bobgarneraudio.com/audio/Bob_Garner_Live_at_Unity_Church.mp3</guid> 
  </item>
  </channel>
  </rss>