<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"
xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/DTDs/Podcast-1.0.dtd">
<channel>
  <itunes:category text="Technology" />
  <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
  <title>Radio Go Daddy Podcast</title>
  <itunes:subtitle>With your host, Bob Parsons</itunes:subtitle>
  <itunes:author>Radio Go Daddy</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:image href="http://www.bobparsons.me/templates/godaddy/img/bobsblog_rgdfeed_image.jpg" />
  <link>http://www.radiogodaddy.com/</link> 
  <description>Radio Go Daddywith Bob Parsons</description>
  <itunes:summary>
Radio Go Daddy -- is a weekly radio show and podcast hosted by Bob Parsons, CEO &amp; Founder of GoDaddy.com. The show is broadcast every Wednesday at 2 pm PST/5 pm EST -- live from Go Daddy's Scottsdale headquarters and streamed from the www.radiogodaddy.com web site. Each installment features a special guest -- ranging from leading Internet entrepreneurs to start-up innovators to controversial newsmakers -- plus a segment called &quot;Internet Files&quot; during which Parsons and his expert panel review and discuss the top tech stories of the week. Detailed descriptions of prior shows can be found at www.radiogodaddy.com, together with free downloads to iPODs, MP3 players and personal computers. Transcripts are also available for download, free of charge. Go Daddy is a leading provider of services that enable individuals and businesses to establish, maintain and evolve an online presence. GoDaddy.com is known for competitive pricing, quality products, and industry leading customer service. The company is also known for its edgy Super Bowl advertisements featuring Danica Patrick, Candice Michelle, Dale Earnhardt Jr., and others. 
</itunes:summary>
  <itunes:keywords>podcasting podcast Bob Parsons Radio Go Daddy LIVE Life Online with Bob Parsons Candice Michelle</itunes:keywords>
  <itunes:duration>01:30:00</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:owner>
    <itunes:email>radio@godaddy.com</itunes:email>
    <itunes:name>Radio Go Daddy</itunes:name>
  </itunes:owner>
  <language>en-us</language> 
  <copyright>Copyright &#xA9; 2005-2009. Go Daddy Software, Inc.  All rights reserved. </copyright> 
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 10:43:49 MST</lastBuildDate> 
  <ttl>60</ttl><item>
      <title>Curtains for Radio Go Daddy + The Best of the Worst of 2009, Part II</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_12_30.mp3</link>
      <description>This is it! After almost four crazy years on the air, we have reached the final installment of &lt;b&gt;Radio Go Daddy&lt;/b&gt;! On tap for this very special occasion: Part II of our 2009 Retrospective. So prepare yourself to re-experience the eerie predictions of loopy clairvoyant Sylvia Browne and author Dave Cullen's stunning revelations about what really happened before, during and after the Columbine massacre. Also on the menu: Comedian Jon Reep's hilarious &quot;Rules For The Locker Room,&quot; plus a conservative broadside against the Left -- courtesy of Ann Coulter and Michelle Malkin!

&lt;b&gt;On that note: Thanks for lending us an ear. It's been a blast!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_12_30.mp3" length="62075699" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Re-Experience the Very Best of Radio Go Daddy 2009!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_12_23.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the end of an era, people! We're going off the air for good. But before Radio Go Daddy enters the pantheon of late great radio shows, we have a special treat for you: &lt;b&gt;A two-part tour de force of the very best - and worst - of Radio Go Daddy 2009!&lt;/b&gt; So tune in, hang loose and prick up your ears for Part I, which serves up that legendary appearance by bona fide madman Ted Nugent, the rants of combustible comedian Adam Carolla, and the unforgettable -- and epically vitriolic -- &quot;Guy From Boston.&quot; And let's not forget LaToya's Jackson's lament to her late great brother and a certain mystery guest that made Nima all mushy! And much more!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_12_23.mp3" length="73924608" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Holy Toledo, Batman! Relive the Great Adam West on Radio Go Daddy!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_12_16.mp3</link>
      <description>To the Batmobile, bat fans! Fasten your bat seat belts for a very special encore presentation of the original Caped Crusader -- the great &lt;b&gt;Adam West&lt;/b&gt; -- entertaining Bob &amp; Crew with intimate anecdotes from the bat cave, including the truth about Cesar -- The Joker -- Romero's mustache and that electrifying sexual tension between the purring Catwoman and the growling Batman. Mr. West also reveals how his hilarious Family Guy gig almost earned him a fatwa! And on &lt;b&gt;The Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, a British school girl gets so sick of her granny's moaning that she tries to sell her on eBay!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Also on tap: Britain asks Governator Schwarzenegger to &quot;terminate&quot; the Calif-based &quot;TripAdvisor for Pimps&quot; Web site!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_12_16.mp3" length="31666995" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>We Love Them Long Time - Relive Raunchy Rap Renegades 2 Live Crew!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_12_09.mp3</link>
      <description>The show was legendary! So we're giving you a chance to relive one of Bob's all-time favorite installments of Radio Go Daddy -- and one of the raunchiest ones, too! That's right: It's &lt;b&gt;2 Live Crew in da house&lt;/b&gt; as the scandalous rappers give us a taste of their new material and reminisce about their glory days and that awesome &quot;Me So Horny&quot; masterpiece of theirs! And on &lt;b&gt;The Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, Warren fills us in on the difference between &quot;good&quot; and &quot;bad&quot; hackers. &lt;b&gt;Plus: With local Internet connections slow as molasses, carrier pigeons could be back in business in South Africa!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  9 Dec 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_12_09.mp3" length="35651584" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Outrageous Ralphie May Rips Oprah &amp; Michael Jackson. Plus: A Lewd New Low for the Internet Files!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_12_02.mp3</link>
      <description>Nothing is sacred to shameless heavyweight comedian &lt;b&gt;Ralphie May&lt;/b&gt;, who -- in a very special encore presentation of one of our most scandalous shows ever -- entertains Bob &amp; Co. with his hilarious take on Michael Jackson's legacy, how he prefers his Oprah &amp; why Paula Dean turns him on! And in &lt;b&gt;The Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, a moronic burglar checks his Facebook® account on victim's computer, but forgets to log out. And this was also the episode in which one story made us crack up so hard we almost couldn't finish the show. Hint: It had to do with cyber toys for the virtual bedroom.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Plus: Tales from Bob's epic cross-country motorcycle ride.&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  2 Dec 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_12_02.mp3" length="27892122" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Spineless Liberals Turn Coldblooded Terrorists Into Victims, Ann Coulter Rages!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_11_25.mp3</link>
      <description>Those bleeding-heart liberals insist on turning everyone -- even hardcore terrorists -- into victims, our guest, conservative icon and agitator extraordinaire &lt;b&gt;Ann Coulter&lt;/b&gt;, claims in a rapid-fire broadside against the Left. And, she fumes, this spineless surrender mentality is exactly why the Army and everyone else failed to act on the chilling rhetoric from Fort Hood massacre suspect Maj. Hasan! And on &lt;b&gt;The Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists discuss Google's plans to double Internet speeds with a new application-layer protocol. Also on the menu: Conspiracy theorists and other nuts believe the world will come to a cataclysmic end on Dec. 21, 2012. So can we kiss our earthly lives goodbye?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_11_25.mp3" length="40999322" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Sen. Fred Thompson Warns of the Dangers of Trying the Sept. 11th Mastermind in NYC!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_11_18.mp3</link>
      <description>Trying Khalid Sheikh Mohammed in New York is a huge mistake, and the inevitable media circus will hand the Sept. 11th mastermind a very public pulpit from which to preach his vile propaganda. That's the disturbing warning from our guest, &lt;b&gt;the esteemed Sen. Fred Thompson&lt;/b&gt;, who also claims that some of the documents handed over to Mohammed's defense went straight to Osama Bin Laden's tent! And on &lt;b&gt;The Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists try to make sense of a new study, which claims that Internet usage makes you more social. And a warped new computer game permanently deletes a random file from your Mac every time you pulverize an alien!

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Playboy's Scott Alexander presents the hottest tech gifts for the Holiday season!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_11_18.mp3" length="44879053" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Adam Carolla Eviscerates the ACLU &amp; How a GPS Receiver Saved Bob's Behind!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_11_11.mp3</link>
      <description>He is cranky, volatile and absolutely hilarious. He's even got an asteroid named after him! In a very special encore presentation of Radio Go Daddy, we're replaying one of our funniest shows ever as combustible comedian &lt;b&gt;Adam Carolla&lt;/b&gt; entirely loses his cool and goes on an epic tirade that ridicules navel-gazing tweets and absolutely eviscerates the ACLU, which, he claims, is destroying our country! And on the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, we reveal how one brainy house cat landed a high school diploma. Also on tap: New study proves what's painfully obvious: Half of all tweets are nothing but mindless babble!

&lt;b&gt;Plus: How a GPS receiver saved Bob from the jaws of a ferocious leopard!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_11_11.mp3" length="50331648" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>What Are John Lennon &amp; Michael Jackson Up To? Psychic Sylvia Browne Connects With the Beyond &amp; Prophesizes on Doom.</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_11_04.mp3</link>
      <description>John Lennon and Michael Jackson are performing divine concerts in Heaven, and Farrah Fawcett has gone into research! So speaks our guest, world-famous psychic &lt;b&gt;Sylvia Browne&lt;/b&gt;. The seeress also predicts a massive recovery of the US economy and assures us that no meteorite impact or other cataclysmic natural disaster will wipe out Mankind anytime soon!
 
And in &lt;b&gt;The Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists examine the &quot;tweeting-after-sex&quot; phenomenon. We also have the strange tale of the NYU researcher who's translating Moby Dick in its entirety into Japanese emoticons.
 
&lt;b&gt;Plus: Balloon Boy video games, nude burglars &amp; Susan Fitter's latest lecture on netiquette!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  4 Nov 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_11_04.mp3" length="48758784" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>TV's Sexy &quot;Money Honey&quot; and Web Celeb Hotty iJustine</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_10_28.mp3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;Maria Bartiromo&lt;/b&gt; made it to the top of a heavily male-dominated world. But does CNBC's original &quot;Money Honey&quot; cringe when she hears that nickname? Or does she kinda like it? You will never guess why she trademarked the term! Maria also delivers her sobering take on the troubled economy: Is there light at the end of the tunnel, or are we only halfway through a devastating &quot;double-dip recession&quot;? Also joining Bob &amp; Co: &lt;b&gt;Web hottie Justine Ezarik -- aka &quot;iJustine&quot;&lt;/b&gt; -- reveals why creepy stalkers forced her to stop &quot;lifecasting&quot; her every waking moment on the Internet and how the phenomenal power of YouTube inspires millions to watch her order pizza or flip through a phone bill. And on which hit TV show will she be making a brief, but bloody appearance?

On the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists learn which country made high-speed Internet a legal right and hear the chilling story of how an iPhone saved a Vermont woman from the jaws of a ferocious bear.

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Owen Thomas lets loose on the alleged inside trader and fired Twitter boss's new start-up.&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_10_28.mp3" length="42572186" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>La Toya Says Michael Knew He Was Going To Die... And Why.  Plus: Kiss &amp; Tell on Google Maps and Tweets From The Afterlife!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_10_21.mp3</link>
      <description>&quot;Michael was a gift from God&quot; -- an absolutely wonderful human being. But justice needs to be served following his tragic and unnecessary death! That's the message from an emotional &lt;b&gt;La Toya Jackson&lt;/b&gt;. In an absolutely extraordinary show, a painfully honest La Toya opens up to Bob about Michael's legacy,  her theory about his untimely death -- and her best-selling Playboy spreads. Also on the menu: &lt;b&gt;Gayle Bass -- aka the &quot;Click Chick&quot; from KTAR Radio&lt;/b&gt; -- joins the cast and tells the crew where to see stories of leprechauns in Alabama and chimpanzees riding Segways!
 
On the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt; a tasteful new website lets you pinpoint on a Google Map where, how and when you just did the nasty and our panelists reach a stunning new low as they discuss &quot;twéances,&quot; &quot;twairvoyances,&quot;&quot;twasturbation&quot; and other ridiculous Twitter twenomena!  

&lt;b&gt;Plus: The ever-vicious Owen Thomas explains how one Silicon Valley exec uses Wikipedia to bed women!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_10_21.mp3" length="67213722" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Liberal Cry Babies, Locker Room Nudity &amp; Gunfire in the Apple Store!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_10_14.mp3</link>
      <description>Is it OK to get naked in the gym locker room? As long as you follow the &quot;5-minute rule&quot; says our guest and &lt;b&gt;Last Comic Standing winner Jon Reep&lt;/b&gt;. Jon also tells us what you should NEVER do with a hair dryer. Plus, &lt;b&gt;Republican advisor and political commentator Mary Matalin&lt;/b&gt; blasts Pres. Obama's track record and slams liberal men who don't fight fair.

In the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;: computer makers plan to release an &quot;instant-on&quot; PC and why you shouldn't shoot your iPhone in the Apple store.

&lt;b&gt;And: Nik the Geek sings the praises of the Hello Kitty iPhone app and reveals embarrassing photos of Bob!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_10_14.mp3" length="48758784" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Batman/Family Guy's ADAM WEST!  Plus TripAdvisor 4 Pimps and Selling Granny on eBay</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_10_07.mp3</link>
      <description>Zapp!!! Kapoww!!! Bamm!!! Holy Sound Effects, Batfans: In a truly legendary show, the great &lt;b&gt;Adam West&lt;/b&gt; joins Bob &amp; Co. from the Batcave to entertain you with anecdotes from the Bat set, his co-starring role with The Three Stooges and how his new Family Guy gig almost earned him a Fatwa. Adam also gives the scoop on that Batcave garage sale and the new &quot;Adam West Naked&quot; DVD, which features the Caped Crusader telling all about every 120 &quot;Batman&quot; episodes. Plus, will the Dark Knight kiss and tell on who he lured into the Bat bedroom? Tune in to find out!  And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists wonder what made a British school girl auction her granny on eBay. A no reserve auction at that!  We also have the lowdown on why Britain wants Arnold Schwarzenegger to &quot;terminate&quot; the Calif-based &quot;TripAdvisor for Pimps&quot; Web site that posts reviews on London's prostitutes!

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Susan Fitter attempts to explain why flaming each other on the Web is a no-no!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  7 Oct 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_10_07.mp3" length="52848230" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Comic Ralphie May's Rants on Oprah &amp; Michael Jackson!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_09_30.mp3</link>
      <description>He's outrageous, politically incorrect, and funny as hell! Nothing is sacred to our guest, the &quot;Austin-tatious,&quot; larger-than-life &lt;b&gt;comedian Ralphie May,&lt;/b&gt; who, in a show for the ages, entertains Bob &amp; Co. with his hilariously irreverent take on Oprah, the hot women of the Food Network, Michael Jackson's legacy &amp; smoking weed with JC! Also on the menu: Pro Bull Rider Cody Ford dishes on rodeo groupies and mounting a 2100 lb. bull!  And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; an epically idiotic burglar checks Facebook account on victim's computer, but forgets to log out. And -- it finally happened -- one story made the panelists laugh so hard they almost couldn't finish the show. You gotta hear it!
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Plus: Susan Fitter's netiquette advice and Owen Thomas points the finger at an alleged Pyramid scheme!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_09_30.mp3" length="50646221" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Disturbing Truth About the Columbine Massacre</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_09_23.mp3</link>
      <description>When Eric Harris and Dylan Klebold slaughtered 13 people and then themselves at Columbine High School, the media helped create an image of the killers as reclusive outcasts who snapped after years of bullying. Not true, says &lt;b&gt;Dave Cullen, author of NYT Bestseller &quot;Columbine,&quot;&lt;/b&gt; who's on a mission to set the record straight about the tragedy. There was, he tells Bob in a jaw-dropping interview, no &quot;Trench Coat Mafia,&quot; and the perpetrators were coldblooded, calculating killers determined to murder hundreds of random students and school personnel.  And on the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; the esteemed panelists discuss how Microsoft's new Visual Search service will work for X-rated material, while Bob finds the positive in Denmark's embarrassingly ill-advised tourism ad.

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Owen Thomas gives a one-two punch at Tesla Motors and Facebook!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_09_23.mp3" length="65955430" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bob Love Them Long Time -- 2 Live Crew in da House!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_09_16.mp3</link>
      <description>Their raunchy lyrics and suggestive videos put Miami rappers &lt;b&gt;2 Live Crew&lt;/b&gt; squarely on the frontline of the late 80s/early 90s rap censorship war. In a show that's bound to up Radio Go Daddy's street cred, the infamous rappers reminisce about &quot;Me So Horny,&quot; give a sneak peak of their latest single and unleash their unfiltered take on strip clubs, censorship and, even, Danica Patrick! And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the pundits try to understand why 2 trapped girls updated their Facebook for help instead of calling for help. Also on tap: Carrier pigeons make a triumphant return in South Africa, and should email messages in &lt;font color=&quot;#ff0000&quot;&gt;BOLD, RED and ALL CAPS&lt;/font&gt; really be grounds for termination?

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Nik the Geek reviews the new iPod &amp; Owen Thomas spits more venom at Silicon Valley CEOs!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_09_16.mp3" length="45193626" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Madoff's Obsessions, Buzz Aldrin's Amazing Final Thought Before Moonwalk</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_09_09.mp3</link>
      <description>Bernie Madoff pulled off one of the biggest swindles in history by shamelessly ripping off friends, celebs, charities, even unsuspecting relatives. &quot;&lt;b&gt;Madoff with the Money&quot; author Jerry Oppenheimer&lt;/b&gt; reveals how Madoff's life of deceit can be traced all the way back to his childhood in Queens and exposes his rampant obsessive compulsiveness, secret sex affairs and personal quirks including wearing two $30K Rolexes on the same wrist.  Also on the menu, &lt;b&gt;AdventureGirl -- aka Stephanie Michaels&lt;/b&gt; -- reveals Buzz Aldrin's unbelievable last thought before stepping on the moon and explains how she racked up a whopping 1 million Twitter followers! And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the pundits weigh in on the new Twitter parody, Woofer.com, and the iPhone exclusive is running out for AT&amp;T. And although marginally intrigued, Bob &amp; Co. are mostly split on the authenticity of the &quot;Nessie&quot; sighting on Google Earth.

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Owen Thomas resurfaces &amp; Nik the Geek hands down the verdict on Apple's new Snow Leopard OS&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  9 Sep 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_09_09.mp3" length="53057946" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>How to Date Out Of Your League &amp; Michelle Malkin Blasts Obama's Washington</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_09_02.mp3</link>
      <description>Obama's message of Hope and Change is a hoax, and voters are facing a serious case of buyer's remorse! At least that's what our guest, conservative blogger and &lt;b&gt;#1 NY Times Bestselling author Michelle Malkin&lt;/b&gt; claims in her devastating expose on the Obama Administration, which, she alleges, is infested with corruption and cronyism. Also on tap: A peek inside the awesome life of &quot;&lt;b&gt;The Imbiber -- aka Playboy blogger Dan Dunn&lt;/b&gt; -- who enlightens us on what it takes to date way out of your league. And in the Internet Files, our esteemed panelists ponder how the infamous &quot;Skank blogger&quot; suddenly became the victim!  Meanwhile, the Swiss are angry with Google, the Brazilians try eCards to stop the spread of STDs, and the French speed up divorce proceedings by using steamy SMS.

&lt;b&gt;Plus, Susan Fitter educates Web heathens on proper netiquette and Nik the Geek takes the new Kindle for a spin!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  2 Sep 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_09_02.mp3" length="56518246" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Adam Carolla Goes Off On Twitter, Swine Flu and Allergies</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_08_26.mp3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;Bob's back with a vengeance!&lt;/b&gt; And in a legendary show, he fills Nima and co-host Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff in on his almost fatal African safari and how a GPS saved his ass. Literally. Meanwhile, radio host, comedian and exceptionally cranky &lt;b&gt;Adam Carolla&lt;/b&gt; let's it fly on everything from the ACLU to Dancing With The Stars.  And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the distinguished panelists give the facts to back up what you already knew: Almost half of all tweets consist of mindless babble. Also on tap, Oreo the cat gets her high school diploma, and the stats on the typical gamer.

&lt;b&gt;Plus: More HamCam footage from Radio Go Daddy's inner sanctum.&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_08_26.mp3" length="52533658" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Ted Nugent on Radio Go Daddy: Relive The Magic That is &quot;The Nuge&quot;</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_08_19.mp3</link>
      <description>&quot;The harder the hunt, the more delicious the meat!&quot; Who, but the Motor City Madman himself, would say such a thing? By popular demand, we are replaying one of our greatest shows ever. Listen with your mouth open as the one and only &lt;b&gt;Ted Nugent&lt;/b&gt; gives you a personal look into his bow hunting, cooking and wilderness survival. This, of course, is also the show in which &quot;Uncle Ted&quot; enlists Nima as prey to be hunted on his new wilderness survival reality TV show! And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, a naughty teen peddles nude pictures of his mom online while a DVD mishap gets a California teacher's students a first-row seat to her sexual exploits.
&lt;b&gt;Plus, Bob &amp; Owen Thomas dissect the Netscape co-founder's new gig &amp; more HamCam footage.&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_08_19.mp3" length="51694797" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Surviving a Robot Uprising, the best use of Album Covers and Where's Chocolate Rain When You Need It?!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_08_12.mp3</link>
      <description>Save yourselves from an inevitable robot attack! That's the chilling message from &lt;b&gt;Dr. Daniel Wilson&lt;/b&gt;, roboticist and author of the tongue-in-cheek &quot;How to Survive a Robot Uprising.&quot; Also joining Nima &amp; guest host Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff: Comedienne &lt;b&gt;Sarah Colonna&lt;/b&gt; from E!'s very funny &quot;Chelsea Lately&quot; gives her take on The Real Housewives of New Joisey, belching on the first date and so much more.
On the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt; learn why Mark wants to get his hands on the SI SwimSuit iPhone app and why no matter how much Nima may loathe it, that YouTube wedding video isn't going anywhere fast!

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Owen Thomas blows the lid off of Silicon Valley narcissism and Nima and Mark span the globe for this week's weirdest news!&lt;/b&gt;  
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.
No hamsters were harmed here, we promise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_08_12.mp3" length="41838182" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Creator Descends on Radio Go Daddy &amp; Mysteries of the Playboy Grotto Revealed!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_08_05.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that reaches for the heavens yet remains firmly planted in the gutter, &lt;b&gt;the Creator himself -- aka Mr. Deity -- aka Brian Dalton&lt;/b&gt; -- descends on Radio Go Daddy to enlighten Nima &amp; guest host Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff on what he would have done differently if he could do that whole Genesis thing all over again. Meanwhile, Playboy Tech Editor &lt;b&gt;Scott Alexander&lt;/b&gt; previews the Apple Tablet PC and spills secrets from the famous Playboy Grotto! And in &lt;b&gt;The Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, after a worker at a Chinese iPhone plant leaped to his death from the factory's 12th floor the company consoles his girlfriend with a free laptop. Also on tap, our pundits doubt the Microsoft-Yahoo partnership won't even rattle Google -- and will the Queen's manservant tweet the Royal Flush? 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Plus: Owen Thomas reports on out-of-control Silicon CEOs.&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.
No hamsters were harmed here, we promise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  5 Aug 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_08_05.mp3" length="36280730" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Naked Nun, Free AK-47s &amp; Donny Osmond Shares His Last Conversations With Michael Jackson</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_07_29.mp3</link>
      <description>Irreverent guest host &lt;b&gt;Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff&lt;/b&gt; may talk about birthmarks and harnesses and question her NYC street cred but if you ever wondered what would get Nima truly flustered and off her game, the answer is right here as she meets her idol &lt;b&gt;Donny Osmond&lt;/b&gt; who shares his heart-breaking last conversations with lifelong friend Michael Jackson! Also on tap: Hacking superstar &amp; ex-con &lt;b&gt;Kevin Mitnick&lt;/b&gt; delivers a chilling primer on social networking! And on the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists explain the connection between God, free AK-47s &amp; pickup trucks and wonder how an aspiring nun's nude picture may impact life behind monastery walls!
&lt;b&gt;Plus: Owen Thomas on why Tesla CEO Elon Musk finds him the meanest person in Silicon Valley!&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.
No hamsters were harmed here, we promise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_07_29.mp3" length="40160461" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Radio Go Daddy Joins the Dark Side -- With Warped Guest Host Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_07_22.mp3</link>
      <description>If you thought Radio Go Daddy would lose its edge in Bob's absence, think again!. With guest host &lt;b&gt;Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff&lt;/b&gt; sitting in with Nima Jones, the show crosses into uncharted territory as we cover brick-hurling retirees, attachment sizes &amp; the USB gadget that's sure to spice up air travel! Meanwhile, &lt;b&gt;Cali Lewis of GeekBrief.TV&lt;/b&gt; feels the force with this Xmas' new Star Wars toy that teaches you to levitate stuff like a true Jedi! And in &lt;b&gt;The Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, Mark explains why Twitter is perfect for Britain's Royal Family and why a Chinese-style boot camp is the only cure for Web addiction. Also on tap: Bill Gates sets his sights on changing the weather!
&lt;b&gt;Plus: Owen Thomas has the lowdown on the Google CEO's latest adventures below the belt. And what is a ziggurat?&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.
No hamsters were harmed here, we promise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_07_22.mp3" length="35441869" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>X-Rated Wildlife Pix &amp; Mini-Me: Inside the Twisted Mind of Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_07_15.mp3</link>
      <description>What do Sarah Palin, Mini-Me and X-rated elephant pictures have in common? Well, they're all fueling the twisted mind of &lt;b&gt;Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff&lt;/b&gt; who joins Bob to offer his warped take on politics, sex tapes &amp; edgy wildlife photography! Meanwhile, Bob bluntly dismisses the Twitter® bid for the Nobel Peace Price and wonders if &quot;Little Elvis&quot; might be behind those recent cyberattacks. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the crew checks out the new smile cam that verifies that Japanese railroad workers, really, really like their jobs and marvels at the idiocy that blew the cover of Britain's new spy chief. Also, a medical marijuana dispensary goes Web 2.0 and starts tweeting its weed!

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Why is the Cisco CEO making duck calls from the corner office?&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.
No hamsters were harmed here, we promise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_07_15.mp3" length="49073357" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Radio Go Daddy Goes Primal -- With the Motor City Madman!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_07_08.mp3</link>
      <description>&quot;The harder the hunt, the more delicious the meat!&quot; In an instant classic of a show, we're joined by the Nuge... the one and only &lt;b&gt;Ted Nugent&lt;/b&gt;. That's right: the Motor City Madman explains the fine art of bow hunting &amp; previews the new TV show in which &quot;Uncle Ted&quot; teaches people wilderness survival skills, then hunts them down! And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, a naughty New Zealand teen peddles nude pictures of his mom online while a DVD mishap forces California parents to stay up late teaching their kids about the birds &amp; bees!
&lt;b&gt;Plus, Bob &amp; Owen Thomas dissect the Netscape co-founder's new gig &amp; more HamCam footage.&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.
No hamsters were harmed here, we promise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  8 Jul 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_07_08.mp3" length="48129638" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bob Gets Close With YouTube Sensation Marina Orlova</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_07_01.mp3</link>
      <description>When someone says &quot;word origins&quot;, what's the first thing that comes to mind?  A hot blonde, right?  It is if you're one of the 230,000 subscribers to &lt;b&gt;Marina Orlova's&lt;/b&gt; YouTube channel!   The sexy Russian from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hotforwords.com&quot;&gt;hotforwords.com&lt;/a&gt; visits with Bob.  Also on deck:  &lt;b&gt;Nik the Geek&lt;/b&gt; bangs heads with Bob about the new iPhone app &quot;Documents To Go&quot;, &lt;b&gt;Owen Thomas&lt;/b&gt; reveals that now Googles plans to go beneath the Earth and more HamCam action!  And, in the Internet Files: The Pentagon sidesteps questions about new CyberCommand and can a Web addresses really save the environment?!

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Ham Cam catches Itsi, Bitsi, &amp; Mini doing their thing!&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.
No hamsters were harmed here, we promise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  1 Jul 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_07_01.mp3" length="37224448" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bob's back, Baby... and ballistic over the iPhone, MySpace and the U.S. Open</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_06_24.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob's back and loving this week's guest - &lt;b&gt;theguyfromboston.net  -- Joe Ligotti&lt;/b&gt;.  Don't miss Joe's no holds barred rants on 21st century parents, gas prices, and the &quot;Octo-mom&quot;.  Meanwhile, Bob has a few choice words of his own for the U.S. Open which refused to run a Go Daddy ad during its telecast.  Also on tap: &lt;b&gt;Nik The Geek&lt;/b&gt; weighs in on the new &lt;b&gt;iPhone 3GS&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Owen Thomas&lt;/b&gt; reports on Steve Jobs' health.  And on the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the Chinese government learns not to get between the people and their porn. Plus, does Bing have Google right where it wants them?

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Ham Cam catches Itsi, Bitsi, &amp; Mini....napping?&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.
No hamsters were harmed here, we promise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_06_24.mp3" length="50331648" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A Special Re-Broadcast of The &quot;Ragin' Cajun&quot; Superstar of Political Spin</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_06_17.mp3</link>
      <description>In a very special, and Twitter-heavy, edition of the show, &lt;b&gt;superstar political advisor James Carville&lt;/b&gt; weighs in on Somali pirates, Congress &amp; Pres. Obama's performance, while &lt;b&gt;Valleywag's Owen Thomas&lt;/b&gt; reports on the SF Mayor's ambitious quest, which was announced via -- you guessed it -- Twitter! And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; the experts have some tough words for the Domino's workers whose prank created a PR nightmare for the pizza chain &amp; agree that Oprah -- who just joined the Twitter craze -- soon will surpass the million-&quot;Follower&quot; barrier, which Ashton Kutcher, of all people, just broke. &lt;b&gt;Plus: Bob has his eyes set on a very special new Go Daddy Girl -- but will Hillary Clinton accept his intriguing $1 million proposition?&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_06_17.mp3" length="58510541" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Celebrating Life's Misery &amp; Microsoft Reinvents Search -- Again</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_06_03.mp3</link>
      <description>Celebrating Life's Misery &amp; Microsoft Reinvents Search -- Again
Life can be a bitch, but &lt;b&gt;FMyLife.com&lt;/b&gt; helps you find some humor in the misery. &lt;b&gt;Alan Holding &amp; Frans van Schoor&lt;/b&gt; join us to discuss their site &amp; explain why people love to share their crappy life experiences with the world.  Also on the menu: Nik the Geek expresses his love for the new Google Android phone and Owen Thomas reports on Yahoo CEO Carol Bartz' penchant for foul language. &lt;b&gt;And in the Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; our tech experts agree that Microsoft's revamped &quot;Bing&quot; search engine looks promising. But will people really make the switch? And as a man's Twitter post about leaving town might have triggered a break-in at his house, Brad admits, that he, too, has Twittered his whereabouts. 

&lt;b&gt;Plus: More in-studio footage from the HamCam!&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  3 Jun 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_06_03.mp3" length="34183578" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Cuban Cigars, Danica Makes History &amp; Who Should Control the Internet?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_05_27.mp3</link>
      <description>With her new commercial and historic Indy 500 3rd-place finish, Go Daddy Girl &lt;b&gt;Danica Patrick&lt;/b&gt; once again stole the headlines, and she joins us to relive the dramatic race and that steamy ad! Also on the guest list: Former NTIA Chief &lt;b&gt;John Kneuer&lt;/b&gt; weighs in on the EU's &quot;misguided&quot; call for globalizing ICANN and wonders what would happen if the UN took over. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists reveal how a 3-year-old girl won an Internet auction for a $12,000 earth moving behemoth while mom was napping. And will intrepid Cuban bloggers succeed in undermining the Castro regime so Bob can finally smoke a good cigar? 

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Nik the Geek &amp; more unedited footage from the HamCam!&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.
No hamsters were harmed here, we promise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_05_27.mp3" length="52323942" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Virginity Auction &amp; America's Obsession With Female Purity!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_05_20.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that never shies away from controversy! &lt;b&gt;Author &amp; outspoken feminist Jessica Valenti&lt;/b&gt; eviscerates abstinence-only education and society's obsession with chastity, which, she says, is hurting young women. Also on the menu: 22-year-old &lt;b&gt;Natalie Dylan&lt;/b&gt; explains what compelled her to sell her virginity to the highest bidder and why the much-publicized Internet auction is a cold, hard business. And in the Internet Files, the pundits examine Dell's grossly miscalculated &quot;Della&quot; initiative, and Bob &amp; Nima consider Twitter's porn star name game and reveal what their screen names could have been! 
&lt;b&gt;Plus: More, unedited in-studio footage from the HamCam!&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.
&lt;br&gt;
No hamsters were harmed here, we promise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_05_20.mp3" length="49702502" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Hanging With the Diggnation Dudes &amp; a Hamster's Eye View of Radio Go Daddy!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_05_13.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that offers a live &amp; unedited behind-the-scenes look at Radio Go Daddy, we check in with &lt;b&gt;Diggnation's Alex Albrecht and Kevin Rose&lt;/b&gt; who reminisce about beer and that memorable show when Candice stripped in front of a raucous live audience. Also on tap: &lt;b&gt;Valleywag's Owen Thomas&lt;/b&gt; brutally dismisses Tesla CEO Elon Musk's dream of a manned mission to Mars! And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists ponder some disturbing news from the FAA and wonder which Federal computer system will be hacked next. And how did sensitive information about the THAAD missile defense system appear on a discarded computer that was sold online?
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Plus: We unveil the HamCam! As our in-studio hamsters spin in their wheel, you'll see what the rodents see!&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.
&lt;br&gt;
No hamsters were harmed here, we promise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_05_13.mp3" length="33554432" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Pole Dancing, Supercomputers &amp; and Internet Super-Celeb!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_05_06.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that boldly declares the death of Twitter, yet gets you the scoop on a possible blockbuster merger involving the micro-blogging phenomenon! Our guest, &lt;b&gt;NonSociety blogger &amp; Web celeb Julia Allison&lt;/b&gt;, tells us the secrets to her Internet fame, while &lt;b&gt;Bree Baker&lt;/b&gt; -- that sexy cop from the new Go Daddy ad -- reveals how pole dancing lessons helped her prepare for the steamy gig.&amp;nbsp; And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists agree that supercomputers capable of outsmarting humans will emerge in a not-too-distant future. Plus: Our experts aren't convinced that the newest &quot;Google Killer&quot; will revolutionize the world of search. But Brad &amp; Warren at least dig its very geeky name!
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  6 May 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_05_06.mp3" length="48549069" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Swine Flu Updates on Twitter &amp; Barbara Lippert Rips our New Commercial!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_04_29.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob's in Hawaii, Nima's in NYC, and our favorite ad critic, &lt;b&gt;AdWeek's Barbara Lippert&lt;/b&gt;, rips our new Danica Patrick commercial. It is, she says, degrading and just &quot;embarassing!&quot; In the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panel ponders the future of MySpace and lauds the CDC's Swine Flu updates on Twitter. And did IBM blow it by allowing Oracle to step in and snatch Sun Microsystems?

Plus: Valleywag's Owen Thomas has the scoop on Libertarian Facebook investor Peter Thiel, who declared women's suffrage a mistake!
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_04_29.mp3" length="45822771" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The &quot;Ragin' Cajun&quot; Superstar of Political Spin &amp; an Intriguing Proposition for Hillary Clinton!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_04_22.mp3</link>
      <description>In a very special, and Twitter-heavy, edition of the show, &lt;b&gt;superstar political advisor James Carville&lt;/b&gt; weighs in on Somali pirates, Congress &amp; Pres. Obama's performance, while &lt;b&gt;Valleywag's Owen Thomas&lt;/b&gt; reports on the SF Mayor's ambitious quest, which was announced via -- you guessed it -- Twitter! And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; the experts have some tough words for the Domino's workers whose prank created a PR nightmare for the pizza chain &amp; agree that Oprah -- who just joined the Twitter craze -- soon will surpass the million-&quot;Follower&quot; barrier, which Ashton Kutcher, of all people, just broke. 

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Bob has his eyes set on a very special new Go Daddy Girl -- but will Hillary Clinton accept his intriguing $1 million proposition?&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_04_22.mp3" length="65640858" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Cyber Spies, Al Sharpton &amp; Sheriff Joe's Very Own Reality TV Show!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_04_15.mp3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;America's Toughest Sheriff -- Joe Arpaio&lt;/b&gt; -- has got his own reality TV show, and he's with us &lt;b&gt;LIVE in-studio&lt;/b&gt; to tell us how it helped reel in over 400 offenders with outstanding warrants, and why neither the Justice Dept., nor the Rev. Al Sharpton has him quaking in his boots. Also on the menu: &lt;b&gt;Nik the Geek&lt;/b&gt; checks out the new iPod Shuffle. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists are underwhelmed by Facebook's new monetization feature, but intrigued by British police's new method of clamping down on distracted drivers. Plus, Bob has his very own reasons for being unconcerned with Chinese cyberwarfare!
 
&lt;b&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#ff0000&quot;&gt;Plus: More $$$ for the people in chat!!!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_04_15.mp3" length="50646221" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Scandalous Mark Nemcoff &amp; a Street View Witch Hunt!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_04_08.mp3</link>
      <description>The Pacific Coast Hellway show is on hiatus, but it's creator -- &lt;b&gt;Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff&lt;/b&gt; -- entertains us with observations on OctoMom, Chris Brown and other tales from his scandalous new show &quot;&lt;b&gt;Things I Learned This Week&lt;/b&gt;.&quot; Meanwhile, &lt;b&gt;Valleywag's Owen Thomas&lt;/b&gt; serves up some juicy stuff on Tesla Motors CEO Elon Musk's disintegrating marriage. In the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the pundits discuss whether it's OK for Britain's &quot;Sexiest Teacher&quot; to show off lingerie on the Web and agree that Rupert Murdoch should worry about fixing MySpace instead of attacking Google and Yahoo. Also on the menu: In a story straight out of the Dark Ages, hordes of English villagers drive a Google® Street View car out of town.

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Nik the Geek returns to tell us about cell phone software that helps circumvent red light cameras and speed traps.&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  8 Apr 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_04_08.mp3" length="57357107" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Lethal SMS, Victorian Ghosts &amp; Radio Go Daddy Turns 4!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_04_01.mp3</link>
      <description>It's April 1st, Radio Go Daddy is turning 4, and &lt;b&gt;Valleywag's Owen Thomas&lt;/b&gt; briefs us on Silicon Valley's April Fool's Day pranks, while our resident techie -- &quot;&lt;b&gt;Nik the Geek&lt;/b&gt;&quot; -- joins the cast. Our guest is &lt;b&gt;Tumblr founder David&lt;/b&gt; Karp, who gets us the lowdown on his mixed-media microblogging platform &amp; how it differs from Twitter. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists discuss a horrifying &quot;Killer SMS&quot; &amp; agree that the media-savvy Mark Cuban deliberately Twittered himself into trouble with the NBA. Also on the menu: Did Google's Street View really capture a Victorian ghost in Wales? 

&lt;font color=&quot;#ff0000&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Plus: A very special anniversary greeting from the irresistible Obama Girl!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  1 Apr 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_04_01.mp3" length="48758784" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>New Go Daddy Girl Burns Up the Golf Course!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_03_25.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that includes gossip, hot women &amp; crazy programmers, Valleywag's Owen Thomas reveals the real reason Jennifer Aniston dumped John Mayer, and &lt;b&gt;our sizzling new Go Daddy Girl' -- Aussie LPGA ace Anna Rawson &lt;/b&gt;-- joins us to chat about her runway and fairway careers &amp; the new putter she procured for Bob. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; Warren is enticed by Cadillac's latest offering, while the panelists wonder what made a deranged Finnish programmer replace his injured finger with a USB drive. Also on the menu: A California high school enrolls the Internet in its battle against plagiarism. And the pundits think it just might work!

&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_03_25.mp3" length="46137344" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Drunken Geeks, Responsible Twittering &amp; the President's Bailout Eviscerated!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_03_18.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that features drunken geeks, girl scouts &amp; the Holy Pontiff -- Valleywag's Owen Thomas talks about the ultimate &quot;Spring Break for Geeks&quot; while &lt;b&gt;world-class spinmeister Dick Morris&lt;/b&gt; weighs in on the Pope, condoms &amp; Pres. Obama's stimulus &amp; bailout plans, which, he says, are just &quot;wrong, wrong, wrong!&quot; And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists discuss the concept of &quot;Tweeting Responsibly&quot; &amp; try to understand how an entrepreneurial Girl Scout got herself in hot water for peddling cookies on the Web. And as the Linden $$$ are starting to dry up in Second Life, Bob &amp; Co. wonder if the financial crisis is slowing things down in the virtual Red Light District, too. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Plus: Susan Fitter tells us how to reply to email while Bob provides his own piece of irreverent etiquette advice to men!&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_03_18.mp3" length="62075699" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Game Theory, Netiquette &amp; a Very Bright New Go Daddy Girl!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_03_11.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that that introduces two new segments, &lt;b&gt;etiquette expert Susan Fitter&lt;/b&gt; offers a sobering lesson on social networking, while &lt;b&gt;ValleyWag's Owen Thomas&lt;/b&gt; briefs us on the SF mayor's kooky cousin Chloe! Our guest is &lt;b&gt;new Go Daddy Girl' Vanessa Rousso&lt;/b&gt;, Team PokerStars Pro -- who tells us about the intellectual approach that propelled her to the top and why poker players wear their sunglasses at night. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists discuss whether Twitter should be allowed in Federal courtrooms &amp; wonder what the Second Life crowd might do with virtual reality for all five senses. Plus, Bob believes Craigslist's Erotic Services section can actually help authorities crack down on prostitution! 
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 23:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_03_11.mp3" length="85458944" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Radio Go Daddy Hits Vegas!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_03_04.mp3</link>
      <description>In a very special -- and rather rowdy -- edition of the show, we're coming to you from Bob's Caesar's Palace suite in Sin City where Bob talks about his new favorite car &amp; &lt;b&gt;pro poker player Mike &quot;The Mouth&quot; Matusow&lt;/b&gt; fills us in on his trash talking table manners, which earned him that very appropriate nickname. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; the panelists digest the fact that Romania has a semi-official UFO Network &amp; reveal Melinda Gates' hidden, forbidden passion for the iPhone. Also on the menu: In a story worthy of Jackass, we tell you about allegations involving a cell phone, a patient's delicate predicament, an X-ray &amp; Facebook that landed two nurses in hot water!
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  4 Mar 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_03_04.mp3" length="60817408" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Diamond Rings, Regifting &amp; Other Tales of Silicon Valley Celebs Behaving Badly!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_02_25.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that takes on global warming, Chevy Impalas, DABA Girls &amp; the concept of an &quot;Anarcho-Transexual Afro-Chicano,&quot; &lt;b&gt;Silicon Valley's top gossip columnist -- Valleywag's Owen Thomas --&lt;/b&gt; entertains us with an exclusive scoop on the Google CEO's regifting habits &amp; other juicy tales of Bay Area celebs behaving badly. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; the panel discusses the implications of bringing the Deep Web to the masses &amp; marvels at Craigslist's ability to procure just about anything -- including human organs. Also on the menu: Should doctors really be Twittering while performing major surgery? Warren offers a conditional &quot;yes.&quot;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;font color=&quot;#ff0000&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Plus, we're handing out more $$$ to the listeners in chat!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_02_25.mp3" length="59663974" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>LIVE From Scottsdale -- It's Candice &amp; the Super Bowl's Most Unexpected Star!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_02_18.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that features air travelers, card counters &amp; edgy women -- the Super Bowl's most unexpected star -- &lt;b&gt;adult actress Tristan Kingsley -- joins us LIVE in-studio&lt;/b&gt; to talk about the &quot;incident&quot; &amp; get Bob's view on how Comcast can make amends for its mistake. Also with us in-studio: &lt;b&gt;Our very own Candice Michelle&lt;/b&gt; shows off the new move that'll help her reclaim her WWE throne. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panelists entertain themselves with a Hong Kong woman's epic airport tantrum &amp; wonder if you can get away with using your iPhone to count cards at Nevada casinos. Plus: Bob thinks its time for anonymous flamers to start owning up to their nasty comments!
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_02_18.mp3" length="79377203" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A Devout Christian Decries our Super Bowl Ads!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_02_11.mp3</link>
      <description>Web 2.0 has shaped the Internet. But how has this phenom affected our culture &amp; values? My guest is &lt;b&gt;Andrew Keen -- a self-proclaimed &quot;elitist&quot; whose &quot;The Cult of the Amateur&quot; decried Web 2.0's worship of amateurism&lt;/b&gt; &amp; made him the blogosphere's &lt;b&gt;Public Enemy No. 1!&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Also on our guest list: &lt;b&gt;Web entrepreneur Brian Harrell&lt;/b&gt; who removed his clients' Web sites from Go Daddy due to our &quot;non-Christian&quot; &amp; &quot;exploitative&quot; Super Bowl ads.
&lt;br&gt;
On the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, my resident panel of experts &amp; I discuss this week's hottest tech stories:

  &amp;bull; Know where your kids are? A new Google tool helps you track them down!
  &amp;bull; &quot;25 Things About Me&quot; -- the latest Facebook fad takes Web 2.0 navel-gazing to another level!
  &amp;bull; Google glitch temporarily flags the entire Internet as malware!

Plus, we'll have a special segment: &lt;font color=&quot;#ff0000&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&quot;What Would Bob Do?&quot;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_02_11.mp3" length="83676365" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Another Super Bowl Home Run &amp; Zombies in Austin</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_02_04.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that spans the Pacific Ocean &amp; revisits the media's post-Super Bowl roasting of Go Daddy, the ad industry's &quot;flaming pen&quot; -- &lt;b&gt;AdWeek's Barbara Lippert&lt;/b&gt; -- tries to understand how &quot;Baseball,&quot; which she hates, became the game's most-watched commercial. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, we relay a chilling story about zombies in Texas &amp; reveal how Google Earth helped Swiss police catch a ring of clueless hemp growers. Also on the menu: The panelists wonder if Venice tourists will pre-pay for public toilets or simply relieve themselves in the canals.

&lt;font color=&quot;#ff0000&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Plus, we're once again handing out $$$ to our listeners in chat!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  4 Feb 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_02_04.mp3" length="66165146" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Pre-Game Buzz &amp; a Real Stinker for the iPhone</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_01_28.mp3</link>
      <description>As we count down to the Super Bowl &amp; sift through the pre-game media buzz, &lt;b&gt;AdRants' Steve Hall&lt;/b&gt; hands down his unforgiving verdict on our Super Bowl ads, while &lt;b&gt;Joel Comm, the brains behind iFart&lt;/b&gt;, tells us how he came up with this outlandish &amp; unexplainably successful iPhone application. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, the panel wonders if -- as Bob hopes -- a disastrous sales report will finally spell the end for the Zune &amp; ponders the fate of a new Web hangout for the rich &amp; famous. And what would a native New Yorker like Nima do if police told her to hand over her iPod as payment for a cab ride? 
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;font color=&quot;#ff0000&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Plus: We give away hundreds of $$$ to the lucky people in chat!!!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_01_28.mp3" length="60922266" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Spring Break Gone Wild &amp; A New Low for iPhone Applications</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_01_21.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that goes where no radio show has gone before, &lt;b&gt;Bob demos his cringe worthy new iPhone application&lt;/b&gt; &amp; updates us on the too-close-to-call Super Bowl ad vote. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, we discuss who's to blame for a 17-year-old's smutty Spring Break activities &amp; wonder who would actually befriend a police department on Facebook. Also on the menu, we check out the next-generation parking meters which render meter maids obsolete. Plus a former director of Faith-Based Services finds himself in hot water after launching a prostitute-rating Web site &amp; peddling raffle tickets for a night with a hooker. 
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_01_21.mp3" length="45822771" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>&quot;Stupid. Just Awful!!!&quot; -- How Barbara Lippert Really Feels About Our Super Bowl Ads</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_01_14.mp3</link>
      <description>It's almost Super Bowl time, and our favorite ad critic -- &lt;b&gt;AdWeek's Barbara Lippert&lt;/b&gt; -- checks in to pass the verdict on our two spots. And while she kinda likes &quot;Shower,&quot; she pulls no punches in eviscerating the &quot;stupid,&quot; &quot;awful&quot; &amp; &quot;not even funny&quot; &quot;Baseball&quot; ad. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, we discuss the carbon footprints of Google searches and Second Life avatars and wonder what virtual stand-ins for active-duty parents will do for -- or to -- the kids. Also on the menu: A virtual escort provides an inside look at Second Life's Red Light District.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;font color=&quot;#ff0000&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Plus: We're asking YOU to help us pick which ad to air during the Big Game!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;hr&gt;
Third-party products and brand names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_01_14.mp3" length="65431142" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A New Platform for Public Self-Pitying &amp; Another Mishap Hits the Zune</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_01_07.mp3</link>
      <description>In the first show of the new year, we examine the Twitter phenomenon &amp; get you the &lt;b&gt;lowdown on Go Daddy's Super Bowl commercial&lt;/b&gt; and the inevitable controversy it attracts. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, we check out the newest Web pulpit for bitching, self-pitying &amp; schadenfreude while the panelists wonder if Chinese porn producers could circumvent the Govt's Internet censors by sticking to old-fashioned hard-copy material. Also on the menu, the team gets a kick out of the latest misfortune to hit Bob's favorite media player as thousands of Zunes simultaneously freeze on New Year's Eve. 
&lt;hr&gt;
Super Bowl, Twitter &amp; Zune are registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  7 Jan 2009 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2009_01_07.mp3" length="52219085" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Ninja Advice, Pink Underwear &amp; the Go Daddy Year in Review</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_12_31.mp3</link>
      <description>In the New Year's Eve edition of the show we revisit the &lt;b&gt;top Go Daddy moments of the past year&lt;/b&gt;, including Danica making history, a Royal visit to Scottsdale, Go Daddy-driven legislation and, of course, Super Bowl ads and a bit of controversy. Also on the menu: &lt;b&gt;Our favorite guest segments of 2008&lt;/b&gt;, including: Sheriff Arpaio's preference for pink underwear, Barbara Lippert's blistering critique, Obama Girl's crush on Go Daddy &amp; some very salient advice from the Web's most famous ninja!
&lt;hr&gt;
Super Bowl is a registered trademark of the National Football League. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_12_31.mp3" length="53162803" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Tumbleweeds, Stupid Gifts &amp; the Very Wackiest Internet Files of the Year!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_12_24.mp3</link>
      <description>In a special Holiday edition of the show, we look back at our favorite Internet Files moments of 2008 &amp; check out the &quot;Potty Putter&quot; and other of the year's dumbest gift ideas as listed by Stupid.com. Our guest is &lt;b&gt;Prairie Tumbleweed Farm founder Linda Katz&lt;/b&gt; who runs one of the wackiest Web businesses we've ever come across. She makes a -- very decent -- living selling real tumbling tumbleweeds from her home on the Kansas prairie! And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, we relive the Top 10 stories of the year, including the unforgettable tales of how an enraged woman exacted revenge on her virtual ex-hubby and the Second Life affair that led to a real-world divorce. Plus, of course, the strange story of the German woman who peddled her services online, slept with 6 men &amp; filed a paternity suit when she realized she was pregnant.
&lt;hr&gt;
Second Life is a registered trademark of Linden Research, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_12_24.mp3" length="60607693" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Virtual Weddings, Flawed Internet Filters &amp; a Candid Discussion About Go Daddy Business Practices</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_12_17.mp3</link>
      <description>In a highly spirited edition of the show, Bob &amp; ardent Go Daddy critic &lt;b&gt;Andrew Allemann of Domain Name Wire&lt;/b&gt; cross swords for a candid discussion about domain auctions, transfers and other parts of Go Daddy's business that have ired the industry watchdog. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; the panel digests the news that almost half of all women prefer the Internet to sex and wonders why the Australian Govt. is moving forward with its Internet filter, which, the panel declares, will not work. Plus, our pundits try to understand why the Second Life bridal industry is doing so well. And how much does a virtual wedding cost anyway?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_12_17.mp3" length="51694797" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Rome Burns, Cyprus Dances, Venice Drowns &amp; Go Daddy Parties Like It's 1999!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_12_10.mp3</link>
      <description>In a highly party-centric edition of the show, Bob &amp; Nima discuss the somewhat critical media coverage of Go Daddy's Holiday Bash &amp; ponder the question: Is it OK to throw a party for the ages while the economy is tanking? Meanwhile, &lt;b&gt;Blip.Tv founder &amp; CEO Mike Hudack&lt;/b&gt; - who has also received his fare share of party-related press lately -- joins us to talk about that much-maligned &quot;Camp Cyprus&quot; video, which placed him at the center of a blogosphere firestorm. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files&lt;/b&gt;, we discuss one teenager's incredibly ill-advised text message to her dad &amp; wonder if the drowning city of Venice will be entirely submerged before it can implement free Internet for all of its citizens. 

&lt;b&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#ff0000&quot;&gt;Plus:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Bob hands us the scoop on the two new Go Daddy Super Bowl commercials!

&lt;hr&gt;
Blip.Tv is a registered trademark of Blip Networks, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_12_10.mp3" length="45717914" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Live From Los Angeles: It's Radio Go Daddy!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_12_03.mp3</link>
      <description>In a very special edition of the show, broadcast from Los Angeles where we're shooting our new Danica Patrick Super Bowl commercials, &lt;b&gt;Danica joins us&lt;/b&gt; to chat about making the ads, her 3-hour shower &amp; the upcoming IndyCar season. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; Bob &amp; his team wonder if the long winter nights are the reason Canadians spend more time on social networking than Americans &amp; discuss what, if anything, can be done to diminish how cell phone conversations distract drivers. Plus, if Internet searches, as a new study suggests, boosts the brain activity of older people, does it matter what they're searching for?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  3 Dec 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_12_03.mp3" length="51589939" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A Very Ninja Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_11_26.mp3</link>
      <description>We celebrate Thanksgiving by replaying one of the year's very best shows. So once again, sit back &amp; enjoy as Bob &amp; Nima cross swords with &lt;b&gt;Ask a Ninja creator Kent Nichols&lt;/b&gt; who debunks a few myths &amp; takes us inside the mind of the Internet's premier martial artist. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; we show you the dangers of adding 
your boss to your Facebook friends list, tell you how an enraged woman exacted revenge on her virtual hubby &amp; ponder the Google execs' decision to add a fighter jet to their already-impressive air fleet.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_11_26.mp3" length="43830477" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Marshmallow Shooters, Virtual Girlfriends &amp; Big Trouble at Yahoo</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_11_19.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that touches on Nigerian scammers, virtual girlfriends &amp; sex in cyberspace, &lt;b&gt;Boing Boing founder Mark Frauenfelder&lt;/b&gt; tells us how to get in touch with our inner geek and build robots, spy cameras &amp; marshmallow shooters from common household items. And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; we check out another weird -- and slightly disturbing -- Japanese toy and list the 5 worst mistakes made by the Yahoo top. Also on the menu: The panel wonders whether having cyber sex with an animated prostitute constitutes real-life cheating.

&lt;b&gt;Plus: Bob reveals that Go Daddy will be back for yet another &quot;GoDaddy-esque&quot; Super Bowl commercial come February.&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_11_19.mp3" length="48653926" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Truth Is Out There...</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_11_12.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show worthy of the X-Files, Black Vault founder John Greenewald, Jr. shares his vast knowledge of UFOs, government cover-ups &amp; the fabled &quot;Area 51&quot; and tells us why -- after 12 years of collecting &amp; studying govt. documents--he's certain that aliens exist. And in the Internet Files, we discuss the British government's draconian new Internet monitoring initiative &amp; tell you what made an Italian judge charge Google executives with defamation. Also on the menu: A new study concludes that violent Web content is more damaging to youths than TV, movies &amp; games.


Plus: Bob calls the bluff on the Rev. John Aboh whose unsolicited e-mail message promises a cool $9.5 million courtesy of the Nigerian Government.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_11_12.mp3" length="44459622" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Pesky Rodents, Rude Flight Crews &amp; How to Protect Your Online Identity</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_11_05.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that covers cyber bullies, Big Apple rats and a new President, our guest, ReputationDefender founder Michael Fertik, explains how you can take control of your online identity before crooks, identity thieves &amp; your own past do it for you. And in the Internet Files, Virgin Atlantic flight crew turn to Facebook to ridicule passengers, while New York City enlists a new weapon in its battle against pesky rodents. And the daughter of the former Yahoo CEO endorses Google ... sort of. 

Plus: With the election in the books, Bob wonders if the President-elect can fix Vista!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  5 Nov 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_11_05.mp3" length="48758784" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>I'm Ninja, He's Ninja, She's Ninja, Too!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_10_29.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that takes you inside the mind of the Web's top martial arts maven! Bob &amp; Nima cross swords with Ask a Ninja creator Kent Nichols who explains the Ninja Path &amp; sets the record straight on some of the many ninja misconceptions that permeate modern culture. And in the Internet Files, we show you the dangers of adding your boss to your Facebook friends list &amp; wonder why Google's Brin &amp; Page just got themselves a fighter jet. Plus, we learn how an enraged woman exacted revenge on her virtual ex-hubby.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_10_29.mp3" length="43830477" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Political Punditry &amp; Tales From the Clinton White House</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_10_22.mp3</link>
      <description>It's a show that covers everything from STD notices via e-greeting to tales from the Clinton inner circle. Pollster, pundit &amp; political strategist Dick Morris joins us LIVE in studio to dissect the presidential race &amp; tell us what went down behind the scenes in the Clinton White House. And in the Internet Files, PBS &amp; YouTube conceive a new way to spice up the vote, while an innovative Web service lets you send anonymous e-greetings to sex partners you might have exposed to an STD.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_10_22.mp3" length="44983910" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Go Daddy Goes Social &amp; Google Saves You From Yourself</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_10_15.mp3</link>
      <description>As we turn the page on a week that saw Go Daddy enter the social networking ring with the release of SmartSpace &amp; a vicious new hacking form targeting users across the Web, our pundits once again tackle the latest &amp; hottest tech topics. In the Internet Files, we discuss Google's Mail Goggles,&quot; which could save you the embarrassment of e-mailing while under the influence &amp; check out the new technology that keeps teenagers from yapping on cell phones while driving.


Plus: The Government strikes a blow against Internet predators as the Go Daddy-supported &quot;Protect Our Children Internet Act of 2008&quot; becomes law.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_10_15.mp3" length="30094131" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Obama Girl, Cloud Computing &amp; Spies on Facebook!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_10_08.mp3</link>
      <description>The election is near &amp; Obama Girl -- aka Amber Lee Ettinger-- makes a triumphant return to the show. We check out her latest videos, listen to her new single &amp; take the temperature on her crush on Obama. And in the Internet Files, we zoom in on Microsoft's planned cloud computing edition of Windows &amp; wonder why Britain's MI6 would recruit spies on Facebook. Also on the menu: A bank robber hires decoys on Craigslist &amp; pulls off one audacious heist...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  8 Oct 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_10_08.mp3" length="32820429" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>McCain Girl Rocks the Vote!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_10_01.mp3</link>
      <description>As the Presidential election campaign enters the home stretch, the &quot;Incredible McCain Girl&quot; aka Kate Secor, pays us a visit to chat about her hit YouTube videos &amp; reveal her true allegiances. And in the Internet Files, we ponder a new study which confirms that Facebook is a haven for narcissists &amp; check out the latest phenomenon to hit Japanese cyberspace: Animated virtual boyfriends. Plus, the &quot;Father of the Internet&quot; -- Vint Cerf -- warns that the Internet is running out of IP addresses.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  1 Oct 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_10_01.mp3" length="31876710" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Google Sets Sail &amp; Do Androids Dream of World Domination?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_09_24.mp3</link>
      <description>Straight from the depths of Africa, Bob returns with a vengeance to spew venom at Windows Vista &amp; those at fault for the nation's economic quagmire. Atty. Jones calls in from Washington to brief us on some crucial legislation Go Daddy helped craft &amp; which is on the verge of being signed into law. And in the Internet Files, Bob &amp; his team check out the first Google Android phone &amp;  discuss whether or not the device will rule the mobile world. Also on the menu, we digest Google's outlandish concept of building &amp; deploying data centers on ships.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_09_24.mp3" length="34288435" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Fashion, Fed-Up Flight Attendants &amp; German Alarmists -- Radio Go Daddy Has it All!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_09_17.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that features everything from unhappy flight attendants to GD Girls on Fashion Week runways, we entertain you with the Best of the Blog &amp; repeat our clues to Bob's mystery location. And in the Internet Files, two new pundits join the line-up to weigh in on the German Govt's dubious decision to warn against Google Chrome &amp; how Facebook content might impact your job hunting success. Plus: Should airlines filter in-flight Internet? Fed-up flight attendants think so while our experts hand in a split decision</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_09_17.mp3" length="28521267" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Will Google Chrome Rule the Web?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_09_10.mp3</link>
      <description>In Bob's continued absence, Nima &amp; the crew bring you up to speed on the latest news, including Go Daddy's first venture into NASCAR's Sprint Cup Series. And in the Internet Files, we take a closer look at Google's new Chrome browser &amp; whether or not the new competition will have Microsoft quaking in its boots. We also give you the low-down on JetBlue's innovative sales tactics &amp; a US Appeals Court's ruling on the usage of Wikipedia information in US Courts.   

Plus: Another clue to Bob's mystery location!


JetBlue, Google, NASCAR &amp; Wikipedia are registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_09_10.mp3" length="38063309" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Would Google Dare to Ditch The Free Dinners?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_09_03.mp3</link>
      <description>With Nima filling in for the Boss, who's in an undisclosed location, we bring back the always-intriguing &lt;b&gt;Where in the World Is Bob?&lt;/b&gt; contest &amp; read you the very &lt;b&gt;Best of the Blog.&lt;/b&gt; And in the &lt;b&gt;Internet Files,&lt;/b&gt; the tech pundits discuss whether Google would dare to ditch its free dinners &amp; what would happen if Go Daddy introduced Google-like afternoon &quot;Tea Trolley&quot; services for the staff. Also on the menu: Can Warren resist the temptation of in-flight Internet &amp; will &quot;Porn Mode&quot; make IE8 an instant hit with Web surfers?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  3 Sep 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_09_03.mp3" length="23278387" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Cell phone service so bad, it's a crime?!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_08_27.mp3</link>
      <description>On this episode of Radio GoDaddy, Bob Parsons and the gang discussed their own experiences with the Apple iPhone 3G! Discover the phone that Bob is dying to get his hands on. Speaking of iPhone, the one and only 'Attorney Jones' was in the studio sharing her expert legal opinion on the iPhone 3G lawsuit! An Alabama woman's iPhone 3G wouldn't work now she's trying to start a class action lawsuit against Apple! Does she have a chance? Plus, the Radio GoDaddy team touches on the top 10 web glitches of 2008 and shares their thoughts on what will be the next big issues for the rest of the year. 
Bob's own Apple iPhone 3G experience!

Apple &amp; iPhone are registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_08_27.mp3" length="33554432" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Return of Radio Go Daddy!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_08_20.mp3</link>
      <description>We're Back! Episode #156! Bob Parsons and the rest of the RadioGoDaddy crew talk about what's been happening with Go Daddy over the past few weeks! Also, Bob has a fascinating chat with Dan Kaminsky, security researcher, who is credited with discovering the DNS flaw. Find out if there's a book in the works about his experiences and why Dan's girlfriend has told him, &quot;Don't break the internet again!&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_08_20.mp3" length="47185920" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Curtain Drops on Go Daddy LIVE!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_03_12.mp3</link>
      <description>In the final installment of the show in its current incarnation, Bob &amp; Co. reminisce about the highs &amp; lows of Radio Go Daddy/Life Online/Go Daddy LIVE's 3-year run &amp; get a dose of gossip from Celebridiot.com founder John Pomponio who entertains the crew with his take on Paris Hilton, Britney &amp; the best &amp; latest scandals involving American Idol hosts &amp; contestants. Plus, Pomponio tells us exactly what a &quot;Celebridiot&quot; is, while decrying the recent lack of really juicy celebrity train wrecks.

In the Internet Files, the team tackles the week's top stories, including Americans' increasing dependency on their cell phones, Ask.com's latest attempt to find itself a market nice &amp; the somewhat odd theory that proliferating iPods have caused an increase in violent crime.

PLUS: We bring you the funniest &amp; most defining moment of the show's history!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_03_12.mp3" length="16357786" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Obama Girl's Got a Crush on Go Daddy!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_03_05.mp3</link>
      <description>As the Presidential campaign heats up, one candidate's most enthusiastic supporter pays us a visit. Amber Lee Ettinger aka &quot;Obama Girl&quot; checks in to chat about her steamy campaign contributions, her favorite candidate &amp; to admit that she's got a crush on Go Daddy, too. And in the Internet Files, the team discusses how Wikipedia founder Jimmy Wales used his online encyclopedia to break up with a girlfriend &amp; what not-so-celibate Thai monks are doing in cyberspace. Plus, Bob hits the street to talk to people about the Internet!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  5 Mar 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_03_05.mp3" length="15833498" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Know Those Neighbors From Hell ... Before You Move!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_02_27.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that takes a close look at busybodies, habitual complainers, howling dogs, Meth labs &amp; other neighbors from Hell, RottenNeighbor.com founder Brant Walker gives us the lowdown on his Web site, which delivers the naked truth on your future neighborhood before you sign the paperwork on your dream home. And in the Internet Files, we discuss how Network Solutions' persistent domain name frontrunning finally led to a lawsuit &amp; how 2 young Belgrade looters became instant celebs on YouTube.

Network Solutions &amp; YouTube are registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_02_27.mp3" length="18874368" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Hanging With America's Toughest Sheriff!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_02_20.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that explores chain gangs, pink underwear &amp; Elvis, &quot;America's Toughest Sheriff&quot; -- Joe Arpaio - joins us in-studio to chat about the job &amp; his re-election campaign. Plus, Sheriff Joe fills us in his &quot;Dead Beat Parents&quot; program, the always-lit &quot;Vacancy&quot; sign at his Tent City &amp; the night he locked up The King. And in the Internet Files, we dissect Microsoft's decision to turn hostile in its Yahoo takeover bid &amp; the strange tale of a German woman who peddled her services online, slept with 6 men &amp; filed a paternity suit when she realized she was pregnant. 
  
Microsoft &amp; Yahoo! are registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_02_20.mp3" length="16252928" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Relive Our Highest-Rated Show of All Time!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_02_13.mp3</link>
      <description>As Go Daddy LIVE! approaches its 3rd anniversary, we thought it was time to replay the highest rated show of all time! &lt;b&gt;Leland Hardy, Sports agent extraordinaire &amp; founder of NewYork.com.&lt;/b&gt; Find out how this one-man show built a top Web portal, was Muhammad Ali's Chinese interpreter and spotted Serena &amp; Venus Williams! With Super Bowl XLII now history, we'll replay &lt;b&gt;Chad &quot;Ocho Cinco&quot; Johnson's mid-season assessment of the Patriots.&lt;/b&gt; Was Chad right? 
&lt;b&gt;The Internet Files&lt;/b&gt; -- you just never get tired of hearing great tech topics discussed by Bob, Warren, Brad (and Nima, too!).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_02_13.mp3" length="21705523" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>No Longer &quot;Lowest of the Low&quot;: Handing Down the Verdict on our Super Bowl Ad!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_02_06.mp3</link>
      <description>As the dust settles on the Super Bowl extravaganza, we recap the post-game media blitz &amp; chat with sharp-penned ad critic 
Barbara Lippert who hands down her verdict on our Big Game commercial. Much to Bob's chagrin, Lippert declares that the 
ad certainly was &quot;stupid&quot; but entirely too effective to claim the title of &quot;lowest of the low.&quot; And in the Internet 
Files, we discuss Microsoft's audacious bid for Yahoo! &amp; whether Yahoo! should fend it off or embrace the enemy.
 
Plus, we bring you some of the very best &amp; most colorful post-game comments from the blog! 
 
Microsoft, Super Bowl &amp; Yahoo! are registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  6 Feb 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_02_06.mp3" length="17406362" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Pre-Super Bowl Buzz &amp; Broken Clavicles with Candice in Studio</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_01_30.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that covers the latest buzz on our Super Bowl ads &amp; the pre-game media blitz, Original Go Daddy Girl Candice Michelle joins us LIVE in studio to tell us what it feels like to crack a clavicle &amp; when she'll be back in the ring to exact some much-needed revenge on her nemesis, Beth Phoenix. Plus, Bob boldly predicts the Giants to pull off a major upset on Sunday. And in the Internet Files, we check out the possibility of nuke-sniffing cell phones &amp; discuss Google's efforts to end domain tasting. 

Bonus Video: The 3 Go Daddy Girls entertaining visitors at Go Daddy's CES booth!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_01_30.mp3" length="22439526" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Life in the Fast Lane &amp; Final Approval of Our Big Game Ad!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_01_23.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that picks Nima's new theme song &amp; celebrates life in the fast lane, LifeOnTop.com co-founders Terry Knealing &amp; David Schoenecker join us in studio to talk about Lamborghinis, yachts, 10-person Ferrari limos &amp; other toys that make the filthy-rich salivate. On the Super Bowl front, Bob announces that on the heels of the &quot;Beaver&quot; incident, Go Daddy finally got an ad past Fox's censors. And in the Internet Files, the panel takes the pulse on Microsoft's creepy big brother monitoring system &amp; ponders the implications of 40-hour laptop batteries.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_01_23.mp3" length="15833498" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Revving it up With Danica &amp; One Controversial Rodent</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_01_16.mp3</link>
      <description>We warm up the engines for the Super Bowl &amp; 2008 IndyCar circuit as our raciest Go Daddy Girl, Danica Patrick, joins us live in studio to chat about her career, her goals &amp; Go Daddy's &quot;Exposure&quot; Super Bowl ad, which stars Danica &amp; a certain dam-building rodent, but was nixed by Fox because Bob insisted on calling a beaver -- a beaver. We also get Bob's take on super models &amp; Victoria's Secret's lingerie line. And in the Internet Files, we discuss the violent death of a Chinese blogger, Britain's new mammoth supercomputer &amp; the Web site that threatens to bring the Sicilian Mafia to its knees.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_01_16.mp3" length="21915238" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Greatest Swimmer of All Time &amp; The Passing of a Once Mighty Browser</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_01_09.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that revisits some of the most memorable moments in Olympic history, the legendary Mark Spitz drops 
in to chat about his phenomenal career, next summer's Beijing Games &amp; the story behind that very un-Olympic 
moustache of his. We also get Mark's take on the infamous Munich Massacre, which he witnessed first-hand. 
And in the Internet Files we discuss the sad but inevitable passing of the Netscape browser &amp; predict a 
possible winner in the ongoing HD DVD format battle. Plus, we review how Network Solutions got 
caught red-handed engaging in domain name &quot;front-running.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  9 Jan 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_01_09.mp3" length="19608371" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Very Best of Go Daddy LIVE 2007</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_01_02.mp3</link>
      <description>We ring in the new year with a very special &lt;b&gt;&quot;Best of the Year&quot;&lt;/b&gt; edition of &lt;b&gt;Go Daddy LIVE!&lt;/b&gt;
Join us as we relive our favorite guests of the year, including political spin &amp; witch doctor &lt;b&gt;FRANK LUNTZ, XXXChurch creator CRAIG GROSS, the remarkable LELAND HARDY,&lt;/b&gt; plus, of course, the audacious &lt;b&gt;Material Bitch founder BETHANY MCNELLY.&lt;/b&gt; Also on the menu, &lt;b&gt;BARBARA LIPPERT's&lt;/b&gt; post-game broadside against Go Daddy's Super Bowl XLI commercial.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  2 Jan 2008 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2008_01_02.mp3" length="15309210" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Connecting People in Need With the Everyday Heroes Willing to Help Them!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_12_26.mp3</link>
      <description>In the last show of 2007, we commemorate the season with a very special edition of Go Daddy LIVE!      

Our guest is Wish Upon a Hero founder Dave Girgenti whose remarkable Web project connects people in need with the everyday heroes willing to help them. Since his site's Sept. launch, more than 2,500 people have had perfect strangers grant their deepest wishes.

Plus, we bring you Bob's Top 10 Keys to Success in 2008!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_12_26.mp3" length="8346665" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Busting Vegas, U R Dumped &amp; Have Wired's Editors Gone Mad?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_12_19.mp3</link>
      <description>He chronicles audacious whiz kids milking Vegas casinos &amp; working the financial markets. Ben Mezrich, NY Times bestselling author of &quot;Bringing Down the House,&quot; &quot;Busting Vegas&quot; &amp; &quot;Rigged&quot; joins us to chat about sophisticated card counting schemes, life in the fast lane &amp; how the part trade floor, part casino &amp; part madhouse that is the New York Mercantile Exchange influences world economy &amp; the price at the pump. In the Internet Files, we discuss the ethical aspect of dumping someone via txt msg &amp; ponder the question: Have Wired's editors lost their minds?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_12_19.mp3" length="15414067" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A Peek Into the Deep End of the Human Soul</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_12_12.mp3</link>
      <description>In a show that ventures into the darkest pits of the human soul, PostSecret founder Frank Warren joins us to talk about his bustling art community, his gut-wrenching new book &amp; some of the quirky &amp; harrowing confessions he has received. In the Go Daddy LIVE Football Report, Chad reveals who should play the leading role when the inevitable Ocho Cinco biopic sees the light of day. And in the Internet Files, we check out JetBlue's Wi-Fi in the sky &amp; the strange, electronic tombstone called the &quot;Serenity Panel.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_12_12.mp3" length="17406362" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Striking Screenwriters, Inflatable Mooseheads &amp; The Top Searches of 2007</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_12_05.mp3</link>
      <description>As the screenwriters' strike enters its fifth week, &quot;Daily Show&quot; scribe Jason Ross joins us to talk about the strike, its reasons, its possible outcome, the specter of more reality TV &amp; the hilarious, studio-exec-lampooning video he &amp; his fellow Daily Show writers posted on YouTube. In the Internet Files, we check out the year's top Internet searches &amp; take a look at this holiday season's most idiotic gift ideas. 

The Daily Show &amp; YouTube are registered trademarks of their respective owners. All rights reserved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  5 Dec 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_12_05.mp3" length="18350080" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Pacific Coast Hellway, The King Is Alive &amp; The Black Friday Zune Frenzy</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_11_28.mp3</link>
      <description>In the return of one our most entertaining guests, Pacific Coast Hellway founder Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff drops in to charm Nima &amp; chat about his crude, lewd &amp; occasionally-offensive podcast. In the Go Daddy LIVE Football Report, Chad &amp; Bob discuss boorish Jets fans, death threats against Leona Helmsley's canine heir &amp; the fate of the Elvis Is Alive Museum. And in the Internet Files, the panel looks at the Black Friday rush to snag discounted Zunes &amp; CNET's naming Windows Vista one of the year's &quot;Top 10 Terrible Tech Products.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_11_28.mp3" length="16462643" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A Walk Down Memory Lane with Toby the Rabbit &amp; the Original Radio Go Daddy Crew</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_11_21.mp3</link>
      <description>Relive the very first Radio Go Daddy broadcast from March 2005 as we kick off the holiday season with a special pre-Turkey Day edition of Go Daddy LIVE. Our inaugural show featured Bob taking on the NTIA's decision to deny private registrations for .us domains &amp; a special report on the controversial SaveToby.com Web site whose founder cynically threatened to slaughter &amp; devour an innocent bunny rabbit unless someone coughed up a $50,000 ransom to save the cuddly critter.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_11_21.mp3" length="15518925" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Muhammad Ali's Chinese Interpreter, a Real-Life Fairy Tale &amp; One Very Good Cause</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_11_14.mp3</link>
      <description>The extraordinary Leland Hardy drops in to chat about his amazingly eventful life, which includes gigs as Muhammad Ali's Chinese interpreter, the Williams sisters' long-time agent and one thrilling heavyweight bout at Madison Sq. Garden. Plus, Bob donates $10,000 to Leland's latest project, Internet Equality, which aims to bring Internet knowledge &amp; access to people around the world. In the Go Daddy LIVE Football Report, Chad ponders Don Shula's suggestion that New England's record this season should be accompanied by an asterisk. And the Internet Files serve up a real 21st century fairy tale as New Yorkers help a love struck young man find the woman of his dreams!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_11_14.mp3" length="21600666" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Google Enters the Wireless World &amp; Should the US Govt. Control the Internet?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_11_07.mp3</link>
      <description>With Bob in an undisclosed location, Nima &amp; Brad take the reins on this domain-industry themed show in which Atty Jones dissects ICANN chief Dr. Paul Twomey's renewed attempts to remove his organization from the US Govt.'s influence. Adam Dicker, owner of thriving online community DNForum.com, drops in for a chat about the domain industry &amp; the present and future state of his DNForum. On the Go Daddy LIVE Football Report, a sore, swollen but good-spirited Chad  Johnson discusses the scary neck injury he suffered on Sunday. And, the Internet Files zoom in on Google's long-awaited entry into the mobile phone world &amp; Time Magazine's decision to name the iPhone &quot;invention of the year.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  7 Nov 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_11_07.mp3" length="21390950" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Pastor Who Offers Rehab for Adult Movie Stars</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_10_31.mp3</link>
      <description>In a Halloween edition of Go Daddy LIVE, Bob &amp; Nima get in touch with their spiritual sides as pastor Craig 
Gross -- founder of XXXChurch.com -- guests the show to explain his virtual church's &quot;porn rehab&quot; services 
and why, as XXXChurch prints on its handout Bibles, &quot;Jesus Loves Porn Stars.&quot; In our weekly football report, 
Bob boldly predicts that the Colts will down the Patriots while Chad reveals that 
he finds Queen Elizabeth sexy, but refuses to believe that Dallas QB Tony Romo has been spotted partying with 
Britney! In the Internet Files, Bob &amp; his tech crew dissect the impending emergence of a Google-powered cell 
phone and discuss whether or not Google's dominance of the tech industry eventually will be total.
 
Bonus Video!: Behind-the-scenes footage from Amanda Beard's photo shoot, press conference and in-studio 
appearance!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_10_31.mp3" length="20971520" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>One Go Daddy Girl takes a nasty fall &amp; another one graces the pages of Playboy</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_10_24.mp3</link>
      <description>Go Daddy Girl Daytona Beach, Lara Haworth describes how winning Employee of the Month won her a recent Playboy photo op --- much to the chagrin of Nima Jones, who only got a GoDaddy.com bumper sticker when she won a similar award.  Bob examines the 'rough &amp; tough' world of WWE and the nasty fall taken by Candice Michelle - how long until she returns to the ring?  Then Chad Johnson tackles head-on the recent criticism he's received regarding his style of play and whether he is giving African-Americans a bad name in pro football.  Finally, in the light-hearted Internet Files,  Warren and &quot;I don't have a job here Brad&quot; debate whether free beer is an adequate reward for a lost laptop.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_10_24.mp3" length="16462643" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Highs &amp; Lows of Go Daddy Advertising - And Do iPhones Make You Sterile?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_10_17.mp3</link>
      <description>Sharp-tongued ad critic Barbara Lippert dukes it out with Bob over the highs &amp; lows of Go Daddy advertising &amp; explains why she thinks that Bob looks &quot;tacky.&quot;  In the Go Daddy LIVE Football Report, Chad &amp; Bob discuss how the reeling Bengals can turn their season around.  The Internet Files look at the &quot;Dark Web&quot; project that might help combat cyber-terrorism - and Greenpeace's claim that iPhones might make you sterile. Plus: We revisit Bob's appearance on the &quot;Renegade Entrepreneurs&quot; edition of CNBC's &quot;Big Idea w/ Donny Deutsch.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_10_17.mp3" length="19713229" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Going deep with the marketing mastermind behind ESPN</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_10_10.mp3</link>
      <description>We go behind the scenes with the ESPN President of Sales &amp; Marketing, Ed Erhardt. Learn how the worldwide leader of sports feels about working with Go Daddy &amp; find out which cool gifts are coming Bob's way -- and which ones he has already received. In the Go Daddy LIVE Pro Football Report, Chad &amp; Bob discuss what goes on during a team's bye week and how a winning record can make a football player's life so much easier. And in what could be the craziest Internet Files story to date, North Korean leader Kim Jong Il almost makes the panel spontaneously combust  or was that an iPod?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_10_10.mp3" length="20552090" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Jumping Into the Pool With our Hot New Go Daddy Girl</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_10_03.mp3</link>
      <description>She is a a world-class athlete &amp; successful model who has graced the cover of FHM® and Playboy®. Listen in as hot new Go Daddy Girl, elite swimmer Amanda Beard, pays Bob &amp; Nima a visit to chat about her career, what makes her GoDaddy-esque and how she's looking forward to donning a Go Daddy-branded cap in the pool. In the Go Daddy LIVE Football Report, Chad Johnson talks about his team's scathing defeat on Monday night and why Ocho Cinco's end zone Go Daddy Dance didn't happen this time around. And in the Internet Files, Bob &amp; his team take a look at the latest dot-com boom hitting Silicon Valley. Plus! Weird News makes its return in spectacular style!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  3 Oct 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_10_03.mp3" length="18559795" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The &quot;Real&quot; Founder of Facebook? &amp; Ocho Cinco Joins the Cast</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_09_26.mp3</link>
      <description>The &quot;Real&quot; Founder of Facebook? &amp; Ocho Cinco Joins the Cast
While at Harvard, he built a social network which, according to a widely circulated e-mail, included a feature called &quot;the Face Book.&quot; 6 months later his classmate, Mark Zuckerberg launched Web 2.0 phenomenon Facebook. Tune in as guest Aaron Greenspan explains his &quot;houseSystem&quot; network and discusses who really came 
up with the idea for Facebook. In a brand-new fixture of the show, Go Daddy's newest spokesperson, Chad Johnson, joins Bob for the inaugural Go Daddy LIVE Football Report -- and promises an end zone Go Daddy Dance during next Monday's game. In the Internet Files, Bob &amp; his team discuss whether Microsoft might buy a 5% 
stake in Facebook -- a move Bob likens to a kiss of death for Facebook.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_09_26.mp3" length="21495808" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Go Daddy LIVE Takes Off &amp; Ocho Cinco Touches Down, Promises a Go Daddy Dance</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_09_19.mp3</link>
      <description>In a gridiron special featuring Cincinatti's most GoDaddy-esque resident, Nima &amp; Bob inaugurate the show's new name -- Go Daddy LIVE. Pro Football's edgy and slightly inappropriate top entertainer, &quot;Ocho Cinco&quot; alias Cincinatti WR Chad Johnson -- chats with Bob about his antics, the charities close to his heart, the possibility of doing a Go Daddy end zone dance, and the HOT new Go Daddy commercials he just shot. In the Internet Files, Bob &amp; Co dissect Microsoft's® stinging defeat at the hands of an EU court and discuss Google's® $30 million bounty for landing a rover on the moon.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_09_19.mp3" length="18140365" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>English 101 With Grammar Girl, College Ball, Wascally Wabbits and Yet Another Zune Rant</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_09_12.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that puts hip back into English grammar and revives Warren's former alias - &quot;thumbs.&quot; Nima &amp; Bob discuss Go Daddy setting up shop in the Mile-High City, followed by Bob's BIG announcement of Go Daddy's sponsorship of ESPN College Football. Grammar Girl stops by to share some &quot;Quick &amp; Dirty Tips&quot; from her podcast and -- inspired by Barry Bonds' bashing of Hank Aaron's home run record -- teach us how to use the asterisk to its full effect. In the Internet Files, Bob and his tech pundits ponder why Apple® cut the price on the iPhone® and whether the EU can preempt terror by banning bomb recipes from the Web. Also, Warner Bros unleashes Elmer Fudd, Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck on the Web and Bob delivers an epic tirade against Microsoft® and its &quot;iPod Killer&quot; - the Zune®. Plus, video of Warren &amp; Bob -- our own &quot;odd couple!&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_09_12.mp3" length="17301504" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Godaddying&quot;, Squidoo's New Take on Search  &amp; Trojans in Germany!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_09_05.mp3</link>
      <description>Our wordiest show ever adds a whole new lexicon to your life --- from &quot;Godaddying&quot; to &quot;SquidWho.&quot;  All-time favorite show guest, Seth Godin, returns to discuss his social network, Squidoo®, and why we should all become &quot;Lensmasters&quot; and donate our profits to charity. In the Internet Files, Brad rises from his couch to predict the end of social networking, while Bob &amp; his expert panel discuss Apple's® golden touch, Bob's troublesome iPhone® text messaging and why Orkut®, despite its bizarre name, could soon rival Facebook® and Myspace®. Plus, Germans &amp; Trojans &amp; spies - oh my!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  5 Sep 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_09_05.mp3" length="24851251" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Twitter, Trivia &amp; Exclusive Sturgis Video!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_08_29.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that never taps its toe in the bathroom. Bob is back to finally unveil the new name of your favorite Internet podcast--Go Daddy LIVE!--and reveals why, under different circumstances, his co-host might have been &quot;Mandy&quot; Jones. Next, Twitter co-founder Biz Stone explains how the mundane &quot;away&quot; IM status served as the inspiration for his Web 2.0 communications startup and discloses how it's caught on with at least two Democratic presidential hopefuls. And in the Internet Files, how Internet users in China might soon be interrupted by an animated police force, why the iPhone's teen hacker won't have to worry about a legal defense fund, and whether Brad might be Life Online's very own Kato Kaelin. Bonus! Catch Bob's man-on-the-street interviews from the world's largest motorcycle rally in Sturgis, South Dakota in this exclusive &lt;a href=http://lifeonlinewithbobparsons.tv/gdshop/radio/view_video.asp?video_id=12 target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_08_29.mp3" length="18979226" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Most Fabulous (And Pink) Life Online Ever!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_08_22.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that Bob's going to kick himself for missing.  Nima and Atty Jones reveal why there's been a recent upswing in .TV domain name registrations to go along with the surging popularity of online video content  -- and reveal the 1st question in our new &quot;Super Fan&quot; trivia contest.  Next, Material Bitch founder Bethany McNelly--in studio w/her entourage of sexy &quot;switches&quot;--reveals how, at 22 years old, she has already broken even after only 5 months of applying her fabulous fashion sense to the launch of her pink, girly clothing line; she also opines why hot girls should always stay together, and why Danica Patrick is her celebrity of choice to sport a Material Bitch hot pink t-shirt.  And in the Internet Files, Brad and Dr. Nick Fuller explain why iTunes will topple only when the iPod sees some stiffer competition, why the Rhapsody America marketing team should attend the Bob Parsons' School of Product Naming, and why Google is poised to make major inroads in China.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_08_22.mp3" length="18559795" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Dirty Scottsdale's Nik Richie Live In Studio!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_08_15.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that parties every night and sleeps all day.  Bob regales fill-in co-host Elizabeth Knight with tales from Sturgis and reveals why Go Daddy may be on the bench for this year's Super Bowl advertising blitz.  Next, Bob welcomes DirtyScottsdale.com creator Nik Richie and learns why a plan to just have a laugh at some &quot;hot-lookin' broads&quot; has turned into a Web site that's exploded in popularity and spawned a sister site targeting Sin City.  And in the Internet Files, Warren comes in with a wild tie, Bob reveals why he's a Mac convert and begs Microsoft to just fix Vista, and we learn why last month alone 48 million domain names were tasted and spit out.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_08_15.mp3" length="17196646" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Water Gun Mayhem &amp; Name This Show Contest Winner!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_08_08.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show whose dossier is classified information. Nima and crew pick the winner of our much ballyhooed Name This Show Contest, explain why a bum tire took Danica out of contention this weekend at the Indy 400, and reveal how Warren was upstaged by Bob's dog Max during the recent AZ Humane Society telethon. Next, entrepreneur and StreetWars co-founder Franz Aliquo joins us from an undisclosed pizza parlor to tell us why practicing equities law can't hold a candle to organizing water gun hit man tournaments and why New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg's admonishment helped put the game on the map. And in the Internet Files, why Warren's new mantra of personal responsibility includes holding out for version 2 of everything--except the iPhone--and how Steve Jobs has shown incredible self restraint to not &quot;sue the hell&quot; out of Fake Steve Jobs blogger Daniel Lyons.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  8 Aug 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_08_08.mp3" length="12373197" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The World's Laziest Entrepreneur &amp; .US Domain Breaking News!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_08_01.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that's looking for quotes but just can't find any. Bob puts the rumors to rest that he has plans to walk down the aisle next week in Sturgis and Warren outlines Go Daddy's plan to put sparkle back in the stars of the .US domain. Next, entrepreneur, author &amp; blogger Fred Gratzon gets an &quot;atta boy&quot; from Bob for being Go Daddy material, learns why removing Warren's Blackberry passes for meditation around these parts, and discovers why nothing good happens for Bob after 10:00 PM. And in the Internet Files, why Mark Cuban's reports of the Web's demise may be greatly exaggerated, how Wikipedia's accuracy stacks up against Encyclopedia Britannica, and Bob's suggestion for how to handle online predators.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  1 Aug 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_08_01.mp3" length="15414067" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Law &amp; Order's Sam Waterston Meets Life Online!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_07_25.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that's not eligible to run for president but is mounting a massive write-in campaign anyway. Bob recounts Go Daddy Girl Danica Patrick's first-turn woes that knocked her off the pace this weekend in Ohio. Next, actor and activist Sam Waterston discusses his role as spokesman for Unity08--a political organization using the Web to field a non-partisan presidential ticket for next year's election--and tells Bob why the two-party system has left the average American voter disenfranchised. And in the Internet Files, why Bob's 70,000-unit order helped boost Apple's initial iPhone sales--and why a recent study shows that people are still falling for the same old phishing schemes. Plus, Bob's endorsement of Firefox!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_07_25.mp3" length="16986931" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Name This Show Contest &amp; Create Your Meosphere</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_07_18.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show whose meosphere is the envy of all other radio shows. Bob joins Go Daddy Girl Danica Patrick in calling out Ed Carpenter for blocking during last weekend's Indy race and not making room for the ladies. Next, founder &amp; CEO of Meosphere, Eric Eliason, explains how a trip to Brussels provided the inspiration for his list-crazy site and how an entirely new word was coined in the process. And in the Internet Files, why Bob applauds the hackers of Microsoft's DRM system, whether Google's &quot;Do No Evil&quot; philosophy still applies when their hand is on your wallet, and why everyone is doing the &quot;Nima shuffle.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_07_18.mp3" length="35127296" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Namibian Babies &amp; Tracking Down Dr. Frank Luntz</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_07_11.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that boasts listeners of every political affiliation--even Libertarians.  Bob clears the air about his latest African safari blog post and points out that unlike Madonna &amp; Angelina Jolie, no babies crossed his path.  Next, political pollster, author &amp; media darling Dr. Frank Luntz explains which presidential candidate is saying the &lt;i&gt;right&lt;/i&gt; things, why he loves angry airline passengers &amp; how the shortest path to a big raise might be incriminating photographs.  And in the Internet Files, how Bob's iPhone attraction is a feeling shared by its multitude of hackers--and why the &quot;Red Ring of Death&quot; spells doom for Xbox 360 gamers and huge PR headaches for Microsoft.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_07_11.mp3" length="17616077" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bob's Back -- Tanned, Rested &amp; Rearing to go!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_07_03.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show we've all been waiting for - Bob's back baby and he's ready to roll.  First up on our special holiday broadcast, Bob describes his recent travels and announces the winners to our &quot;Where's Bob&quot; contest.  We then revisit Best of the Blog and Bob sets an international speed reading record going through this weeks Strange Domains.  In the Internet Files - Find out what Warren did with his iPhone and hear Bob let loose on Google's archiving of your search information. Plus, GoDaddy.com's annual Independence Day Holiday card.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue,  3 Jul 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_07_03.mp3" length="15099494" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Searching For The Big Guy &amp; Dave Novak's eBay Selling Secrets</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_06_27.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show with first-hand knowledge that showers and iPhones don't mix. Our &quot;Where in the World Is Bob&quot; contest rolls on with a reading of the best, albeit incorrect, guesses so far--and the unveiling of a 3rd clue that will appeal to all you movie buffs. Next, 27-year-old entrepreneur Dave Novak tells us how his online selling strategies helped him escape life in a cubicle and why untapped eBay® markets still exist for those dedicated to finding them. And in the Internet Files--why your bookie may be watching the unveiling of Apple's new iPhone with interest--and how it's going to be every man, woman &amp; child for themselves when it finally hits retail store shelves on Friday.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_06_27.mp3" length="12058624" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Where's Bob Clue #2 &amp; HelloMetro's .MOBI Madness</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_06_20.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show whose instant gratification issues are being worked out with the help of a licensed therapist.  Our &quot;Where in the World Is Bob&quot; contest entrants have yet to locate our wayward traveler, so we're reading the best guesses, repeating clue #1 &amp; debuting clue #2.  If you think you know the place, shoot us an email at radio@lifeonline.com.  Next, HelloMetro founder &amp; CEO Clark Scott takes time out from his birthday to tell us why community is at the center of his company's online city guides &amp; how their recent deployment of 600+ .MOBI sites went without a hitch.  And in the Internet Files--why company co-founder Jerry Yang's stay in Yahoo's CEO chair might be a brief one, how eBay's cojones were on full display when it boycotted Google® &amp; finally, how YouTube's upcoming foray into the presidential debates says as much about television's declining influence as it does about the rise of the Web.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_06_20.mp3" length="36385587" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>New Show Time, Where In the World Is Bob &amp; Rocky Mirza</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_06_13.mp3</link>
      <description>We've moved to an earlier time slot and like it!  Weblo.com founder and CEO Rocky Mirza joins us on the eve of his company's auction of England (yes, England!) to tell us how virtual properties are earning its owners &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; profits --- and why folks are registering virtual domain names.  And in the Internet Files -- the outrage over an anti-Web 2.0 book, how Apple(R) let the privacy genie out of the bottle and why animals are more than man's best friend -- they're the basis for a new twist on an old technology.  &lt;b&gt;Plus, we unveil the first clue in our Where In the World Is Bob contest.&lt;/b&gt;  Email us your best guess!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_06_13.mp3" length="11848909" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Jason Calacanis (a/k/a Mr. Mahalo), Google Gears &amp; Tech Lexicon!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_06_06.mp3</link>
      <description>It's a super-tight, new format for the show that hasn't gotten more than 6 hours of sleep since the late '70s.  Web entrepreneur, blogger, podcaster &amp; NYC marathoner Jason Calacanis tells us why Mahalo, his human-powered search engine, is bringing sanity to an industry gripped by SEO fever -- and even works in a shout-out to his favorite GD customer service rep.  And in the Internet Files--why MySpace jokes are no laughing matter if you work for Wal-Mart. Plus, Where are Bob &amp; Thumbs?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  6 Jun 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_06_06.mp3" length="14784922" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Indy Wrap-Up, RegisterFly Transfer &amp; The #1 Chris on the Web</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_05_30.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that's not after tougher standards, it's after some standards.  Seriously, Bob tells us what the view is like from Indy's pit row and why the Andretti Green racing team serves up an outstanding pre-race peanut butter pie.  Next, Warren Adelman &amp; Tim Ruiz explain why Go Daddy's recent acquisition of RegisterFly's domain portfolio is good news for customers who found themselves &quot;caught between the sheets.&quot;  Then podcaster and tech guru Chris Pirillo tell us why his success can be traced back to a Parsons Technology application called Announcements &amp; what it's like to call Michael Dell on the carpet in a room full of CEOs.  And in the Internet Files-why you'll be able to watch old episodes of &quot;24&quot; in bed on your wife's back and how employers should never hire an employee who uses a Zune.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_05_30.mp3" length="18559795" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Inside Track On Indy &amp; Mr. Deity Goes Hollywood</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_05_23.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show whose religious affiliation is still up for grabs.  Danica Patrick takes time out from Indy's Community Day to tell us why her pre-race eating routine would put a football linebacker's to shame.  Next, Brian Dalton, from the hilarious &quot;Mr. Deity&quot; Web video series, drops in to explain why, despite its success, he still can't quit his day job along with pointing out the startling similarities between Bob and himself. And in the Internet Files-why Boomer's &quot;nut huggers&quot; unduly influenced tonight's sound clips.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_05_23.mp3" length="20447232" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Passionate Podcasting, Killer Rebranding &amp; Those Crazy Canadians</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_05_16.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show whose brand isn't going anywhere. Podcasting forerunner Todd Cochrane dials in from the Big Apple to tell us how his social podcasting community Blubrry has already attracted over 1,200 podcasters since inception. Next, Mike McDerment, CEO of Freshbooks.com, explains how rebranding online can be murder and why Toronto is the city that really flips his switch. And in the Internet Files, we see a side of Warren hitherto kept under wraps --plus, will Microsoft one day raise the white flag in surrender to the open source community?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_05_16.mp3" length="23488102" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Indy Racers &amp; Racy Models</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_05_09.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that's not without a couple piercings of its own--but we can't tell you where. Danica Patrick takes a break from her Indy 500 prep to reveal her strategy for beating the boys in 2 weeks &amp; why her racing suit comes clean with common household laundry detergent. Next, Missy Suicide explains how eschewing the advertisers helped streamline the publishing of her new Suicide Girls magazine--and why taxidermy is the perfect hobby for one of her models. And in the Internet Files--Uncle Al joins us to get to the bottom of who is responding to these tech surveys, anyway. Plus, a scintillating, tell-all &lt;a href=&quot; http://lifeonline.com/gdshop/radio/view_video.asp?video_id=7 &quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;video interview&lt;/a&gt; with Diggnation and Revision3's own Alex Albrecht--he's the one with the hair.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  9 May 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_05_09.mp3" length="23802675" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Making A Podcast Splash &amp; Squelching A Digg User Revolt</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_05_02.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that's always mixing business with pleasure, and tonight is no exception. Marshall Kirkpatrick of SplashCast tells why the best rich media player is one that goes &quot;skinless.&quot; Next, we learn why this week's Digg® user revolt could make founder Kevin Rose a bigger hero than Spiderman. And in the Internet Files-hear why, when Bob hooked up his first 2400 baud modem, he thought it was the &quot;cat's ass.&quot; Plus, a &lt;a href=https://www.lifeonline.com/gdshop/radio/view_video.asp?vid=050207 target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;kick ass video&lt;/a&gt;! Take a peak behind Digg.com when Bob chats w/founder Kevin Rose.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  2 May 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_05_02.mp3" length="26738688" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Diggnation joins Bob live - and the uproar over domain names seeking to profit from tragedy.</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_04_25.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that asks the tough questions but doesn't wait around for the answers. Web pioneer Todd Cochrane explains why podcasting content already rivals that of TV &amp; radio. Then Warren Adelman and Atty. Jones dissect the domain name speculation that invariably accompanies tragic events. And in the Internet Files, Kevin &amp; Alex of Diggnation explain what happened to AOL's &quot;garden experiment.&quot; Plus, our bonus What Would Bob Do &lt;a &quot;https://www.lifeonline.com/gdshop/radio/view_video.asp?vid=042507 &quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; shows how to optimize your search engine marketing efforts.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_04_25.mp3" length="19713229" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Apple TV Analysis &amp; World Champion Gaming</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_04_18.mp3</link>
      <description>Our resident tech expert Charles &quot;I Love Steve Jobs&quot; Ludwick drops by to inform us as to whether Apple TV is worth a $400 HDMI cable and a new high-def TV.  Next, Johnathan &quot;Fatal1ty&quot; Wendel tells us how he was in the right place at the right time to become a professional gamer and industry-leading entrepreneur.  And in the Internet Files-why, if Sanjaya's American Idol run comes to an end, he can always model for our very own Christine Jones.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_04_18.mp3" length="22229811" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Sit on Justin's Head &amp; Pick Seth Godin's Brain</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_04_11.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that knows the difference between a Dip and the dreaded Cul-De-Sac.  Justin Kan of Justin.tv leads off the show--explaining how strapping a camera to his head 24/7 has impacted his love life. Next, author &amp; Web guru Seth Godin previews his forthcoming book The Dip . And in the Internet Files-why Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff is lobbying for mandatory body piercing in middle schools.  Plus, What Would Bob Do makes its video debut--solving an age-old Web site dilemma with a fresh, new approach.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_04_11.mp3" length="19188941" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>From Runways to Hellways to Lattes</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_04_04.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that struts down the catwalk in a tight tank top. First, Marisa Peck, Go Daddy Girl Scottsdale, hooks up with Bob to explain why growing up she played sports &amp; her brothers played with dolls. Next, &quot;Pacific Coast Hellway&quot; podcaster MYN discusses the success of his podcast &amp; tells why it's a good idea to have an empty Snapple® bottle on hand. And in the Internet Files--why so many domain registrars are up on the block. Our bonus video is part two of the hottest &lt;a href=http://www.lifeonline.com/gdshop/radio/view_video.asp?vid=040407 target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Go Daddy Girl contest&lt;/a&gt; yet!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  4 Apr 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_04_04.mp3" length="20342374" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Go Daddy Girl Daytona Beach, a New Format &amp; Scorching Video!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_03_28.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob debuts the new format with a show-stoppin interview with Go Daddy Girl Daytona Beach, Lara Haworth! This contest winner is never at a loss for words &amp; shows that she's attractive, smart &amp; funny -- the total package. Atty Jones drops in to offer insight into everything from a million $$$ laptop to the third -- and hopefully final -- round of the .XXX extension. And if you couldn't make it to the Go Daddy Girl Scottsdale contest, don't despair! We've been up all night so you don't miss one moment.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_03_28.mp3" length="19503514" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Our 1st videocast! New phone technology you can use &amp; productivity tips!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_03_21.mp3</link>
      <description>Another Go Daddy Girl contest &amp; Bob's BIG announcement! Attorney Jones drops in to discuss RegisterFly's options in view of its  decreditation -- and GrandCentral CEO Craig Walker talks about his new streamlined phone service that everyone can use.  Then, best-selling author  David Allen takes us to the happy place where great ideas are born.  Plus, why CEO blogs need to bring the hot sauce or not show up at all. BONUS:  Watch smoking hot footage from the Go Daddy Girl Daytona Beach contest!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_03_21.mp3" length="27472691" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Avoid RegisterFly®, make millions online, play golf</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_03_14.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the show that helps you become an online millionaire just so you can turn around and play golf every day.  First, Jeff Johnson joins the RegisterFly scandal discussion to shed light on the gender of those company personal escorts.  Then Bob has Scott Fox, author of &quot;Internet Riches,&quot; explain how you can dip your pan in the inviting waters of today's Internet gold rush.  Brett Darrow, GolfNow.com CEO, reveals how he's managed to sell $47 million of other people's golf tee time inventory.  And in the Internet Files-how push-ups are replacing online porn for China's Internet-addicted youth.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_03_14.mp3" length="28730982" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Roaring engines, Go Daddy Girls &amp; land-speed records, all live from Bike Week 2007!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_03_07.mp3</link>
      <description>This show's worth driving across country in a chopper for. Live from the Broken Spoke Saloon in the middle of Bike Week 2007, Go Daddy Girls Candice Michelle &amp; Valerie Thompson join Bob to talk wrestling, drag racing &amp; what it's like to be along for the ride when Go Daddy rolls.  The results are in and Go Daddy Girl - Daytona Beach - 2007 has been crowned. Lara may be from Cleveland but she can really heat things up. Did this Go Daddy Girl actually enter the contest on a whim? And, Jay Allen sits down to talk about his Broken Spoke Saloon and how he's going to break 200 MPH on his latest bike.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  7 Mar 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_03_07.mp3" length="17301504" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Today's Internet biz:  shoes, morals &amp; scandals!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_02_28.mp3</link>
      <description>It's a show about liposuction, shoes &amp; social responsibility.  Seriously, former RegisterFly® customer Jeff Johnson joins Bob to talk about the scandal that's rocking the beleaguered domain name registrar.  Then online shoe retailer Zappos.com® CEO Tony Hsieh and Bob have a meeting of the minds over the importance of customer experience while Nima picks out a pair of black pumps. Finally, Bob and DoTheRightThing.com co-founder Ryan Mickle talk about the tough choices facing businesses today.  And in the Internet Files--why the Grammar Girl is taking Eric Clapton to task.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_02_28.mp3" length="26528973" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>100 candles, Missy Suicide, Booth Colman &amp; Alex Albrecht</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_02_21.mp3</link>
      <description>It's our 100th show and we've saved you a piece of birthday cake.  SuicideGirls.com founder Missy lets us in on why a Suicide Girl is more than just tattoos and how burlesque is making a comeback, SG style.  Actor Booth Colman reminisces about his five-decade long career, including appearances in Go Daddy's infamous Super Bowl® ads.  He has high praise and even some advice for our own Go Daddy® Girl, Candice Michelle.  And special guest Alex Albrecht of Diggnation joins us for a birthday version of Internet Files to explain how Yahoo!® makes second best sound first rate.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_02_21.mp3" length="27367834" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>It's a Valentine's Day show filled with hot ratings and elite matchmaking.</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_02_14.mp3</link>
      <description>Our Valentine's Day show fans the flames of love so you don't have to.  James Hong, co-founder of HOTorNOT.com drops in to tell us why he'll risk tipping his cash cow to expand the HOTorNOT brand.  Margot Chavellier shares her secrets for pulling Silicon Valley 's elite executives out of the boardroom and into the arms of their perfect match.  And in the Internet Files-why Uncle Sam can't find his laptops.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_02_14.mp3" length="26843546" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A Critic, the Go Daddy® Chopper, &amp; Directing Web Traffic</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_02_07.mp3</link>
      <description>The Super Bowl® may be over, but Bob and Nima are still in Super Bowl form. Renowned ad critic Barbara Lippert &amp; Bob &quot;square off&quot; over the game's ads -- and hear why Go Daddy's ad can no longer be called &quot;the lowest of the low.&quot; Paul Teutul, Sr. of Orange County Chopper takes us behind the scenes of the Go Daddy chopper's unveiling at the oh-so-hot Maxim party and previews their next show featuring Candice Michelle. Then Brad Rinklin of Akamai has the skinny on which big game ads generated the most Web traffic. Finally, in the Internet Files--why is Steve Jobs taking on the music industry?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  7 Feb 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_02_07.mp3" length="27367834" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A Critic, Candice &amp; the Pre-Super Bowl® Go Daddy Bash!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_01_31.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob throws his own pre-Super Bowl party and you're invited. Hear AdWeek 's legendary commercial critic Barbara Lippert's honest review of this year's big ads. &quot;Go Daddy Girl&quot; Candice Michelle drops in-studio to explain how she broke her nose in the ring. Bob gets advice from Maxim Magazine's publisher on what to wear to their party in Miami. Plus in the Internet Files - how the Web is center stage at the Super Bowl.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_01_31.mp3" length="27367834" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Transforming TV &amp; Text-book Marketing</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_01_24.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob gets the scoop on how Sling Media' has leveraged the Web so you can watch TV from virtually anywhere. Also, an authority on the all-important topic of advertising walks us through the power of brand-marketing - Author George Belch, Ph.D. goes one-on-one with our own Super Bowl® &quot;Daddy.&quot;  In the Internet Files, how Yahoo® &quot;blew it,&quot; plus will anyone ever be able to surpass Google®?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_01_24.mp3" length="26738688" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bob poses his own questions to Ask Men and also gets important answers for Vets.</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_01_17.mp3</link>
      <description>AskMen.com's Editor-in-Chief explains how this &quot;GQ-style&quot; site has made it big where others have failed. With 5 million readers monthly, this formula is worth a listen for anyone looking for a spike in Web traffic. Plus, NEVBRC.org - we've all seen the stories of war vets returning home, on this program Bob chats with a CEO who helps military personnel transition back into civilian life.  Hear how the 'Net assists these aspiring business minds. In the Internet Files, Google® and Yahoo® duke it out on-the-go.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_01_17.mp3" length="26948403" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bob conquers cable with SuperBowl news!  Then zips through a crash course in speed reading too!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_01_10.mp3</link>
      <description>If ever a show was busting at the seams - it's this one!  Bob's back after last week's whirlwind coast-to-coast tour - boasting spots on CNBC and EXTRA!  After he settled in - he got dirty with HillClimb Media, sped through a lesson in speed reading with The Literacy Company, and even brought back Cameron Johnson for a another guest spot  Whew!  After this ride - everyone's gonna need some water and good night's sleep!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_01_10.mp3" length="28730982" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bob's back from The Big Apple, the Butler family, and entrepreneur Cameron Johnson!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_01_03.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob slid into town late after a long day in New York City!  After that - he dished out news on Go Daddy's role in the big game this February, then took time to sit with rock and roll father-daughter pair the Butler family!  Young entrepreneur Cameron Johnson rounded out the show - before Bob had to take off once again to L.A. What a day!  What a case of jetlag!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  3 Jan 2007 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2007_01_03.mp3" length="27892122" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Year in Review---Best of 2006</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_12_27.mp3</link>
      <description>It's a breakdown of the best bits from the past year!  Bob quarterbacks us through an entire year's worth of shows - from the craziest of guests, to the funkiest of Web sites and everything in between.  You're guaranteed to get your fill of the Internet world's most premiere people and ideas!  Plus, you get the kind of unique perspective only Bob and Nima can give!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_12_27.mp3" length="17511219" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Dawn and Drew get down, while we talk DVD's with Peerflix.com CEO Billy McNair</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_12_20.mp3</link>
      <description>If you thought Bob would send out this year with a bang - YOU WERE RIGHT!  Dawn and Drew dish on their ultra-trendy podcast - which has devout &quot;minions&quot; - stretching from the heartland to both coasts.  Meanwhile - Peerflix.com CEO Billy McNair keeps the vibe moving with his own revelation in online movie sharing.  Happy Holidays - and hang on for next year - if you can!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_12_20.mp3" length="28730982" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>ZeFrank gives us all he's got!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_12_13.mp3</link>
      <description>When all else fails - Bob delivers!  Bob took on ZeFrank for a whole hour - tackling all of the Internet funnyman's trademark material.  And when Bob sees what he likes - he takes control: stretching ZeFrank for a whole hour!  Toss in some sound business advice from Warren &quot;Wild Thing&quot; Adelman, you've got one heck of a platinum-plated show!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_12_13.mp3" length="27996979" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Danica Patrick, the OCC Guys, and Internet news galore!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_12_06.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob can't seem to slow down - even with the holidays near!  And who could, with sexy racing superstar Danica Patrick behind the microphone?  She's the newest GoDaddy girl!  And next up - the rough and tumble New Yawk fellas from Orange County Choppers!  From the east coast to the west coast, and all Internet points in between; no one's got the net covered like Bob Parsons and GoDaddy.com!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  6 Dec 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_12_06.mp3" length="29360128" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Goowy.com, LiveByCampus.com, and WWBD!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_11_29.mp3</link>
      <description>In this online entrepreneur's 'show of shows,' Bob talks with a 24-year-old who was recently named one of the nation's Top 25 Young Entrepreneurs - Eric Wu of LiveByCollege.com. Find out how he's working his online business and paying users who seek homes near campus.  Plus, Bob get &quot;Goowy&quot; with a guest who some say is blazing the future of the Internet by working to replace PC-based applications and files for Web interfaces. Also, Bob tells one listener how not having tons of cash can actually help his business.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_11_29.mp3" length="25480397" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Encore! Encore!....Meet Our New, RACY GoDaddy Girl -- Danica Patrick!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_11_22.mp3</link>
      <description>In this encore presentation of an up close and personal interview, Bob chats with racing star Danica Patrick. Find out how family supports her competitive spirit and why she's excited to become a Go Daddy Girl. Danica tells Bob  she's &quot;sick of not winning&quot; and pledges her new team will make the difference. Go Daddy Girl Candice Michelle joins Bob in studio to talk about her &quot;racy,&quot; soon-to-be Go Daddy colleague.  Plus, hear about Candice's 'cover girl' status and we're not talking Playboy (R).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_11_22.mp3" length="17091789" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bob talks with Blogger Robert Scoble and MyPleasure.com</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_11_15.mp3</link>
      <description>In an Internet-extravaganza, Bob talks with &quot;blogger legend&quot; Robert Scoble about telling it like it is and how that concept helped him get his first big break.  The former Microsoft® technical evangelist tells all about his experiences back then and his current adventures in video podcasting.  Plus, the Internet's largest seller of adult bedroom toys, MyPleasure.com tells us why education is the key to its success. In this week's Internet Files (TM), engaging and varying opinions about the future of video on the Internet with Attorney Jones, Robert Scoble and a &quot;surprise guest.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_11_15.mp3" length="27787264" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Geek Brief TV's Rising Star, Tracking Users at comScore and &quot;The Break Up Song&quot;</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_11_08.mp3</link>
      <description>Geek Brief TV &quot;fearless leader&quot; Cali Lewis is in studio telling Bob how she was able to quit the &quot;tyranny of the day job&quot; to become a full-time podcaster. She's got 15 million regular downloads and some major corporate sponsors footing the bills. Find out how she developed the show and where she wants to take the Geek Intelligence Network. Plus, comScore Network&amp;reg; Chairman Gian Fulgoni details the new frontiers on the Web - and why video is only beginning to take hold. Should advertisers view 'net traffic data with suspicion? In Strange Domains -- hear Bob's very own &quot;break up song.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  8 Nov 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_11_08.mp3" length="28521267" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Beers with Diggnation, Confronting a Busty Ad Critic and What Yahoo Does</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_11_01.mp3</link>
      <description>Kevin Rose &amp; Alex Albrecht toss back beers with Bob and talk about the rise of Internet video &amp; why vidcasts will become the 'minor leagues' for network TV. Find out why Kevin is deflecting Digg.com acquisition offers - interested more in having fun with his project of passion. Then, Bob goes one-on-one with the publisher of a snippy advertising site. Steve Hall tells Bob that the new Go Daddy ads have too much fake boob. Bob gets him to back down -- and updates us about future Super Bowl spots! Plus, What Would Bob Do, Strange Domains and lots of uncensored fun with Kevin, Alex and Nima.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  1 Nov 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_11_01.mp3" length="28835840" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bob's Talks With French Maids &amp; a Fanny Artist</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_10_25.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob tackles asinine art and knavish maids - oh la, la! First up is French Maid TV! Bob finds out why their advertising strategy is so very hot &amp; how viral marketing is developing into mainstream business. From there, Bob contains his laughter long enough to chat with Butt Print Artist Stan Murmur. Learn how video helped Stan's fabulous fanny art gain fame! Find out which of Stan's &quot;brushes&quot; extend painting costs. And in The Internet Files, our own Atty. Jones and Bob discuss Go Daddy's fight on behalf of Internet users when it comes to ICANN, Congress &amp; the proposed .com agreement.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_10_25.mp3" length="26948403" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bob's Back from Zimbabwe with Tales of Lions, Skeeters &amp; Flies</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_10_18.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob's back from Zimbabwe - with stories of lions, mosquitoes &amp; tsetse flies. Find out about his 21-day safari &amp; why he's still popping anti-malaria pills. Bob talks with the man behind PageMaker&amp;reg; &amp; Visio&amp;reg;. He tells Bob about world-changing innovations and how acquisitions encouraged a new venture. Then, the president of Zipcar&amp;reg; gets quizzed by Bob about neighborhood cars. In Strange Domains, Bob talks about BugsGoneWild.com - these creepy crawlies will kill you, even out of Africa! And in The Internet Files, Bob reviews the latest industry news - and talks more about life in Zimbabwe.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_10_18.mp3" length="26528973" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Big Bucks in Gaming, Guessing -- Not Betting -- on Sports and Bob's Tips</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_10_11.mp3</link>
      <description>Consumers spend $8 billion annually on video games. The founder of GameFly.com talks about gamers and how businesses can tap into this huge market. Gamers aren't who you might expect -- girls and adults are playing more than ever. And from gamers to games -- we hear from the founder of PicksPal.com about why his customers are paying to get advice on who will win the big game. For fun, bragging rights or other &quot;endeavors,&quot; we hear how this site is reaching men by connecting sports and ego. Plus, Bob helps a landscaper mow down competitors through superior service, in What Would Bob Do.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_10_11.mp3" length="17616077" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Business of Blogging, How Charity Helps Companies and Media Accuracy</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_10_04.mp3</link>
      <description>Find out how a CEO blog can help your company connect with customers - and fend off bad PR. The founder of the Blog Business Summit tells us why companies should focus on providing a &quot;customer benefit&quot; via a blog. Charity can help businesses - and not just at tax time. The executive director of CharityNavigator.com talks about the benefits of entrepreneurs supporting nonprofits and how charities can be vetted for financial prudence. In Strange Domains, we find out about a man tracking the errors of the world's media at RegretTheError.com. Plus: Best of the Blog and a classic What Would Bob Do.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  4 Oct 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_10_04.mp3" length="16777216" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Become.com's Bargain Hunt, Filling Up with GasBuddy and Big Blog Bucks</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_09_27.mp3</link>
      <description>Become.com has created a new way to help shoppers research, find and buy both online and in local stores. Hear how a veteran entrepreneur shunned retirement to launch this new venture and why every online business should be looking beyond English-speaking markets. At Federated Media' they're working to make blogging pay. Find out why companies are bravely entering blog advertising and what makes a blog attractive to marketers. In Strange Domains, GasBuddy helps you get a good deal at the pump. Plus: Best of the Blog and What Would Bob Do. Bob's office furniture isn't what you might expect.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_09_27.mp3" length="16672358" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>CafePress.com, DeadSpin.com and Bob in the Arctic</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_09_20.mp3</link>
      <description>Weathering the dot-com bust by being careful with cash, the serial entrepreneurs at CafePress.com®  have created a successful business producing creative products for innovators. Find out this CEO's tips for starting a new business and learn which match he wants to see in the upcoming presidential election. The editor of DeadSpin.com tells us how NOT being connected to the world of sports gives this Gawker Media site more credibility with readers. Plus, hear about Bob's adventure in the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge. Thinking of heading to the frozen north for a trek - then tune in to Bob!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_09_20.mp3" length="22963814" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Meet Our New, RACY GoDaddy Girl -- Danica Patrick!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_09_13.mp3</link>
      <description>In an up close and personal interview, Bob chats with racing star Danica Patrick. Find out how family supports her competitive spirit and why she is excited to become a Go Daddy Girl. Danica tells Bob that she's &quot;sick of not winning&quot; and pledges that her new team will make the difference. In the Internet Files' -- Bob, Rachel Storm, Candice Michelle and &quot;Thumbs&quot; Adelman talk about Go Daddy's new sponsorship of Danica, their latest projects and update you on news affecting the Internet industry. Hear about Candice's upcoming photo spread and why Bob wants the U.S. to retain control over ICANN.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_09_13.mp3" length="27472691" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Evangelism with Guy Kawasaki, Don't Date Him Girl and Domain Trends</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_09_06.mp3</link>
      <description>From Apple® evangelist to author, Guy Kawasaki talks about how entrepreneurs can get ahead. Learn about &quot;The Art of the Start&quot; and tips for making winning VC pitches. Plus, Tasha Joseph has turned tales of bad dates into a thriving business with DontDateHimGirl.com. Find out how she has cultivated a fan base, why online romance is so popular and how she protects her business from legal challenges. And in the Internet Files' -- Bob and &quot;Thumbs&quot; Adelman delve into the latest domain industry trends. Did you know 70% of people online don't speak English?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  6 Sep 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_09_06.mp3" length="26528973" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Biz Ads with ValueClick, Blackboard's Learning Revolution  and Bob on Skates</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_08_30.mp3</link>
      <description>Elusive online customers get snagged by ValueClick&amp;reg Media's advertisements. Hear how businesses can attract visitors and generate sales through impactful online ads - without going broke or using adware. Plus: They get hit with criticism for it, but Blackboard&amp;reg is aggressive about protecting its future by filing patents. Find out how high-tech learning is sold to low-tech educators and why e-learning is fueling changes in education. In this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do,&quot; Bob helps a skate-master create a customer-targeted Web site. And we learn about Bob's own &quot;experience&quot; on in-line skates.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_08_30.mp3" length="16777216" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>BlueNile.com, RateMyTeachers.com ... and What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_08_23.mp3</link>
      <description>When a ring shopper got frustrated, he created a successful new venture selling jewelry on the Internet with BlueNile.com. Find out how customers - and investors - respond to gem sales online and why competitors are so angry with Blue Nile. Plus: Students and parents get an opportunity to grade educators. RateMyTeachers.com has received its share of criticism, but the site is generating positive returns for its founders based on strong interest from advertisers. In this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do,&quot; Bob recommends strategies for an entrepreneur to launch a new business Web site.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_08_23.mp3" length="16777216" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>James Altucher, Indeed.com, Warren Adelman....What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_08_16.mp3</link>
      <description>Financial writer James Altucher discusses the tech market, the IPO process and what most Wall Street writers don't tell you. Plus: Learn how Indeed® took an idea, developed a unique service &amp; turned it into the leading search engine for open jobs. Hear Bob's view on all the current Go Daddy IPO media attention. And during the Podcast, Warren Adelman, President of Go Daddy, joins Bob to talk about the latest news concerning acquisitions of domain name registrars. Finally, in this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do,&quot; Bob advises an entrepreneur on navigating a joint venture.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_08_16.mp3" length="27996979" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>ShieldZone.com, Dogster.com...and What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_08_02.mp3</link>
      <description>The quest to protect the face of a wrist watch led an entrepreneur on a search for solutions. Learn how Shield-Zone perfected a military-grade film for consumers and took advantage of an emerging market aimed at protecting handheld devices. Plus: Is the Internet &quot;going to the dogs?&quot; An entrepreneur looking for untapped markets found it with Dogster.com. Hear how this successful innovator focused on a user base, integrated advertising within the site and controlled costs to build a profitable start-up. In this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do,&quot; Bob helps a listener deal with seasonal sales declines.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  2 Aug 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_08_02.mp3" length="16777216" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Oasysmobile.com, Mominventors.com and ...What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_07_26.mp3</link>
      <description>With a new generation of Web-enabled mobile devices, it's important to backup portable data.  Oasysmobile' provides the personalization of the Web and the immediacy of cell phones to help people make their mobile phones part of their lives.  Hear how this company's innovation created a crossover between mobile devices and the Web. Plus: the best products don't always come from big companies.  A mother's personal struggle to find resources led her to launch a successful online business -- and she ended up launching a whole new movement and group of fledgling entrepreneurs, too!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_07_26.mp3" length="16882074" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Lowermybills.com, FilmLoop.com..What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_07_19.mp3</link>
      <description>There is a glut of financial information on the Web but not everything is good for the bottom line. Lowermybills.com helps boost your financial standing without sacrificing time or energy. Learn how this company generates revenue by working as a liaison to service providers. Plus: The opportunities posed by the digital-camera boom minted a new generation of entrepreneurs. FilmLoop.com's entrepreneurs developed a new technology, leading to partnerships and investor attention. And in this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do,&quot; Bob advises a listener on the difference between domain extensions.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_07_19.mp3" length="16777216" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Answers.com, MyYearbook.com and ... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_07_12.mp3</link>
      <description>It doesn't consider Google a competitor, but Answers.com is in the business of helping users organize the data-clogged Internet. Learn how this acclaimed site successfully transitioned its business focus, launched an IPO and generates strong returns from ads. Plus: When a brother-and-sister team grew tired of low-tech school yearbooks, they developed the newest social networking rage. Find out how they attracted a million users with an aim to overtake MySpace. And in this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do,&quot; an entrepreneur seeks Bob's guidance in marketing a product that customers seem slow to accept.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_07_12.mp3" length="16672358" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Roommates.com, DippinDots.com and ... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_07_05.mp3</link>
      <description>When a pair of brothers wanted a small business to generate extra cash, Roommates.com was born. Since its 2001 launch, the site has become the leading roommate-matching service on the Web. As the business gained momentum, it devoured competitors and is now funding other ventures. Also: DippinDots.com is the story of an old family recipe being brought into the space age. Learn how a scientist's hobby developed into an innovative product and a fast-growing international franchise. And in this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do,&quot; Bob helps a listener tackle troubles with a free-spending business partner.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  5 Jul 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_07_05.mp3" length="16777216" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>I-SoldIt.com, Proof Point, Inc. and ... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_06_28.mp3</link>
      <description>Bridging the innovation of online auctions with traditional storefronts, I-SoldIt.com has become one of the top franchise opportunities for entrepreneurs. Learn how business experience nurtured this new idea. And when a group of Silicon Valley entrepreneurs joined forces to create Proof Point, they did so to create new solutions to combat the increasing number of cyber threats facing business leaders today. Finally, in this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do,&quot; a listener asks how to go about advertising during the Super Bowl®. Does Bob think it's a touchdown or fumble for this start-up?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_06_28.mp3" length="16777216" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>PriceGrabber.com, Kayak.com and ... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_06_21.mp3</link>
      <description>Helping 21 million customers review and research products, PriceGrabber.com has created a successful venture serving as a portal between merchants and shoppers. Hear how these entrepreneurs generate revenue helping large and small businesses connect with customers. At Kayak.com, travelers are staying ahead of increasing costs with powerful tools to search for good deals. Formed by online-travel veterans, learn how revenues are generated through advertising and referral fees - not commissions. In this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do,&quot; find out how to reach a specific customer segment via the Web.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_06_21.mp3" length="16882074" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>AbeBooks.com®, StuffBak.com and ... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_06_14.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the Web's largest bookstore without any books. AbeBooks.com specializes in new, used, hard-to-find and rare volumes. Hear how this retailer draws customers and generates revenue acting as a bibliophile middleman. And discover how one firm is making money from your lost items. StuffBak.com provides hope for our misplaced gadgets - and the data they contain. Learn how they have become an online market leader. In this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do,&quot; find out if picking up and relocating to a larger market is the key to spurring business growth.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_06_14.mp3" length="53477376" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>HowStuffWorks.com, HealthGrades.com and  What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_06_07.mp3</link>
      <description>From ice cream to fireworks, HowStuffWorks.com gives an inside look into how most everything functions. Learn how a passion to understand turned into a successful business venture. And before you schedule your next doctor visit, check out HealthGrades.com. This site is a source of reviews on doctors, hospitals and competitive prices for common medical procedures. Find out how they collect reviews, draw customers and create revenue. In this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do,&quot; find out if taking on investors is a wise business move - or whether a loan is your best bet.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  7 Jun 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_06_07.mp3" length="17511219" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Classmates!, AAA.com ... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_05_31.mp3</link>
      <description>Do you ever wonder what happened to your high school friends? Or the girl you were too shy to ask to senior prom? Reconnect with your past at Classmates.com. Discover how they became one of the most popular subscription-based sites on the Web. Also, learn the value of customer service in your business from AAA.com, a simple premise turned into a one-stop resource for travel. Find out about our rising fuel prices and how to maximize your summer adventures. In this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do&quot; segment, Bob gives advice for entrepreneurs on Web site building when entering a high potential market.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_05_31.mp3" length="16672358" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Woot.com!, Alcor.org and ... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_05_24.mp3</link>
      <description>Woot.com is a modern Internet success story, with tens of thousands of subscribers. Yet Woot® doesn't advertise and has just a few dedicated employees. Find out the secret behind Woot's entrepreneurial triumph. Also, Alcor® Life Extension Foundation is selling a shot at immortality. Find out how their Web site clears up myths about cryonics and brings them clients. In this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do&quot; segment, Bob weighs in on whether Better Business Bureau® or Chamber of Commerce memberships help generate online business.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_05_24.mp3" length="17616077" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Zillow.com!, Fark.com andsavvy Internet marketing tips!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_05_17.mp3</link>
      <description>Using the latest satellite imagery to shop for your next home! Obtain estimates; get a &quot;birds-eye&quot; view of the property AND save time otherwise spent driving around with a realtor at Zillow.com! Also FARK®, a four-lettered word for weird news --- it's strangely addictive and a nice break from the daily grind! Fark.com delivers humor - while mainstream media provides the source. Plus! Back by popular demand, Rachel brings a STORM of savvy Internet marketing tips - use pay per clicks and the power of real-time advertising to maximize your budget!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_05_17.mp3" length="16672358" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Netflix.com!, Wikipedia.com, LegendaryGuns.com and...What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_05_10.mp3</link>
      <description>Netflix has the answer to traditional DVD rentals - millions use the online service and save time doing it. Find out what made this idea so successful? Also, an online Encyclopedia FOR the people AND by the people - hear how you can help contribute to Wikipedia. Plus, go &quot;Back to the Future&quot; with LegendaryGuns.com -- antique firearm sales online! This gun store fires a bull's eye in cyberspace. In this week's &quot;What Would Bob Do&quot; segment, learn why getting seasonal with your Website pays dividends and how looking closely at all areas of your business is best.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_05_10.mp3" length="28311552" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>YES @ Yale!, MotherEarthNews.com, AirTroductions.com and ... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_05_03.mp3</link>
      <description>Only have a few minutes to impress a captive CEO? Hear the winning &quot;Elevator Pitch&quot; from Yale's Entrepreneurial Society®! Also, learn about hybrids and saving money without sacrificing the environment or your lifestyle -- Mother Earth News® shows us how. Then we take to the skies with AirTroductionsT -- whether finding romance or networking, it's a great way to make the most out of uncomfortable airplane seats and stale air. Plus, when to spend money on search engine placement and why failure can lead to success-- Bob answers more questions!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  3 May 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_05_03.mp3" length="28311552" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>FTVLive! CARFAX.com, NeverDie.com and ... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_04_26.mp3</link>
      <description>What happens when reporters want the inside scoop about their own industry BEFORE anyone else? They to go FTVLive! Find out how this labor of love translated into money for one intrepid newscaster. Then, fire, flood, theft and car accidents - do YOU know what your car has experienced? Find out the &quot;real deal&quot; on any used vehicle before you make the purchase, we take a ride with CARFAX. And, how to make &quot;real&quot; money in the virtual world of Neverdie.com. Bob talks about re-investing your profits and taking a business with curb appeal global!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_04_26.mp3" length="27682406" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>JibJab parodies!  GoldenPalace.com, Zunafish and ... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_04_19.mp3</link>
      <description>Take two brothers, one an MBA, the other an animator... mix in some political humor, sprinkle on some parodies -- it's all a recipe for JibJab! What caused this sensation?  Who bought William Shatner's kidney stone and why?  We enter the exciting world of online gambling with the one and only GoldenPalace.com!  Finally, everyone likes a great trade.  There is a home for your old CD collection and it's called Zunafish!  Bob gives advice on the merits of owning a business vs. sharing it with others.  Finally, &quot;should I stay or should I go&quot;...the benefit of staying outside your comfort zone!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_04_19.mp3" length="28521267" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Web cameras! Multiply.com, the Smoking Gun and ... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_04_12.mp3</link>
      <description>Who has 'The Smoking Gun®?&quot; - we do! Hear the true story behind those revealing celebrity news stories. Then travel around the world in 'real time&quot; from the comfort of your favorite chair - the popularity of web cams allows you to see events 1st-hand. And start multiplying your relationships online - with a safer way to share photos, videos &amp; more w/family &amp; friends! Have a great site but limited budget? Bob gives advice on how measuring the small things everyday can lead to great success. Finally, the ultimate question -- balancing a passion for work &amp; family without compromise!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_04_12.mp3" length="27682406" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Girls Gone Wild! Blog Marketing, the Sock Clip and... What Would Bob Do?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_04_05.mp3</link>
      <description>Learn online &quot;secrets&quot; to marketing your inventions and products and head to the beach with Girls Gone Wild(R) it's more than just a wild site -- it's an example of marketing genius! Then learn why you should write a business blog for fun &amp; profit! And did you know that Bob's &quot;right hand&quot; man is a woman! Barb and Bob talk about their decades working together and why never quitting - even in the face of failure - can make you a winner! Finally, get great biz tips in our segment &quot;What Would Bob Do?&quot; Bob offers his advice to listeners. Find out how to pose your question!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  5 Apr 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_04_05.mp3" length="35756442" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Life Online! Perverted-Justice.com, Slivercasting and... the Internet-Only Podcast!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_03_29.mp3</link>
      <description>Finally, the answer to last week's BIG announcement! It's the premier of our new show, w/a new look, new format &amp; more high-energy discussion by the one &amp; only Bob Parsons. We'll ride along w/heroes who patrol the 'net to catch sexual predators. Then we transition to Slivercasting, unique programs you can't get on cable or satellite, with Daily Pike --stand-up comedian &amp; creator of Yuks.tv. Finally, learn how to make a Podcast for fun AND profit w/Ron Bloom, co-founder of Podshow.com. Learn how to turn $10 in raw materials into 15 minutes of fame &amp; $15k profit!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_03_29.mp3" length="27682406" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>WE MADE IT!  RADIO GO DADDY'S 1 YEAR ANNIVERSARY!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_03_22.mp3</link>
      <description>Time flies when you're having fun!  We've been on the air for 1 year!  To celebrate, Bob makes a BIG announcement!  In tonight's lineup, Dr. Paula Domenici talks candidly about Post Traumatic Stress Disorder and her new book 'Courage After Fire.&quot;  Then CNN's Jacki Schechner joins Bob to discuss Internet reporting, blogs as sources, separating fact from fiction -- and what it's like to be called a 'blog chick.&quot;  And the podcast features Adam Lovell, who runs a pen-pal service for inmates - you'll be surprised by what he has to say!  Finally, aliens are abducting cows from a pasture near you!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_03_22.mp3" length="27682406" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Anonymous Forum Posting, Overnight Internet Stardom, Risky Business &amp; IE7!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_03_15.mp3</link>
      <description>A N.J. legislator thinks 'net should be a 'civil&quot; place - so he wants to ban anonymous forum posting!  Could this initiative take hold?  And forget about Hollywood or the footlights of Broadway if you want to be a star - look to the Internet instead!  Hear the true story of David Lehre, the hottest filmmaker on the 'net!  But if stardom isn't for you and you want to be a business mogul, then stay tuned as Bob &amp; Dr. Donald Wehrung of the Univ. of Brit. Columbia discuss risky business decisions!  Finally, learn about the exciting new changes coming your way soon with IE7!  Plus, wild Weird News!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_03_15.mp3" length="27472691" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Super Bowl wrap-up, more on ICANN's .COM decision &amp; entrepreneurship at its finest!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_03_08.mp3</link>
      <description>It's Show # 50!  Bob reads the final Super Bowl stats &amp; Candice calls-in live from NY! Then Bruce Schneier, a leading Internet CTO, fills us in on mock cyber attacks! Well, it's a week later -- do we know anymore about the bizarre approval of the .COM Registry Agreement?  Attorney Jones tries to decipher recent statements by ICANN Board Members.  Does she succeed? For the 1/2 podcast, Bob goes one-on-one with in-studio guests Rich &amp; Jeff Sloan of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.startupnation.com&quot;&gt;www.startupnation.com&lt;/a&gt; - leading entrepreneurs and authors who tell us exactly how to start a business!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  8 Mar 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_03_08.mp3" length="26528973" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>All things ICANN.  Find out all the details of the raw deal that went down with ICANN and VeriSign.  Plus all you need to know about Credit Cards shopping for your Cyber Store and our usual features.</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_03_01.mp3</link>
      <description>ICANN and You Can't.  A new agreement has been reached with ICANN and VeriSign that rocked the .COM world.  The GoDaddy brain trust is in the studio to spell it out.  It takes the whole show and the Best of the Blog. Think you're not affected? Think again.  The Extended Podcast looks at all that you need to know to add credit card shopping privileges to your cyber store.  Strange Domains and Weird News round out the festivities for Show #49 of Radio Go Daddy.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  1 Mar 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_03_01.mp3" length="26214400" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Online Privacy; US Companies fighting freedom in China; Your Car as iPod(r) accessory</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_02_22.mp3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;How private is your private online life?&lt;/b&gt; Not Very! Hear Bob talk with &lt;b&gt;Dr. Sandy Askland &lt;/b&gt;from &lt;b&gt;ASU's College of Law&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;b&gt;Lucie Morillon &lt;/b&gt;from &lt;b&gt;Reporters with out Borders &lt;/b&gt;just testified before Congress about US companies helping to squelch freedom in China-an international disgrace. Lucy joins Bob in the second half. Finally in our extended Podcast a rowdy time with &lt;b&gt;Edmunds. COM&lt;/b&gt;'s Road Test Editor, &lt;b&gt;Brian Mooney &lt;/b&gt;talking car 'tech' and more! Great Weird news, new production elements in Strange Domains and more!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_02_22.mp3" length="23907533" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bad news from ICANN. Plus Paid For Email! &amp; Mega issue if you take credit cards online and more!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_02_15.mp3</link>
      <description>The price of domain registration just may be going up.  Go Daddy is not letting this happen without a fight.  The fireworks start with our guest, Tim Ruiz.  Goodmail Systems bypass all your spam filters and deliver bulk email to your mailbox.  Is free email coming to an end?  Our guest is the President of Goodmail and makes his case with Bob and David double teaming him with questions.  A MEGA security issue you MUST know about if you take credit cards online you MUST be PCI compliant or face the consequences.  Plus strange domains, best of the blog, wierd news and all the madness you know and love Radio Go Daddy for.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_02_15.mp3" length="27892122" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Last Word on Super Bowl® XL - plus some new words on VD!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_02_08.mp3</link>
      <description>Well, Super Bowl® Sunday came and went - so what's the final verdict?  Bob &amp; company examine the results and whether it was worth it!  And hear from Booth Coleman - Candice's 'foil' in the ad!  Then Bob gets serious about VD - that's Valentine's Day folks..with a most unusual set of 'dos and don'ts' that we bet you've never heard anywhere else.  Of course, if those fail, James Hong will tell you how to save yourself at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.savemyass.com&quot;&gt;www.savemyass.com&lt;/a&gt;.  If things are really bad, you can always sign up for 'the list to go.&quot;  Finally, learn about newsgroups and forums!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  8 Feb 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_02_08.mp3" length="27367834" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A jam-packed show! The news conference! Down to the wire on our Super Bowl® ad! Candice is here!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_02_01.mp3</link>
      <description>Could the anticipation be any greater w/4 days until the Big Game? At air time, there was no approval - but then, no rejection, either! Bob brings us all up to date on the very latest. And CANDICE is in-studio! Atty Jones drops in to explain the different content standards that apply to commercials vs. TV shows. Then our own LisaAnn tells how to find out what's being said about your business online - you MUST know! And check out the rough cuts that didn't get approved. Oh, Bob has a &quot;Saxon moment&quot; in honor of Warren!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  1 Feb 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_02_01.mp3" length="27053261" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The clock is ticking on Go Daddy's Super Bowl® ad - will we be benched or be in the starting line-up?</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_01_25.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob updates us on the media frenzy surrounding the status of our commercial - and Totally Traci reviews 'Window Washer!&quot;  Fred Marshall returns to dedicate a special 'camkaraoke&quot; song to Bob - who then tracks down Marc Rhatigan, the creative force behind Go Daddy's commercials.  Marc &amp; Bob discuss the growing trend of 'internet-only ads&quot; and exactly how many times Candice was raised and lowered on the scaffold!  Finally, Attorney Jones drops in for a riveting legal discourse - why DOES Google cooperate with China, but not the U.S.? Why would anyone sell sex.com for a mere $12 million?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_01_25.mp3" length="27577549" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A Big Game revelation! Men, women and the 'net - plus, the King of Internet karaoke!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_01_18.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob leaks a new Super Bowl revelation -- we don't dare print it here!  And, 'Men are from Google, Women are from Yahoo&quot; - according to Deb Fallows, senior research fellow at The Pew Internet Project.  Learn how men are more 'intense&quot; about their Internet usage than women - and other online differences between the sexes!  Finally, the illustrious Fred Marshall, the King of CamKaraoke, performs 'Your Love&quot; - LIVE!   If you can't get enough of Fred don't worry - he'll be back next week!  Thumbs Adelman gives the low-down on TiVo.  Plus, coffee beans processed in a most unusual way...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_01_18.mp3" length="27262976" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Online confessions, an update on our Super Bowl commercial, &amp; viewing the Big Game in Hi-Def!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_01_11.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob interviews NY Times' Best Selling Author, Frank Warren, the guiding force behind &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.postsecret.com&quot;&gt;postsecret.com&lt;/a&gt; -- a thought-provoking site showcasing individuals' anonymous - and deepest secrets.  Then it's Super Bowl update time - with special guest Dr. John Craft (Walter Cronkite School of Journalism) discussing Go Daddy's ad approval dilemma.  And, hear about Bob's upcoming appearance on CNBC's Squawk Box! Finally, Wayne Thayer clears up all the confusion about the latest TV technology, and explains the best way to watch the Big Game in Hi-Def!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_01_11.mp3" length="26738688" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A new year! A new show! Non-English Domains, the invasion of Fallujah &amp; Bob's BIG ad news!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_01_04.mp3</link>
      <description>We're off to a rockin' start!  Tim Ruiz explains the ruckus over non-English domains.  Think this isn't a big deal?  Well, think again - hear why the repercussions are huge.  Bob interviews USMC Reservist Charles Fletcher, who was on the ground when the Marines pushed into Fallujah.  Hear about it from someone who lived it!  Then Bob breaks BIG news about Go Daddy's ad during the upcoming NFC Wildcard game!  Atty Jones concludes her Legal 101 seminar on issues you need to know about if you're on the web - including copyright &amp; trademark!  Finally, we end w/a 'mooving&quot; story - and a blowhole</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  4 Jan 2006 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2006_01_04.mp3" length="26843546" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Our 40th show! Defective TREOs, technology &amp; sports, a key Internet arrest &amp; effective newsletters!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_12_28.mp3</link>
      <description>It's the end of the year &amp; our 40th show to boot! Find out how some California folks are suing the makers of the Treo 650, claiming it's defective. Is a class action suit on the horizon? Then sports mogul Jerry Colangelo, former owner of several AZ professional sports teams, discusses technology &amp; sports. And Attorney Jones drops in to discuss the arrest of the 'net's 'most wanted' domain hijacker - the fugitive who stole sex.com is a fugitive no more! Finally, Rachel Storm tells listeners how to create an effective newsletter that drives business to a web site. And, there's camkaraoke!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_12_28.mp3" length="26948403" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Go Daddy Year in Review! Radio Go Daddy Highlights! The Best of the Best!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_12_21.mp3</link>
      <description>The Radio Go Daddy team takes a look back at 2005.  Hard to believe all that happened this year - so listen as Bob (together with Barb Rechterman, his 'true&quot; side-kick for 20+ years) relives an extraordinary 12 months - from his blog, to the Super Bowl commercial, to the launch of Radio Go Daddy.  We also have clips from the VERY BEST Radio Go Daddy shows, including our humble beginnings.  Bob announces the Top 10 Strange Domains &amp; Weird News Stories for 2005.  And our Legal 101 seminar w/Atty Jones starts with good intentions, but soon strays off course.  Oh well, it's the holidays, right?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_12_21.mp3" length="27472691" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>'Merry Christmas&quot; vs. 'Happy Holidays.&quot;  Honesty pays! Lying online could land you in court!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_12_14.mp3</link>
      <description>The Radio Go Daddy team tackles the 'Merry Christmas' vs. 'Happy Holidays' debate.   Even America's toughest Sheriff -- Joe Arpaio -- gets in on the act, telling us how he's handling the holidays in AZ jails.  Herb Vest, CEO of True.com, returns to discuss his Federal Court lawsuit against a customer who lied about his criminal background.   This isn't a frivolous lawsuit - Herb's serious &amp; looking for justice.  Then email guru Dave Koopman returns to the podcast - but this time to 'demystify' hosting.  We've also got a cell phone for your dog, African spells &amp;, Santas taking NY by storm!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_12_14.mp3" length="27787264" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Internet addicts &amp; a female erotica entrepreneur! Plus, an ICANN update &amp; SSL Primer!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_12_07.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob dives into the problem of Internet addiction with Paul Gallant, an expert in behavioral disorders.  No, it's not a joke, and yes, it's a very real problem.  Find out who's at risk.  Then Bob showcases a leading multimedia entrepreneur in couples' erotica - Candida Royalle -- a woman who has made it in the adult industry on her own terms.  Then Tim Ruiz checks in with the latest update on ICANN and .XXX domains.  And because you asked for it -- Bob &amp; Thumbs Adelman provide a primer on SSL certificates!  Of course, there's Best of the Blog, Strange Domains &amp; Weird News!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  7 Dec 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_12_07.mp3" length="26319258" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A Dutch plan to overhaul the 'net, Candice talks about Playboy &amp; a guest bails before air time!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_11_30.mp3</link>
      <description>A packed show! Warren calls in from Vancouver to update us on a Dutch plan to overhaul the Internet .  Candice Michelle calls in from LA the night before her Playboy photo shoot - w/breaking news that she'll grace the COVER of this legendary magazine.  Our 3rd guest doesn't call in from anywhere - b/c she backed out minutes before air time!  Find out why! (And yes, we covered the story without her!) Discover the advantages of personalized email from our very own email guru!  Finally, there are shopping carts, sweaters knitted from dog hair, &amp; sneakers for crossing the border!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_11_30.mp3" length="27996979" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Radio Go Daddy is LIVE from NY! From Marines to the Penthouse Executive Club to Black Friday!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_11_23.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob takes to the road, reading a 'Top 10' list of what he's thankful for (other than family, friends &amp; health). Major Dave Andersen, USMC, Public Affairs, drops in to discuss his extraordinary career, from combat to 9/11 recovery efforts to how to embed 600+ media in Iraq.  Then Bob discusses his trip to The Penthouse Executive Club, NYC's premier gentlemen's club.  The club's manager  -- and Entertainers Farrah &amp; Avery stop by for a hot interview.  Plus, smokin' holiday product reviews of  the Video iPod &amp; Xbox 360!  And learn where to find the best Black Friday shopping deals on the 'net!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_11_23.mp3" length="27787264" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Breaking Internet News, 'PayPal 101' &amp; LIVE interviews from Afghanistan and Qatar!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_11_16.mp3</link>
      <description>It's been decided -- the U.S. will retain control over the Internet! Learn WHY this is important &amp; whether the battle is truly over.  Then Jason Miner of PayPal provides a 'PayPal 101' tutorial -- and yes -- consumers &amp; merchants ARE safe using PayPal!  The wonders of modern technology allow Bob to speak LIVE with our military in Afghanistan &amp; Qatar about medical miracles for Afghani citizens.  And during the podcast, Bob offers sage advice on optimizing your website &amp; improving search engine rankings! Oh yes, there's a drunk moose, a giant penguin, a love-sick giraffe &amp; the iBuzz!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_11_16.mp3" length="28101837" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Happy Birthday USMC! America's toughest sheriff! Totally Traci LIVE in-studio!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_11_09.mp3</link>
      <description>WHOA!  Can you believe this show? Bob previews Go Daddy's annual e-Card celebrating the US Marine Corps' 230th birthday! Then it's on to discuss various aspects of 'crime &amp; punishment' with America's Toughest Sheriff - Arizona's own Joe Arpaio.  Hear what Sheriff Joe has to say about Tent City, Chain Gangs, his Posse, &amp; feeding inmates on a mere $.15/day.  (Yes, 15 cents a day!)  And best of all, the Radio Go Daddy staff surprises Bob with an in-house LIVE visit by Totally Traci!  (Yes, we took pictures &amp; we plan to post them).  Finally, there's your life in dog years &amp; people against milk!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  9 Nov 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_11_09.mp3" length="28101837" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Viva Las Vegas w/Mayor Goodman! Also, Blackberry Thumb, NFL technology &amp; maximizing online ad $$$!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_11_02.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob leads off discussing 'Blackberry Thumb&quot; with Warren 'Thumbs' Adelman.  Find out if your email &amp; text messaging addiction will lead to medical woes! Then Las Vegas Mayor Oscar Goodman calls in to tell Bob the latest 'Sin City' happenings!  Learn about 'what happens in Vegas, stays in Vegas&quot;, the future of topless dancing in casinos &amp; more!  And Mark Feller, IT Director for the AZ Cardinals, discusses how NFL teams use technology to prepare for each week's match-up.  Finally, our 'other Go Daddy Girl&quot;, Rachel Storm, goes in-depth with Bob about how to maximize your eCommerce ad $$$$!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  2 Nov 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_11_02.mp3" length="27682406" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Mobile movies, 'Spy&quot; printers, How to Get Smarter, &amp; Doing eCommerce on the Web!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_10_26.mp3</link>
      <description>SO much to cover &amp; SO little time!  'Mobisodes&quot; are BIG overseas, but will they play in Peoria?  Also, is your printer spying on you?  Seth Schoen of the Electronic Frontier Foundation shares interesting &amp; somewhat troubling news. The talk turns to flossing your brain, with Will Pearson, founder of MentalFloss.com.  This 'brain mag' has built a loyal following - is its board game the next Trivial Pursuit®? Can a game show be far behind?  Then Bob, 'Thumbs' Adelman &amp; the 'sidekick' give a detailed primer on eCommerce.  And, not to be outdone by D.C., Bob 'leaks&quot; next week's celebrity guest!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_10_26.mp3" length="27682406" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Our 30th Show! The Perils of Internet Dating, Website Building 'Dos &amp; Don'ts!'</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_10_19.mp3</link>
      <description>We've made it to show # 30!  Bob explores the good &amp; the bad of internet dating.  Our 1st guest is Grace Davis from Internet Probation &amp; Parole Control - an organization whose software tracks the online activity of convicted felons on parole.  And yes, these guys visit online dating sites!  Then it's on to Kat &amp; Totally Traci - they both met men online, but with very different outcomes!  Finally, Bob chats with Herb Vest, CEO of True.com, the online dating site that screens all users!  Finally, we learn some tips &amp; tricks on web site design &amp; hear about bachelors, fregans &amp; toy destruction!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_10_19.mp3" length="28940698" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>A drinking monkey, counterfeiters &amp; technology, brain exercises &amp; domain speculating!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_10_12.mp3</link>
      <description>Hear Bob's adventures during his ride-along with the Phoenix police - including the drinking monkey!  Bob then interviews Dr. Joe Alexander, forensic document expert, about using technology to create counterfeit money, deeds &amp; more - virtually any document is susceptible.  Dr. Alexander was even an expert in a case involving handwriting on a truck-stop bathroom wall!  Bob also explores brain exercises as a way to fight dementia.  Wait, there's more! Learn the ins &amp; outs of buying &amp; selling domains on the secondary market (a/k/a speculating) &amp; hear Bob's personal tips for picking a domain!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_10_12.mp3" length="27682406" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The debut of 'Car Wash - Uncut' - Battling Internet Giants &amp; Shutting Down Domains!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_10_05.mp3</link>
      <description>The 'totally Internet&quot; show! In response to ever-growing demand, Bob debuts Go Daddy's Internet-only version of Car Wash LIVE in Radio Go Daddy's chat room! Hear comments from Go Daddy customers, Totally Traci, Preston &amp; Lili! Then Warren drops in to give us the lowdown on the jockeying amongst Microsoft, AOL, Google &amp; Sun Microsystems - WHO will ultimately rule the 'net? Maybe none of them! And our own Network Abuse guy educates us about shutting down nefarious domains &amp; websites. But leave room for Strange Domains &amp; Weird News -- we have naked gardening, bad girls &amp; the love boat!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  5 Oct 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_10_05.mp3" length="28101837" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The 'A&quot; show - from 'Authors&quot; to 'Afghanistan&quot; to 'Ass-saving&quot; to 'Anti-magnets&quot;!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_09_28.mp3</link>
      <description>Truly a class 'A&quot; show!  Lincoln Child and Bob have a blast discussing his books, how he gets ideas, and great 'behind-the-scenes&quot; stories of his authorship.  Then Lt. Patrick Sullivan, U.S. Army, calls Bob from half-way around the world - Afghanistan!  Hear first-hand about the military's success in building 'The Road to Kandahar&quot; --- you won't hear about it in the mainstream media, that's for sure!  Then Bob briefly explores the impending problem presented by expanding Daylight Savings Time in 2007.   Will you be ready?  But wait - there's so much more - especially in tonight's Weird News!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_09_28.mp3" length="29779558" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Go Daddy's newest commercials, 'Totally Traci&quot; and the newest scam weapon - Splogging!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_09_21.mp3</link>
      <description>What a show!  Bob gets Candice Michelle on the phone to discuss her latest Go Daddy commercials - 'Car Wash&quot; and 'Art Class.&quot;   So are these commercials 'too hot for prime time?&quot;  Will Bob EVER reveal the Internet-only version of 'Car Wash&quot; that he's keeping under lock and key?  Only Bob knows for sure!  Then Ben Butler, Go Daddy's own Network Abuse Administrator - and Spamurai Warrior -- joins Bob in-studio to explain Splogging - the latest in the scammer's arsenal of dirty tricks.  And, Bob introduces us to 'Totally Traci&quot; - entrepreuer, web designer, thespian, clown and so much more!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_09_21.mp3" length="27158118" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Our 25th show!  What John D. Rockefeller &amp; Go Daddy have in common, and the rise of digital thugs!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_09_14.mp3</link>
      <description>It's Radio Go Daddy's 25th show, and we're going strong!  Bob &amp; Dr. Darwin Stapleton, from The Rockefeller Archive Center, discuss John D. Rockefeller's business methods and practices, many of which still hold true over a century later!  Then Bob explores 'digital thugs&quot; with Scott Larson, Managing Director of a leading cyber-crime response company.  Hear how an extortionist almost took down a famous patent firm.  And only during our 25th show would you hear about the World Testicular Cooking Championships &amp; how many cats you need to make diesel fuel in Germany.  You can't make this stuff up!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_09_14.mp3" length="31771853" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Looting &amp; violence in New Orleans, and a first-hand account from an AmeriCares relief worker!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_09_07.mp3</link>
      <description>Hurricane Katrina destroyed more than just homes - it destroyed the social order. Bob interviews Dr. 'Hank&quot; Fischer, a leading sociologist who claims that the crime &amp; looting in New Orleans was an anomaly overplayed by the media. Do you agree? Bob also gets an AmeriCares relief worker on the phone LIVE from Mississippi; Brian Hoyer tells how people who have 'lost everything'-- haven't lost hope. And on tonight's Weird News, Bob covers everything from pushy Indian eunuchs to bungling Austrian thieves, and discusses startling British research that claims men no longer prefer blondes...</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  7 Sep 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_09_07.mp3" length="26633830" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The ultimate security show! Experts abound! The &quot;Other&quot; Go Daddy Girl!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_08_31.mp3</link>
      <description>The show of shows! Dave Jevans, of the Anti-Phishing Working Group, picks up where he left off &amp; explains &quot;crimeware&quot; -- the phishers' latest tactic to dupe you. Then hacker-turned-good-guy (and best-selling author) KEVIN MITNICK discusses the increasing popularity -- and dangers of WI-FI access. Hard to believe, but even Kevin had his personal information compromised -- so make sure it doesn't happen to you! And, we meet the &quot;other&quot; Go Daddy Girl -- Rachel Storm (complete with her own custom sound effect!) Of course, the show wouldn't be complete without the UFO Freeway &amp; Strange Domains!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_08_31.mp3" length="26948403" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>&quot;Armageddon!&quot; The scoop on Windows Vista, hotel heaven &amp; hotel hell, and .XXX is back!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_08_24.mp3</link>
      <description>Windows Vista is coming! Just how big a deal is it? Well, Warren got his hands on an advance copy &amp; tells Bob what's new and hot about Microsoft's biggest launch since Windows XP! Bob interviews Marc Johnson, a Go Daddy customer who built &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hotelchatter.com&quot;&gt;www.hotelchatter.com&lt;/a&gt; - read hotel reviews from 'real people' about the places you should stay at -- and the ones you should avoid. And it isn't over -- Bob updates us on the resurgence of the .XXX domain battle. Plus, 'Armageddon', the 'iron grip' &amp; an unusual library 'check-out' policy..you gotta hear these!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_08_24.mp3" length="30618419" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Wow! eBaumsworld.com, keeping U.S. troops cool, &quot;smoke &amp; mirrors&quot;, and new phishing scares!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_08_17.mp3</link>
      <description>Learn how &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ebaumsworld.com&quot;&gt;eBaum's World&lt;/a&gt; grew from a small cult site into one of the most popular sites on the 'Net when Bob interviews COO Jason Martorano. Then Bob covers a &quot;cool&quot; charity - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coolourtroops.com&quot;&gt;Cool Our Troops.com&lt;/a&gt; -- and proceeds to donate $12,000 to the organization! Dave Jevans, head of the Anti-Phishing Working Group briefs Bob about the latest crimeware &amp; spear-phishing scams. Plus, Bob sets the record straight on NetSol's misinformation. And lest we forget, there's a postman, a rocketman &amp; and a barking man!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_08_17.mp3" length="27053261" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Our 20th Show! Sex therapy on the 'net, car viruses, hot advances in medical technology &amp; On Combat!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_08_10.mp3</link>
      <description>What a lineup for our 20th show! Bob interviews Dr. Patti Britton, Certified Clinical Sexologist &amp; founder of  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoursexcoach.com&quot;&gt; www.yoursexcoach.com&lt;/a&gt;, about the popularity of online sexual coaching! Then, Bob explores car computer viruses &amp; warns about the Car Whisperer! Bob discusses cool advances in medical technology with orthopedic surgeon Dr. Tony Tyler -- such as &quot;wired&quot; hospitals &amp; online databases of patient medical records. Plus, Bob's recommendation for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/detail/-/0964920514/&quot;&gt;On Combat&lt;/a&gt; &amp; celebrity ducks!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_08_10.mp3" length="27262976" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Hot robotics, money laundering mules -- and Sen. Frist &amp; the stem cell debate.</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_08_03.mp3</link>
      <description>Are robots taking over your daily life? Bob covers the latest robotic trends, from domestics that clean your floor, to female androids &amp; bionic knees! Bob interviews Paul Luehr, former US Atty, who discusses the connection between the Russian mob &amp; black mules. Then Bob explores how stem cell research might have helped Christopher Reeve, with reknown expert, Dr. Andrew Yeager. Plus, 'dumb Texas laws,' a cursing Macaw, &amp; safety tips -- such as don't use a vacuum to siphon gas!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  3 Aug 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_08_03.mp3" length="27158118" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Making it big in the restaurant biz, how to beat a casino, a wild diving story.</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_07_27.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob talks with Dennis Mastro and learns how he made it big in the restaurant biz. Michael Shackleford, the wizard of odds and author of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/detail/-/0929712072/&quot; target=&quot;_info&quot;&gt;Gambling 102&lt;/a&gt; tells you the best way to beat casinos. Bob interviews Tim Zimmerman, who relays the incredible story of Dave Shaw's last deep sea dive (889 feet!). Plus Strange Domains and some really wierd news -- like a brown bear who has learned to knock on doors to get into houses.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_07_27.mp3" length="27262976" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Control of the 'net, technology making your kids heavy, mules &amp; anorexia sites!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_07_20.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob tackles Internet control -- will the U.S. or U.N. prevail? And is technology making your child overweight? Get the facts first-hand from expert &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.trimkids.com&quot; target=&quot;_info&quot;&gt;Dr. Melinda Sothern&lt;/a&gt;. Then, Lizzy, the creator of a 'pro-ana' site, tells her personal story to Bob. Avoid becoming a black market mule &amp; hear a tale from the deep (scuba-diving). As for the podcast - it's a blast! There's the Vaseline Man, an update on the outhouse guy &amp; a different type of 'horse' story!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_07_20.mp3" length="26738688" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Outrageous! Darwin Awards, Author of &quot;The Loch&quot;, .MOBI &amp; Go Daddy Girls!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_07_13.mp3</link>
      <description>Tonight, the Radio Go Daddy team learns about .MOBI - the future of web sites on cell phones! Then it's on to the best Darwin Award stories ever! There's a wild discussion about the Loch Ness monster with Steve Alten, author of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/detail/-/0976165902/%22&quot; target=&quot;_info&quot;&gt;The Loch&lt;/a&gt; &amp; more! Finally, Bob discusses feedback on the Go Daddy Girls idea. Will he or won't he? And the podcast has some pretty weird news - spitters, robbers &amp; killer cows - yes, killer cows.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_07_13.mp3" length="26319258" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The 4th of July, Internet Gambling, Bob's Mom, Save Toby, Candice &amp; More!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_07_06.mp3</link>
      <description>What a lineup! So much to say &amp; so little time! Bob leads off with July 4th facts &amp; internet gambling. He even calls a gambling expert - his mom! The team addresses Toby's 'stay of execution' and gets one of Toby's owners on the line. Before you know it, Candice Michelle calls in &amp; updates us on the latest, and Bob 'wraps up' with the Supreme Court's file share ruling. Best yet, the extra half hour of Weird News covers men in toilets, cremation, and Sweden's new &quot;skirt&quot; law!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  6 Jul 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_07_06.mp3" length="28311552" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Good night eBay? Google ranking secrets, XM &amp; the military, and a movie prophet!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_06_29.mp3</link>
      <description>On tonight's show, Bob exposes the secrets of Google site ranking, and why people are leaving eBay due to high costs &amp; other issues. Our movie prophet, David Mumpower, discusses rating movies before they open at the box office. Bob talks about a site devoted to a wounded &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jarodbehee.com/&quot; target=&quot;_info&quot;&gt;U.S. Soldier&lt;/a&gt;, and the military's intention to use XM radio. The live podcast covers Iraq's TLD, the Timber Mafia, pennies &amp; Nima's favorite word (not really)!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_06_29.mp3" length="27158118" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>WOWZA! Adult Film Star Ashton Moore, Credit Card Hacking &amp; TV show downloading!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_06_22.mp3</link>
      <description>An outta-this-world show! Bob takes on the allegation that Go Daddy will support pornography when it sells .XXX. We then hear a unique perspective about .XXX and the porn industry from the one and only Ashton Moore, adult film star. But there's lots more -- credit card hacking, why downloading tv shows for non-personal use is illegal, Special Guest Bill Hely, author of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hackersnightmare.com/godaddy/&quot; target=&quot;_info&quot;&gt;Hacker's Nightmare&lt;/a&gt; and a 'Strange Domain&quot; about camels!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_06_22.mp3" length="27472691" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Our &quot;ET&quot; Show w/Prophet Yahweh, &quot;Zeta Nancy&quot; &amp; the latest internet happenings!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_06_15.mp3</link>
      <description>An out-of-this-world lineup. Prophet Yahweh talks about summoning UFOs, while Zeta Nancy tells us what the &quot;Zetas&quot; are thinking -- and if they listen to Radio Go Daddy! Bob takes a serious turn though, discussing Internet 2 -- faster than a speeding bullet, WIFI access on airplanes and his thoughts on the real estate bubble. And our extra 30 minute podcast segment discusses blogging discrimination, phishing, what Warren saw in Costa Rica &amp; more!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_06_15.mp3" length="27158118" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>&quot;Freakonomics&quot; co-author, Stephen Dubner, Urban Legends, &amp; .XXX domains!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_06_08.mp3</link>
      <description>The podcast starts with Strange Domains - voodoo potions, bizarre art &amp; more! Bob then goes 'one-on-one' w/Stephen Dubner, co-author of best selling &lt;a href=&quot;http://amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/detail/-/006073132X&quot; target=&quot;_a&quot;&gt;Freakonomics&lt;/a&gt;. They cover interesting economic theories, including online dating, &lt;u&gt;Roe v. Wade's&lt;/u&gt; impact on the crime rate &amp; monkey sex! Yes, you read correctly. Then there are .XXX domains, the Chinese &amp; so much more the podcast was extended an extra 30 minutes!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  8 Jun 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_06_08.mp3" length="25060966" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>&quot;Hot&quot; TV ads, New Trends in Email Surveillance &amp; Hot Domain Auction Prices!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_06_01.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob opens with a vivid discussion of Paris Hilton's racy new TV ad &amp; the Parents Television Council's refusal to appear on Radio Go Daddy! The team then moves on to a more serious topic -- new trends in email surveillance based on traffic patterns &amp; keywords. Amazon's Purchase Circles are also reviewed &amp; then it's on to domain auctions. You'll be surprised what domain names are selling for on the auction market --- it isn't peanuts! And, our 'Best of the Blog' segment is priceless tonight!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  1 Jun 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_06_01.mp3" length="17406362" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Wow! The Blog Revolution, Stripped Stewardesses (???) &amp; Connectivity!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_05_25.mp3</link>
      <description>This week, Bob broadcasts LIVE from the Domain Roundtable Conference in Seattle and with our 1st ever LIVE AUDIENCE, too! After the gang covers the Blog Revolution and its widespread impact, Bob turns to Stewardesses who posed semi-clothed for a calendar in protest of having their pensions taken away. It's a fun, but serious conversation. Finally, connectivity is everywhere, an update on Toby's plight it isn't looking good and of course, Strange Domains and Best of the Blog!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_05_25.mp3" length="17825792" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Hour Long One-on-One Interview with Kevin Mitnick</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_05_13.mp3</link>
      <description>In a special broadcast of Radio Go Daddy, Bob has a personal, one-on-one interview with celebrated hacker turned good-guy, Kevin Mitnick. Bob &amp; Kevin discuss cybercrime, its prevention, and draw upon true-to-life hacker stories in Kevin's latest, best selling book, &lt;a href=&quot;http://amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/detail/-/0764569597&quot; target=&quot;a&quot;&gt;&quot;The Art of Intrusion&quot;&lt;/a&gt;. But don't worry, Bob brings some wild and wacky 'Strange Domains' to our attention, along with some amusing 'Best of Blog' entries.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_05_13.mp3" length="17406362" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Cell Phone Viruses Take Center Stage, Jail Time for Spammers &amp; More Predators</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_05_11.mp3</link>
      <description>Tonight, Bob discusses cell phone viruses -- what they do, how they spread &amp; how to prevent your phone from falling victim to this growing problem. Bob talks about the recent conviction of a prolific spammer &amp; continues to raise awareness about Internet predators. Add to that our new television ads - some with, and some without, The Go Daddy Girl. Finally, 'Strange Domains' covers time travel and the &quot;pop vs. soda&quot; controversy, while 'Best of the Blog' suggests Go Daddy airplanes!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_05_11.mp3" length="17511219" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Human Verifier, Internet Predators &amp; the &quot;Other&quot; Go Daddy Girl!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_05_04.mp3</link>
      <description>This week's Strange Domains range from chicken juice to frogs. In Best of the Blog, learn Bob's views on returning to Vietnam! And meet Rachel - our GoDaddy.com model! In a serious vein, learn about Human Verifiers &amp; dangers of Internet Predators. Bob reviews &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/detail/-/0743448804/&quot; target=&quot;_info&quot;&gt;&quot;Anyone You Want Me to Be&quot;&lt;/a&gt; - a chilling account of a serial killer who lurked on the 'Net.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  4 May 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_05_04.mp3" length="17616077" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>The Pharming scam, &quot;Freakonomics&quot; reviewed &amp; Candice Michelle LIVE in studio!</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_04_27.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob &amp; Warren talk about Pharming, the latest scam. And yes, it IS worse than phishing. On a lighter note, Bob reviews a New York Times Best Seller -- &quot;Freakonomics.&quot; Learn about Go Daddy's latest commercials, featuring Bob, Candice &amp; live bulls! Speaking of Candice, she's live in studio! Chat room folks get in the mix too, with questions answered in REAL TIME by Bob. And it wouldn't be Radio Go Daddy without Strange Domains (funky chunkies?) and Best of Blog. Oh yes, and we meet Nima.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_04_27.mp3" length="17301504" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Go Daddy Dethrones NetSol &amp; Talks About the Dangers of DDOS, Worms &amp; Viruses</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_04_20.mp3</link>
      <description>Tonight, Bob announces that GoDaddy.com has become the No. 1 registrar worldwide -- both in terms of new domain registrations &amp; domains under management. Learn how Go Daddy achieved this status in record time. Team Go Daddy explains worms, DDOS attacks &amp; how YOU can protect yourself against zombies. You'll even hear about the most recent DDOS attack against savetoby.com! Along the way, Bob previews his new blog article, reads an angry customer's voicemail message &amp; takes lots of calls!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_04_20.mp3" length="17720934" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>New commercials, Candice, the Super Bowl's Final word &amp; shady domain transfers</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_04_13.mp3</link>
      <description>Bob previews Go Daddy's new commercials, &quot;leaks&quot; the identity of a future actor in our commercials &amp; updates us on Candice, the Go Daddy girl. He then gives the FINAL WORD on our Super Bowl ad (with supporting statistics) and alerts YOU to shady domain transfers! Radio Go Daddy also introduces new features -- like LIVE CHAT! and FREE t-shirts for on air callers. Finally, on BOB &amp; WARREN UNCENSORED: more really Strange Domains and the premier of &quot;The Best and Worst of the Blog.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_04_13.mp3" length="17616077" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Bob tackles blog spamming, the 9th Circuit &amp; premiers &quot;Strange Domains&quot;</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_04_06.mp3</link>
      <description>The Go Daddy team discusses how you can protect yourself against a 9th Circuit ruling that says someone can add &quot;sucks&quot; to your trademarked domain -- and not violate your trademark. Bob calls Argentina for a LIVE ICANN update from Tim Ruiz, Go Daddy's ICANN representative, and discusses Go Daddy' latest efforts to overturn the NTIA's decision denying your right to privacy. Best of all: Bob premiers &quot;Strange Domains&quot; -- a new feature available only to LIVE stream listeners.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed,  6 Apr 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_04_06.mp3" length="13946061" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item><item>
      <title>Our 1st show! The NTIA, your privacy rights &amp; the controversy over SaveToby.com</title>
      <link>http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_03_30.mp3</link>
      <description>The inaugural launch of Radio Go Daddy, hosted by Go Daddy president &amp; founder, Bob Parsons. In our premier show, Bob takes on the NTIA's recent decision to deny you of your Constitutional right to privacy. Bob also discusses the controversy over SaveToby.com --- will the rabbit be saved? Bob gets Toby's owner on the line!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2005 00:00:00 MST</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://mediafiles.godaddy.com/GDRadio/radio_2005_03_30.mp3" length="12373197" type="audio/mpeg" />
    </item>  </channel>
</rss>