<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live</title>
        <description>The World&apos;s First Interactive, Sports Talk Bloggers Show.

&quot;One Small Step For Blogs.  One Giant Leap for Blog Kind!&quot;</description>
        <link>http://www.sportsbloggerslive.com/</link>
        <category domain="">Sports</category>
        <copyright>AOL Sports</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 2 Feb 2007 16:18:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>shawnschrager@aol.com (Shawn Schrager)</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Fri, 2 Feb 2007 16:16:28 -0500</pubDate>
        <webMaster>AOL Sports and Community</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.1.5) unlicensed version http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>Bringing Sports Talk and Blogging Together!</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>AOL Sports</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Shawn Schrager</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>shawnschrager@aol.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Sports &amp; Recreation"/>
        <itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Personal Journals"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>sports, blogs, nfl, mlb, nhl, nba, sports talk, talk radio, football, baseball, basketball</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://cdn.news.aol.com/aolnews_photos/02/05/20060914221109990006"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast_162.jpg</url>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live</title>
            <link>http://www.sportsbloggerslive.com</link>
            <description>&quot;Bringing Blogging and Sports Talk Radio Together!&quot;</description>
            <width>162</width>
            <height>162</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - SBL at Super Week in Miami Florida - Friday</title>
            <description>Friday at Super week with guests Clinton Portis, Alex Smith, Willis McGahee, Shaun Alexander, Merril Hoge, Tony Siragusa, With Leather, and Angela Evans. </description>
            <link>http://www.sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020207.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020207.mp3" length="51524860" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">27FD3C80-196D-4576-B4C2-9281F4C86F45</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 2 Feb 2007 16:16:28 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - SBL at Super Week in Miami Florida - Thrusday</title>
            <description>Thursday at Super week with guests Joe Theismann, Deadspin, Michael David Smith and Brian Powell.</description>
            <link>http://www.sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020107.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020107.mp3" length="58114371" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">27FD3C80-196D-4576-B4C2-9281F4C86F45</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 1 Feb 2007 14:49:36 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - SBL at Super Week in Miami Florida - Wednesday</title>
            <description>Wednesday at Super week with guests Chad Johnson, Bill Simmons, Peter Schrager, and Dave&apos;s Football Blog.</description>
            <link>http://www.sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast013107.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast013107.mp3" length="59725242" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">27FD3C80-196D-4576-B4C2-9281F4C86F45</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2007 15:37:28 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - SBL at Super Week in Miami Florida - Tuesday</title>
            <description>SBL&apos;s second day at Super Week featuring Mike Florio, Bob Reno, Big Daddy Drew, and Carl Grovslovsky.</description>
            <link>http://www.sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast013007.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast013007.mp3" length="59582211" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">27FD3C80-196D-4576-B4C2-9281F4C86F45</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2007 14:11:24 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - SBL at Super Week in Miami Florida - Miami</title>
            <description>SBL&apos;s first day at Super Week featuring Sarah Spain, Jared Fogel, Brandon Langer and Matthew Ballard.</description>
            <link>http://www.sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast012907.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast012907.mp3" length="59411658" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">27FD3C80-196D-4576-B4C2-9281F4C86F45</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2007 14:39:45 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - &quot;Best of 2006 Show&quot;</title>
            <description>The year end spectacular with interviews from Wade Boggs, Ron Artest, Reggie Jackson, Icky Woods, Frank Caliendo, Lee Corso, Will Clark, Tony Dorsett, Bill Walton, Peter King, Bob Costas, Don Mattingly, Chris Webber and Wayne Brady.</description>
            <link>www.sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast122106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast122106.mp3" length="55429265" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9CF88CAE-8874-4A69-88ED-4FDC710A729D</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2007 14:39:42 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - &quot;Best of 2006 Show&quot;</title>
            <description>The year end spectacular with interviews from Wade Boggs, Ron Artest, Reggie Jackson, Icky Woods, Frank Caliendo, Lee Corso, Will Clark, Tony Dorsett, Bill Walton, Peter King, Bob Costas, Don Mattingly, Chris Webber and Wayne Brady.</description>
            <link>www.sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast122106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast122106.mp3" length="55429265" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9CF88CAE-8874-4A69-88ED-4FDC710A729D</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2007 03:05:18 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 14 Recap, Detroit Tigers&apos; Justin Verlander, MLB  Hot Stove Update, Heisman &amp; OSU Legend Archie Griffin, NCAA Basketball Update</title>
            <description>NFL Insider Mike Florio recaps Week 14, LT&apos;s TD record, the Colts&apos; collapse &amp; more. MLB Rookie of the Year Detroit Tigers&apos; Justin Verlander. ESPN&apos;s Will Carroll updates the MLB Hot Stove including Andy Pettitte&apos;s to New York, Boston&apos;s problems signing Matsuzaka &amp; more. Two-time Heisman winner Archie Griffin on the BCS, Troy Smith &amp; Greg Oden. CBS SportsLine&apos;s Gary Parrish talks NCAA Hoops.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast121106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast121106.mp3" length="51283290" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2006 12:41:23 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 14 Preview with Peter King, 2006&apos;s Top Sports Stories with Bob Costas, FMX Superstar Travis Pastrana, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King previews NFL Week 14 and more. The SBL Crew picks games against a 2-year-old. HBO&apos;s Bob Costas discusses SI&apos;s Sportsman of the Year Dwyane Wade, the biggest stories of the year &amp; more. FMX star Travis Pastrana talks about landing a double back flip on a motorcycle &amp; the Action Sports Awards. Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast120706.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast120706.mp3" length="58655135" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 7 Dec 2006 09:59:11 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - BCS Analysis with Jason Whitlock, NFL Week 13 Recap, NBA HOFer Walt Frazier, NCAA Basketball Update</title>
            <description>Outspoken columnist Jason Whitlock explains why there&apos;s nothing wrong with the BCS. NFL Insider Mike Florio recaps the action from NFL Week 13, the emerging playoff picture and more. NBA HOFer Walt Frazier talks about his career, the Knicks, style in the league &amp; more. SI&apos;s Seth Davis talks NCAA Hoops, Greg Oden&apos;s debut &amp; more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast120406.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast120406.mp3" length="51688011" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 4 Dec 2006 15:43:21 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 13 Preview with Peter King, Pigskin Pick Off, Charlotte Bobcats&apos; Emeka Okafor, MLB Hot Stove Update, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King previews NFL Week 13, discusses his change of heart with Art Monk and the HOF and more. The SBL Crew picks games against a 2-year-old. Charlotte Bobcats center and former UConn superstar Emeka Okafor. ESPN&apos;s Will Carroll discusses the biggest stories of the MLB off season. Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast113006.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast113006.mp3" length="52197916" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2006 16:34:14 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 12 Recap, NCAA Football Recap, NCAA Basketball Update, Arctic Marathon Runner Mike Pierce</title>
            <description>NFL Insider Mike Florio recaps all of the action from NFL Week 12, Vick&apos;s future, Irvin&apos;s offensive remarks and more. Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megargee breaks down the BCS and more. TSN&apos;s Mike DeCourcy names his early-season standouts, blasts the AP poll and more. Extreme athlete Mike Pierce talks about preparing for the Antarctica 100K in a San Diego freezer.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast112706.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast112706.mp3" length="50676832" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2006 15:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Analysis with Bob Costas, Charlotte Bobcats Rookie Adam Morrison, NCAA Football, MLB Hot Stove Update</title>
            <description>HBO&apos;s Bob Costas breaks down NFL Week 11, previews Week 12, makes his playoff predictions and more. Bobcats Rookie Adam Morrison talks about the playing in the NBA, how he spent his Draft money and more. NCAA Football analysis with Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megargee.  ESPN&apos;s Will Carroll on the latest MLB off season action.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast112006.mp3</link>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast112006.mp3" length="54350332" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2006 14:37:07 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 10 Recap, NCAA Football Recap, NBA Update, NASCAR&apos;s Ryan Newman</title>
            <description>NFL Insider Mike Florio recaps all of the action from NFL Week 10. NCAA Football review with Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megargee. NBA update with blogger Henry Abbott of TrueHoop.com. Driver of the No. 12 Alltel Dodge Ryan Newman talks about the Chase, plays &quot;Name Your Sponsors&quot; and more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast111306.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast111306.mp3" length="50784614" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2006 15:41:52 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 10 Preview with Peter King, Pigskin Pick Off, Redskins Legend Darrell Green, NCAA Basketball Season Preview, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King previews NFL Week 10. The SBL Crew picks games against a 2-year-old. Redskins legend Darrell Green discusses the current team, trash talking, the Hall of Fame and more. The Sporting News&apos; Mike DeCourcy previews the 2006-07 NCAA Basketball season. Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110906.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110906.mp3" length="53064061" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 9 Nov 2006 14:48:39 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 9 Recap, NFL HOFer Tony Dorsett, MLB with ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney, NCAA Football Recap</title>
            <description>NFL Insider Mike Florio recaps all of the action from NFL Week 9. NFL legend Tony Dorsett talks about the Redskins vs. Cowboys rivaly, what he thinks of Tony Romo and more. ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney breaks down the MLB Hot Stove and more. NCAA Football review with Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megargee.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110606.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110606.mp3" length="52272745" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 6 Nov 2006 11:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 9 Preview with Peter King, Pigskin Pick Off, Sacramento Kings Forward Ron Artest, NCAA Football Preview, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King previews NFL Week 9. The SBL Crew picks games against a 2-year-old. Sacramento Kings All-Star Ron Artest previews the season, names the NBA&apos;s best rappers, previews his new CD and more. FoxSports.com&apos;s Peter Schrager previews NCAA Football. Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110206.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110206.mp3" length="55176354" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 2 Nov 2006 11:00:03 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 8 Recap, World Series Recap with Ken Rosenthal, NBA Season Preview, Charlotte Bobcats&apos; Gerald Wallace</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Jeff Chadiha recaps all of the action from NFL Week 8. FoxSports&apos; Ken Rosenthal recaps the World Series and looks ahead to the off season. NBA season preview with True Hoop&apos;s Henry Abbott &amp; JE Skeets from the Basketball Jones.  Charlotte Bobcats forward Gerald Wallace talks about the franchise, the new season and more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast103006.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast103006.mp3" length="55176354" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 15:29:35 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 8 Preview with Peter King, Bob Costas on the MLB, ESPN College GameDay&apos;s Lee Corso, Lions Coach Rod Marinelli, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King previews NFL Week 8. The SBL Crew picks games against a 2-year-old. HBO&apos;s Bob Costas discusses the state of the MLB. ESPN&apos;s Lee Corso on the best places to watch a game, rooming with Burt Reynolds &amp; more. Detroit Lions Head Coach Rod Marinelli. Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast102606.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast102606.mp3" length="61158666" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2006 14:31:09 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 7 Recap, World Series with Tigers &amp; Cards Bloggers, NCAA Football Recap, &apos;Murderball&apos; Star Mark Zupan</title>
            <description>NFL Insider Mike Florio recaps all of the action from NFL Week 7. MLB Bloggers Bill Ferris and Larry Borowsky discuss the Kenny Rogers controversy. NCAA Football review with Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megargee. &apos;Murderball&apos; star Mark Zupan discusses his new book, &apos;Jackass 2&apos; and more!</description>
            <link>http://www.sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast122106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast102306.mp3" length="53778799" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2006 15:11:12 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 7 Preview with Peter King, Pigskin Pick Off, &apos;86 Mets World Series MVP Ray Knight, NCAA Football Preview, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King previews NFL Week 7. The SBL Crew picks games against a 2-year-old. &apos;86 World Series MVP, 3-Time All-Star and Mets hero Ray Knight. FoxSports.com&apos;s Peter Schrager breaks down the Miami vs. FIU brawl and previews NCAA Football. Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101906.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101906.mp3" length="53724350" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2006 13:20:40 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 6 Recap, Tampa Bay&apos;s Will Allen, MLB with ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney, NCAA Football Recap</title>
            <description>NFL Insider Mike Florio recaps all of the action from NFL Week 6. Tampa Bay Bucs&apos; safety Will Allen talks about their big win over Cincy and more. ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney updates the MLB Playoffs action, A-Rod trade rumors and more. NCAA Football review with Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megargee.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101606.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101606.mp3" length="51894865" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2006 14:56:01 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 6 Preview with Peter King, Pigskin Pick Off, MLB Playoffs with Bloggers, NASCAR&apos;s Kurt Busch, NCAA Football Preview, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King previews NFL Week 6. The SBL Crew picks games against a 2-year-old. Baseball Bloggers go head-to-head in  our ALCS &amp; NLCS previews. 2004 NEXTEL Cup Winner Kurt Busch. FoxSports.com&apos;s Peter Schrager previews NCAA Football. Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101206.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101206.mp3" length="63274295" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2006 13:07:08 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - 2006-07 NHL Season Preview</title>
            <description>Hockey blogger Eric McErlain of &quot;Off Wing Opinion&quot; previews the 2006-2007 NHL Season, names the year&apos;s top young talent and predicts who will win it all.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/101006_sbl_msr_nhlpreview.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/101006_sbl_msr_nhlpreview.mp3" length="15407414" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2006 11:49:30 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Yankees Fallout and ALCS/NLCS Previews, HOFer Bruce Sutter, NFL Week 5 Recap, San Antonio Spurs Star Tony Parker, NCAA Football Recap</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Will Carroll and HOF Bruce Sutter discuss the fallout from the Yankees collapse and the MLB Playoffs. NFL Insider Mike Florio recaps all of the action from NFL Week 5. San Antonio Spurs star Tony Parker talks about the new season, his rapping career, EA&apos;s NBA Live &apos;07 and more. NCAA Football review with Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megargee.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast100906.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast100906.mp3" length="53763405" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 9 Oct 2006 16:06:37 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 5 Preview with Peter King, Pigskin Pick Off, MLB Playoffs with HOFer Wade Boggs, &amp; MetsBlog.com, Fantasy Football Focus</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King previews NFL Week 5. The SBL Crew picks games against a 3-year-old. HOFer Wade Boggs and MetsBlog.com discuss the MLB Playoffs, big game hunting and more. Shawn Schrager reports from Yankees Stadium. Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast100506.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast100506.mp3" length="51932260" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Fri, 6 Oct 2006 10:00:32 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - MLB Playoffs Preview, NFL Week 4 Recap with Jeff Chadiha, Houston Rockets Superstar Tracy McGrady, NCAA Football Recap</title>
            <description>TSN&apos;s Sean Deveney previews the MLB Playoffs. SI&apos;s Jeff Chadiha recaps all of the action from NFL Week 4. NBA superstar Tracy McGrady talks about the new season, his future in baseball, EA&apos;s NBA Live &apos;07 and more. NCAA Football review with Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megargee.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast100206.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast100206.mp3" length="52750165" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 2 Oct 2006 12:44:26 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - T.O &amp; NFL Week 4 Preview with Peter King, Pigskin Pick Off, MLB Playoffs with Bob Costas, NCAA Football Preview, Fantasy Football Focus</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King updates the T.O. soap opera &amp; previews NFL Week 4. The SBL Crew picks games against a 2-year-old. HBO&apos;s Bob Costas on Warner vs. Leinart &amp; the MLB Playoffs. CBS SportsLine&apos;s Dennis Dodd previews NCAA Football Week 4 &amp; lists his 1/3 season awards. Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092806.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092806.mp3" length="52783380" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 13:51:40 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - HBO&apos;s Bob Costas on T.O.&apos;s Suicide Attempt</title>
            <description>HBO&apos;s Bob Costas discusses Terrell Owens&apos; suicide attempt, saying he&apos;s a &quot;deeply, deeply disturbed man&quot; and more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/092706_sbl_msr_costas.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/092706_sbl_msr_costas.mp3" length="6824622" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 12:10:50 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Special Report: Terrell Owens Attempts Suicide?</title>
            <description>NFL Insider Mike Florio from ProFootballTalk.com discusses the reports that outspoken Dallas Cowboys wide receiver Terrell Owens attempted suicide.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/092706_sbl_msr_to.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/092706_sbl_msr_to.mp3" length="6119940" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2006 11:38:37 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 3 Recap with Mike Florio, MLB Update with ESPN&apos;s Jayson Stark, NCAA Football Recap, Ryder Cup Recap</title>
            <description>Mike Florio of &quot;Pro Football Talk&quot; recaps all of the action from Week 3. ESPN&apos;s Jayson Stark breaks down the biggest stories in the MLB. NCAA Football review with Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megargee and blogger &quot;Heisman Pundit.&quot; Golf Channel&apos;s Brian Hewitt recaps the Ryder Cup.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092506.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092506.mp3" length="53905390" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2006 15:18:26 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 3 Preview with Peter King, Pigskin Pick Off, MLB Update, NCAA Football with ESPN&apos;s Pat Forde, Fantasy Football Focus</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King previews Week 3 of the NFL. The SBL Crew and The Mighty MJD pick games against 2-year-old football phenom &quot;The Kid.&quot; SI.com&apos;s Alex Belth on ARod and the Yankees. ESPN&apos;s Pat Forde previews the Week 4 of NCAA Football and Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092106.mp3" length="53034549" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2006 12:08:57 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 2 Recap with Mike Florio, MLB Update, NCAA Football Recap, Ryder Cup Preview</title>
            <description>Mike Florio of &quot;Pro Football Talk&quot; recaps all of the action from Week 2. Baseball insider David Pinto breaks down the biggest stories in the MLB. NCAA Football review with Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megargee and Michigan blogger Brian Cook. ESPN&apos;s Jason Sobel previews the Ryder Cup.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091806.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091806.mp3" length="51631826" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 12:12:31 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 2 Preview with Peter King, Pigskin Pick Off, NASCAR Update, Fantasy Football Focus</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King previews Week 2 of the NFL. The SBL Crew and The Mighty MJD pick games against 2-year-old football phenom &quot;The Kid.&quot; TSN&apos;s Matt Crossman previews the Chase for the NEXTEL Cup and Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091406.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091406.mp3" length="50822600" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2006 13:32:44 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 1 Recap with Carl Banks, MLB Update, NCAA Football Recap, U.S. Open Recap with ESPN&apos;s Luke Jensen</title>
            <description>SBL has NFL Week 1 covered with Giants&apos; legend Carl Banks and Football Prospectus&apos; Michael David Smith. ESPN&apos;s Will Carroll on Ryan Howard &amp; the MLB Playoffs race. NCAA Football review with Ohio St. blogger J.D. Arney &amp; the SBL Crew. ESPN&apos;s Luke Jensen recaps the action on and off the court at the U.S. Open.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091106.mp3" length="50312695" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2006 13:29:29 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - HBO&apos;s Bob Costas, Pigskin Pick Off: Week 1, Fantasy Football Focus</title>
            <description>HBO&apos;s Bob Costas kicks off the NFL season with his take on T.O, the Mannings, Reggie Bush, Barry Bonds &amp; more. The SBL Crew and The Mighty MJD try to pick games against 2-year-old football phenom &quot;The Kid&quot; and Fantasy Focus with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast090706.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast090706.mp3" length="50312695" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 7 Sep 2006 13:29:29 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Playoffs Preview, NCAA Football Legend Archie Griffin, U.S. Open with ESPN&apos;s Luke Jensen, NASCAR Driver No. 16 Greg Biffle</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Jeff Chadiha takes a look at who might be playing in the NFL Playoffs this year. Two-time Heisman Trophy winner Archie Griffin previews the Ohio St. vs. Texas game. The SBL Crew takes a trip to the FanHouse.  ESPN&apos;s Luke Jensen live from the U.S. Open. NASCAR Driver No. 16 Greg Biffle.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast090506.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast090506.mp3" length="50336790" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 5 Sep 2006 13:13:20 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFC East Preview with Michael Wilbon, Fantasy Draft Focus, Heisman Preview, Tennis Star Andy Murray, Wayne Brady &amp; Anthony Mackie</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Michael Wilbon previews the NFC East. The SBL Crew takes a trip to the FanHouse. FanBall&apos;s Paul Charchian tells you everything you need to know for your Fantasy Football draft. Heisman preview with Rivals.com&apos;s Olin Buchanan. &apos;Crossover&apos; stars Wayne Brady &amp; Anthony Mackie</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast083106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast083106.mp3" length="51219355" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2006 13:26:51 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - AFC East Preview, MLB Update with Buster Olney, Notre Dame &amp; Non-BCS Football Preview, Tennis Star Andy Murray</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Don Banks previews the AFC East. ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney talks baseball. Blogger Brian Stouffer previews Notre Dame football while Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megaragee previews the non-BCS teams that could make noise this season. Scottish tennis rising star Andy Murray talks U.S. Open and more!</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082806.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082806.mp3" length="50866264" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 13:23:01 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - AFC North Preview with Peter King, Andre Dawson, SEC Preview with Pat Forde, Eddie George</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King previews the AFC North. MLB legend and 8-Time All-Star Andre Dawson talks baseball. ESPN&apos;s Pat Forde previews the SEC football season. Pro Bowl RB and Heisman Trophy winner Eddie George discusses Madden &apos;07 and more!</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082406.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082406.mp3" length="57154255" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 13:31:50 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - MLB Update with Will Carroll, NFC North Preview, Big Ten Preview, Tiger Beat</title>
            <description>Baseball Prospectus&apos; Will Carroll talks about the Yankees&apos; dominance of the Red Sox at Fenway, the Wildcard Race, Glavine&apos;s injury and other MLB news. SI&apos;s Tim Layden previews the NFC North. Rival.com&apos;s Steve Megargee previews the Big Ten. Golf Magazine&apos;s Connell Barrett discusses Tiger&apos;s latest win and his place in PGA history.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082106.mp3" length="51332101" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2006 14:15:53 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - SBL&apos;s 2006 Fantasy Football Draft: First Round</title>
            <description>Join the SBL Crew and Friends as they conduct the first round of their 2006 Fantasy Football Draft live on air with in-depth analysis by FanBall&apos;s Court Mann and insults provided by all.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/081706_sbl_msr_sbldraft.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/081706_sbl_msr_sbldraft.mp3" length="25583728" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2006 11:18:32 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFC South Preview, ESPN&apos;s John Kruk, Big 12 Preview, No. 31 Jeff Burton</title>
            <description>We preview the NFC South with SI&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha and Pigskin Blogger Dave Warner. ESPN baseball analyst Jon Kruk talks about the &apos;93 Phillies, MLB mullets and the pennant race. Rival.com&apos;s Olin Buchanan and Matt Berg of Bevo Sports preview the Big 12. NASCAR driver No. 31 Jeff Burton talks about the Chase, RCR&apos;s resurgence, Carolina Panthers football and more!</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast081706.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast081706.mp3" length="57403185" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2006 14:27:19 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - AFC South Preview, MLB Legend Cal Ripken, ACC Preview, PGA Championship Preview</title>
            <description>AFC South preview with Pro Football Talk&apos;s Mike Florio and Colts blogger Big Blue Shoe. MLB legend and Future Fall of Famer Cal Ripken Jr. ACC Preview with Rival.com&apos;s Steve Megargee. PGA Championship preview with Golf.com&apos;s David Dusek.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast081406.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast081406.mp3" length="53939273" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2006 15:40:01 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - HOFer Johnny Bench, NCAA Football Update, Top Fantasy WRs, Poker Star Phil Gordon</title>
            <description>Hall of Fame catcher and baseball legend Johnny Bench talks steroids, Pete Rose, hot prospects and more. Rivals.com&apos;s Steve Megargee explains how Oklahoma will deal with the loss of it&apos;s QB and what it means to rest of the Big 12. Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian names the top fantasy wide receivers. Poker Champ and host of &apos;Celebrity Poker Showdown&apos; Phil Gordon talks about the WSOP, his ultimate sports adventures and more!</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast080306.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast080306.mp3" length="52422345" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 3 Aug 2006 15:22:15 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - MLB Trade Reax and Analysis, NFL Update, NCAA Football Update, X Games Preview with Skateboarder Bucky Lasek</title>
            <description>Complete coverage and reactions on all of the big trades around the MLB with Baseball Prospectus&apos; Will Carroll, Phillies Blogger Erico Camitelli and Brewers Blogger Jeff Sackman. Mike Florio of &quot;Pro Football Talk&quot; with the latest news and rumors from the NFL and NCAA Football including Reggie Bush&apos;s money issues, Matt Leinart&apos;s no-show, QB issues in Florida and Texas and more. Skateboarding legend Bucky Lasek previews the X Games.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast080106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast080106.mp3" length="52039510" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2006 13:24:02 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Preview with ESPN&apos;s Ron Jaworski, Twins Blogger, USA Basketball Preview, Top Fantasy Running Backs</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Ron Jaworski tells us how he would have handled T.O., previews the upcoming NFL season and more. Twins blogger &quot;Batgirl&quot; talks about her team resurgence and explains LegoVision. Henry Abbott of &quot;TrueHoop&quot; previews the new USA Basketball team lead by Coach K and Fantasy Focus returns with Fanball&apos;s Paul Charchian who names the top fantasy running backs.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast072706.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast072706.mp3" length="51463039" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2006 12:02:01 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - MLB HOFer Ozzie Smith, MLB News &amp; Trade Update, British Open Recap, NASCAR Update, NFL News and Rumors</title>
            <description>MLB HOFer and 15-time All-Star Ozzie Smith talks about the state of the game, the Cardinals, Hometown Heroes and more! Baseball Prospectus&apos; Will Carroll on trade rumors and A-Rod&apos;s struggles. British Open recap with Golf Mag&apos;s Connell Barrett. NASCAR update with TSN&apos;s Matt Crossman and Mike Florio of &quot;Pro Football Talk&quot; on Reggie Bush&apos;s potential hold our and more NFL News.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast072506.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast072506.mp3" length="53281917" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2006 10:35:01 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - MLB Trade Rumors, ESPN&apos;s Digger Phelps, British Open Preview, NFL Update</title>
            <description>FOX Sports&apos; Ken Rosenthal tells us where Soriano, Abreu, Schmidt and others may be headed in the MLB. ESPN&apos;s Digger Phelps discusses GMU&apos;s off season, OSU&apos;s &quot;Fab Five&quot; and more. Golf Magazine&apos;s Connell Barrett previews the British Open and ProFootballTalk.com&apos;s Mike Florio discusses Arizona, NFL rumors and more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071806.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071806.mp3" length="53866654" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 12:07:51 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Miami Heat&apos;s Alonzo Mourning, Bears Legend Dan Hampton, MLB Update, Dodgers Draft Pick Clayton Kershaw, NASCAR Update</title>
            <description>Seven-time NBA All-Star Alonzo Mourning talks about winning it all in Miami. NFL HOFer and Chicago legend Dan Hampton talks about the &apos;85 Bears and breaks down this year&apos;s squad. Dave Pinto on Manny&apos;s injury, Barry Bonds&apos; legal trouble and more. Dodgers No. 1 draft pick Clayton Kershaw on playing in the pros. Matt Crossman on the Gordon-Kenseth feud, Danica &amp; &quot;Talledega Nights.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071306.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071306.mp3" length="52905649" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2006 16:08:03 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Bengals Legend Ickey Woods, NFL Update, ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney on MLB&apos;s 2nd Half, The Smithereens Pat Dinizio</title>
            <description>Cincinnati Bengals legend Ickey Woods talks about the NFL&apos;s crackdown on TD celebrations and more. Pro Football Talk&apos;s Mike Florio on Ricky Williams, Randy Moss and all the latest NFL news. ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney previews MLB&apos;s second half and The Smithereens frontman and life-long baseball fan Pat Dinizio on his new ESPN special.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071106.mp3" length="55198897" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2006 11:49:20 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - MLB 1st Half Recap, NBA Update, Wizards&apos;s Oleksiy Pecherov, World Cup Finals, Wimbledon Update with Luke Jensen</title>
            <description>Richard Justice recaps the biggest stories of baseball&apos;s first half.  Akron Journal writer Brian Windhorst on LeBron and more NBA news. Wizards first round draft pick Oleksiy Pecherov. World Cup finals preview with Bob Kellet.  Wimbledon update with ESPN&apos;s Luke Jensen.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast070606.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast070606.mp3" length="50987932" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2006 15:23:42 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NBA Draft Spectacular Live from Jay-Z&apos;s 40/40 Club</title>
            <description>Join SBL on location for the NBA Draft with Lottery Picks Rodney Carney and Rudy Gay, Rookie of the Year Chris Paul and Philadelphia 76ers Chris Webber live from the Toyota NBA Charity Stripe Party at Jay-Z&apos;s 40/40 Club in New York City.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast062906.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast062906.mp3" length="54453687" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2006 10:36:37 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NBA Draft with Chris Paul, Tampa Bay Safety Will Allen, Wimbledon Preview</title>
            <description>NBA Draft Preview with NBA Rookie of the Year Chris Paul, blogger J.E. Skeets and expert Johnathan Givony. Tampa Bay safety Will Allen talks Bucs pre-season, Ohio State football and more. Tennis analyst Murphy Jensen previews Wimbledon.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast062706.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast062706.mp3" length="55626305" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2006 11:54:18 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Yankees vs. Red Sox, Tigers vs. White Sox, NBA Finals, French Open, Stanley Cup Finals, NFL Rumor of the Week</title>
            <description>Hardball Bloggers Alex Belth and Vince Gallaro break down the two biggest MLB battles of the week. True Hoops&apos; Henry Abbott previews the NBA Finals. ESPN&apos;s Luke Jensen updates the French Open live from Paris. Eric McErlain previews the NHL Finals and NFL Rumor of the Week with Mike Florio of &quot;Pro Football Talk.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast060606.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast060606.mp3" length="60076917" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 6 Jun 2006 11:10:13 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - ESPN&apos;s Jayson Stark and David Pinto on MLB&apos;s Top Records, NBA Playoffs with Roundball Bloggers, World Cup Preview</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Jayson Stark and Baseball Musings&apos; David Pinto on baseball&apos;s top 10  records and the Rocket&apos;s return. Roundball Bloggers Brian the Cavalier and Need 4 Sheed&apos;s Natalie Sitto on the NBA Playoffs. World Cup preview with blogger Sean Keener from Berlin.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast060106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast060106.mp3" length="50745948" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2006 13:41:32 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Spawn Creator Todd McFarlane, French Open with Luke Jensen, NCAA Football, NFL Rumor of the Week</title>
            <description>Uber-collector Todd McFarlane discusses Barry Bonds memorabilia, HR records &amp; man toys. CT tells us about his trip to the Coke 600. ESPN&apos;s Luke Jensen updates the French Open live from Paris. CBS SportsLine&apos;s Dennis Dodd talks NCAA Football and NFL Rumor of the Week with Mike Florio of &quot;Pro Football Talk.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast053106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast053106.mp3" length="56239545" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NBA Playoffs with Bill Walton, NBA Draft, MLB with ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney, Indy 500, Coca-Cola 600</title>
            <description>Basketball legend Bill Walton breaks down the NBA Playoffs while J.T. Magee previews the Draft. ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney on Bonds, the Yankees and more MLB news. Indy 500 and Coca-Cola 600 previews with C.T. live from Charlotte and blogger Matt Mercer.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast052506.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast052506.mp3" length="50608919" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Yankees Coach Don Mattingly, HOFer Tom Seaver, MLB Bloggers, NBA Playoffs, NFL Rumor of the Week</title>
            <description>Yankees coach Don Mattingly discusses the Red Sox rivalry and more. HOFer Tom Seaver takes a look a today&apos;s top pitchers. Bloggers Yanksfan vs. Soxfan preview the upcoming series. Bloggers from &quot;Yay Sports&quot; and &quot;Detroit Bad Boys&quot;  talk NBA Playoffs and NFL Rumor of the Week with Mike Florio of &quot;Pro Football Talk.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast052306.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast052306.mp3" length="55476303" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - MLB with Richard Justice, Serena Williams, NBA Playoffs, NHL Playoffs, Preakness Preview</title>
            <description>Houston Chronicle&apos;s Richard Justice talks about Roger Clemens&apos; imminent return. Blogger Geoff Young on the Padres. Tennis superstar Serena Williams talks tennis, fashion and more. NBA Playoffs with Tas Melas. NHL Playoffs with Eric McErlain. Daily Racing Form&apos;s Dan Illman previews the Preakness.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051806.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051806.mp3" length="50658297" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - MLB with HOFer Ernie Banks and Will Carroll, NBA Playoffs, World Cup Preview, NFL Rumors</title>
            <description>Baseball Insider Will Carroll and Cubs legend Ernie Banks talk Bonds, Pujols and more. Roundball Bloggers Henry Abbott and Joe Boikess discuss the NBA Playoffs. Blogger Bob Kellet previews the 2006 World Cup and NFL Rumor of the Week with Mike Florio of &quot;Pro Football Talk.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051606.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051606.mp3" length="52504832" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Barry Bonds &amp; MLB Surprise Teams, NBA Playoffs with Scoop Jackson, NASCAR Fans with Matt Crossman</title>
            <description>Hardball Bloggers discuss the Barry Bonds backlash and this season&apos;s surprise teams, the Tigers, Reds and Rockies. ESPN&apos;s Scoop Jackson discusses LeBron and the NBA Playoffs. The Sporting News&apos; Matt Crossman visits the world of NASCAR fans.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051106.mp3" length="50787506" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NBA Playoffs, Yankees vs. Red Sox Preview, NHL Playoffs, NFL Rumor of the Week</title>
            <description>NBA Playoff update with Roundball Bloggers. Yankees vs. Red Sox series analysis with Fox Sports&apos; Ty Hildenbrandt and Chad Finn. NHL Playoff update with Eric McErlain of Off WIng Opinion and NFL Rumor of the Week with Mike Florio of &quot;Pro Football Talk.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050906.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050906.mp3" length="54046592" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 9 May 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL&apos;s Most Improved Teams, MLB Update, NBA Playoffs, Kentucky Derby with Robin Leach and the DRF</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Jeff Chadiha lists the NFL&apos;s most improved teams after the Draft. Baseball insider Will Carroll on the MLB&apos;s 1st month and Barry Bonds. NBA Playoff update with TrueHoop.com&apos;s Henry Abbott. Kentucky Derby preview with Robin Leach and Daily Racing Form&apos;s Dan Illman.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050406.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050406.mp3" length="50608710" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - HBO&apos;s Bob Costas on State of the MLB, NFL Draft Recap, NBA Playoffs</title>
            <description>HBO&apos;s Bob Costas talks about his exclusive interview with Willie Mays, the steroid problem in baseball and more.  Mike Florio from &quot;Pro Football Talk&quot; and the Pigskin Bloggers recap the NFL Draft. SI&apos;s Chris Ballard discusses LeBron&apos;s NBA Playoff problems and the rest of the hardwood action.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050206.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050206.mp3" length="56059849" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 2 May 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Reggie Bush, NFL Draft Preview with Pat Kirwan, Golf Hottie Natalie Gulbis</title>
            <description>Heisman Trophy winner and probable No. 1 Draft Pick Reggie Bush on his future, his blog and more! NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan and Pigskin Bloggers break down the Draft. LPGA star &amp; cover girl Natalie Gulbis talks about Michelle Wie, her calendar shoot and more!</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast042406.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast042406.mp3" length="52425680" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Barry Bonds Author, Philly Eagles Safety Brian Dawkins, NBA &amp; NHL Playoff Previews</title>
            <description>Author Jeff Pearlman on &quot;Love Me Hate Me: Barry Bonds and the Making of an Antihero.&quot; Eagles safety Brian Dawkins on TO and more. Roundball Bloggers preview the NBA Playoffs.  Eric McErlain previews the NHL Playoffs.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast042006.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast042006.mp3" length="53337450" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NBA Star Carmelo Anthony, HBO&apos;s Mary Carillo, MLB, NFL Update</title>
            <description>Denver Nuggets star Carmelo Anthony and Harball Blogger Henry Abbot preview the NBA Playoffs. Baseball Musings&apos; David Pinto talks about MLB&apos;s offensive explosion. HBO&apos;s Mary Carillo on former Phillies star Darren Daulton and NFL update with Mike Florio.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast041806.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast041806.mp3" length="53081165" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney, NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan, NBA Playoffs, NASCAR</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney and SI&apos;s Alex Belth discuss MLB injuries, Barry Bonds and New York&apos;s slow start and more. NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan on off-season news. Steve Aschburner&apos;s early NBA Playoff preview.  TSN&apos;s Matt Crossman on the NASCAR cat fights.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast041106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast041106.mp3" length="50554189" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Yankees Jorge Posada, MADtv&apos;s Frank Caliendo, NFL, NBA Draft Watch</title>
            <description>New York Yankees All-Star catcher Jorge Posada and David Pinto talk about the new MLB season.  MADtv and NFL on FOX funnyman Frank Caliendo drops by the studio to talk NFL and make us cry. Dave&apos;s Football Blog off-season update. Blogger Jason Kent&apos;s NBA Draft stock watch.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast040606.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast040606.mp3" length="51536840" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 6 Apr 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - 2006 MLB Preview Spectacular</title>
            <description>SBL&apos;s star-studded MLB 2006 Preview covers all the bases with legends Cal Ripken, Reggie Jackson, Will Clark, Bruce Sutter, Prison Break&apos;s Amaury Nolasco and a bevy of Harball Bloggers.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast040306.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast040306.mp3" length="68210679" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 3 Apr 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - SBLX: 2006 Masters Preview with Dean Reinmuth</title>
            <description>Golf expert and Phil Mickelson&apos;s former trainer Dean Reinmuth previews the 2006 Masters.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast033106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast033106.mp3" length="13465703" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - AL and NL West Preview, Will Clark, Final Four, Prison Break&apos;s Amaury Nolasco</title>
            <description>Six-Time All-Star Will Clark joins Hardball Bloggers Jon Weisman and Tyler Bleszinski to preview the AL and NL West. Author John Feinstein preview the Final Four. &apos;Prison Break&apos; star and die-hard Yankees fan Amaury Nolasco talks about the new season and his new movie &apos;Benchwarmers.&apos;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast033006.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast033006.mp3" length="61324974" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Final Four Preview with ESPN&apos;s Michael Wilbon, AL and NL Central Preview, Jon Lovitz</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Michael Wilbon discusses George Mason&apos;s historic Tournament run and previews the Final Four. The SBL Crew shares audio from their DC Regional experience. Hardball Bloggers preview the AL and NL Central. Actor Jon Lovitz on &quot;The Benchwarmers.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast032806.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast032806.mp3" length="57906155" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - AL and NL East Preview, Reggie Jackson, NCAA Hoops, Players Championship</title>
            <description>Yankees legend and HOFer Reggie Jackson joins Hardball Bloggers Chad Finn and Michael Elkon to preview the AL and NL East. Sports Illustrated&apos;s Andy Gray fills us in on the NCAA Hoops &quot;What If&quot; Tournament. Golf expert Dean Reinmuth previews the Players Championship.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast032306.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast032306.mp3" length="52957070" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Sweet 16 Preview, T.O. and Tagliabue Analysis, NASCAR Update</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated&apos;s Luke win previews all of the action from the Sweet 16, AOL&apos;s Jim Armstrong talks about T.O. to Dallas and Paul Taglibue&apos;s retirement.  The Sporting News&apos; Matt Crossman previews NASCAR&apos;s Food City 500 and talks about Bill Lester&apos;s historic race.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast032106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast032106.mp3" length="50812327" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NCAA Hoops, HOFer James Worthy,  NFL Offseason Update, HOFer Mike Schmidt</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Dan Shanoff names his &quot;All-Talent&quot; Tournament team. Hoops legend James Worthy makes his Final Four picks &amp; talks about Kobe and the Lakers.  NFL off season update with Mike Florio. Baseball HOFer Mike Schmidt discusses his new book, Barry Bonds and the Phillies.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast031606.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast031606.mp3" length="51500716" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Final Four Picks &amp; Georgetown&apos;s John Thompson III</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated&apos;s Stewart Mandel make his picks for the Final Four. Georgetown Head Coach John Thompson III gives us his thoughts on the Big Dance and blogger &quot;Eagles in Atlanta&quot; on Boston College&apos;s chances.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast031406.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast031406.mp3" length="27141923" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Syracuse Coach Jim Boeheim, Cinderellas and Upsets</title>
            <description>Syracuse Head Coach Jim Boeheim discusses his team&apos;s incredible late-season performance, previews their 1st Round game, tells us who he likes in the Tourney and more. Rivals.com Managing Editor Bob McClellan picks 2006&apos;s Cinderellas and biggest potential upsets.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast031306.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast031306.mp3" length="28746982" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - March Madness Preview: Bracket Tips</title>
            <description>Impress your friends, amaze your co-workers and win your office pool! FanBall&apos;s Court Mann tells you everything you need to know to fill our your brackets.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/031206_sbl_msr_bracket.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/031206_sbl_msr_bracket.mp3" length="18950986" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2006 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - March Madness Preview: Atlanta Region</title>
            <description>CBS SportsLine&apos;s Tony Mejia previews the Atlanta Region with bloggers from March Madness All Season, Colonial Hoops and more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/031206_sbl_msr_atlanta.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/031206_sbl_msr_atlanta.mp3" length="17669067" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2006 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - March Madness Preview: Minneapolis Region</title>
            <description>Chris and Craig from Bracketology 101 preview the Minneapolis Region with Florida Head Coach Billy Donovan and bloggers from Florida Baskeball.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/031206_sbl_msr_minny.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/031206_sbl_msr_minny.mp3" length="15440764" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2006 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - March Madness Preview: Oakland Region</title>
            <description>Sportz Assassin previews the Oakland Region with bloggers from Pitt Panthers Hoops, Kansas&apos; Phog Blog and more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/031206_sbl_msr_oakland.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/031206_sbl_msr_oakland.mp3" length="14520731" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2006 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - March Madness Preview: Washington D.C. Region</title>
            <description>Rivals.com Managing Editor Bob McClellan previews the Washington D.C. Region with bloggers from Husky Blog, Illini Wonk and UNC Basketball Update.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/031206_sbl_msr_dc.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/031206_sbl_msr_dc.mp3" length="22001564" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - 2006 Most Hated Athletes Show</title>
            <description>Bloggers from around the Blogosphere join the The SBL Crew to name this year&apos;s &quot;Most Hated Athletes&quot; in the NFL, MLB, NBA, NHL, NCAA Football, NCAA Basketball and NASCAR as voted on by their readers.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast030906.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast030906.mp3" length="50503449" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 9 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Florida Men&apos;s Basketball Coach Billy Donovan</title>
            <description>The Madness is mounting as Florida Gator Head Coach Billy Donovan stops by to talk about his young squad&apos;s impressive 17-0 start, their impressive win over Kentucky to end the season, the upcoming Tourney and more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast030806.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast030806.mp3" length="16985524" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 8 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - SI&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha on the NFL, ESPN&apos;s Pat Forde on the Madness, John Rocker, Deadspin</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha says T.O. could be headed to Miami as SBL covers NFL labor issues, free agents and The Draft. ESPN&apos;s Pat Forde previews the Madness. Former MLB bad boy John Rocker discusses &apos;Pros vs. Joes.&apos; Deadspin talks about facing Rocker.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast030706.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast030706.mp3" length="50365216" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 7 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney on the WBC, Georgetown&apos;s John Thompson III, NFL Fallout, NBA, NHL</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney previews the World Baseball Classic, Georgetown head coach John Thompson III discusses his team&apos;s success, the Football Outsiders break down the NFL&apos;s CBA deadline, &apos;The Basketball Jones&apos; talks NBA and Off Wing Opinion on post-Olympics hockey.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast030206.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast030206.mp3" length="50601746" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 1 Mar 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Combine Report, Yanks vs. Red Sox, NCAA Hoops, NCAA Football</title>
            <description>NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan reports from Combine where Leinart plays it cool, Cutler&apos;s stock soars, Young suffers through the Wonderlic and Bloom and Vick fail to impress. Yanksfan vs. Soxfan on the renewed rivalry. Bloggers on College Hoops. CSTV&apos;s Tom Lemming on NCAA Football&apos;s top recruiting classes.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022806.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022806.mp3" length="50745533" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Women&apos;s Figure Skating Recap with Michael Weiss</title>
            <description>Two-time Olympic figure skater Michael Weiss wraps up the Women&apos;s Olympic Figure Skating action, tells us what&apos;s in store for Sasha Cohen now, looks ahead to 2010 and more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022506.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022506.mp3" length="24096067" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Hot Olympians, MLB with Cal Ripken and Will Carroll, NCAA Hoops with ESPN&apos;s Pat Forde, NBA Update</title>
            <description>We name the hottest 2006 Winter Olympians with HotAthletes. Future HOFer Cal Ripken and baseball insider Will Carroll on Bonds and the MLB. ESPN&apos;s Pat Forde on college hoops. NBA 2nd half preview with Brent Edwards from &quot;The Association&quot; blog.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022406.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022406.mp3" length="50370655" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Michael Weiss Updates Women&apos;s Figure Skating</title>
            <description>Two-time Olympic figure skater Michael Weiss recaps the Women&apos;s Figure Skating short program, takes a look ahead to the long programs and tells us who he thinks will end up on the podium. Olympics blogger Noelle reports in from Italy.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022306.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022306.mp3" length="24096067" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Olympian Shaun White, NFL and NBA Trade Rumors, West Coast NCAA Hoops, Daytona 500 Recap</title>
            <description>Coztanza&apos;s Jets Commentary and Bolts Blog on trade and signing rumors in N.Y. and San Diego. Hoops Hype with NBA trade deadline rumors. Fred Wallin on West Coast college hoops. Monte Dutton recaps the Daytona 500. Olympian Shaun White on winning Gold.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022206.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022206.mp3" length="50804680" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Olympic Figure Skating Update</title>
            <description>Two-time Olympic figure skater Michael Weiss recaps the Men&apos;s Event and Johnny Weir&apos;s breakdown before he previews the Women&apos;s competition, tells us who Sasha Cohen has to beat to win the gold and points out some underdogs who could make a run at a medal.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast021706.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast021706.mp3" length="20681180" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Free Agents, NCAA Bracketology, Gretzky&apos;s Gambling, Daytona, Olympics</title>
            <description>Football Outsiders&apos; Al Bogdan picks the NFL free agent class of &apos;06. Bracketology 101 names his NCAA Tourney Field of 65. Off Wing on Gretzky&apos;s gambling . Diecast Dude&apos;s Daytona picks. Former Olympic skater Michael Weiss on Turin, Kwan &amp; more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast021406.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast021406.mp3" length="52909617" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Winter Olympics Preview</title>
            <description>Medal favorites Johnny Weir, Shaun White and Sasha Cohen weigh in on everything from the Bode and Kwan controversies to meeting Lohan and rating Russian mullets while Olympians Jaret Peterson, Casey FitzRandolph and Hannah Teter preview their events and more!</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast010906.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast010906.mp3" length="56458461" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Super Bowl XL Postgame Show</title>
            <description>Steelers Nation and Dave&apos;s Football Blog are fired up following Pittsburgh&apos;s 21-10 victory while Seattle&apos;s 12th Man and others are griping about three big blown calls. AdJab Rates the Super Bowl commercials and TV Squad dishes on the broadcast.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020606.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020606.mp3" length="50334862" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 6 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Super Bowl Spectacular Live from Detroit - Part 2</title>
            <description>It&apos;s Hour 2 of the XL-sized Super Bowl show co-hosted by Tom Arnold live from the NFL Experience featuring Mad TV&apos;s Frank Caliendo, Seattle&apos;s Michael Boulware, ESPN&apos;s Michael Wilbon, Detroit&apos;s Scott Vines, Steelerbaby, Deadspin and more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020306b.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020306b.mp3" length="50504238" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sat, 4 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Super Bowl Spectacular Live from Detroit - Part 1</title>
            <description>It&apos;s Hour 1 of the XL-sized Super Bowl show co-hosted by Tom Arnold live from the NFL Experience in Detroit featuring Joe Montana, Jon Bon Jovi, John Elway, Big Ben, Matt Hasselbeck, Mike Holgram, Jerome Bettis, Flea, Dan Marino and more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020306a.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020306a.mp3" length="50145808" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Fri, 3 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Super Bowl Extra Live from Detroit #1</title>
            <description>SBL&apos;s Super Bowl week extravaganza continues with CT&apos;s report from Media Day in Detroit, while Seahawks blogger &quot;The 12th Man&quot; talks about the lawsuit the Texas A&amp;M has brought against the team and more.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast020106.mp3" length="13579706" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 1 Feb 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Super Bowl Preview with Michael Wilbon &amp; Tom Arnold, NBA with Flea, Tennis, Snowboarder Shaun White</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Michael Wilbon and special correspondent Tom Arnold join us from Detroit to preview the Super Bowl, talk about Brett Favre&apos;s retirement and more. Rock legend Flea talks Lakers and the NBA. SI&apos;s Justin Gimelstob on tennis. Olympic snowboarder Shaun White on Torino.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast013106.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast013106.mp3" length="53949521" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Super Bowl Preview with Dan Marino, Steeler Baby, MLB, NBA, NCAA Hoops, Tennis</title>
            <description>NFL legend Dan Marino and Steeler Baby preview the Super Bowl. MLB Insider Will Carroll on baseball&apos;s free agents. Ron Artest reaction with Kings Super Fans. NCAA hoops with Husky Blog. Australian Open with Tennis Channel madman Murphy Jensen.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast012606.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast012606.mp3" length="50292932" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Super Bowl Preview with Jeffri Chadiha, NBA, Alexander Ovechkin, Sasha Cohen</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated&apos;s Jeff Chadiha, Fox&apos;s Mike Tanier and Pigskin Bloggers break down the AFC and NFC championships, Super Boxl XL and more. Sportz Assassin on Kobe&apos;s 81-point game. Hockey phenom Alexander Ovechkin. Figure skating star and Olympic gold medal favorite Sasha Cohen.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast012406.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast012406.mp3" length="50492204" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Conference Championship Preview, ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney, NBA Update</title>
            <description>Pigskin Bloggers preview the NFC &amp; AFC Championship games. ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney and Blogger &apos;Dodger Thoughts&apos; on the World Baseball Classic, free agent moves and more. Deadspin on the NBA and the Antonio Davis incident.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast011906.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast011906.mp3" length="50537810" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live -  AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Conference Championship Preview, Gilbert Arenas, Olympian Jeret Peterson</title>
            <description>NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan weighs in on Peyton Manning&apos;s playoff performance and the Denver Post&apos;s Jim Armstrong and Pigskin Bloggers discuss the NFL&apos;s final four. Wizards All-Star Gilbert Arenas drops by and Olympian ski aerialist Jeret &apos;Speedy&apos; Peterson talks Torino.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast011806.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast011806.mp3" length="51280623" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Divisional Playoffs with Peter King, MLB HOF, NCAA Hoops, Gambling</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated&apos;s Peter King and Pigskin Bloggers preview the NFL Divisional Playoffs.  FOX&apos;s Ken Rosenthal talks about the MLB Hall of Fame. Roundball Bloggers discuss the three undefeated teams in NCAA Hoops and legendary sports gambler Brandon Lang.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast011206.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast011206.mp3" length="52167199" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live -  NFL Divisional Playoff Preview, Actor Josh Lucas, NHL, Olympian Casey FitzRandolph</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha and FOX&apos;s Mike Tanier talk NFL Playoffs. &apos;Detroit Bad Boys&apos; and Bloggers talk NBA. &apos;Glory Road&apos; star Josh Lucas on his new movie. Off Wing Opinion&apos;s Eric McErlain on the NHL. Gold-medalist speed skater Casey FitzRandolph on Torino.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast011006.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast011006.mp3" length="52766527" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Wild Card Preview with Cris Collinsworth, Rose Bowl Reactions, MLB HOF with ESPN&apos;s Jayson Stark</title>
            <description>HBO&apos;s Cris Collinsworth and the Pigskin Bloggers preview NFL Wild Card Weekend and more. Texas and USC bloggers react to the Rose Bowl. ESPN&apos;s Jayson Stark and MLB Insider David Pinto discuss the 2006 Baseball Hall of Fame ballot.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast010506.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast010506.mp3" length="51465312" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 5 Jan 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 17 Recap, BCS Bowls Recap, CSI: Miami&apos;s Rex Linn, NCAA Hoops Midseason Awards</title>
            <description>CBS SportsLine Senior NFL Writer Pete Prisco and the Pigskin Bloggers discuss Week 17, coaching changes, the Playoffs and the Draft. CSTV&apos;s Brian Curtis, CSI: Miami&apos;s Rex Linn and Bloggers on the BCS Bowls. FOX Sports&apos; Yoco Hoops gives out NCAA Hoops midseason awards.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast010406.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast010406.mp3" length="51154020" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 3 Jan 2006 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Best of 2005</title>
            <description>Take a look back at SBL&apos;s first year with the best and the worst moments of 2005 including itnerviews with Ron Artest, Jerry Rice, Roger Clemens, Don Mattingly, Reggie Jackson, Mike Tyson, Chad Johnson, Jim Brown, Dwyane Wade, J.J. Redick and more!</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast122705.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast122705.mp3" length="51098431" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 16 with Michael Wilbon, Yankees vs. Red Sox, NBA, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Michael Wilbon and the Pigskin Bloggers preview Week 16 and more. Yankees and Red Sox Bloggers discuss the Johnny Damon signing.  We break down the big XMas NBA games with the Mighty MJD and our final Fantasy Football Focus with Charch.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast122205.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast122205.mp3" length="50790429" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 15 Recap, ESPN&apos;s Scoop Jackson on the NBA, BCS Bowl Preview, Olympics Preview</title>
            <description>NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan and Colt Freaks recap Week 15, discuss New England&apos;s resurgence, Indy&apos;s loss and more. ESPN&apos;s Scoop Jackson on Artest and the NBA. ESPN&apos;s Pat Forde and SI&apos;s Stewart Mandel preview the BCS Bowls and we start talking Winter Olympics with our Road to Torino Blogger.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast122005.mp3</link>
            <author>shawnschrager@aol.com (Shawn Schrager)</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast122005.mp3" length="60445393" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 15 with John Riggins, Don Shula and Roy Firestone, Survivor Winner Danni Boatwright, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>NFL Hall of Famers John Riggins and Coach Don Shula preview Week 15, discuss the &apos;72 Dolphins vs. &apos;05 Colts and more with the help of AOL&apos;s Roy Firestone. Survivor winner and sports fan Danni Boatwright and Fantasy Football with Charch.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast121505.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast121505.mp3" length="59079108" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 14 Recap with Jeffri Chadiha, Author John Feinstein, MLB Update, NBA TV on Artest and Riley, 2006 Heisman Race</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha breaks down the evolving playoff picture and Week 14 while author John Feinstein goes behind the scenes of the NFL. Fox&apos;s Ken Rosenthal on the latest MLB moves. NBA TV&apos;s John Andariese on Ron Artest and Pat Riley. Heisman Pundit&apos;s 2006 predictions.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast121305.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast121305.mp3" length="57624093" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 14 with Cris Carter, MLB Hot Stove, Venus Williams, Murderball, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>HBO&apos;s Cris Carter and Pigskin Bloggers preview NFL Week 14. Will Carroll talks MLB Hot Stove from the Winter Meetings. Tennis superstar Venus Williams discusses her career and more. Murderball and Quad Rugby star Mark Zupan on the movie, his life and more. Fantasy Football with Charch.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast120805.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast120805.mp3" length="60069730" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 8 Dec 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 13 Recap, MLB Winter Meetings, BCS Bowls, NBA, NHL</title>
            <description>NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan and Pigskin Bloggers recap Week 13 and look ahead to the playoffs. MLB Insider Will Carroll reports from the Winter Meetings while Alex the Blog Phenom discusses Manny. TSN&apos;s Tom Dienhart discusses the BCS Bowl matchups. NBA with blogger FreeDarko.com and NHL with Off Wing Opinion.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast120605.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast120605.mp3" length="56021833" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 6 Dec 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 13 with Jeffri Chadiha, MLB, NCAA Football Preview, Boxing with Bert Sugar, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha previews NFL Week 13. We analyze all of the latest MLB Hot Stove action. CBS SportsLine&apos;s Dennis Dodd breaks down the weekend&apos;s NCAA football championship games. HBO&apos;s Bert Sugar talks Taylor-Hopkins 2 and Fantasy Football with Charch.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast120105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast120105.mp3" length="53636608" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sat, 3 Dec 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 12 with Peter King, NCAA Hoops, Survivor Gary Hogeboom, NBA, Snowboarder Hannah Teter</title>
            <description>Sport Illustrated&apos;s Peter King breaks down Indy&apos;s perfect season and NFL Week 12 before real-life Bears superfan John Kent discusses his lucky beard. SI&apos;s Luke Winn on College Hoops. Ex-Dallas QB Gary Hogeboom on &apos;Survivor.&apos; NBA TV&apos;s Fred Carter on LeBron and snowboarder Hannah Teter on &apos;First Descent.&apos;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast112905.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast112905.mp3" length="57111387" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Duke&apos;s J.J. Redick, NFL Week 11 Recap, NCAA Football Preview, MLB Hot Stove</title>
            <description>Duke&apos;s J.J. Redick discusses haters, Crazies, poetry, cars and more. SI&apos;s Seth Davis makes Final Four predictions. NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan and Deadspin recap Week 11. New York Times&apos; Warren St. John previews NCAA Football and Baseball Musings on the MLB Hot Stove.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast112105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast112105.mp3" length="54520988" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2005 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 11 with Cris Carter, ESPN&apos;s Pat Forde, WSoP Champ Joe Hachem, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>Inside the NFL&apos;s Cris Carter previews Week 11, talks about T.O. and takes some shots at Bill Romanowski. ESPN&apos;s Pat Forde talks about the Miami rap scandal and previews Rivalry Week. World Series of Poker Champ Joe Hachem goes all in and Fantasy Football with Court Mann.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast111705.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast111705.mp3" length="50958340" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 3 Nov 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - MLB with ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney, NFL Week 10 Recap, NBA with TNT, NASCAR</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney and Mets Blog discuss Manny and Ichiro going to New York, free agents, steroids and fake news conferences. NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan recaps Week 10. TNT&apos;s David Aldridge and Yay! Sports on the NBA and The Sporting News&apos; Matt Crossman on NASCAR.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast111405.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast111405.mp3" length="54096844" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2005 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 10 with CBS&apos; Jim Nantz, NCAA Football Preview, NCAA Hoops Preview, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>The voice of CBS Sports Jim Nantz, Pigskin Bloggers and author Jere Longman preview NFL Week 10, talk TO. and discuss Eagle Fans. CSTV&apos;s Brian Curtis previews NCAA Football&apos;s biggest games.  The Sporting News&apos; Mike DeCourcey looks at NCAA Hoops All-Americans and Fantasy Football with Charch.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast111005.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast111005.mp3" length="52233164" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 3 Nov 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Ron Artest, SI&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha on T.O., NCAA Football, NASCAR</title>
            <description>NBA superstar, rapper and aspiring boxer Ron Artest discusses his game, music, a bout with Ben Wallace, cars and more. SI&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha talks about the latest T.O. suspension and the NFL. &quot;Football Outsiders&quot; on the BCS and more NCAA football. Bloggers Diecast Dude and Scottish Racer on NASCAR.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110805.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110805.mp3" length="51407892" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 8 Nov 2005 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Boomer Esiason Previews NFL Week 9, HBO&apos;s Bernie Goldberg on Ron Artest, NCAA Football, NCAA Hoops, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>CBS Sports&apos; Boomer Esiason previews NFL Week 9, ESPN &quot;Playmakers&quot; writer Peter Eagan on his controversial new football game, &quot;Blitz: The League,&quot; HBO&apos;s Bernie Goldberg discusses his interview with Ron Artest, NCAA Football and Basketball previews and Fantasy Football.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110305.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110305.mp3" length="52997837" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 3 Nov 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Bill Romanowski, NFL Week 8 Recap, MLB, Miami Heat&apos;s Dwyane Wade, NHL</title>
            <description>Bill Romanowski discusses his new tell-all book. NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan and the Mighty MJD recap NFL Week 8. Baseball Musings talks Theo leaving Boston and MLB free agents. Dwyane Wade previews the NBA East and Off Wing reviews the NHL&apos;s first month.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast110105.mp3" length="53265730" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 1 Nov 2005 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 8 Preview, World Series Wrap, NCAA Football, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>The Denver Post&apos;s Jim Armstrong and Pigskin Bloggers preview NFL Week 8. Baseball insider Will Carroll wraps up the World Series and talks MLB Hot Stove.  A White Sox blogger celebrates his win. New York Times writer Warren St. John previews college football and Fantasy Football Focus with Charch!</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast102705.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast102705.mp3" length="53436570" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - SI&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha Recaps NFL Week, ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney, NBA Preview, Heisman Update</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha and Pigskin Bloggers discuss Pittsburgh&apos;s domination of the Bengals, Eli&apos;s arrival and TD dances. ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney discusses the World Series. The Sporting News&apos; Sean Deveney previews the NBA West and the Heisman Pundit updates the Heisman Chase.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast102405.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast102405.mp3" length="50979373" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Cris Collinsworth Previews NFL Week 7, World Series Preview, NCAAF Preview, NBA Dress Code, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>HBO&apos;s Inside the NFL co-host Cris Collinsworth previews Week 7. USA Today&apos;s Mel Antonen and Hardball Bloggers preview the World Series. New York Times writer Warren St. John previews NCAA Football. Deadspin discusses the NBA dress code and Fantasy Football with Charch.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast102005.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast102005.mp3" length="54576463" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - &quot;John Madden,&quot; Houston&apos;s Craig Biggio, NCAA Football, NASCAR</title>
            <description>&quot;John Madden&quot; discusses the Vikings sex party, his man crush on Favre and more before Pigskin Bloggers recap Week 6. Astros star Craig Biggio talks about the MLB Playoffs. Fanblogs Kevin Donahue on the BCS. Sporting News NASCAR writer Matt Crossman on the Chase for the Nextel Cup.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101705.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101705.mp3" length="52741946" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Cal Ripken, NFL Week 6, NCAA Football, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>Future Hall-of-Famer and MLB Legend Cal Ripken discusses the playoffs and more.  Sports Illustrated&apos;s NFL senior writer Michael Silver talks about Ricky Williams&apos; return while bloggers preview Week 6.  CBS SportsLine&apos;s Dennis Dodd previews NCAA Football and Charch talks Fantasy Football.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101305.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101305.mp3" length="50522383" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 5 Recap, MLB Playoffs, Caps Owner Ted Leonsis, NASCAR</title>
            <description>NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan and Pigskin Bloggers recap Week 5. Baseball insider Will Carroll talks MLB Playoffs. Caps owner Ted Leonsis discusses the return of the NHL and Scottish Racer on the Chase for the NEXTEL Cup.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101005.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast101005.mp3" length="51711510" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 5 with Peter King, MLB with Ken Rosenthal,  NCAAF Preview, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated NFL writer Peter King previews all of the action in Week 5. FOX Sports&apos; Ken Rosenthal and DeadSpin break down the MLB Playoffs, NCAA Pigskin Bloggers preview college football&apos;s biggest games and Charch&apos;s Fantasy Football Focus.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast100605.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast100605.mp3" length="50278220" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 6 Oct 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Buster Olney &amp; Reggie Jackson Preview the MLB, NFL Week 4 Recap, NHL, Sumo</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney, &quot;Mr. October&quot; Reggie Jackson and Alex the Blog Phenom preview the MLB Playoffs. Football Outsiders recap Week 4 in the NFL.  Sports Illustrated&apos;s Michael Farber previews the NHL and sumo wrestling with Musashimaru!</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast100305.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast100305.mp3" length="52514176" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 3 Oct 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - MLB with Bill Simmons &amp; Mick Foley, NFL Week 4, NCAAF Preview, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s &quot;Sports Guy&quot; Bill Simmons and WWE&apos;s Mick &quot;Mankind&quot; Foley discuss their new books, the Yankees-Red Sox battle for the playoffs and more. NFL.com&apos;s Vic Carucci previews Week 4. ESPN&apos;s Dan Shanoff previews NCAA Football&apos;s biggest games and Charch&apos;s Fantasy Football Focus.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092905.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092905.mp3" length="56372618" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 3 Recap, MLB Pennant Chase, Heisman Chase, Golf</title>
            <description>NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan breaks down Week 3 and AOL&apos;s Roy Firestone discusses Brett Favre&apos;s career. Sports Illustrated&apos;s John Donovan on MLB&apos;s pennant chase, Heisman Pundit updates the 2005 campaign and GOLF Magazine&apos;s Connell Barrett on USA&apos;s weekend Presidents Cup win.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092605.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092605.mp3" length="50898686" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Dan Marino, NFL Week 3, NCAA Football, Matt Kenseth, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>HBO&apos;s Dan Marino and Pigskin Bloggers preview Week 3 in the NFL. The Sporting News college football writer Tom Dienhart previews the weekend&apos;s NCAA action. NASCAR&apos;s No. 17 Matt Kenseth talks about the Chase for the NEXTEL Cup and Paul Charchian on Fantasy Football.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092205.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast092205.mp3" length="50276375" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Reggie Jackson, MLB, NFL Week 2 Recap, NASCAR</title>
            <description>Reggie Jackson discusses the Yanks, Red Sox, Bonds, &apos;Naked Gun&apos; while MLB Insider Will Carroll breaks down the playoff push. Sports Illustrated&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha and Pigskin Bloggers on the NFL, The Sporting News&apos; NASCAR writer Matt Crossman and bloggers Scottish and the Dude on The Chase.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091905.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091905.mp3" length="53132127" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 2 Preview, NCAA Football Preview, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>CBS Sports NFL announcer Dave Sims previews Week 2.  Sports Illustrated college football writer Stewart Mandel breaks down Florida vs. Tennessee and the rest of big NCAA football matchups and Fantasy Football Focus with Charch.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091505.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091505.mp3" length="51772136" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Week 1, MLB Hot Topics, U.S. Open Wrap, NASCAR</title>
            <description>NFL.com&apos;s Vic Carucci and Pigskin Bloggers recap Week 1. MLB insider Dave Pinto discusses Randy Johnson&apos;s resurgence, Barry Bonds&apos;s return, Manny Ramirez&apos;s odd behavior and more. The Tennis Channel&apos;s Murphy Jensen recaps the Open and TNT&apos;s Allen Bestwick previews the Chase for the NEXTEL Cup.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091205.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast091205.mp3" length="55081597" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Jerry Rice, Joe Theismann, Ken Rosenthal, NCAA Football</title>
            <description>NFL great Jerry Rice joins SBL to discuss his recent retirement, the game today and his future. ESPN&apos;s Joe Theismann previews Week 1 in the NFL.  Fox Sports&apos; Ken Rosenthal previews the Yankees-Red Sox series.  SI&apos;s Austin Murphy previews the big NCAA football matchups and Fantasy Football Focus with Charch.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast090805.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast090805.mp3" length="52261982" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 8 Sep 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - NFL, Barry Bonds Comeback, U.S. Open&apos;s Justin Gimelstob, TNT&apos;s Wally Dallenbach</title>
            <description>NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan and Jim Armstrong discuss Pats-Raiders, Jerry Rice&apos;s retirement and the Saints unfortunate problems. U.S. Open player Justin Gimelstob discusses women&apos;s tennis, bloggers talk Barry Bonds and NASCAR on TNT&apos;s Wally Dallenbach previews Richmond.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast090605.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast090605.mp3" length="52632105" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 6 Sep 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AOL&apos;s Sports Bloggers Live - Yanx-Sox, ACC Preview, Anthony Munoz, Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>MLB Insider Will Carroll takes a look at the surging Yankees and other baseball hot topics, we preview the ACC with Rival.com&apos;s Chris Wallace, discuss college football with NFL great Anthony Munoz and get you ready for Fantasy Football with Charch.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast090105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast090105.mp3" length="45291210" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 1 Sep 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - NFC East Preview, Donovan McNabb, Michael Stahan, Heisman, U.S. Open</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated&apos;s Jeffri Chadiha, Eagles QB Donovan McNabb, Giants&apos; DE Michael Strahan, podcasters and an NFL cheerleader preview the NFC East.  Heisman Pundit takes any early look at the favorites and ESPN&apos;s Luke Jensen breaks down the U.S. Open.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082905.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082905.mp3" length="52118164" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Big Ten Preview, MLB Hot Topics, NCAA Hoops with Mike DeCourcey and Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated&apos;s college football writer Mark Beech previews the Big Ten. Dave Pinto takes a look at MLB young phenoms while Houston Chronicle&apos;s Richard Justice explores the problem with steroid rumors.  The Sporting News&apos; college hoops expert Mike DeCourcey tells us why firing Cincinnati&apos;s Bob Huggins was a bad move and FanBall&apos;s Paul Charchian provides fantasy football tips.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082505.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082505.mp3" length="51135974" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - NFC North Preview, Peter King, Daunte Culpepper, Buster Olney, Video Games</title>
            <description>SI&apos;s Peter King, Vikings QB Daunte Culpepper, Lions&apos; WR Roy Williams and the Pigskin Bloggeers help preview the NFC North. ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney on MLB&apos;s rampant steroid rumors and we debate the best sports video games ever.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082205.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast082205.mp3" length="57361365" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Big XII Preview, Art Monk, NASCAR and Fantasy Football</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated&apos;s Gene Menez and bloggers preview the Big XII. We ask Redskins legend Art Monk about the Hall of Fame, T.O. and more. NASCAR bloggers update the Chase for the Cup and FanBall&apos;s Paul Charchian provides fantasy football tips.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast081805.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast081805.mp3" length="42779250" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - AFC East Preview, MLB Update and PGA Championship Recap</title>
            <description>NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan and bloggers preview the AFC East, FOX Sports&apos; Kevin Kennedy and a Yankees podcaster update the MLB playoff races and we recap the PGA Championship that was.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast081505.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast081505.mp3" length="51432960" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - ESPN&apos;s Michael Wilbon, SEC Preview, Don King, Fantasy TEs</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Michael Wilbon discusses the T.O. situation, Palmiero and steroids, Tiger Woods and more.  CBS SportsLine&apos;s college football columnist Dennis Dodd previews the SEC.  Don King talks boxing and pretty much everything else while FanBall&apos;s Paul Charchian previews Fantasy Football TEs.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast081105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast081105.mp3" length="44624710" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - AFC North Preview, Chad Johnson, Kevin Millar, PGA Championship Preview</title>
            <description>NFL.com&apos;s Vic Carucci previews the AFC North while Chad Johnson, Jim Brown, Big Ben and others give us their predictions. Alex the Phenom interviews Kevin Millar at Fenway and MLB expert Will Carroll talks hot topics while GOLF MAG&apos;s Connell Barrett previews the PGA Championship.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast080805.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast080805.mp3" length="50488439" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 8 Aug 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Kurt Warner, Big East, Dave Mirra, Fantasy WRs</title>
            <description>Arizona QB Kurt Warner looks ahead to the new season with a new team, SI&apos;s college football writer Stewart Mandel previews Notre Dame and the Big East, BMX superstar Dave Mirra takes us inside the XGames and FanBall&apos;s Paul Charchian takes a look at fantasy football WRs.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast080405.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast080405.mp3" length="43770233" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 4 Aug 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - NFC West Preview, Tom Verducci, Johnny Damon</title>
            <description>NFL.com&apos;s Vic Carucci previews the NFC West and the new-look Cardinals. Sports Illustrated&apos;s Tom Verducci discusses Rafael Palmeiro&apos;s legacy and MLB hot topics, Alex the Phenom interviews Johnny Damon from Fenway and NASCAR writer Monty Dutton talks Brickyard 400.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast080105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast080105.mp3" length="50392422" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 1 Aug 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Ben Roethlisberger, MLB Trade Rumors, Pac-10, Fantasy QBs</title>
            <description>Steelers QB Ben Roethlisberger takes a look at Pittsburgh&apos;s upcoming season, Ken Rosenthal talks MLB trade rumors, CBS SportsLine&apos;s Dennis Dodd previews the Pac-10 and FanBall&apos;s Paul Charchian breaks down the top QBs in Fantasy Football.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast072805.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast072805.mp3" length="39822755" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - NFC South Preview, Jim Brown, DeShaun Foster</title>
            <description>Our NFL preview continues with a look at the NFC South with NFL.com&apos;s Pat Kirwan and Carolina RB DeShaun Foster. NFL legend Jim Brown discusses Ricky Williams, the league and more, we spar with 12-year-old blog phenom Alex and recap the Tour de Lance with OLN&apos;s Paul Sherwen.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast072505.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast072505.mp3" length="55462285" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Drew Rosenhaus, MLB Trade Rumors, Fantasy RBs</title>
            <description>MLB expert Will Carroll gets us up to speed on the latest trade rumors, Super Agent Drew Rosenhaus tells us about his latest heroics and updates us on his war of words with Brett Farve, Fantasy Football guru Paul Charchian previews this year&apos;s crop of RBs and Mr. Moviefone reviews &quot;The Bad News Bears.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast072105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast072105.mp3" length="38307296" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - AFC West Preview, Tony Gonzalez, Trent Green</title>
            <description>Our NFL Preview continues with the AFC West. Sports Illustrated&apos;s Michael Silver and Kansas City Chiefs&apos; superstars Tony Gonzalez and Trent Green join us to break down the division. Baseball expert Will Carroll talks MLB hot topics and trade rumors and OLN&apos;s Phil Liggett takes a ride with Lance at the Tour de France.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071805.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071805.mp3" length="55320495" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Jennie Finch, Buster Olney, Robin Leach</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney previews the 2nd half of the MLB season, softball superstar and Sports Illustrated cover girl Jennie Finch stops by to express her anger at the IOC, USA Today&apos;s Michael McCarthy discusses the end of the NHL lockout and Robin Leach takes us beyond the velvet ropes at the World Series of Poker in Las Vegas.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071405.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071405.mp3" length="37996500" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - AFC South Preview, Byron Leftwich</title>
            <description>Are you ready for some football? Jaguars QB Byron Leftwich and Sporting News&apos; Vinnie Iyer help us preview the AFC South, author John Feinstein remembers Jack Nicklaus and GOLF MAGAZINE editor Josha Hill previews the British Open while OLN&apos;s Craig Hummer talks Lance and Tour de France.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast071105.mp3" length="53393074" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Don Mattingly, Ken Rosenthal</title>
            <description>Yankees legend and current batting coach Don Mattingly joins SBL to discuss his career, his future with the organization and more while The Sporting News&apos; Ken Rosenthal hands out his MLB mid-season awards.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast070705.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast070705.mp3" length="25845034" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 7 Jul 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - 7.05.2005</title>
            <description>The &apos;Football Scientist&apos; explains why Michael Vick doesn&apos;t live up to his hype and dispels other commonly held NFL myths. MLB trade rumors with baseball expert Will Carroll, Yankees talk with the Pinstripe Pulse, All-Star snubs with Alex the Blog Phenom and ESPN&apos;s Luke Jensen recaps Wimbledon.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast070505.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast070505.mp3" length="51304529" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 5 Jul 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - TNT&apos;s David Aldridge, Author Buzz Bissinger, OLN&apos;s Bob Roll</title>
            <description>TNT&apos;s NBA Insider David Aldridge and ESPN.com&apos;s Dan Shanoff break down the draft and preview the free agent free-for-all.  Author Buzz Bissinger discusses his new book, &quot;3 Nights in August,&quot; and OLN&apos;s Bob Roll previews the Tour de France.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast063005.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast063005.mp3" length="38003928" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - 6.27.2005</title>
            <description>Jim Armstrong explains why NBA teams should look overseas for the next great player and Hoops Bloggers preview the NBA Draft. MLB expert Will Carroll on the BoSox and other MLB hot topics, ESPN&apos;s Luke Jensen talks Wimbledon and NASCAR with Racing Bloggers.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast062705.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast062705.mp3" length="52477290" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - &quot;Best of...&quot; Volume 1</title>
            <description>Join the SBL 1-million-listen celebration with a look back at some of our best interviews including a candid conversation with Roger Clemens. Stick around for more hits from Mike Tyson&apos;s press conference, Drew Rosenhaus&apos; feisty interview and Alex the 12-year-old Blog Phenom&apos;s best phone call.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast062005.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast062005.mp3" length="54499280" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Offseason Report, MLB Update, HBO&apos;s Bernard Goldberg on OSU</title>
            <description>Phil Barber of The Sporting News gives us his NFL off season update, Baseball Musings discusses MLB hot topics and 8-Time Sports Emmy Award Winner and HBO Real Sports reporter Bernard Goldberg joins us to discuss recruiting problems with Ohio State hoops.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast061605.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast061605.mp3" length="34900717" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - 6.13.2005</title>
            <description>Blogger John Perricone says moving Derek Jeter to center would help the Yanks but Houston Chronicle and AOL baseball columnist Richard Justice disagrees. Author John Feinstein previews the U.S. Open and Denver Post columnist Jim Armstrong calls Mike Tyson&apos;s entire career a fraud.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast061305.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast061305.mp3" length="51342860" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Mike Tyson Interview, NBA Finals, Belmont Stakes</title>
            <description>We preview the weekend&apos;s big fight with an exclusive interview with Iron Mike Tyson.  We find out five reasons to watch the NBA Finals with columnist Steve Aschburner and we handicap the Belmont Stakes with Dave Grening of the Daily Racing Form.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast060905.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast060905.mp3" length="30658710" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 9 Jun 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - 6.6.2005</title>
            <description>The Sporting News&apos; Ken Rosenthal explains why Barry Bonds shouldn&apos;t come back, updates trade rumors and breaks down the MLB Draft. ESPN&apos;s Scoop Jackson previews the NBA Finals and talks about Shaq and bloggers talk about the NFL&apos;s ugly offseason and the latest NASCAR news.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast060605.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast060605.mp3" length="51592887" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 6 Jun 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Roger Clemens Interview</title>
            <description>Future Hall of Famer and current Houston Astros pitcher Roger Clemens joins SBL to discuss his career, his future and and more.  Mr. Moviefone reviews two new sports movies, &quot;Cinderella Man&quot; and &quot;The Lords of Dogtown.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast060205.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast060205.mp3" length="27830631" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 2 Jun 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - 5.31.2005</title>
            <description>Sports Illustrated&apos;s Andrew Perloff names the NFL&apos;s breakout stars of 2005. RealGM and RaptorBlog break down the NBA Draft. Author and Blogger Will Carroll hands out his MLB Almost Mid-Season Awards. AOL and Denver Post columnist Jim Armstrong loves Danica Patrick and blogger Scottish Racer tells us why Robby Gordon was right.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast053105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast053105.mp3" length="57178447" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - 5.26.2005</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney previews the big Yankees-Red Sox series, the bloggers from &quot;Yanksfan vs. Soxfan&quot; take some cheap shots at each other and Mr. Moviefone reviews &quot;The Longest Yard.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast052605.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast052605.mp3" length="21004288" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Drew Rosenhaus, Peter King</title>
            <description>Superagent Drew Rosenhaus and Sports Illustrated&apos;s football analyst Peter King join SBL to pick apart T.O.&apos;s contract situation, Ricky&apos;s return and much more. Baseball Musings&apos; David Pinto talks MLB and former doubles champ Luke Jensen previews the French Open.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast052305.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast052305.mp3" length="50485472" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - 5.19.2005</title>
            <description>The SBL Crew takes a look at the Abreu sex scandal, MLB author Will Carroll talks about the proposed universal drug policy and Barry Bonds&apos; latest deception, Hardball Bloggers preview MLB interleague play, Jim Armstrong picks the NBA champion and Kenny Peck from the Daily Racing Form handicaps the Preakness.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051905.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051905.mp3" length="33908923" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - 5.16.2005</title>
            <description>ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney and 12-year-old blog phenom Alex discuss the Yankee&apos;s sudden turnaround. We also cover T.O.&apos;s situation with the Denver Post&apos;s Jim Armstrong and Tiger&apos;s missed cut before announcing our McFarlane figure winners and the Rookie Blogger of the Week.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051605.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051605.mp3" length="51803114" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Spud Webb, Mr. Moviefone</title>
            <description>Former NBA superstar Spud Webb joins this week&apos;s SBL Extra to discuss the NBA Playoffs, bloggers debate the NBA All-Ugly Team and report on Charles Barkley and MJ&apos;s &quot;freak&quot; dancing in Vegas while Mr. Moviefone reviews Will Ferrell&apos;s new movie &quot;Kicking &amp; Screaming.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051205.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast051205.mp3" length="32450029" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Ken Rosenthal, Todd McFarlane</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[This week's SBL features the Sporting News' Ken Rosenthal discussing the best teams in baseball, other MLB hot topics and more, including:<br>
<b> </b>12 Year-Old Sports Phenom Alex on the Yanks' Demise<br>
<br>
<b> </b>NBA Playoffs Update with Heat and Spurs Bloggers<br>
<br>
<b> </b>Todd McFarlane, Spawn creator and sports toy maker<br>
<br>
<b> </b>Rookie Blogger of the Week<br>
<br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050905.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050905.mp3" length="60301119" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 9 May 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - Richard Justice, Robin Leach</title>
            <description>MLB columnist Richard Justice joins us on this week&apos;s SBL Extra to discuss the latest Yankees misfortunes, we preview the Churchill Downs party scene with Robin Leach and get Kentucky Derby analysis and predictions with the Daily Racing Form&apos;s Lauren Stich.</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050505.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050505.mp3" length="31847106" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 5 May 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - ESPN&apos;s Scoop Jackson</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ESPN's Scoop Jackson and Team SBL talk about Phil Jackson's possible return to the Lakers, the likelihood of anyone stopping Miami or Phoenix and more, including:<br>
<b> </b>Author Will Carroll hands out MLB's April awards<br>
<br>
<b> </b>Pigskin Bloggers discuss the T.O.-McNabb feud and more<br>
<br>
<b> </b>12-Year-Old Phenom Alex on the NFL<br>
<br>
<b> </b>Rookie Blogger of the Month<br>
<br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050305.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast050305.mp3" length="57855452" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 3 May 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - ESPN&apos;s Buster Olney</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[ESPN's Buster Olney joins us on this week's SBL Extra to discuss the hottest stories around the MLB including:<br>
<b> </b>Roger Clemens' Situation<br>
<br>
<b> </b>The Yankees' Slow Start<br>
<br>
<b> </b>The Schilling/Pinnella Fued<br>
<br>
<b> </b>Baseball Musings on the Dykstra Accusations<br>
<br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast042805.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast042805.mp3" length="29898078" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - SI&apos;s Peter King, Will Carroll</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[Are you ready for some football? SBL sure is! This week, Sports Illustrated and Inside the NFL's Peter King joins us to break down the draft and more, including:<br>
<b> </b>Pigskin Bloggers on the NFL Draft<br>
<br>
<b> </b>Author Will Carroll on his new book, 'The Juice'<br>
<br>
<b> </b>12-Year-Old Phenom Alex on the MLB<br>
<br>
<b> </b>NBA Playoffs<br>
<br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast042505.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast042505.mp3" length="74761845" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - NBA Playoffs Preview</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[It's our first SBL Extra as the crew breaks down the NBA Playoffs with writer Steve Aschburner and the top hoops bloggers on the web, including:<br>
<b> </b>Top Playoff Stories<br><br>
<b> </b>Western Conference 1st Round Preview<br><br>
<b> </b>Eastern Conference 1st Round Preview<br><br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast042105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast042105.mp3" length="36932690" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2005 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - NFL Draft Preview</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[We're feeling a draft on this week's SBL with NFL.com's Adam Schefter who tries to choose between Aaron Rodgers vs. Alex Smith. That's right, it's the NFL Draft and more, including:<br>
<b> </b>The Red Sox Ring Ceremony<br>
<br>
<b> </b>Talking Baseball<br>
<br>
<b> </b>Masters Recap<br>
<br>
<b> </b>2005-06 NBA Awards<br>
<br>
<b> </b>Rookie Blogger of the Week<br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast041105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast041105.mp3" length="57518729" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - 4.05.2005</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[Pedro and Beltran may lead the Mets to its first NL East title since '88. This week on SBL, take a look at New York's "other" baseball team and more, including:<br>
<b> </b>Yankees vs. Red Sox<br>
<br>
<b> </b>MLB's Breakout Stars of 2005<br>
<br>
<b> </b>Masters Preview<br>
<br>
<b> </b>March Madness Wrap-up<br>
<br>
<b> </b>Rookie Blogger of the Week<br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast040505.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast040505.mp3" length="59324922" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sat, 5 Mar 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - USA Today&apos;s Paul White, MLB Preview</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[This isn't the "Year of Steroids," it's the year the Yankees-BoSox rivalry reaches its zenith. This week on SBL, we predict who comes out on top and more, including:<br>
<b> </b>MLB Preview with USA Today's Paul White<br><br>
<b> </b>Final Four Forecast with Yoco Hoops<br><br>
<b> </b>'One Shining Moment' Songwriter<br><br>
<b> </b>Rookie Blogger of the Month<br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast032805.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast032805.mp3" length="57541830" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - March Madness</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[This week's SBL reviews the first 2 rounds of the NCAA Tournament and more!  The crew discusses all things Madness and debates the steroids issue in baseball:<br>
<b> </b>Biggest Tourney Upsets Ever<br>
<b> </b>Sweet 16 Preview<br>
<b> </b>MLB and Steroids<br>
<b> </b>Fan Frenzy!<br>
<b> </b>Rookie Blogger of the Week<br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast032105.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast032105.mp3" length="69143009" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - March Madness Preview</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[This week's Sports Bloggers Live previews the NCAA Tournament!  The crew debates all things Madness and we get you ready for the Big Dance:<br>
<b> </b>Bracket Tips<br>
<b> </b>Albuquerque Region<br>
<b> </b>Austin Region<br>
<b> </b>Chicago Region<br>
<b> </b>Syracuse Region<br>
<b> </b>Fan Frenzy!<br>]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast031405.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast031405.mp3" length="82397783" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - 3.07.2005</title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[This week's Sports Bloggers Live covers Sean May's heroic effort, NCAA conference tournaments, bracketology and hot MLB topics:<br>
<b> </b>NCAA Championship Week<br>
<b> </b>Spring Training Update<br>
<b> </b>Monponsett's Top 10 List<br>
<b> </b>Rookie Blogger of the Week]]>
            </description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast030705.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast030705.mp3" length="57219906" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 7 Mar 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sports Bloggers Live - 2.28.2005</title>
            <description>This week&apos;s show features a healthy debate on hate with Moss and Bonds rating high on the most-despised list. Hear more and weigh in on this and other topics, including:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;College Hoops Top 10 Players&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;MLB Update &amp; Fantasy Foresight&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;NBA Stretch Drive&apos;s Top Stories&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <link>http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022805.mp3</link>
            <author>AOL Sports and Community</author>
            <category domain="">Podcast</category>
            <enclosure url="http://sportsbloggerslive.podcast.aol.com/sbl_podcast022805.mp3" length="57573224" type="mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2005 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
