<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
	<ttl>60</ttl> 
        <title>Melodic Sessions by Prototype 202: Progressive House Podcast</title>
		<description>A monthly talk free DJ mix of all the best melodic progressive House, Trance and Progressive Breaks, featuring slabs of quality and uplifting aural stimulation with a sprinkling of shimmering vocals on top. Please rate this podcast and visit the www.prototype202.com website for all tracklistings and buy links for all the featured tracks</description>
        <link>http://www.prototype202.com</link>
		<category domain="">Trance</category>
        <copyright>Simon White</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 11:23:47 +0100</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>simon@prototype202.com</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 11:23:47 +0100</pubDate>
		<image>
			<url>http://www.prototype202.com/images/itunes_podcast.jpg</url>
			<title>Melodic Sessions by Prototype 202</title>
			<link>http://www.prototype202.com</link>
			<width>144</width>
			<height>144</height>
		</image>
        <itunes:subtitle>A monthly talk free mix of all the best melodic progressive House, Trance and Progressive Breaks</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>A podcast of deep progressive house and trance, featuring slabs of quality melodic and uplifting aural stimulation with a sprinkling of shimmering vocals on top. Releases from labels including Anjunadeep, Silk Royal Records, Macarize, Anjunadeep and artists including Ad Brown, Jaytech, Andrew Bayer, Soundprank, Deadmau5, Stan Kolev, Loquai, Above and Beyond, Peter Illias and much much more. Please rate this podcast and visit the Prototype202 website for all tracklistings and buy links for all the featured tracks. Spread the love for Melodic EDM. </itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>Various Artists</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
        <itunes:name>Melodic Sessions by Prototype 202 - Progressive House and Trance Podcast</itunes:name>
        <itunes:email>simon@prototype202.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Music"/>
        <itunes:keywords>Progressive House, Progressive Trance, Vocal Trance, Trance, Melodic House, , progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, Chilled Trance, Electronic, Melodic Trance, Progressive, Deep Progressive, Progressive Breaks, Ibiza trance, Ibiza balaeric, Ibiza, Deadmau5, Silk Royal Recordings, Silk Digital, Anjunadeep, Particles, Macarize </itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.prototype202.com/images/itunes_podcast.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
		<item>
		<title>
		Warm Air Mix - Melodic House and Progressive Mix by Protoype202
		</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>
June brings deep house, melodic house and Ibiza beachside trance all mixed into a summer warmup session for your listening pleasure. Featuring tracks and remixes from Jaytech, Andrew Bayer, Gabriel Batz, Above and Beyond, Martin Roth and Deadmau5. Track of the month is the awesome Dynamis by Terry da Libra. Melodic fans enjoy the podcast.
 </itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>
June brings deep house, melodic house and Ibiza beachside trance all mixed into a summer warmup session for your listening pleasure. Featuring tracks and remixes from Jaytech, Andrew Bayer, Gabriel Batz, Martin Roth and Deadmau5. Track of the month is the awesome Dynamis by Terry da Libra. Melodic fans enjoy the podcast.

Magnolia - Nuera - Enhanced Recordings
The Known Universe (Original Mix) - Nigel Good  - Silk Royal Records
Circles (Blood Groove and Kikis Remix) - Evren Furtuna - Spring Tube
Far Away (Summer (Brendon Collins) Remix) - Ucleden - Tulipa Recordings
Prelude (Andrew Bayer and James Grant Remix) - Above and Beyond  - Anjunadeep
Pepes Garden (Original Mix) - Jaytech -  Anjunadeep
Can You Feel Me (Andycap Remix) - Lovetone - Macarize
Talamanca (Original Mix) - Gabriel Batz -  Ora Recordings
Dew Point (Martin Roths Morning Dew Remix) - Answer42  - Anjunadeep
Meet The Morning (Loquai vocal mix) - Klinedea - Reelaux Digital
Dynamis (Original Mix) - Terry Da Libra -  Silk Royal Records
Day We Met (Original Mix) - M+D Substance -  WeRecommendRecords
Daydream (Hazem Beltagui Sunrise Mix) - Toby Hedges  - Fractal
Marmara (Matias Chilano Remix) - Mehmet Akar, Dr Avalance  -  Pervurt Records
The Veldt (8 Minute Edit) - Deadmau5 -  mau5trap

			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:04:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>
			trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, deep house, melodic house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza house, ibiza mix, ibiza balaeric, Deadmau5, Silk Royal, Anjunadeep, Particles, Macarize
			</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>June brings deep house, melodic house and Ibiza beachside trance all mixed into a summer warmup session for your listening pleasure. Featuring tracks and remixes from Jaytech, Andrew Bayer, Gabriel Batz, Martin Roth and Deadmau5. Track of the month is the awesome Dynamis by Terry da Libra. Melodic fans enjoy the podcast !
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/Prototype202SummerBreezeMix/MelodicSessionsSummerBreezeMix.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2012 00:01:01 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>
		Poolside Mix - Deep House and Progressive Mix by Protoype202
		</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>
May brings a deep house tinged mix to wash away those April showers and bring the sun out ready for May. New tracks and remixes from Nigel Good, Martin Roth, EDX, Guy Gerber, Andrew Bayer and more. Track of the month is the fantastic Matao remix of Olympus by Mindset but a close second is Guy Gerbers, One Day in May, good work fella's.
 </itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>
May brings a deep house tinged mix to wash away those April showers and bring the sun out ready for May. New tracks and remixes from Nigel Good, Martin Roth, EDX, Guy Gerber, Andrew Bayer and more. Track of the month is the fantastic Matao remix of Olympus by Mindset but a close second is Guy Gerbers, One Day in May, good work fella's.

Boiling - Disclosure - Greco Roman Recorings
Make Love To Me Baby (Original Mix) - Martin Roth  - Anjunadeep
Frisky (Original) - Maceo Plex  - Crosstown Rebels
Gravity (Andrew Bayer and James Grant Remix) - P.O.S. - Anjunadeep 
One Day In May (Original Mix) - Guy Gerber - Visionquest
No Gravity (Tom Middleton Liquatech Mix) - Paronator   - Anjunadeep
Everything feat. Hadley (Original Vocal Mix) - EDX    - PinkStar Records
Twisted Monkey (Nigel Good Remix) - Alexey Sonar  - Particles 
On the Loose - Stan Kolev - Recovery Tech
Perfect Morning (Original Mix) - Rainbow Addict - Silk Royal Records 
Here Comes The Sun (Original Mix) - Hazem Beltagui - Macarize
Symmetry (Original Mix) - Oliver Smith  - Anjunabeats 
Olympus (Matao Remix) - Mindset  Matao - Macarize 
Beautiful Life (Original Mix) - Martin Roth - Anjunadeep

			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:04:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>
			trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, deep house, melodic house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza house, ibiza mix, ibiza balaeric
			</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>May brings a deep house tinged mix to wash away those April showers and bring the sun out ready for May. New tracks and remixes from Nigel Good, Martin Roth, EDX, Guy Gerber, Andrew Bayer and more. Track of the month is the fantastic Matao remix of Olympus by Mindset but a close second is Guy Gerbers, One Day in May, good work fella's.
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/Prototype202MelodicSessions-PoolsideMix/MelodicSessionsPoolsidemixMa.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 00:01:01 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>
		Spring Melt - Vocal and Progressive Trance Mix by Protoype202
		</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>
April 2012's Sunset Sessions podcast brings beautiful vocal trance and progressive sounds. With new tracks and remixes from Johan Vilborg, Cosmic Gate, David Folkebrandt, Nick Stoynoff, Eximinds and Max Graham. Track of the month is the awesome Kobana Remix of Alien by Poison Pro and Miusha . Enjoy!
 </itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>
April 2012's Sunset Sessions podcast brings beautiful vocal trance and progressive sounds. With new tracks and remixes from Johan Vilborg, Cosmic Gate, David Folkebrandt, Nick Stoynoff, Eximinds and Max Graham. Track of the month is the awesome Kobana Remix of Alien by Poison Pro and Miusha . Enjoy!

In And Out Of Phase feat. Kerry Leva (Original Mix) -  Andrew Bayer and Matt Lange -   Anjunabeats 
Star Journey Begins (Mindset remix) - MH20 and Sedi -  Yellow Avenue Recordings
Not Enough Time feat. Emma Hewitt (Andy Duguid Remix) -  Cosmic Gate  Andy Duguid -  Maelstrom Records 
Nothing Else Matters feat. Ana Criado (Original Mix) -  Max Graham - Armada Music 
Serenity (Original Mix) -  Eximinds and Aleksey Yakovlev -   Macarize 
Exemption (Original Mix) -  Jan Martin -   Enhanced Progressive  
Alien (Kobana Remix) -  Poison Pro and Miusha - Proton Music 
Into Your Eyes - Poison Pro - Free Download
Here We Go feat. Hannah Ray (Original Mix) -  Masoud -   AVA Recordings (Armada) 
Supremacy (Original Mix) -  David Folkebrant -   Macarize  
Altara (Original Mix) -  Johan Vilborg -  Silk Royal Records 
On A Rainy Day (Lessov Remix) -  Roald Velden and Lessov -  Portrait Digital  
Gaffs Eulogy - Andrew Bayer - Anjunadeep

			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:04:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>
			trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza house, ibiza mix, ibiza balaeric
			</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>April 2012's Sunset Sessions podcast brings beautiful vocal trance and progressive sounds. With new tracks and remixes from Johan Vilborg, Cosmic Gate, David Folkebrandt, Nick Stoynoff, Eximinds and Max Graham. Track of the month is the awesome Kobana Remix of Alien by Poison Pro and Miusha . Enjoy!
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/Prototype202SunsetSessions_SpringMeltMix/SunsetSessions_Prototype202Spr.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 00:01:01 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>
		Dawn Breaks - Progressive Trance Mix by Protoype202
		</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>
Progressive breaks make a return this month. Some deep beautiful melodic breakbeat productions from Hybrid, Aeron Aether, Loquai, Eximinds Ad Brown and more. Track of the month is Enjoy This from Tom Lue with an awesome remix by Gregory Essayan. Blast from the past comes courtesy of Nick Muir with Forge on Bedrock Classics </itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>
Progressive breaks make a return this month. Some deep beautiful melodic breakbeat productions from Hybrid, Aeron Aether, Loquai, Eximinds Ad Brown and more. Track of the month is Enjoy This from Tom Lue with an awesome remix by Gregory Essayan. Blast from the past comes courtesy of Nick Muir with Forge on Bedrock Classics 

Communication Down (Original Mix) -  Hazem Beltagui  -   Macarize
On A Rainy Day (Original Mix) -  Roald Velden   -  Portrait Digital
L.A. (Alfoa Angel Cit' Mix) - Ad Brown   - Nueva Digital  
Fly (Hybrid Soundsystem Remix)  - Guy J and Miriam Vaga - Bedrock Records   
Flashback (Aeron Aether Remix) -  East Cafe   -   Morphosis Records 
Counting On Love (Wellenrausch Remix)  - D Mad - Afterglow 
Lullaby (Original Mix)  - Abdomen Burst   -  Armada Music 
Reborn Of Eclipse (Loquais Strong Remix)  - Junitoshi  - OLD SQL Recordings
Daydream feat. Leusin (Eximinds Remix)  - Moonbeam  - Moonbeam Digital 
Caramel Sticks (LoQuai Raze Remix) - Orelse - Balkan Delights        
Fear (MSZ Breaks Remix)  - Deep Fog  -  Mistiquemusic  
The Cosmic Game (Andrew Philippov Remix)  - Dellife  -  Mistiquemusic   
Enjoy This (Gregory Esayan Remix) -  Tom Lue  -   Morphosis Records 
Forge (Original Mix)  - Nick Muir -  Bedrock Records

			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:04:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>
			trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza house, ibiza mix, ibiza balaeric
			</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>Progressive breaks make a return this month. Some deep beautiful melodic breakbeat productions from Hybrid, Aeron Aether, Loquai, Eximinds Ad Brown and more. Track of the month is Enjoy This from Tom Lue with an awesome remix by Gregory Essayan. Blast from the past comes courtesy of Nick Muir with Forge on Bedrock Classics 
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202DawnBreaksMix/MelodicSessions_DawnBreaksmix.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thur, 01 Mar 2012 00:01:01 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
				<item>
		<title>
		High Tide - Progressive Trance Mix by Protoype202
		</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>
February brings another selection of beautiful melodic, progressive house - with new tracks and remixes from D-Nox and Beckers, Zack Roth, Stan Kolev, SHato and Moonbeam. Track of the month is the beautiful melodic drifter It's Just a Bad Dream from Deep Fog out on Mistique Music. Sit back relax and enjoy !</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>
February brings another selection of beautiful melodic, progressive house - with new tracks and remixes from D-Nox and Beckers, Zack Roth, Stan Kolev, SHato and Moonbeam. Track of the month is the beautiful melodic drifter It's Just a Bad Dream from Deep Fog out on Mistique Music. Sit back relax and enjoy !

I Will Rise (Guy J Remix) - D-Nox and Beckers  - Tronic  
Outland (Luiz B Remix) - Zack Roth  -  Particles 
Far Away (Vipul Remix) - Ucleden  - Whose Haus 
Croatia (Annual Report Part 4) - Croatia Squad -  Recovery Tech 
Awakening Of The Sun (Stan Kolev Remix) - Kolokol Production  - Kolokol Digital  
Sundari (Loko Remix) - Dave Kurtis  -  Recovery Tech  
Beginnings (Original Mix) - Soundprank  - Anjunadeep 
Kisses From The Clouds (Phaxe Remix) - Behind Blue Eyes and Krusseldorf - Iboga Records 
Ghost (Original Mix) - Moonbeam - Moonbeam Digital  
Its Just A Bad Dream (Dub Mix) - Deep Fog  - Mistiquemusic  
Landmine Hopscotch (Cid Inc Remix) - Shiloh  - Proton Music 
Deserted Places (Original Mix) - Roald Velden  - Portrait Digital
Something Between Us (Original Mix) - SHato  - Unearthed Records  


			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:04:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>
			trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza house, ibiza mix, ibiza balaeric
			</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>February brings another selection of beautiful melodic, progressive house - with new tracks and remixes from D-Nox and Beckers, Zack Roth, Stan Kolev, SHato and Moonbeam. Track of the month is the beautiful melodic drifter It's Just a Bad Dream from Deep Fog out on Mistique Music. Sit back relax and enjoy !
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202MelodicSessions-HighTideMix/MelodicSessions_HighTideMixPr.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 23:01:01 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		
		<item>
		<title>
		Pale Sunlight - Progressive Trance Mix by Protoype202
		</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>
January brings a New Year and a new crop of melodic gems for your listening pleasure. Usual suspects include Schodt-  Hazem Beltagui and Shingo Nakemura-  Remixes of some past classics from Orkidea and The Thrillseekers-  with track of the month from Luiz B with Hidden Beauty
 Enjoy!</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>

January brings a New Year and a new crop of melodic gems for your listening pleasure. Usual suspects include Schodt-  Hazem Beltagui and Shingo Nakemura-  Remixes of some past classics from Orkidea and The Thrillseekers-  with track of the month from Luiz B with Hidden Beauty. Enjoy!


Lemonakia (Original Mix) - Embliss  - Armada Music 
Ever After (Hazem Beltagui's Sunset Remix)  - Lessov  Hazem Beltagui  - Gold Shore Records 
Morning (Original Mix)  - Sergey Franc   - Round Triangle  
Skysurf (Original Mix)  - Biotones   - Gold Shore Records 
Hidden Beauty (Original Mix)  - Luiz B   - Silk Digital Records
Daylight (Original Mix)  - Mehilove   - Infrasonic Recordings   
Unity (Orkidea 15th Anniversary Club Mix)  - Orkidea   - Solaris
Universal Language (Tritonal Club Mix)  - Mark Eteson   - Monster Tunes   
The Last Time (Johan Malmgren 2012 Remix)  - The Thrillseekers  - Adjusted Music
Remember That (Shingo Nakamura Remix)  - T4L and Oza - Enhanced Recordings
Arrow (Andy Tau Remix)  - Leolife   - InfraProgressive
Sexophone (Nuera Remix)  - Kaste  Nuera  - Alter Ego Digital
Kisses (Tom Lue Remix)  - Mango  - Morphosis Records  
Cinematico (Original Mix)  - Schodt   - Nero Bianco
Night Flight (Art Project Remix)  - Yadek  - Rune Recordings 


			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:04:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>
			trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza house, ibiza mix, ibiza balaeric
			</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>January brings a New Year and a new crop of melodic gems for your listening pleasure. Usual suspects include Schodt-  Hazem Beltagui and Shingo Nakemura-  Remixes of some past classics from Orkidea and The Thrillseekers -  with track of the month from Luiz B with Hidden Beauty. Enjoy!
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202PaleSunlightMix/Prototype202PaleSunlightMix.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		
		
		<item>
		<title>
		Mists - Progressive Trance Mix by Protoype202
		</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>
Melodic Sessions bring you another month of the best melodic deep and progressive tunes around. This month sees new tracks from Nick Warren, Peter Illias, Jacob Henry, Soundprank, and more. Tune of the month is Andy Moors awesome melodic gem Halcyon, with Alexey Sonars Flashback and Nick Warrens Rumbletump all hot on its heels. Blast from the past is Probspots I'll Kill For You sounding as fresh as ever. Enjoy!</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>

Melodic Sessions bring you another month of the best melodic deep and progressive tunes around. This month sees new tracks from Nick Warren, Peter Illias, Jacob Henry, Soundprank, and more. Tune of the month is Andy Moors awesome melodic gem Halcyon, with Alexey Sonars Flashback and Nick Warrens Rumbletump all hot on its heels. Blast from the past is Probspots I'll Kill For You sounding as fresh as ever. Enjoy!


   Absolute Intro (Original Mix) - Francesco Pico  - Manual Music
   Captivated (Original Mix) - Soundprank  - Anjunadeep 
   Moments Are Forever (Original Mix) - Peter Illias  - Arrival  
   Timeless (Original Mix) - Ad Brown and Ben Coda -  Enormous Tunes   
   Halcyon (Original Mix) - Andy Moor -  Armind
   Carry On (Peter Illias Remix) - Ninesh Babu, Lameduza - Arrival
   Rumbletump (Original Mix) - Nick Warren -  Sudbeat Music
   Recoder (Lank Remix) - Envotion - Armada Music  
   Flashback (Original Mix) -  Alexey Sonar - Tactal Hots Music
   Serengeti (Noel Sanger Remix) - Jacob Henry, Coastal - Silk Royal Records  
   I Kill For You (Probspot Remix) - Endre - Anjunabeats 
   Calidore (Loquai Remix) - Rodrigo Mateo - Soulfire Download 
   I'll Be Ok (Hazem Beltagui Remix) - Kenneth Cruz Dirt - Lies And Audio Recordings


			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:04:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>
			trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza house, ibiza mix, ibiza balaeric
			</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>Melodic Sessions bring you another month of the best melodic deep and progressive tunes around. This month sees new tracks from Nick Warren, Peter Illias, Jacob Henry, Soundprank, and more. Tune of the month is Andy Moors awesome melodic gem Halcyon, with Alexey Sonars Flashback and Nick Warrens Rumbletump all hot on its heels. Blast from the past is Probspots I'll Kill For You sounding as fresh as ever. Enjoy!
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202MistMix/Prototype202_MistMix_Dec2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>		
		<item>
		<title>
		Breaking Fall - Progressive Breaks Mix by Protoype202
		</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>

Autumn brings Breaking Fall, awesome melodic breakbeats, chords and synth lines from Hybrid, Sed and Dream Logic alongside the usual from the likes of Schodt, Ad Brown, Audien and Claes Rosen. Track of the month is the beautiful progressive breaks of Funk Harmony Park with Bianco Soleil and Moecule		</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>

Autumn brings Breaking Fall, awesome melodic breakbeats, chords and synth lines from Hybrid, Sed and Dream Logic alongside the usual from the likes of Schodt, Ad Brown, Audien and Claes Rosen. Track of the month is the beautiful progressive breaks of Funk Harmony Park with Bianco Soleil and Moecule

Sed - Law of Physics feat. Lisette van den Berg (Abdomen Burst - Back In Time Mix) - Particles     
Hybrid - Blind Side (Radio Edit) Kill City Records   
Funk Harmony Park - Sweet Impressions feat Hjatalin (Original Mix)-Particles     
Bianco Soleil - Moecule (Original Mix) - Morphosis Records   
Schodt Falling (Embliss Remix) Colorize    
Hypnotic Duo - Life Particle (Original Mix)- Mistiquemusic   
Mike Foyle - Simple Things feat. Zo - Soundpiercing   
Ad Brown - Scared (Dub Mix) - Intuition Recordings   
Audien - Selective Hearing (Original Mix) - Magik Muzik      
Claes Rosen - Closing In (Original Mix) - Macarize   
Aleksey Yakovlev - We Won't Forget (Alfoa  In Memory  Remix) - Nueva Digital   
Trukers Round - Trip Dreams (Digital Department Remix) - Rune Recordings    
Dream Logic - Wake Me Up feat. Ange (Original Mix) - Morphosis Records 

			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:04:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>
			trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza house, ibiza mix, ibiza balaeric
			</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>Autumn brings Breaking Fall, awesome melodic breakbeats, chords and synth lines from Hybrid, Sed and Dream Logic alongside the usual from the likes of Schodt, Ad Brown, Audien and Claes Rosen. Track of the month is the beautiful progressive breaks of Funk Harmony Park with Bianco Soleil and Moecule
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202BreakingFall_0/Prototype202_BreakingFall_Nov2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		
		<item>
		<title>
		Bonus FB Mix - Melodic House mix by Prototype202
		</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>
October brings an FB bonus mix with some tracks chosen by FB listeners thrown in the mix for good measure. Big THANKS to Subash and Ricardo. Also playing plenty of new tracks including 2Night the awesome new track from Eric Prydz. Enjoy!
		</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>
October brings an FB bonus mix with some tracks chosen by FB listeners thrown in the mix for good measure. Big THANKS to Subash and Ricardo. Also playing plenty of new tracks including 2Night the awesome new track from Eric Prydz. Enjoy!


Dreaming (Original Mix) - BT - Black Hole Recordings
Hunt The Clues (Original Mix) - Martin Etchegaray - Per-vurt Records
Khafre (Original Mix) - Kyohei Akagawa, Shingo Nakamura - Silk Digital Records
Catching Tides (Kaspar Kochker Remix) - Embliss - Arrival
Airwave (Original Mix) - Atlantis Ocean - Arrival
Tansania (Original Mix) - George F. Zimmer - Unreleased Digital
Vor dem Fliegen (Kobana Remix) - Kyohei Akagawa - Particles
2Night (Original Mix) - Eric Prydz - Pryda Recordings
Here We Go (Jaytech Remix) - Mango - Silk Digital Records
Suburban Train (Marc O'Tool Dub Mix) - Tiesto - Nebula
Angel (Magnetique Remix) - Fulvio Perniola - Baroque Records
Subtle Nature - Blue Haze - Mistique Music
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:04:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>
			trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza house, ibiza mix, ibiza balaeric
			</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>
October brings an FB bonus mix with some tracks chosen by FB listeners thrown in the mix for good measure. Big THANKS to Subash and Ricardo. Also playing plenty of new tracks including 2Night the awesome new track from Eric Prydz. Enjoy!
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202BonusFbMix/Prototype202_BonusFBmix_oct2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tues, 18 Oct 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>
		Fade to Black Mix - Progressive and Tech House mix by Prototype202
		</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>
		October brings an Indian Summer here in the UK and to celebrate we have a mix of the melodic with an indie-electro tinge. With new tracks and remixes from Josh Gabriel, Super8 and Tab, Kay-D, Eelkje Klein and classics from Courtney Tidwell and Gui Boratto. Track of the month the beautiful piano tinged Flashpoint by Rodrigo Deem. Enjoy!
		</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>
October brings an Indian Summer here in the UK and to celebrate we have a mix of the melodic with an indie-electro tinge. With new tracks and remixes from Josh Gabriel, Super8 and Tab, Kay-D, Eelkje Klein and classics from Courtney Tidwell and Gui Boratto. Track of the month the beautiful piano tinged Flashpoint by Rodrigo Deem. Enjoy!

Don't Let Stars Keep Us Tangled Up (Ewan Pearson's All This Has Happened Before Beatless Version) - Cortney Tidwell - RS Records
Everybody Loves Ice Cream (Vincenzo Remix) - Wiretappeur - Bedrock Records
Hot As Hades (Album Mix) - Josh Gabriel, Winter Kills - Armada Music
Drums Are Not Dangerous (Original Mix) - Inkfish - Inkfish Recordings
Flashpoint (Roby K and Daniel Rems Remix) - Rodrigo Deem - Dirt, Lies and Audio Recordings
The Blue Room (Original Mix) - Relaunch - Mistiquemusic
Puzzle Piece (Original Mix) - Space Rockerz - Aropa Records (Armada Music)
Not Trippin feat Polarsets (Eelke Kleijn Is Trippin Mix) - Dibby Dougherty, David Young - Baroque Digital
Feel It (Original Mix) - Scuba - Hotflush Recordings
Eternal Sequence (Jaytech Remix) - Super8 and Tab - Anjunabeats
A Stroke Of Luck (Deepfunk's Royal Flush Remix) - Ella, Tom Eales - Deepfunk - Stripped Recordings
I Say Goodbye (Kay-D Remix) - Aquadro - Mistiquemusic
Never Let Go (Original Mix) - Soulfinder - Mistiquemusic
No Turning Back (Original Mix) - Gui Boratto - Kompact
Drifting Off feat. Molay (Original Mix) - Joni - Anjunadeep
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:04:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>
			trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza house, ibiza mix, ibiza balaeric
			</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>
			October brings an Indian Summer here in the UK and to celebrate we have a mix of the melodic with an indie-electro tinge. With new tracks and remixes from Josh Gabriel, Super8 and Tab, Kay-D, Eelkje Klein and classics from Cortney Tidwell and Gui Boratto. Track of the month the beautiful piano tinged Flashpoint by Rodrigo Deem. Enjoy!
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202Fade2BlackMix/Prototype202_Fade2BlackMix_oct2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		
		<item>
		<title>
		Ibiza Sunset Mix - Progressive and Tech House mix by Prototype202
		</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>
		September 2011 brings a build down sunset mix for fans of uplifting melodic tech house with a deeper feel. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Tom Middleton, Suffused, Sasha, and Layo and Bushwacka. Classic track is Steve Mills with Let Me Go Higher from 2008 and Track of the Month is Jason Van Wyk and Audien with Someday. Enjoy!
		</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>
		September 2011 brings a build down sunset mix for fans of uplifting melodic tech house with a deeper feel. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Tom Middleton, Suffused, Sasha, and Layo and Bushwacka. Classic track is Steve Mills with Let Me Go Higher from 2008 and Track of the Month is Jason Van Wyk and Audien with Someday. Enjoy!

Steve Mill - Lets Go Higher - Urban Torque
DJ T - Sense feat James Teej (Tale Of Us Remix) - Get Physical Music
Passenger 10 - Trust In You (Original Mix) - Recovery House
Sasha - Cut Me Down (Layo and Bushwacka Remix) - Last Night On Earth
Fingerfest Inc - Autoporno (Inkfish Remix) - Splash Records
Evren Ulusoy - Nightflowers (Eelke Kleijn Remix) - Outside The Box Music
DeepSoul Duo - Fellowship (Suffused Remix) - Mistiquemusic
Ralph Project - Here I Am (Original Mix) - Dirt, Lies and Audio Recordings
Jason Van Wyk, Audien - Someday (Original Mix) - Essential Dance
Humate - Love Stimulation (Tom Middleton Remix) - Grand Casino Records
Mobilize - Something In Your Head (Kasey Taylor Remix) - Particles
Shingo Nakamura - Move On (Original Mix) - Silk Digital Records
Cassius - The Sound Of Violence (Franco Cinelli Remix) - Cassius Records
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:09:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>
			trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza house, ibiza mix, ibiza balaeric
			</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>
			September 2011 brings a build down sunset mix for fans of uplifting melodic tech house with a deeper feel. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Tom Middleton, Suffused, Sasha, and Layo and Bushwacka. Classic track is Steve Mills with Let Me Go Higher from 2008 and Track of the Month is Jason Van Wyk and Audien with Someday. Enjoy!					
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202IbizaSunset/Prototype202_IbizaSunset_sep2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>Sundown Mix - Progressive Trance mix by Prototype202</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>Aug 2011 brings a melodic mix for lovers of melodic deep progressive trance. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Shimgo Nakemura, Above and Beyond, Gabriel Batz, Super8 and Tab and Robert Oleyseck.Track of the month Alpha Duo, Beautiful Dream with Hazem Belatagui on the remix duties. Enjoy!</itunes:subtitle>
				<itunes:summary>Aug 2011 brings a melodic mix for lovers of melodic deep progressive trance. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Shimgo Nakemura, Above and Beyond, Gabriel Batz, Super8 and Tab and Robert Oleyseck.Track of the month Alpha Duo, Beautiful Dream with Hazem Belatagui on the remix duties. Enjoy!

Soulforge - It Was Destiny (Luiz B Remix) - Neuroscience Deep
Freska - Snowshoes (Spieltape North Tale Remix) - Lo Recordings
Inertia - Juxtaposition (Robert Oleysyck Open Air Remix) - Stainless Digital
Parker Hanson - Arabesque (Original Mix) -  Anjunabeats
Shingo Nakamura - Sapporo (Sunn Jellie Remix) - Silk Royal Records
Alpha Duo - Beautiful Dream (Hazem Beltagui Sunrise Mix) - LW Recordings
Gabriel Batz - Breezes (Original Mix) - Ora Recordings
Super8 and Tab - Helsinki Scorchin (Bart Claessen Alternative Mix) - Anjunabeats
Above andBeyond - Thing Called Love (Mat Zo Remix) - Anjunabeats
Markus Schulz - Not The Same feat. Jennifer Rene (Eelke Kleijn Remix) - Coldharbour Recordings (Armada)
Andain - Promises (Soundprank Remix) - Black Hole Recordings
Kahraman - A Prophet (M and D Substance Remix) - Nemesis (Subtrax)
Andrew Stets - Silver Clouds (Original Mix) - Rune Recordings
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:09:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza balaeric</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>Aug 2011 brings a melodic mix for lovers of melodic deep progressive trance. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Shimgo Nakemura, Above and Beyond, Gabriel Batz, Super8 and Tab and Robert Oleyseck. Track of the month Alpha Duo, Beautiful Dream with Hazem Belatagui on the remix duties. Enjoy!</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202SundownMix/Prototype202SundownMixAug2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
<item>
		<title>Balearic Breeze - Balearic House and Breaks mix by Prototype202</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>July 2011 brings a melodic mix for lovers of melodic and balaeric deep progressive house and breaks. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Passenger 10, Soundprank, Duderstadt and Elfsong. Track of the month Passenger 10 with Come Back, with a beautiful chilled melodic house number and kicking off the mix this month. Enjoy!</itunes:subtitle>
				<itunes:summary>July 2011 brings a melodic mix for lovers of melodic and balaeric deep progressive house and breaks. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Passenger 10, Soundprank,Duderstadt and Elfsong. Track of the month Passenger 10 with Come Back, with a beautiful chilled melodic house number and kicking off the mix this month. Enjoy!

Passenger 10 - Come Back (re-vibes remix) - Mango Alley
Soarsweep - Losing Rays (Johnny Juice remix) - Spring Tube
Shato and Rockseek - Wonderfoold (Duderstadt Remix) - Tool Trance
Sezer Uyzal - Aura (Matan Caspi Remix) - Galore Music
Audien - People Do Not Change - Enhanced Progressive
Eta Carinae - Elfsong (Aeron Aether Remix) - Solaris
Reii - Ghostly Sea - Lost Language 
Ad Brown - Motion - Silk Royal Records
Soundprank - Solid Ground - Silk Digital Records
Craving - Summer Memories - Per-Vurt Records
Luiz B - Mystery - Enhanced Progressive
Soundprank - Burner (Shingo Nakemura Remix) - Silk Digital Records
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:09:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza balaeric</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>July 2011 brings a melodic mix for lovers of melodic and balaeric deep progressive house and breaks. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Passenger 10, Soundprank,Duderstadt and Elfsong. Track of the month Passenger 10 with Come Back, with a beautiful chilled melodic house number and kicking off the mix this month. Enjoy!</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202BalearicBreezeMix/Prototype202BalearicBreeze_July2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
	<item>
		<title>Dusk - Progressive House and Trance mix by Prototype202</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>June 2011 brings hot summer days and a progressive trance mix featuring tracks and remixes from Proff, Cressida, Sun Jellie. Hazem Beltagui and several of the standout tracks from the awesome Solarstone compilation Electronic Architecture 2, Pure class once again from the Solarstone guys. Track of the month is the awesome One Of Us by Peter Illias and classic track is True Love by George Acosta from Jan 2010. Enjoy!</itunes:subtitle>
				<itunes:summary>June 2011 brings hot summer days and a progressive trance mix featuring tracks and remixes from Proff, Cressida, Sun Jellie. Hazem Beltagui and several of the standout tracks from the awesome Solarstone compilation Electronic Architecture 2, Pure class once again from the Solarstone guys. Track of the month is the awesome One Of Us by Peter Illias and classic track is True Love by George Acosta from Jan 2010. Enjoy!

Hazem Beltagui - 222 - Macarize 
Croatia Squad - Marbella -Unreleased Digital
George Acosta - True Love feat Fisher - Songbird
Thomas Feijk and Worst Voorhoofd - Late Night Snack - Macarize
Peter Illias - One Of Us - Arrival
Bobina - You Belong To Me (Proff Remix) - Anjunabeats
Sonic Element - Lost Inside ( Cressida Remix) -Tool Trance
Aeron Aether and Embliss - A New Dawn - Electronic Architecture 2
First State - Reverie ( Feat Sarah Howells) - Songbird
Mehilove - Reality Bites - Arrival
Janeiro and Sovt - Dreams Of the Sea - Electronic Architecture 2
Medway - Resurrection (Proff Remix) - Electronic Architecture 2
Andrey Potyomkin - Yonaguni - Arrival
Alex Pich - Tinctures (Sunn Jellie Remix) - Perceptive Recordings
OceanLab, Above and Beyond - Breaking Ties (Flow Mix) - Anjunabeats
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:09:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza balaeric</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>June 2011 brings hot summer days and a progressive trance mix featuring tracks and remixes from Proff, Cressida, Sun Jellie. Hazem Beltagui and several of the standout tracks from the awesome Solarstone compilation Electronic Architecture 2, Pure class once again from the Solarstone guys. Track of the month is the awesome One Of Us by Peter Illias and classic track is True Love by George Acosta from Jan 2010. Enjoy!</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202DuskMix/Prototype202_Dusk_Mix_Jun_2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>Melodica - Progressive House and Trance mix by Prototype202</title>
		<itunes:subtitle>May 2011 brings sunshine and a mix with the best of this months melodic progressive house and trance. Featuring awesome music across the full spectrum with the best new tracks and remixes from Matt Lange, Arty, Sunn Jellie, Ad Brown and a classic from Allure. Track of the month Ad Browns remix of Painted Faces with its super deep breakdown. Enjoy!</itunes:subtitle>
				<itunes:summary>May 2011 brings sunshine and a mix with the best of this months melodic progressive house and trance. Featuring awesome music across the full spectrum with the best new tracks and remixes from Matt Lange, Arty, Sunn Jellie, Ad Brown and a classic from Allure. Track of the month Ad Browns remix of Painted Faces with its super deep breakdown. Enjoy!

Li-Polymer - Second Skin - Mistiquemusic
Allure - Somewhere Inside - Black Hole Recordings
Flashtech - Vakuum - Arrival
Stan Kolev - Water Of Life - Unreleased Digital
David Ackermanis - Aura (G Tek Remix) - Silk Digital Records
Sou Kanai - Awakening (Sunn Jellie Remix) - Vendance Rercords
Arty and Mat Zo - Rebound - Anjuna Beats
Hazem Beltagui - Pornography - Arrival
Ad Brown- Painted Faces - 
Jerome Ismae Ae - Triangle and Strings - Armada 
Way Out West - We Love Machine ( Jaytech Remix) - Hope Recordings
Deep Fog - Drifting Away ( Blusoul Dub) - Mistique Music
Matt Lange - Rift - Anjuna Deep
Solid Sky - Going Around ( Aleksey Beloozerov Remix) - Enhanced Progressive
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:09:36</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza balaeric</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>May 2011 brings sunshine and a mix with the best of this months melodic progressive house and trance. Featuring awesome music across the full spectrum with the best new tracks and remixes from Matt Lange, Arty, Sunn Jellie, Ad Brown and a classic from Allure. Track of the month Ad Browns remix of Painted Faces with its super deep breakdown. Enjoy!</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202MelodicaMix/Prototype202_Melodica_May2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>Awaken - Progressive House and Trance mix by Prototype202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>Another month of awesome melodic music to awaken the senses. This month superb new tracks from Stan Kolev, Dinka, Soundprank, Jaytech, Michael Cassette and more all blended seamlessly into a musical journey of deep progressive house.</itunes:subtitle>
				<itunes:summary>Another month of awesome melodic music to awaken the senses. This month superb new tracks from Stan Kolev, Dinka, Soundprank, Jaytech, Michael Cassette and more all blended seamlessly into a musical journey of deep progressive house.

Fusion F - Begin Now - Nueva Digital 
Stan Kolev - Part Of Me - Unreleased Digital
Dinka - Luminal feat. Albena Veskova - Unreleased Digital
Stan Kolev - Solitude - Unreleased Digital
Reii - Panic (Paronator Deeper Mix) - Springtube 
Soundprank - A Single Many - Fruit Machine
Sezer Uysal - Regular Synchronisation - Afterglow
Michael Cassette - Memories - Anjunadeep
Jaytech - Pranktech (Soundprank) - Anjunadeep
Exoplanet - Shepherd of Conciousness - Proton Music
Dark Soul Project - Pegasus (Loquai remix) - Mistiquemusic
Bodytemp - Kalm - Silk Textures
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:08:03</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance mix, progressive house mix, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza balaeric</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>Another month of awesome melodic music to awaken the senses. This month superb new tracks from Stan Kolev, Dinka, Soundprank, Jaytech, Michael Cassette and more all blended seamlessly into a musical journey of deep progressive gems.</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202Awaken/Prototype202_Awaken_April2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>Rise - After Dark Mix - Progressive House and Trance mix by Prototype202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>March 2011 and a bonus after dark mix for lovers of melodic progressive with a deeper feel. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Loquai, Soundprank, Shiloh, Ad Brown and Mehilove. Enjoy!</itunes:subtitle>
				<itunes:summary>March 2011 and a bonus after dark mix for lovers of melodic progressive with a deeper feel. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Loquai, Soundprank, Shiloh, Ad Brown and Mehilove. Enjoy!

Canis - Nightwax - Zelubration 
Mehilove - Emotions (Loquai Deep Emotions Remix) - Mistiquemusic
Soundprank  - Cloudsound - Anjunadeep
Evren Ulusoy - Lonely Places I've Never Been - Proton Mixed 
Shiloh - Landmine Hopscotch (Soundprank Remix) - Proton Mixed 
Suffused - Differences (Loquai Remix) - Mistiquemusic 
Ad Brown - Marimba - Perspectives Digital 
Mizar B - Satori (Elfsong Remix) - Arrival 
Jozhy K - Odessa 5 A.M. (Terry Da Libra Remix) - Arrival 
Audio Dropouts - Dark Life (Loquai remix ) - Frisky Records
Ad Brown - Memorial (You Were Loved) - Enhanced Progressive
Rodskeez - Incada (Inkfish Remix) - Nueva Digital 	
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:08:03</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza balaeric</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>March 2011 and a bonus after dark mix for lovers of melodic progressive with a deeper feel. Featuring awesome tracks and remixes from Loquai, Soundprank, Shiloh, Ad Brown and Mehilove. Enjoy!</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202Rise-AfterDarkMix/Prototype202Rise_AfterDarkMixMar2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>Rise - Terrace Mix - Progressive House Trance mix by Prototype202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>This months melodic mix Part 1 is a sunset selection to wash away those winter blues with beautiful synth laden tunes from Ilya Maluev, Quarrel, Cosmic Gate. Aeron Aether, Schodt, Sundriver and many more including a remastered version of the classic Treatment Declined by Andy Moor from 2003. Enjoy!</itunes:subtitle>
				<itunes:summary>This months melodic mix Part 1 is a sunset selection to wash away those winter blues with beautiful synth laden tunes from Ilya Maluev, Quarrel, Cosmic Gate. Aeron Aether, Schodt, Sundriver and many more including a remastered version of the classic Treatment Declined by Andy Moor from 2003. Enjoy!
				
Ilya Maluev - Purple Sky - Iji Recordings 
Claes Rosen - Feel You - Deep Digital 
Tom Lue - Into The Closet (Shingo Nakemura Remix) - Morphosis Records 
Schodt - Here With Me feat. Aida Fenhel (Sundriver Vocal Mix) - Silk Royal Records 
Gabriel Batz - Pilgrim - Ora Recordings 
Sundriver - Here With Me feat. Aida Fenhel (Schodt Vocal Mix) - Silk Royal Records
Aeron Aether - Twilight (Zodiax Mix) - Morphosis Records 
Quarrel - Spring (Luis B Remix) - Silk Textures
Cosmic Gate - Raging (Duderstadt Remix) - Black Hole Recordings
Soundprank - The Far Side- Anjunadeep 
Adam K - Wake Up - Hotbox Digital 
Schodt - The Spirit and the Harmony - Particles
Ilya Maluev - Art Nouveau - Nueva Digital 
Sworn - Treatment Declined - Armada Music 	
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:07:03</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza balaeric</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>This months melodic mix Part 1 is a sunset selection to wash away those winter blues with beautiful synth laden tunes from Ilya Maluev, Quarrel, Cosmic Gate. Aeron Aether, Schodt, Sundriver and many more including a remastered version of the classic Treatment Declined by Andy Moor from 2003. Enjoy!</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202Rise-TerraceMix/Prototype202Rise_TerraceMixMar2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
				<item>
		<title>Daybreak - Progressive House Trance and Breaks mix by Prototype202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>Kicking off February 2011 we are back with new tunes from all the usual suspects and more. Sundriver, Schodt, Ad Brown, Aeron Aether, Shingo Nakemura and more. Track of the month the superb Japan tinged melodic trance of Submarine from Hiroyuki ODA with Shingo Nakemura on the remix duties</itunes:subtitle>
				<itunes:summary>Kicking off February 2011 we are back with new tunes from all the usual suspects and more. Sundriver, Schodt, Ad Brown, Aeron Aether, Shingo Nakemura and more. Track of the month the superb Japan tinged melodic trance of Submarine from Hiroyuki ODA with Shingo Nakemura on the remix duties
				Angel - Blue Neptune 
Shingo Nakamura - Im With You 
Johan Gielen - Jonko 
Bodytemp - All Night Long 
Abdomen Burst - Sakkura (Dmitry Bessonov Remix) 
Elfsong and Aeron Aether - Kaivalaya (Original Mix)
Sundriver - Here With Me feat Aida Fenhel (Schodt Vocal Mix)
Dinka - Violet
Vinny Troia - Do For Love (Matt Lange Remix) 
Ad Brown and Proff - I'll Try (Ad Brown Remix) 
Aeron Aether - Twilight Feat. Catherine (Not Okay Remix ) 
Shipstad - I'm Never Alone (Schodt Remix) 
Hiroyuki ODA - Submarine (Shingo Nakemura Remix) 
Hiroyuki ODA - Luminescence (Kyohei Akagawa Remix) 		
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:04:03</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza balaeric</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>Kicking off February 2011 we are back with new tunes from all the usual suspects and more. Sundriver, Schodt, Ad Brown, Aeron Aether, Shingo Nakemura and more. Track of the month the superb Japan tinged melodic trance of Submarine from Hiroyuki ODA with Shingo Nakemura on the remix duties </description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202DaybreakMix/Prototype202Daybreak_Feb2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>New Yearmix by Prototype202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>A roundup of the best progressive trance tunes of the year .. perfect for playing loud new years Eve. Featuring the best of progressive 2011 from the likes of Oceanlab, Yuri Kane, Ad Brown, Maor Levi, Arty, Kayu and Albert and more ..... Enjoy and Happy New Year.</itunes:subtitle>
				<itunes:summary>A roundup of the best progressive trance tunes of the year .. perfect for playing loud new years Eve. Featuring the best of progressive 2011 from the likes of Oceanlab, Yuri Kane, Ad Brown, Maor Levi, Arty, Kayu and Albert and more ..... Enjoy and Happy New Year.
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:12:03</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza balaeric</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>A roundup of the best progressive trance tunes of the year .. perfect for playing loud new years Eve. Featuring the best of progressive 2011 from the likes of Oceanlab, Yuri Kane, Ad Brown, Maor Levi, Arty, Kayu and Albert and more ..... Enjoy and Happy New Year. 
			</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202NewYearmix2010/Prototype202Yearmix_January_2011.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>Drift by Prototype202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>More melodic mayhem with Super8 and Tab, First State, Shingo Nakemura, Cosmic Gate and more. Track of the Month the Elfsong remix of Meridian by Eryo and Kay-D .. deep progressive quality</itunes:subtitle>
				<itunes:summary>More melodic mayhem with Super8 and Tab, First State, Shingo Nakemura, Cosmic Gate and more. Track of the Month the Elfsong remix of Meridian by Eryo and Kay-D .. deep progressive quality
Mishalekseev - Try
First State - Surrounds Me (feat. Elliot Johns)
Alexander Popov - Vapour Trails (Shingo Nakemura Remix)
Aruna - Let Go
Maxi Valvona - Lost In Vagueness (Soundprank Remix)
Gareth Emery - Stars (Jerome Ismae remix)
Julie Thompson - Shine (JPL and George Hales Remix)
Shevskee - Deep Breath ( Shevskee and Piotro mix)
Super8 and Tab - Slow To Learn (feat Jan Burton)
Eryo and Kay-D - Meridian ( Elfsong remix)
Shingo Nakemura - Linear Light (Embliss Remix)
Super8 and Tab - Empire (Feat Jan Burton)
Crafty Cuts - Stimpack (Soundprank Remix)
Cosmic Gate - Under Your Spell feat Aruna						
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:06:53</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza balaeric</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>More melodic mayhem with Super8 + Tab, First State, Shingo Nakemura, Cosmic Gate and more. Track of the Month the Elfsong remix of Meridian by Eryo and Kay-D .. deep progressive quality ! </description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202DriftMix/Prototype202_Drift_Dec2010.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
		<title>November Rain by Prototype202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>Another Month of superb melodic music from Soundprank, Maor Levi, BT and Andrew Bayer Nick Stoynoff and More. Track of the month this month is the superb Uncle Jonney likes Cocaine by Cassino and Laben, a bouncy melodic little house tinged number that just keeps moving. Enjoy!</itunes:subtitle>
				<itunes:summary>Another Month of superb melodic music from Soundprank, Maor Levi, BT and Andrew Bayer Nick Stoynoff and More. Track of the month this month is the superb Uncle Jonney likes Cocaine by Cassino and Laben, a bouncy melodic little house tinged number that just keeps moving. Enjoy!
Alex Monakhov - Order of Chaos
Aeron Aether - Searching For a Memory (Sundriver Instrumental Mix)
Soundprank - Storm
Audio Junkies - Deeper
Tom Fall - Dive
Maor Levi - Chasing Love
Nick Stoynoff - Tokyo Nights
BT + Andrew Bayer - Emergency (Today is the Day Mix)
Pablo Acenso - In Bold Letters 
Soundprank -Endgame (Stefan Anions Fallout Mix)
Ad Brown - As The Rain Falls feat Kerry Leva
Blackwatch and Hybrid - Alright (Blackwatch Vocal Mix)
Cassino and Laben - Uncle Jonney Likes Cocaine
Jemmy - The Annexe								
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:09:53</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks, ibiza trance, ibiza balaeric</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>Another Month of superb melodic music from Soundprank, Maor Levi, BT and Andrew Bayer Nick Stoynoff and More. Track of the month this month is the superb Uncle Jonney likes Cocaine by Cassino and Laben, a bouncy melodic house tinged number that just keeps moving. Enjoy!</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202NovemberRainMix/Prototype202_November_RainNov2010.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tues, 02 Nov 2010 10:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
            <title>Autumn Leaves by Prototype202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>Another great month for melodic music fans, track of the month has to be the superb Sylleptica by Aeron Aether and Elfsong, cant get enough of that track pure class. Alternatively for something more uplifting Ad Browns Something for the Pain is also doing the business. Enjoy!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Another great month for melodic music fans, track of the month has to be the superb Sylleptica by Aeron Aether and Elfsong, cant get enough of that track pure class. Alternatively for something more uplifting Ad Browns Something for the Pain is also doing the business. Enjoy!
							Sylleptica - Aeron Aether + Elfsong 
							Mossy - Beautiful
							Mobil / Eximinds - Lost Dreams 
							Mango - Good Morning Track : Sunn Jellie Remix 
							Terry Da Libre - Enchanted Waters : Ayelon Remix 
							Pulstate + Juventa  - Somnia : Yuri Kane Remix 
							Luigi Lusini - Set You Free (Bahamut)
							Joonas Hahmo - Pizzi (Proff and Vadim Solviev Remix) 
							Ad Brown - Something for the Pain ft Renee Six 
							Dapple Apple - Cognac 1994
							Tom Fall - Relections : Embliss Remix 
							Andre Sobota - One Day Out : Shingo Nakemura Remix 
							The Emissary - Synapse : Fretwell Remix 
							Mossy - The Light 								
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:12:18</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>Another great month for melodic music fans, track of the month has to be the superb Sylleptica by Aeron Aether and Elfsong, cant get enough of that track pure class. Alternatively for something more uplifting Ad Browns Something for the Pain is also doing the business. Enjoy!</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202AutumnLeaves/Prototype202Autumn_LeavesOct2010.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 11:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
            <title>Bonus Purists Mix by Prototype202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>Deep Progressive and Breaks Bonus Mix, presented by Prototype202</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>So much awesome music this month heres a bonus mix. Enjoy!
							The Emmisary - Synapse - Frakture Rmx 
							Sylleptica - Aeron Aether + Elfsong 
							Pit Stoner - Flying Paper Planes
							Stan Kolev - Devastating
							Andre Sobota - One Day Out - Soliquid remix 
							Stefan Anion - Strangers - Aeron Aether Remix 
							Duane Barry - Soft Light 
							Nick Stoynoff - Highway
							Pit Stoner - Flying Paper Planes - Piotro Microprog Mix								
			</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:00:00</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance, melodic trance, progressive breaks</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>So much awesome music this month heres a bonus mix. Enjoy! . Enjoy!</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202PuristsBonusMix/Prototype202_PuristsBonusMix_2010.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tues, 14 Sep 2010 11:29:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
            <title>After Sunset by Prototype 202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>New tracks and remixes from Solarstone, Cressida, Rex Mundi, Beltek, Susana and  Mat Zo. Track of the month Kalua Islands : Rex Mundi - Paronator Remix. Enjoy!</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>New tracks and remixes from Solarstone, Cressida, Rex Mundi, Beltek, Susana and  Mat Zo. Track of the month Kalua Islands : Rex Mundi - Paronator Remix. Enjoy!</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:09:00</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>This mix features new tracks and remixes from Solarstone, Cressida, Rex Mundi, Beltek, Susana and  Mat Zo. Track of the month Kalua Islands : Rex Mundi - Paronator Remix. Enjoy!</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202AfterSunsetMix/Prototype202After_SunsetAug2010.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 1 Aug 2010 11:23:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
            <title>Summer Breaks by Prototype 202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>New tracks and remixes from Aeron Aether, Elfsong, Amador, Stefan Anion, Ridgewalkers and  Fretwell. Track of the month Red Dust:Nick Stoynoff.</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>New tracks and remixes from Aeron Aether, Elfsong, Amador, Stefan Anion, Ridgewalkers and  Fretwell. Track of the month Red Dust:Nick Stoynoff. Enjoy!</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:08:00</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>New tracks and remixes from Aeron Aether, Elfsong, Amador, Stefan Anion, Ridgewalkers and  Fretwell. Track of the month Red Dust:Nick Stoynoff. Enjoy!</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202SummerBreaks/Prototype202_Summer_Breaks_July2010.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 1 Jul 2010 11:23:47 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
            <title>Ibiza Sunrise by Prototype 202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>New tracks and remixes from the likes of Stoneface and Terminal, Aarmin Van Buuren, Andain, Gary Orvis and Arty. Track of the month mike Koglin Autumn</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>New tracks and remixes from the likes of Stoneface and Terminal, Aarmin Van Buuren, Andain, Gary Orvis and Arty. Track of the month mike Koglin Autumn</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:12:00</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>New tracks and remixes from the likes of Stoneface and Terminal, Aarmin Van Buuren, Andain, Gary Orvis and Arty. Track of the month mike Koglin Autumn</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202IbizaSunrise/Prototype202IbizaSunrise_June2010.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 1 Jun 2010 11:23:10 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
            <title>Lighter Nights by Prototype 202</title>
			<itunes:subtitle>A monthly podcast of melodic progressive house and trance, presented by Prototype202 New tracks and remixes from the likes of  Way Out West, Tilt, Tritonal, Xgenic, Anhken and Blackfeel Wite. Track of the month Yuri Kane: Right Back</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>New tracks and remixes from the likes of  Way Out West, Tilt, Tritonal, Xgenic, Anhken and Blackfeel Wite. Track of the month Yuri Kane: Right Back</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>1:21:00</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Prototype202</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>trance, dj, progressive, radio, prototype202, mix, progressive house, progressive trance</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
			<category domain="">Music</category>
            <description>New tracks and remixes from the likes of  Way Out West, Tilt, Tritonal, Xgenic, Anhken and Blackfeel Wite. Track of the month Yuri Kane: Right Back</description>
            <enclosure url="http://www.archive.org/download/Prototype202LighterNights/Prototype202LighterNights_May2010.mp3"/>
            <pubDate>Sat, 1 May 2010 11:21:33 +0100</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
