<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Cloak &amp; Dagger Radio</title>
<link>http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</link>
<description>A two-hour weekly radio show curated by the unappreciated scholars responsible for Cloak &amp; Dagger Media. Listen in as they fight the good fight against awkward dead-air, fumbled punch-lines, and general incompetence - all while spinning records by the best songwriters in indie rock.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Cloak &amp; Dagger Media, 2006</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle>A weekly indie rock radio show dedicated to the lost art of songwriting.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>Cloak &amp; Dagger Media</itunes:author>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Mike Dutkewych</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>mike@cloakanddaggermedia.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/radio_logo.jpg" />
<itunes:category text="Music"/>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit> 
<generator>Cloak &amp; Dagger Media</generator>
<ttl>1</ttl>

<item>
<title>Show 01 | 2006-02-20</title>
<description>This is our first show, cut us some slack. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych &amp; Dave Frazee. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 11:59:53 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-02-20.mp3" length="6595000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>109:55</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 03 | 2006-03-06</title>
<description>Our third show and things are still a little dicey. We try to compensate by playing a ton of new tunes. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych &amp; Dave Frazee. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2006 11:59:57 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-03-06.mp3" length="6624000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>110:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 04 | 2006-03-13</title>
<description>No more screwin' around! In this episode, we celebrate some birthdays and finally learn how to run the phones. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych &amp; Dave Frazee. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2006 11:59:50 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-03-13.mp3" length="6571000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>109:31</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 06 | 2006-03-27</title>
<description>More Cloak &amp; Dagger history in the making! This week we welcome not one, but TWO in-studio performers! Listen as Novi Split and Desert Places perform live, give away CDs, and try to make the mundane seem interesting. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych &amp; Dave Frazee. In-studio performances by: Novi Split &amp; Desert Places. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2006 11:59:05 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-03-27.mp3" length="4791000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>79:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, novi split, desert places, david j</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 08 | 2006-04-10</title>
<description>Thankless intern, Joshua Gillis steals the show and the hearts of freshman girls everywhere. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2006 11:59:58 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-04-10.mp3" length="5859000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>97:39</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 09 | 2006-04-17</title>
<description>The Cloak &amp; Dagger Radio ROCK-A-THON! Featuring Downriver Detroit mudrock legend, Dan McMath.  Listen as we discuss all of his previous 108 bands, including his hilarious prank phone call project, Phonework. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych &amp; Dave Frazee. Theme music by: Novi Split. Guest DJ: Dan McMath. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-04-17.mp3" length="4731000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>78:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 10 | 2006-05-08</title>
<description>For Cloak &amp; Dagger Radio's triumphant return from vacation, we showcase the new split CD by Kind Of Like Spitting and Lemuria. We even throw a couple of impromptu interviews in for good measure. Listen to Alex from Lemuria talk about his favorite love triangles, while Ben from KOLS reflects on living the high-life (pun intended) on the top floor of the Philadelphia Ritz-Carlton. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. Interviews with: Alex Kerns &amp; Ben Barnett. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2006 11:59:50 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-05-08.mp3" length="3890000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>64:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, kind of like spitting, lemuria, ben barnett</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 11 | 2006-05-15</title>
<description>This time we take our first crack at WHFR's annual Theme Week. Our genius concept is "alternates". We play only alternate versions - demos, live cuts, acoustic renditions, etc. - of great songs by great bands. And since Frazee flaked AGAIN (this time to go to the Tool concert!!), we even go so far as including Dan McMath as our alternate co-host. This can't miss.... Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 11:59:29 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-05-15.mp3" length="4055000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>67:35</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 12 | 2006-05-22</title>
<description>A Tool concert leads to an alternate co-host leads to listener e-mail leads to a decisive arm-wrestling match leads to loose animals in the studio leads to a big personnel shake-up in the Cloak &amp; Dagger crew. The dawn of a new, more crowded era in indie rock radio. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2006 11:59:49 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-05-22.mp3" length="4400000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>73:20</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 13 | 2006-05-29</title>
<description>This week we drop the curtain on two of our new segments (read: gimmicks), "Wyandotte Off The Blotter" and "We've Got Angry Voicemail". We also take some phone calls, shamelessly plug our new MySpace account (ahem... myspace.com/cloakanddaggerradio), and find out Frazee only pretends to like The Flaming Lips. Oh yeah, and we play a bunch of tunes, too. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2006 11:59:52 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-05-29.mp3" length="4109000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>68:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 14 | 2006-06-05</title>
<description>On the eve of 6/6/06, we unleash screaming and distortion in remembrance of one of Detroit's heaviest bands, Thoughts Of Ionesco. We even got Ionesco frontman, Sean Hoen to take part in the festivities. Listen as Dan and Sean rehash the past, while Frazee is accosted by angry Flaming Lips fans. The hits just keep coming on C&amp;DR. And this week they're in drop D tuning. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. Interview with: Sean Hoen. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-06-05.mp3" length="3254000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>54:14</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, hoen, ionesco, detroit</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 15 | 2006-06-12</title>
<description>New tunes, same dudes. This week we make some shocking discoveries in Dave Frazee's wallet, talk our usual trash on Wyandotte, Michigan, and listen to the highlight reel from Dan McMath's stand-up comedy debut. If you listen to one hard-hitting, investigative indie rock comedy show today, make it this one. 'Cause we ask the tough questions on C&amp;DR. Like, what's brown and sticky? Stay tuned to find out. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2006 11:59:13 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-06-12.mp3" length="4197000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>69:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 17 | 2006-06-26</title>
<description>Another big C&amp;DR comeback show. Thanks to the shitty equipment in Studio A, last week's show was forever lost in the radio abyss. To compensate, we took Show 17 by the balls, and it's our distinct pleasure to present them to you. This week, Ill Lit vocalist, D. Ahearn calls in to talk shop, we showcase the brand new Bonnie 'Prince' Billy EP in its entirety, debut an improved Wyandotte Off The Blotter segment, and engage in a friendly round of Battle Of The Hot Songwriters. That's right, Nedelle vs. Jarboe. Now that's entertainment. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-06-26.mp3" length="4784000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>79:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, ill lit, ahearn, nedelle, jarboe</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 18 | 2006-07-03</title>
<description>O Cloak &amp; Dagger, we stand on guard for thee! You know summer is officially here when the grill gets fired-up and the only thing louder than C&amp;DR is the sound of a loved one exploding himself with illegal fireworks. So escape from that relentless July sun, close the windows, pull the shades, and join us in celebrating the most important summer holiday in American history: Canada Day. Listen as we enjoy some pointless Canadian trivia, fresh Canadian bacon, and an all-Canadian soundtrack. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2006 11:59:41 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-07-03.mp3" length="4264000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>71:14</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, canada, canadian, bacon</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 19 | 2006-07-10</title>
<description>We spent last week celebrating Canadians. We spend this week catching shit from Americans. We thought we'd heard it all until one particularly red-blooded patriot threatened to beat us with a cactus. Besides the profanity and threats of violence, we play a ton of hot new tunes from this summer's most anticipated releases. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-07-10.mp3" length="3848000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>64:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, canada, usa, patriot, springsteen</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 20 | 2006-07-24</title>
<description>C&amp;DR hits the big 2-0! No way in hell did I ever expect to make it to episode 20, but thanks to the unwavering support of our loyal listeners and the dedication of my humble sidekicks, we came, we saw, and we kicked the shit out of #20. Join us as we stroll down Cloak &amp; Dagger memory lane with a modest studio audience and the best tunes of the past 20 weeks. This is our finest hour. Thanks for listening. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-07-24.mp3" length="4632000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>77:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, audience, crowd, cheering, celebration, 20th, anniversary</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 21 | 2006-08-07</title>
<description>Season 2 of Cloak &amp; Dagger Radio gets underway with a (muffled) bang. Bad attitudes, missing equipment, disagreeable callers... This show reminds me of the old days. Listen as we discuss nothing in particular and play tunes by a bunch of nobodies. C&amp;DR at its finest. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-08-07.mp3" length="3460000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>57:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, oldham</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 23 | 2006-08-21</title>
<description>Man, we're funny. And handsome. It's a shame we're on radio and not television. I guess we just have to do our best with what we've got... And this week, what we've got is Bonny motherf'ing Billy! That's right. Bonnie 'Prince' Billy dropped by the WHFR Studios to play a few tunes as part of his Free Bonny Tour, and it's our pleasure to host this encore presentation. And if that ain't enough, we're also spinning brand new tunes from the likes of Akron/Family, Jeremy Enigk, and Golden Smog! So steal a pair headphones and call-in sick to work. We'll handle the rest. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. In-studio performance by: Bonnie 'Prince' Billy. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-08-21.mp3" length="3727000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>62:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, oldham, bonny</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 24 | 2006-09-11</title>
<description>C&amp;DR: Post-Op Edition. After Mike Dutkewych's traumatic pilonidal cystectomy kept us off the air for two weeks, we're primed and ready to resume our usual shit-talking and "gem"-dropping. This week we welcome back Cloak &amp; Dagger Media's thankless intern, Joshua Gillis who helps us roll out brand new cuts from Bonny, Yo La Tengo, and Nedelle. We also talk shop with all-star surgeon, Dr. Lewis, and fourth-string radio personality, Dave Frazee. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dan McMath &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-09-11.mp3" length="4319000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>71:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, gillis, cyst, pilonidal</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 25 | 2006-09-18</title>
<description>In the face of nearly indomitable negativity, C&amp;DR still manages to bring the love. This week we reconcile with ex-listeners, make new friends in Mother Russia, and help ourselves to some hot new jams from Bonnie 'Prince' Billy, Cornelius, Viking Moses, and Elliott Smith - back from the dead! Not even round two of the Frazee/Gillis death-match can derail this posi-train. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-09-18.mp3" length="3708000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>61:48</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, gillis</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 26 | 2006-09-25</title>
<description>So much for peace and love. This week round three of the Frazee/Gillis death-match escalates to new heights of stupidity. And speaking of stupidity, we also make Joshy the thankless intern feel right at home by assigning him menial chores, rifling through his wallet without permission, and making fun of Uncle Jack White. We even let him play a Xiu Xiu song! Rest-assured that won't happen again. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee, Dan McMath &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-09-25.mp3" length="3936000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>65:36</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, gillis</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 27 | 2006-10-02</title>
<description>Winner takes all this week as Dave Frazee and Joshua Gillis settle the score once-and-for-all in C&amp;DR's first ever rap battle. Will Josh question Frazee's masculinity? Will Frazee settle for knocking Josh's Uncle White Stripes? The answers and the champion lie within... Along with the usual onslaught of great tunes, including a hot new track from The Hold Steady, aka the most-hyped band of 2006. Blow it out your ass, Pitchfork. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee, Dan McMath &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2006 11:57:42 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-10-02.mp3" length="3626000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>60:26</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, gillis, rap, battle</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 28 | 2006-10-09</title>
<description>When Kind Of Like Spitting hands you lemons, toss 'em in Josh's rock tumbler and turn 'em into gems. That's what we always say on Cloak &amp; Dagger Radio. This week we prepare for an exciting in-studio performance by Ben Barnett of KOLS only to have the band break up and Ben leave town - opting to drive 35 hours home to Portland, Oregon rather than play on our show. Dejected and humiliated, we somehow manage to persevere by channeling strength from '80s cartoon character Jem, and our imprisoned Russian immigrant pal Ivan. By the time we reach our compensatory gem storm (new ones by The Evens, Viking Moses, Lemuria, Detachment Kit, The Curtains), one can't help but wonder, "Kind Of Like who?" Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee, Dan McMath &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2006 11:58:52 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-10-09.mp3" length="3205000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>53:25</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, gillis, kols</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 29 | 2006-10-16</title>
<description>Not since God has one man's gigantic head and booming voice captured the hearts of so many. Ladies and gentlemen, this week we proudly welcome C&amp;DR's biggest fan, Bosley to the studio. Get to know this living legend as he discusses being dishonorably discharged from the military, performs Wilco karaoke, and jokes about being raped by a priest. Hallelujah, amen! Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee, Dan McMath &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. Guest: Bosley. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2006 11:59:51 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-10-16.mp3" length="4180000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>69:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, gillis, bosley</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 30 | 2006-10-30</title>
<description>From the burning bosom of mighty Lucifer comes the most ghastly, ghouly, and spooky edition of C&amp;DR ever. We invite you to follow us down to the tenth level of hell where we'll celebrate the bloody guts of Halloween with thirteen skin-crawling tunes by demonically-possessed performers like Scott Walker, Nick Cave, Fantomas, Jarboe, and Current 93. This episode is NOT for the faint-of-heart. Mmwaahahahahahahaha, etc. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee, Dan McMath &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 11:59:45 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-10-30.mp3" length="4068000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>67:48</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, mcmath, wyandotte, gillis, devil, satan, halloween, hell, death, blood, guts</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 31 | 2006-11-06</title>
<description>Experience the rise and fall of the Soviet Union this week on C&amp;DR. A Russian illegal alien hijacks our show and consequently, our hearts. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-11-06.mp3" length="3555000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>59:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, ivan, russia</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 32 | 2006-11-13</title>
<description>Thanks to generous contributions from this week's fantastic guests, Peter And The Wolf and Dodo Bird, C&amp;DR can move ahead two more spaces in our quest for indie rock radio domination. Listen as the bands collaborate, debut brand new tunes, and talk in-depth about their songwriting. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. In-studio performances by: Peter And The Wolf &amp; Dodo Bird. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2006 11:59:44 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-11-13.mp3" length="2771000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>46:11</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, red, hunter, meric, long, dodo, bird, peter, wolf</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 33 | 2006-11-20</title>
<description>Aha! Proof that good punk bands aren't completely extinct. Lemuria joins us this week to talk the talk and rock the rock. These wholesome guys and girl perform ten pop-punk gems about life, love, and the pursuit of... vagina juice? Ahem. Yeah, I'll let them explain that one. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. In-studio performance by: Lemuria. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2006 11:59:24 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-11-20.mp3" length="2726000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>45:26</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, lemuria, buffalo</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Show 34 | 2006-12-11</title>
<description>It's been almost two years since I started taking advantage of Joshua Gillis's inability to tell me no. Soon after he started hangin' around C&amp;DHQ, I started giving him shitwork assignments to take home with him. He traded me countless hours of tape transcription and menial labor for the status of Cloak &amp; Dagger Media's thankless intern. Since then, he's been our only reliable contributor and he's sprouted new patches of freak-folk facial hair, signaling the dramatic end of his long battle with puberty. Tonight, Josh Gillis graduates to the ranks of C&amp;D clerical assistant and full-fledged radio co-host. Tomorrow, who will transcribe this two-hour Colin Meloy interview? (Answer: No one. The Decemberists suck.) Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2006 11:59:43 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-12-11.mp3" length="3670000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>61:10</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, graduation</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 35 | 2006-12-18</title>
<description>Ho ho ho's about you throw another chestnut on the fire and turn off that infernal "Carol Of The Bells" song. C&amp;DR's got you covered this holiday season. So, curl up next to your decomposing Christmas tree and listen to us celebrate the season the only way we know how... By spreading peace and goodwill with a festive playlist (Parenthetical Girls, Yo La Tengo, The Polyphonic Spree) and other seasonal gags (Wyandotte Off The Blotter holiday madlibs, carrolling prank phone calls)! It's a festivus for the rest of us here on Cloak &amp; Dagger Radio. Thank Baby Jesus it only happens once a year. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2006 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2006-12-18.mp3" length="3678000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>61:18</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, christmas, holiday, kwanza, snow, santa, nathaniel, carroll</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 36 | 2007-01-01</title>
<description>2006 certainly was a limp noodle. That's why we're spending the first broadcast of '07 pondering over the last 365 days in our exciting year-end wrap-up. During this extended 90-minute edition of C&amp;DR, we treat the live studio audience to our respective top 10 lists, as well as the first round of ill-conceived Cloaky awards. We even enlisted a live drummer to fulfill any novelty requirements we had left in our 2006 contract. According to the placemat at Golden China, 2006 was the Year Of The Dog. According to Mike Dutkewych, 2007 will be the Year Of The Dagger. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2007 11:59:25 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-01-01.mp3" length="5400000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>90:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, new, years, awards</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 37 | 2007-01-15</title>
<description>Still ridin' high on 2007, C&amp;DR turns this week's spotlight on the year's first wave of releases. We preview forthcoming records by heavy-hitters like The Arcade Fire, Modest Mouse, and Deerhoof, as well as newbies like Menomena, The Broken West, and Au Revoir Simone. And while the anticipation storm bears down upon us, we even manage to work Novi Split's 2007-cents into the mix. All this AND Dave Frazee-Gone-Wild. Hold on to your butts. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. Interview with: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2007 11:59:36 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-01-15.mp3" length="4309000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>71:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, david</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 38 | 2007-01-22</title>
<description>We're still in the pink this week on C&amp;DR. Join us for an exclusive listening party as we unveil Novi Split's long-awaited new album, "Pink In The Sink". Listen as David J. personally walks us down the aisles of his sophomore record, track by track. He shares everything you've ever wanted to know, but didn't care enough to ask: the good, the bad, the Beyonce. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. Interview with: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 11:59:23 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-01-22.mp3" length="2592000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>43:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, david</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 40 | 2007-02-04</title>
<description>Testify, brothers and sisters! The fury of the Dagger knows not the meaning of mercy, nor the limitations of cretinous fascism. And thus, for our 40th episode, we proclaim our freedom from the mutant shackles of WHFR. When station "management" threatened us with indefinite "suspension" for breaking arbitrary "rules", we proudly told them where to shove it. And by all accounts, shove it they did! So join us, loyal compatriots, as we conclude Season 2, rejuvenated, fully-realized, and uninhibited by dumbfucks. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee, Joshua Gillis &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 4 Feb 2007 11:59:44 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-02-04.mp3" length="3425000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>57:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, mcmath, sermon, dmx, dikembe, mutombo, gems, star, wars, rap, battle</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 41 | 2007-02-12</title>
<description>Three seasons in and we're still up to no good. This time, to start the season off proper, we reunite with our biggest fan, a mortal enemy, and Jodeci. You may be saying to yourself, "Jodeci? I know it's almost Valentine's Day, but what the f'?" Yeah, I don't know. Blame 'Cupid' McMath. My apologies to ladies and gay guys. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2007 11:59:51 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-02-12.mp3" length="2658000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>44:18</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, mcmath, bosley, jodeci</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 43 | 2007-02-26</title>
<description>For further proof of C&amp;DR's commitment to quality, look no further than this very episode. Just when you thought we couldn't break any more ground, we bust out a brand new bit that will revolutionize the way the world drinks beer (and piss). That's right! Brace yourself for the drinking game that's sweeping the nation: Piss Or Beer*! And you know the good times don't end there... No sir, not when you've got a soundtrack including alcoholics like Peter Bjorn &amp; John, Jeffrey Lewis, and Sunset Rubdown! So listen to this stupidity. We'll call you a cab. (*state-appointed convicted criminal not included). Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Joshua Gillis &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2007 11:59:34 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-02-26.mp3" length="2683000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>44:43</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, mcmath, bosley, ryan, beer, piss</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 44 | 2007-03-05</title>
<description>Leave the crystal-ballin' to the professionals. Before C&amp;DR, seeing the future was never so cheap and painless. Join us as we take another peek under 2007's skirt, previewing new music from Feist, Bill Callahan, Dr. Dog, and beyond. We also make time to answer the burning questions 'Is Dave Frazee Here Or Not?' and 'What's In Your Wallet, Janitor Ryan?'... So climb in. You don't need plutonium to power this podcast. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2007 11:59:02 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-03-05.mp3" length="2887000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>48:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, ryan, king, jammers</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 45 | LA Movie</title> 
<description>LA Movie is a sociological exercise shedding old light on a tale of two cities. Filmed over the course of a typical LA weekend, Detroiter Mike Dutkewych set out to document the cultural divide between these rival cities -- as seen through the eyes of a vegan, a loan officer, a grant writer, a longshoreman, an avocado heiress, an ex-reality TV star, the Detroit Pistons, the Los Angeles Clippers, and countless musicians. LA Movie is heartwarming, thought-provoking, and mildly successful in answering at least one age-old question: Why did the feminist cross the road? LA Movie contains brief nudity and strong language and may not be suitable for anyone.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 03:00:00 EST</pubDate> 
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/LAMOVIE.mp4" length="938000" type="video/mov" />  
<itunes:duration>15:38</itunes:duration> 
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, la, detroit, clippers, pistons, hollywood, novi, split, dutkewych, biazevich, feminists, cure, billy, joel, four, tops, greyson, watson, lopez, gutierrez, hernandez, bean, garza</itunes:keywords>  
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 46 | 2007-04-16</title>
<description>This week the 'C' in C&amp;DR stands for Castanets. We spent an evening with them in the basement of a University of Michigan dorm building where they introduced us to material from their forthcoming album and discussed a phenomenon called "night week". Listen as Ray Raposa and friends perform an intimate set of brand new songs and covers of Viking Moses and Jana Hunter. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. Performance by: Castanets. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 11:59:18 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-04-16.mp3" length="1973000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>32:53</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, castanets</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 47 | 2007-04-23</title>
<description>We believe that the best kind of experiment is the accidental kind. The kind that involves new friends and recording gear at 2 AM. And a NYC singer-songwriter named Jeffrey Lewis. And that guy from Dr. Dog. And a keyboard tone called 'The Human Voice'. And a left-handed guitar played upside-down with a lighter. And that terrible action movie, 'Ricochet'. And seven great songs available exclusively on C&amp;DR. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. Performance by: Jeffrey Lewis. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 11:59:11 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-04-23.mp3" length="2211000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>36:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, jeffrey, lewis, dr, dog</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 48 | 2007-05-28</title>
<description>The de-shackling continues as C&amp;DR gets a much-needed 30-minute-makeover that summons Harry Nilsson, Ian Curtis, and Baby Huey from beyond the grave. Meanwhile, Ben Gibbard dispels some pesky rumors as the first victim of our new segment, "Ambush Interview". An instant classic! Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. (Ambush) Interview with: Ben Gibbard. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2007 11:59:38 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-05-28.mp3" length="2046000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>34:06</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, ambush, ben, gibbard, postal, service, death, cab</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 49 | 2007-06-11</title>
<description>After spending two weeks sorting through fanmail and MySpace comments, we think we've finally found the winning formula: dead musicians and prank phone calls to Pacific Northwestern lit rock supergods. That's all it takes to be an internet success. This time we roll the dice with Silkworm, Screamin' Jay Hawkins, and Dusty Springfield. Then we talk to Decemberist Colin Meloy about losing his virginity. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. (Ambush) Interview with: Colin Meloy. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 11:59:56 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-06-11.mp3" length="1838000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>30:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, ambush, colin, meloy, decemberists</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 50 | 2007-07-09</title>
<description>C&amp;DR spotlights Chicago reissue label, Numero Group, and their amazing "Eccentric Soul" compilations. Label founder Ken Shipley gives us a guided tour of the series, playing a song from each volume and sharing the stories behind the best soul music you've never heard. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Interview with: Ken Shipley (Numero Group). For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2007 11:59:41 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-07-09.mp3" length="2534000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>42:14</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, eccentric, soul, numero, group, shipley, capsoul, bandit, big, mack, deep, city, lenaburg, twinight, prix, motown, reissue</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 51 | 2007-07-30</title>
<description>Last month, Cloak &amp; Dagger hosted our first "Singles Mixer", inviting a handful of friends to gather 'round a set of speakers with the sole purpose of sharing good times and great tunes with one another. This is what happened. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2007 11:59:15 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-07-30.mp3" length="2410000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>40:10</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, singles, mixer, party</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 52 | 2007-08-20</title>
<description>The return of the standard issue C&amp;DR. This time, we introduce the world to the aptly-titled "Fun Party Guess Game", and get the Ambush Interview tables turned on us by one of the only Pacific Northwestern songwriters we haven't tried to fuck with. And of course, we compliment our cheap gags with some fine forgotten tracks by Jim Ford, Shel Silverstein, and The Ink Spots. No, we don't care about the young folks. Hosted by: Mike Dutkewych. Co-hosted by: Dave Frazee &amp; Joshua Gillis. Theme music by: Novi Split. (Ambush) Interview by: Ben Barnett. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-08-20.mp3" length="2043000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>34:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, ambush, ben, barnett, kols, game, snl</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 53 | 2007-09-17</title>
<description>What happens when you're stranded in Ann Arbor after midnight with the Dirty Projectors and no electricity? Another C&amp;DR Session fiasco with a happy ending. After a brief scramble for an electrical outlet, we managed to stretch out in a bank parking lot to capture an incredible set by the Projectors, with help from the occasional drunk passerby. Hosted by: Joshua Gillis. Performance by: Dirty Projectors. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 11:59:46 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-09-17.mp3" length="1281000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>21:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, dirty, projectors, black, flag, ann, arbor</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Show 55 | 2007-10-29</title>
<description>Confronted by its own mortality and double-crossed by a deranged #1 fan, the Cloak &amp; Dagger Radio crew must come together once more to defend its legacy and save one of its own. This is the final episode. Starring: Mike Dutkewych, Dave Frazee, Joshua Gillis, Dan McMath. Co-starring: Jack White, Chris Hansen, Jazzy, Lauren LoPiccolo, Ben Gibbard, David Berman. Written by: Mike Dutkewych &amp; Dan McMath. Theme music by: Novi Split. For playlists and additional information, visit www.cloakanddaggermedia.com</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2007 11:59:59 EST</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://www.cloakanddaggermedia.com/radio/shows/2007-10-29.mp3" length="1920000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>32:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cloak, dagger, indie, punk, folk, songwriter, songwriting, lyrics, dutkewych, frazee, wyandotte, gillis, novi, split, jack, white, stripes, dateline, bosley, catch, predator, ben, gibbard, death, cab, david, berman, silver, jews, jazzy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>