<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Christian Apologetics by Windmill Ministries</title>
		<link>http://www.WindmillMinistries.org</link>
		<itunes:subtitle>Christian Apologetics and evidences</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:author>Windmill Ministries</itunes:author>
		<itunes:summary>Does God exist? Is the Bible true? Is Jesus God? Windmill Ministries is a Christian apologetics ministry that equips believers and challenges skeptics through the sharing of evidences for the foundations of the Christian faith. Messages presenting the facts, finds and features for our faith</itunes:summary>
		<description>Does God exist? Is the Bible true? Is Jesus God? A Christian apologetics ministry that equips believers and challenges skeptics</description>
		<itunes:owner>
			<itunes:name>Rob VandeWeghe</itunes:name>
			<itunes:email>rob@windmillministries.org</itunes:email>
		</itunes:owner>
		<itunes:image href="http://www.windmillministries.org/images/PtA_podcast.jpg" />
		<itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">
			<itunes:category text="Christianity"/>
		</itunes:category>
		<itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality" />
		<itunes:keywords>Apologetics, Christianity, Jesus, Resurrection, Creation, Crucifixion, Evolution, scripture, bible, Christ, biblical, prophecy</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>2008, Windmill Ministries</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 11:06:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<webMaster>rob@windmillministries.org</webMaster>
		<item>
			<title>Jesus Resurrection - Would YOU die for a Lie?</title>
			<itunes:author>Rob VandeWeghe</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle>Historical evidence for the truth of the resurrection</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>After Jesus resurrection the apostles abandoned their possessions and professions and committed the remainder of their lives to preach the gospel of Jesus. Almost all paid the ultimate price: a gruesome death. Was their faith based on fact or did they die for a lie? This Podcast is an excerpt from Robs book Prepared to Answer that was recently published</itunes:summary>
			<description>After Jesus resurrection the apostles committed their lives to preach the gospel of Jesus. They paid the ultimate price: a gruesome death. Was their faith based on fact or did they die for a lie?</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 09:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.windmillministries.org/slides/die_for_a_lie.mp3" length="5237863" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:duration>5:27</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>Resurrection, Jesus, apostle, martyr, Christ, gospel, martyrdom, testimony, evidence, apologetics</itunes:keywords>
			</item>

		<item>
			<title>The conversion of Saul to Paul</title>
			<itunes:author>Rob VandeWeghe</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle>Historical evidence for the truth of the resurrection of Jesus Christ</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The great apostle Paul was initially a zealous persecutor of Christians. What made him change his mind? Only Jesus resurrection can explain his dramatically changed life, his commitment to Christ and ultimately his martyrdom. This Podcast is an excerpt from Robs book Prepared to Answer that was recently published</itunes:summary>
			<description>The great apostle Paul was initially a zealous persecutor of Christians. What made him change his mind? Only Jesus resurrection can explain his dramatically changed life and ultimately his martyrdom.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 09:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.windmillministries.org/slides/conversion_of_paul.mp3" length="3939264" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:duration>4:06</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>Resurrection, Jesus, apostle, martyr, Christ, gospel, martyrdom, testimony, evidence, apologetics, Paul, Saul, conversion, bible, scripture</itunes:keywords>
			</item>

		<item>
			<title>The conversion of James, Jesus brother</title>
			<itunes:author>Rob VandeWeghe</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle>Historical evidence for the truth of the resurrection of Jesus Christ</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The gospels mention that Jesus had other brothers and sisters, including a man named James. While Jesus was alive, His brother James did not believe in Jesus, however he later becomes the leader of the early Christian church and is stoned to death for his faith. What made him change his mind? This Podcast is an excerpt from Robs book Prepared to Answer that was recently published</itunes:summary>
			<description>While Jesus was alive, His brother James did not believe in Jesus, however he later becomes the leader of the early Christian church and is stoned for his faith. What made him change his mind?</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 09:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.windmillministries.org/slides/conversion_of_james.mp3" length="4651048" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:duration>4:50</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>Resurrection, Jesus, apostle, martyr, Christ, gospel, martyrdom, testimony, evidence, apologetics, James, conversion, Josephus</itunes:keywords>
			</item>

		<item>
			<title>The Bible: Original Text versus Translations</title>
			<itunes:author>Rob VandeWeghe</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle>Why are the so many different English Bibles translations?</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Why are the so many different English Bibles translations? Does that imply that there is no reliable original Bible text preserved?  Or is it because translation is not an exact science and requires the translator to make subjective choices and allows for human error? This Podcast is an excerpt from Robs book Prepared to Answer that was recently published</itunes:summary>
			<description>Why are the so many different English Bibles translations? Does that imply that there is no reliable original Bible text preserved?  Or is it because translation is not an exact science and requires the translator to make subjective choices and allows for human error?</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 09:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.windmillministries.org/slides/bible_translations.mp3" length="7064763" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:duration>7:21</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>scripture, translations, bible, NIV, KJV, apologetics, creed, evidence</itunes:keywords>
			</item>

		<item>
			<title>The Dead Sea Scrolls</title>
			<itunes:author>Rob VandeWeghe</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle>What the Dead Sea Scrolls teach about the reliability of the Bible</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The original texts of the Old Testament were written on scrolls of papyrus and animal skins. However these would last only for a few centuries, so again and again the Bible had to copied by scribes. Was this copying accurate or were errors introduced. Hear about how the discovery of the Dead Sea Scrolls provides the unexpected and amazing evidence for the accuracy and reliability of the copying of the ancient manuscripts over the ages. This Podcast is an excerpt from Robs book Prepared to Answer that was recently published</itunes:summary>
			<description>The original texts of the Old Testament were written on scrolls of papyrus and animal skins. However these would last only for a few centuries, so again and again the Bible had to copied by scribes. Was this copying accurate or were errors introduced. Hear about how the discovery of the Dead Sea Scrolls provides the unexpected and amazing evidence for the accuracy and reliability of the copying of the ancient manuscripts over the ages.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.windmillministries.org/slides/dead_sea_scrolls.mp3" length="9769377" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:duration>10:10</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>dead sea scrolls, archaeology, old testament, scripture, translations, bible, apologetics, creed, evidence</itunes:keywords>
			</item>

		<item>
			<title>The Letters from the Early Christian Church</title>
			<itunes:author>Rob VandeWeghe</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle>What the thousands of quotations from the Early Church tell us about the Bible</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Like the apostles before them, the leaders of the early Christian church wrote letters to each other for encouragement and teaching. In these letters, written by the generation that sat at the feet of the apostles, we find thousands and thousands of quotations of books from the New Testament even before it was officially accepted. This Podcast is an excerpt from Robs book Prepared to Answer that was recently published</itunes:summary>
			<description>Like the apostles before them, the leaders of the early Christian church wrote letters to each other for encouragement and teaching. In these letters, written by the generation that sat at the feet of the apostles, we find thousands and thousands of quotations of books from the New Testament even before it was officially accepted.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.windmillministries.org/slides/early_church_leaders_letters.mp3" length="10722741" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:duration>11:10</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>clement, ignatius, polycarp, didache, scripture, translations, bible, NIV, KJV, apologetics, creed, evidence</itunes:keywords>
			</item>


		<item>
			<title>The resurrection creed - earliest resurrection testimony</title>
			<itunes:author>Rob VandeWeghe</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle>A very early, credible source for the ressurrection </itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Did Jesus resurrection really happen? Likely one of the first composed texts of the New Testament - the Resurrection Creed - provides remarkable eyewitness testimony to the appearances of Jesus after the crucifixion. This Podcast is a summary of material from Robs book Prepared to Answer that was recently published</itunes:summary>
			<description>Did Jesus resurrection really happen? Likely one of the first composed texts of the New Testament - the Resurrection Creed - provides remarkable eyewitness testimony to the appearances of Jesus after the crucifixion.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2008 09:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.windmillministries.org/slides/Resurrection%20Creed.mp3" length="37965235" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:duration>39:32</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>Resurrection, Jesus, creed, apostle, martyr, Christ, gospel, martyrdom, testimony, evidence, apologetics, Paul, Saul, conversion, bible</itunes:keywords>
			
		</item>

		<item>
			<title>Be prepared to answer WHY you are a Christian</title>
			<itunes:author>Rob VandeWeghe</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle>Testimony - cornered by the evidence, I had no choice to accept Christ</itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>A skeptics testimony of how the evidence for the truth of the Christian claims convicted a believer in evolution to commit himself to Christ. An inspiring overview of the case for Christianity. This Podcast contains an overview of material from Robs book Prepared to Answer that was recently published</itunes:summary>
			<description>A skeptics testimony of how the evidence for the truth of the Christian claims convicted a believer in evolution to commit himself to Christ. An inspiring overview of the case for Christianity</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 8 Mar 2008 09:06:32 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.windmillministries.org/slides/Fact%20or%20Fiction%20-%20RobVandeWeghe.mp3" length="25242906" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:duration>42:04</itunes:duration>
			<itunes:keywords>testimony, skeptic, evolution, creation, God, Bible, Scriptures, truth, Christ, Messiah, resurrection, prophecies</itunes:keywords>
		</item>


		</channel>
	</rss>