<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>California Western School of Law Podcast: Law in 10</title> 
  <link>http://www.cwsl.edu</link> 
  <language>en-us</language> 
  <copyright>2006 California Western School of Law</copyright> 
  <itunes:subtitle>A Weekly Legal News Analysis</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:summary>On Law in 10, California Western's weekly podcast, professors provide legal analysis on current news topics, all in 10 minutes.</itunes:summary> 
  <description>On Law in 10, California Western's weekly podcast, professors provide legal analysis on current news topics, all in 10 minutes.</description> 
- <itunes:owner>
  <itunes:name>California Western Podcast: Law in 10</itunes:name> 
  </itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/images/CWSLPodcastLogo.jpg" />
- <itunes:category text="Education">
  <itunes:category text="Higher Education" /> 
  </itunes:category>
  <itunes:category text="News and Politics" /> 
- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: JonBenet Ramsey</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on JonBenet Ramsey and San Diego Mt. Soledad Cross</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>Criminal law Professor Justin Brooks, also director of the California Innocence Project, discusses media coverage, false confessions, and DNA testing concerning the 10-year-old JonBenet Ramsey murder. Professor Marilyn Ireland, a long-time San Diego resident and First Amendment specialist, talks about the ongoing San Diego Mt. Soledad Cross controversy.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_JonBenet_Ramsey_and_Mt_Soledad_Cross.mp3" length="6590802" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:33</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, professor, law school, JonBenet Ramsey, San Diego Mount Soledad Cross, Mt. Soledad Cross, false confessions, first amendment, DNA testing</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>
- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Middle East Conflicts</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on middle east conflicts and an analysis of the changing legal workplace</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>Professor James Cooper offers his thoughts on whether the current ceasefire resolution between Israel and Hezbollah can be successful and Professor Jackie Slotkin gives her analysis on generational gaps contributing to changes in the legal workplace.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Middleeast_Conflicts_and_Changing_Legal_Workplace.mp3" length="6554729" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:37</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, professor, law school, law podcasts</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>
- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Chargers Linebacker Shooting</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perpectives on Chargers linebacker shooting and polygamist Warren Jeffs</itunes:subtitle> 
  <itunes:summary>Ruth Hargrove, a professor at California Western and former district attorney, weighs in on the police shooting incident involving San Diego Chargers linebacker Steve Foley. Hargrove has represented the city of Chula Vista in police shooting cases and helped write police department policies and procedures. Janet Bowermaster, an associate dean at California Western who specializes in family law, discusses the case against polygamist Warren Jeffs along with legal and cultural aspects of polygamy. Bowermaster has helped draft and negotiate legislation dealing with family law and domestic violence issues in California.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Chargers_Lineback_Shooting_and_Warren_Jeffs.mp3" length="7229982" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 7 Sep 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>10:42</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, professor, law school, polygamy, Foley, Chargers, police shootings, Warren Jeffs, law podcasts</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>
- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Detainees and Military Commissions</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on Bush's military commissions proposal and secret detention centers abroad</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Professor William Aceves, an expert on international and human rights law, discusses why the president's military commissions may not be legal and whether various interrogation techniques used on terror suspects could be considered torture. Aceves frequently works with Amnesty International and the Center for Justice and Accountability and is principal author of the 2002 Amnesty International USA report on torture and impunity. </itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Detainees_and_Military_Commissions.mp3" length="6494063" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:23</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, professor, law school, law podcasts, secret prisons, terrorist, interrogation, war crimes, detainee, Bush</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>
- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Hewlett Packard Investigation and Vioxx Litigation</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on the Hewlett Packard news leak investigation and the latest blow drug company Merck faces in Vioxx litigation</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Professor Andrea Johnson, also director of California Western's Telecommunication and Intellectual Property Law Center, discusses the Hewlett-Packard news leak investigation. Johnson served on President Clinton's transition team for Science, space, and technology. Professor Bryan Liang, also director of the California Western's Institute of Health Law Studies gives his input on the latest blow drug company Merck faces in the Vioxx litigation. Liang is co-director and adjunct professor of anesthesiology at UCSD School of Medicine.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_HewlettPackard_and_Merck.mp3" length="6494063" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:23</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, professor, law school, law podcasts, Hewlett Packard, Merck, Vioxx</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>
- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Abortion and Roberts' Court</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on what the U.S. Supreme Court faces during the 2006-07 term</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Constitutional Law Professor Glenn Smith, who teaches a nationally recognized Supreme Court Seminar at California Western, gives a preview of the U.S. Supreme Court and what to expect in the upcoming 2006-07 term. Smith is an expert on court controversies, and has written on topics involving free speech, church versus state, and privacy concerns. He is also a visiting political science professor at UCSD.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Abortion_and_Roberts_Court.mp3" length="6404219" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:21</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, professor, law school, law podcasts, U.S. Supreme Court, Abortion, John Roberts, Preview</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>
- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Foley's Illicit IMs and Chargers Player's Drug Charges</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on Congressmen Mark Foley's illicit IMs and Chargers player Terrence Kiel's drug charges</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Adjunct Professor Gary Gibson addresses the charges Congressman Mark Foley could face for exchanging sexually-explicit instant messages with a teenage page. Plus, Gibson gives background on the felony drug charges against San Diego Chargers Safety Terrence Kiel. Gibson teaches Advanced Criminal Procedure and California Trial Evidence at California Western. He is a San Diego deputy public defender and is currently exclusively trying death penalty cases. He has also tried multiple three strikes cases and cases involving sexually violent predators.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Foleys_illicit_IMs_and_Chargersplayers_drug_charges.mp3" length="4997218" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 5 Oct 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>7:18</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, professor, law school, law podcasts, Mark Foley, Terrence Kiel, Dateline</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>
- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Immigration Reform</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on the ongoing Immigration Debate and City Ordinances</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Adjunct Professor Lilia Velasquez and Professor Ruben Garcia give an update on the battle over immigration reform, and current city ordinances that verge on discrimination. Velasquez, a San Diego immigration attorney who teaches immigration law at California Western, has been dealing with the complex immigration issues for more than 20 years. Garcia teaches Employment and Labor Law and has published articles about guest workers and immigrants in the labor force.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Immigration_Reform.mp3" length="8212620" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>12:07</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, Immigration, Immigration Reform, city ordinances, Immigrants, illegal aliens  </itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: North Korea</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on issues surrounding North Korea testing a nuclear weapon.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Professor James Cooper returns to Law in 10 to weigh in on issues surrounding North Korea testing a nuclear weapon. Cooper is Director of Proyecto ACCESO, California Western's rule of law training program. He is an expert on international law and international terrorism. </itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_North_Korea.mp3" length="6327779" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:24</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, North Korea, Iraq, nuclear weapon testing, international law, terrorism</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: California Innocence Project</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on the California Innocence Project, a clinical program at California Western School of Law.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>California Innocence Project Assistant Director and Case Manager Jeff Chinn talks about student involvement in the project and 2L Solomon Chang talks about his experiences with the California Innocence Project. Chinn is responsible for reviewing each inmate's claim of innocence and deciding whether the project should investigate the case further. He also guides law students as they reinvestigate cases for evidence of actual innocence. Chang is a second-year student who is part of the Innocence Project Clinic at California Western. Solomon received his bachelor's in business administration from the University of Texas at Austin. He moved to San Diego to attend California Western in 2005. He is also one of the law school's student bloggers. The California Innocence Project, a member of the national network of Innocence Projects, is a non-profit clinical program that operates out of the Institute of Criminal Defense Advocacy at California Western. Founded in 1999, the project annually reviews more than 1,000 claims of innocence from California inmates and has earned the release of four wrongfully convicted clients.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_California_Innocence_Project.mp3" length="6558642" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:41</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, California Innocence Project, Innocence Project, clinical program</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Timothy Atkins</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on new evidence in a 20-year-old murder conviction</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Professor Jan Stiglitz explains why his client, Timothy Atkins, may have served 20 years in prison for a crime he didn't commit. Stiglitz is co-director of the California Innocence Project and a professor of law at California Western.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Timothy_Atkins.mp3" length="5271375" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 2 Nov 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>7:44</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, California Innocence Project, Innocence Project, Timothy Atkins, Atkins, Los Angeles, murder</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Child Sex Scandals</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on the legal and social aspects of several child sex incidents.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Professor Robert DeKoven breaks down the legal and social aspects of several child sex incidents, from the Mark Foley scandal to illicit relationships between teachers and their young students. DeKoven is a professor at California Western and an expert in education law. He publishes more than 50 commentaries a year on issues concerning education, privacy, civil rights, and safety in schools.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Child_Sex_Scandals.mp3" length="7345127" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 9 Nov 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>10:45</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, child sex scandal, Foley, foley page scandal</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Same-Sex Marriage</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on the country's political and legal battles over same-sex marriage.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Professor Barbara Cox joins Law in 10 to talk about the country's political and legal battles over same-sex marriage and where the movement will go after the tough election day losses in early November. Cox is a professor at California Western and a national authority on sexual orientation and the law. Her research and scholarship focuses on same-sex marriage laws and obtaining recognition for alternative families. She also chairs the Steering Committee for the National Freedom to Marry Organization. At California Western, Cox teaches Civil Procedure, Women and the Law, and Comparative Issues in Gender, Family, and Sexuality.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Same_Sex_Marriages.mp3" length="6618150" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:47</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, gay marriage, same-sex marriage, freedom to marry, gay movement, sexual orientation, same sex couples</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Thanksgiving Edition</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on the history of Thanksgiving.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Michal Belknap is a constitutional law professor and legal historian at California Western and an Adjunct Professor of History at the University of California, San Diego. He has written extensively about the U.S. Supreme Court and the history of civil rights and civil liberties in 20th century America. His books include "American Political Trials", "The Vincent Court", and "The Supreme Court under Earl Warren".</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Thanksgiving.mp3" length="7346449" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>11:14</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, Thanksgiving, Thanksgiving history, pilgrims, indians</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>


- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Saddam Hussein</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on Saddam Hussein's death sentence and the legitimacy of his trial.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Professor William Aceves, an expert on international and human rights law, discusses Saddam Hussein's death sentence and raises questions about the legitimacy of his trial. Aceves frequently works with Amnesty International and the Center for Justice and Accountability and is principal author of the 2002 Amnesty International USA report on torture and impunity. </itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Saddam_Hussein.mp3" length="6110777" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:20</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, Saddam Hussein, death sentence, Hussein, Saddam, tribunal, international law</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Divorce Law</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on divorce and child custody.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Janet Bowermaster, an associate dean at California Western who specializes in family law, discusses divorce and child custody laws - from what's covered in a prenuptial agreement to 
how child custody is decided. Bowermaster has helped draft and negotiate legislation dealing with family law and domestic violence issues in California. </itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Divorce_Law.mp3" length="5630375" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 7 Dec 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>8:38</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, divorce, britney spears, nick and jessica, k-fed, pamela anderson and kid rock,  child custody</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: 2006 Highlights</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Listen to highlights from 2006.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Listen to California Western professors provide analysis on the hottest legal news topics in 2006.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_2006Highlights.mp3" length="4878864" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2006 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>7:26</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Ashley X Controversy</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on the controversial treatment of Ashley X</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Professor Bryan Liang - also director of California Western's Institute of Health Law Studies - discusses a family's controversial decision to stunt the growth of their severely disabled daughter.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_AshleyX.mp3" length="7993441" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>12:14</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, Ashley X, Pillow Angel, Seattle Children's Hospital, stunt growth, medical ethics, disability</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>


- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: New Way Forward</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on President Bush's recent announcement of a surge in Iraq and whether the "New Way Forward" can help the situation in the Middle East.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>Professor James Cooper is also director of Proyecto ACCESO, the law school's rule of law education program. Cooper is an expert in international terrorism and teaches The Law of Armed Conflict and Peacekeeping.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_New_Way_Forward.mp3" length="6581434" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:49</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, New Way Forward, Iraq, Middle East, Surge, Iraq War, President Bush</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>


- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: California Innocence Project Update</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on several of the project's upcoming cases.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>California Innocence Project Attorney Alex Simpson joins Law in 10 to discuss several of the project's upcoming cases. Simpson oversees all the cases currently in the court system and represents the project at court hearings and motions. He received his B.A. from University of California, Santa Barbara and J.D. and LL.M. in Trial Advocacy from California Western School of Law. While at California Western, he received the Joe and Denise Walsh Award for Excellence in Advocacy as the top student in the California Innocence Project. The California Innocence Project, a member of the national network of Innocence Projects, is a non-profit clinical program that operates out of the Institute of Criminal Defense Advocacy at California Western. Founded in 1999, the project annually reviews more than 1,000 claims of innocence from California inmates and has earned the release of four wrongfully convicted clients.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_CIP_Update.mp3" length="6217987" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 2 Feb 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:22</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, California Innocence Project, Innocence Project, clinical program, Larson, Atkins, post conviction</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>


- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Global Warming</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on Global Warming and what kind of government regulations could help the problem.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>California Western Professor Richard Finkmoore teaches Property Law, Environmental Law, International Environmental Law, and The Environmental Law of NAFTA.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Global_Warming.mp3" length="7336723" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>11:12</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, Global Warming, government regulations, environmental law, environment, Inconvenient Truth</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>


- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Catholic Church Bankruptcy</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on the Catholic Church in San Diego filing for chapter 11 bankruptcy.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>California Western Professor Scott Ehrlich teaches Bankruptcy Law, Secured Transactions, and Business Planning.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Catholic_Church_Bankruptcy.mp3" length="6972143" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>10:35</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, San Diego, Catholic Church, Bankruptcy, Chapter 11, San Diego Catholic Church Bankruptcy</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: U.S. Attorney Firings</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on the controversy over the Justice Department recently firing 8 U.S. Attorneys.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>California Western Distinguished Jurist James Stiven teaches Alternative Dispute Resolution and Pretrial Practice at California Western. He was U.S. Magistrate Judge for the Southern District of California for 11 years.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_U.S._Attorney_Firings.mp3" length="6972143" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>12:02</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, U.S. Attorneys, U.S. Attorney Firings, federal prosecutors firings, U.S. Justice Department, Carol Lam</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Street Law</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on California Western's Street Law Program.</itunes:subtitle> 
<itunes:summary>San Diego Street Law Director Alex Simpson talks about California Western's Street Law Program, including expansions and plans for the future.</itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Street_Law.mp3" length="5716839" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>8:39</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, San Diego, Street Law, San Diego Street Law, Street Law San Diego</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Duke Lacrosse</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on charges being dropped against the former Duke lacrosse players who were accused of rape last year.</itunes:subtitle> 
Ruth Hargrove, a professor at California Western and former district attorney, weighs in on charges being dropped on the former Duke lacrosse players who were accused of rape last year.<itunes:summary></itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Duke_Lacrosse.mp3" length="5408003" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>8:20</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, Duke, Lacrosse, Duke Lacrosse, Rape, charges dropped, race</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Campus Security</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on campus security as related to the recent Virginia Tech shootings.</itunes:subtitle> 
The shootings at Virginia Tech last week have brought back discussions of campus safety as college and university officials around th ecountry consider how to prevent such an attack. On this week's podcast, Professor Robert DeKoven - an education law expert and legal writing professor at California Western - discusses campus security. DeKoven publishes more than 50 commentaries a year on issues concerning education law, privacy, and civil rights.<itunes:summary></itunes:summary> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Campus_Security.mp3" length="5408003" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>12:09</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, Virginia Tech, shootings, school shootings, campus security, school safety, education law</itunes:keywords>

  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Summer Break</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Summer Break</itunes:subtitle> 
 <itunes:summary>We're taking a short summer break and will be back in August. Tune in this fall for more expert analysis of the latest legal news.</itunes:summary>
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Summer_Break.mp3" length="388123" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>0:34</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Loving Decision</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on Loving v. Virginia</itunes:subtitle> 
 <itunes:summary>Professor Barbara Cox, a national authority on sexual orientation and the law and women and the law, joins Law in 10 on the 40th anniversary of the U.S. Supreme Court decision to strike down Virginia's law (Loving v. Virginia), prohibiting interracial couples from marrying. She talks about the significance of this decision and what we can all learn from it today.</itunes:summary>
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Loving_Decision.mp3" length="6264927" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 12 June 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>9:31</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, Loving, Virginia, interracial marriage, same-sex marriage, Loving v. Virginia, Supreme Court</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

- <item>
  <title>Law in 10: Labor Day</title> 
  <itunes:author>California Western School of Law</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:subtitle>Perspectives on the state of labor on Labor Day 2007.</itunes:subtitle> 
 <itunes:summary>Professor Ruben Garcia teaches Employment Discrimination, Employment Law, Labor Law, and Professional Responsibility at California Western. His research focuses on labor and employment law, with particular attention to the effects of race, gender, immigration, and globalization on the world of work.</itunes:summary>
  <enclosure url="http://www.cwsl.edu/content/podcasts/Law_in_10_Labor_Day.mp3" length="8186251" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 29 July 2007 13:00:00 PDT</pubDate> 
  <itunes:duration>11:56</itunes:duration> 
  <itunes:keywords>law, legal, legal news, legal podcast, law school, law podcasts, Labor Day, Labor Law, Employment Law, Employment Discrimination, State of Labor</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>


  </channel>
  </rss>