<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Horse Girl TV: Horses For Wired Equine Enthusiasts</title>
<link>http://www.horsegirltv.com/</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>&#xA9; 2007-2012 HorseGirlTV LLC</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle>By an equestrian for the next generation of equestrians</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Horse Girl TV is by an equestrian for equestrians and horse enthusiasts of all ages and skill levels. HorseGirlTV plugs the classic equine world into the wired generation. The show is hosted by Angelea Kelly Walkup.</itunes:summary>
<description>Horse Girl TV is by an equestrian for equestrians and horse enthusiasts of all ages and skill levels. HorseGirlTV plugs the classic equine world into the wired generation. The show is hosted by Angelea Kelly Walkup.</description>
<itunes:owner>
	<itunes:name>horse girl tv</itunes:name>
	<itunes:email>mail@horsegirltv.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://www.horsegirltv.com/itunes/logo2.jpg" />
<itunes:category text="Sports &amp; Recreation">
	<itunes:category text="Outdoor" />
</itunes:category>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

<item>
<title>Developing Your Equestrian Career with Anky</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>What was it like to groom for Anky van Grunsven at Aachen? How to develop your career.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Educational and entertaining content is timeless which is why we're launching HorseGirlTV Classics! After producing five years of amazing equine-based content in new media we realized that some of our fan base may have never seen our early years. We take a look back to classic HorseGirlTV webisodes. What was it like grooming for Anky van Grunsven? Let's chat with Tiffany Tyler and find out. In this pilot episode of HorseGirlTV we meet former groom of Anky van Grunsen, Tiffany Tyler and learn some of Anky's grooming secrets! We catch up with Tiffany in Ashland, Oregon where she continues to develop her career in competitive equestrian sports. Tiffany plans to show this season and aspires to compete on an international level in the CDIs.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep01.m4v" length="72628837" type="audio/x-m4a" /> 
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep01.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2007 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, dressage, anky, anky van grunsven, olympic, olympian</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Importing Horses and CEM Quarantine Facilities</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>What you need to know about importing, CEM and secondary quarantine</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Educational and entertaining content is timeless which is why we've launched HorseGirlTV Classics! After producing five years of amazing equine-based content in new media we realized that some of our fan base may have never seen our early years. We take a look back to classic HorseGirlTV webisodes. What is involved with importing horses and secondary quarantine? Let's ask CEM facility owner, Penny Barerras and find out.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep02.m4v" length="53663421" type="audio/x-m4a" /> 
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep02.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2011 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>5:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, horse tv, horse channel, equine, importing, cem, quarantine</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>It's Reining. It's Pouring.</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>What is competitive reining all about?</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Educational and entertaining content is timeless which is why we've launched HorseGirlTV Classics! After producing five years of amazing equine-based content in new media we realized that some of our fan base may have never seen our early years. We take a look back to classic HorseGirlTV webisodes. Follow Angelea, as she meets with reining trainer and competitor, John Irish to learn about this competitive FEI sport that is growing in popularity. "Whoa" is given a WHOLE new meaning with this sports sliding stops!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep03.m4v" length="69306362" type="audio/x-m4a" /> 
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep03.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2011 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>equestrian, horse, horse tv, horse channel, horses, equine, reining, western, sliding stop, spins</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Athleticism of the Equestrian and the Equine Athlete</title>
<itunes:author>HorseGirl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Angelea learns about the athleticism of the equestrian and the equine athlete.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We're back at Silver Spring Farm meeting with Lara Schliening, two time Cosequin Juniors Team and two time Young Rider Team competitor and FEI rider, to talk about the athleticism of the equestrian and the equine athlete. Lara trains with Anky van Grunsven and shows at the FEI level understanding the importance of treating yourself AND your horse as the athletes that they AND we are. Lara opens up to HorseGirlTV about her rigorous and dedicated training program for both herself and her horses!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep04.m4v" length="72691075" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep04.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2007 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:31</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, athlete, physial, training</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Modern Day Cowboy</title>
<itunes:author>HorseGirl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Riding fence, roping and moving cattle are all in a days work for Richard Damon.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Where has the real cowboy gone? Oh where or where can he be? In this episode Angelea takes a look at what ridin' fence, roping calves, and moving cattle are all about. This and more is part of the average workday for Richard Damon, real modern day cowboy. Join HorseGirl as she meets with Rich to learn about the lifestyle of this fading American icon!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep05.m4v" length="89776825" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep05.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>8:44</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, cowboy, western, roping, cattle, cows, herding, dogs</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Innovative Riding Breeches</title>
<itunes:author>HorseGirl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>This episode Angelea takes a look at an innovative technology in breeches and learns about their design first hand from developer and entrepreneur Sheryl Rudolph.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We all have had trouble getting our breeches on, issues with chafing and more importantly actually finding a pair that just fit! Did we say FITS? This episode Angelea takes a look at an innovative technology in breeches and learns about their design first hand from developer and entrepreneur Sheryl Rudolph.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep06.m4v" length="72691075" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep06.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2007 20:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:41</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, breech, clothes, tack, training, horses</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Patrolling with the Mounted Police</title>
<itunes:author>HorseGirl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>What is a day in the life of a mounted police officer like? Check out this episode of HorseGirlTV to find out!
</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Have you ever wanted a career in horses but didn't want to be a trainer, groom or exercise rider and are you too tall to be a jockey? What about a career working with the mounted police? It's a real 'ride along,' COPS style! Follow Angelea as she literally rides along on patrols with the Prince William County Mounted Police and discover this beneficial and rewarding career option.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep07.m4v" length="72691075" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep07.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2007 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>8:02</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, police, mounted police, cops, law, enforcement, patrol
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Vote and Win Contest</title>
<itunes:author>HorseGirlTV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Want your opinion to be heard? Want to help shape the programming of HorseGirlTV?</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We want to hear from you. Vote for your favorite episode, tell us why you like it and automatically be entered to win prizes. Simply click on the button below the video podcast to vote for your favorite episode. Winner will be announced in our next episode.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/contest.m4v" length="12968623" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/contest.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2007 23:30:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, contest, win, breeches, riding pants, giveaway, vote</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Applying Standing Wraps</title>
<itunes:author>HorseGirlTV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>How to properly apply standing bandages and polo wraps</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow HorseGirl to Bluegrass Farm in Northern Virginia. In this episode Angelea takes a look at applying standing wraps and polos. Learn the ins and outs of proper application. We're announcing our contest winners in this episode!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep08.m4v" length="72691075" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep08.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2007 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:35</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, health, wraps, bandage, care</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Hillary Dobbs: The teen at Grand Prix to watch</title>
<itunes:author>HorseGirlTV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Competing with the best of the best at The Hampton Classic Grand Prix</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>HorseGirlTV goes high style at The Hampton Classic. Catch up with Angelea in Bridgehampton, NY where she talks candidly with this years teen to watch, Hillary Dobbs. Catch a slice of life from this talented teen and discover what it is like to juggle Harvard, interning at CNN, and a string of successful mounts competing not only in the Adult Amateurs but holding her own against the best of the best in the Grand Prix ring.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep09.m4v" length="72691075" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep09.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2007 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, jumping, grand prix, hillary dobbs, lou dobbs, equestrian
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Hors d'oeuvres and Horses at The Hampton Classic</title>
<itunes:author>HorseGirlTV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Fabulous food. Top riders. Perfect weather. All at this year's Hampton Classic.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Meet Chris Robbins of Robbins Wolfe Eventeurs for an exclusive luncheon at The Hampton Classic and learn about upscale event catering. Chris sat down with HorseGirl to speak about happenings, horses and The Hamptons!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep10.m4v" length="77214775" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep10.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:27</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, catering, food, events, jumping, hunter
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Breyer Model Horses</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Breyer is the World's Premier Model Horse!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>It's a far cry from the # 57 Western Horse of the late 50s but Breyer Model Horses is still going strong and accurately capturing our equine friends. Catch up with the Breyer Horse Tour as it makes it's stop on the east coast. Angelea enjoyed a lively conversation with Breyer spokeswomen, Kathleen Fallon, and cozied up with a real live Breyer Model Horse! Watch as HorseGirlTV gets up close and personal with Breyer specialists and discovers the rich history of this home grown American company. Learn why Breyer is the model horse of choice for so many generations.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep11.m4v" length="86219441" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep11.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 15:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>8:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, breyer, model, hobbyist, breyer model horse, breyerfest
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bonus Material: Breyer Model Horse Hobbyist</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Breyer Model Horse Hobbyist collect, sell, show and trade.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Model horse hobbyists collect, sell, show, trade and customize their Breyer models. For those of you interested in horses but not able to, due to scheduling, location or finances, ride becoming a horse hobbyist would be a great outlet to share your love of horses with others. We simply had too much good information from Kathleen Fallon to cut this out and opted to put it in as a bonus. A big, HUGE thank you to appaloosa for allowing HorseGirlTV to use her amazing photos from this past years Breyerfest!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep11_bonus.m4v" length="21914623" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep11_bonus.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:06</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, breyer, model, hobbyist, breyer horse, breyerfest
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Steeplechase Horses At The International Gold Cup</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>International Gold Cup Steeplechase with Nick Arundel</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>A menagerie of finely tuned equine athletes coupled with a plehtora of world class jockey talents comprise just some of the days events at the International Gold Cup in The Plains, Virginia. Follow HorseGirlTV as we get the exclusive behind the scenes look at the stables, the jockeys, the paddock and the events leading up to this world renound event. HorseGirlTV gets exclusive passes for this spectacular show of athleticism, precision and glory that IS the International Gold Cup!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep12.m4v" length="60311958" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep12.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>5:48</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, race, racing, steeplechase, timber racing, thoroughbred, jockey, jump jockey</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Timber Racer and Jump Jockey, Carl Rafter</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Jump Jockey, Carl Rafter at The International Gold Cup Steeplechase Event</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Part two of our series and we catch jump jockey, Carl Rafter during the after party celebration. A menagerie of finely tuned equine athletes coupled with a plethora of world class jockey talents comprise just some of the days events at the International Gold Cup in The Plains, Virginia. Follow HorseGirlTV as we get the exclusive behind the scenes look at the stables, the jockeys, the paddock and the events leading up to this world renowned event. HorseGirlTV gets exclusive backstage passes for this spectacular show of athleticism, precision and glory that IS the International Gold Cup!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep13.m4v" length="60817333" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep13.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, race, racing, steeplechase, timber racing, thoroughbred, jockey, jump jockey
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Holiday Wish List Giveaway with LC at Smartpak!</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirlTV and Smartpak give away over $400 of equine products</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Happy Holidays from HorseGirlTV and our friends at Smartpak! Angelea connected with LC, co-host from the upcoming audio podcast Up on Horses from the Smartpak Network, to highlight some of this seasons top wish list items. Tune in to find out the hot picks on this years holiday shopping list. Plus, in the spirit of the holidays, we are giving it all away! All winners will be drawn at random from Team HorseGirlTV! Just join Team HorseGirlTV and watch our December 15th episode to find out if you won any of these fabulous items! Check out OVER $400 in cool equestrian products below as not all items are featured in this episode!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep14.m4v" length="81297950" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep14.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 11:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>8:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, holiday, prize, equine products, smartpak, free, giveaway, give away
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>US Park Police and Holiday Wish List Giveaway Winners!</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>US Park Police and Holiday Wish List Giveaway Winners!
</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Angelea spoke with First Lieutenant Stacey Collins of the US Park Police from Washington DC. Discover the rich history of the US Park Police. Learn about their intensive 10 week course and the challenges and rewards of the US Park Police Musical Ride. What is life like for a mounted officer with a fulfilling career in public service. Getting paid to ride horses AND serve the community! PLUS in this episode we announce the Holiday Wish List Giveaway Winners! Thanks so much to SmartPak for giving HorseGirlTV over $400 in fabulous horse and rider prizes!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep15.m4v" length="81297950" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep15.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:02</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, police, mounted, prize, products, free, giveaway
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>horsegirltv 2.0</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>It is HorseGirlTV 2008! horsegirltv 2.0!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Happy New Year! We had a GREAT year in 2007 and are looking forward to a pretty amazing line up for 2008! Stay tuned as we go International with shoots in Sweden, Germany, Canada and tentatively Ireland, Spain and Holland! Of course we'll still have fabulous coverage of stateside events spanning the gamut of the equine world. Watch for some serious training interviews, more riding, more helpful how to and of course in the spirit of HorseGirlTV they will all be educational while entertaining. Tune in. Tack up. and thanks for being a part of HorseGirlTV!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep16.m4v" length="35348587" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep16.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 01:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:23</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, new, international, products, free, interviews
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Horse Publishing and Point to Points</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Learn about horse publishing and point to point with Chronicle of the Horse Publisher</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Angelea meets Robert Banner, Publisher of the top equine magazine stateside, The Chronicle of the Horse. Robert talks candidly about the equestrian publishing business as well as his passion for NAPPA (North American Point-to-Point Association) and helping developing young riders learn the basics. Our kids are our future of riding and NAPPA was created in order to take Steeplechasing back to its Foxhunting roots and rejuvenate amateur participation.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep17.m4v" length="90039896" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep17.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 05:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>9:06</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>equestrian, horse, horses, equine, horse tv, horse video, interviews
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Introduction to Fox Hunting</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>All the basics of fox hunting you could want to know</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>What is fox hunting? Where did it come from? How can someone get involved in fox hunting? Why shouldwe support the preservation of our country's countryside? Get a glimpse of this and more in this introductory episode to fox hunting or more true to the event, fox chasing. HorseGirl met up with Joint Masters of the Old Dominion Hounds during a fundraiser to stop the expansion of the power lines. Several local hunt clubs joined forces for a mega-hunt fundraiser and some family fun! Catch this episode to learn more about this family oriented, true outdoor sport where horse, hound and human alike bond for a common goal! Enjoyment of the amazing Virginia countryside!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep18.m4v" length="83212003" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep18.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>fox hunt, horse, horses, equine, horse tv, horse video, sport horse, interviews</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dressing for Fox Hunting and Fox Chasing</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Learn about the requirements for hunting habit</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>What attire is required for fox hunting? Can I use some of my show jumping, dressage or eventing attire for fox hunting? Does the dress vary from hunt? Why do fox hunters wear a stock tie? Why those brick colored breeches in Virginia? These questions and more will be answered in this episode of HorseGirlTV. Angelea visits the fox hunting store in Virginia and the other 48 for that matter! Wendy, Horse Country's Sales Manager and resident fox hunting habit expert, talks with Angelea about the ins and outs of fox hunt attire and helps her get set up for the next installment of our fox hunting series... Stayed tuned as Angelea will be going fox hunting!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep19.m4v" length="73134340" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep19.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:10</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>fox hunt, horse, horses, equine, horse tv, horse video, sport horse, interviews
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>In the Tack Basic Tack Requirements for Horseback Riding</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>What is the essential tack you need to go horseback riding</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Have you just bought your first horse and do not know the first thing about what else you need? Angelea gets down to the basics with Wendy at Horse Country in Warrenton, Virginia to discuss the different types of saddles, bridles, girths and other things you might need to get yourself and your first horse in the tack. This episode also discussed styles of saddles and touches on saddle fitting for those more seasoned equestrians!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep20.m4v" length="73134340" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep20.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2008 09:39:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>9:23</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>tack, tacking, horse, horses, equine, horse tv, horse video, sport horse, interviews
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Riding to Hounds in America</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Answers to some basic questions about the sport of fox hunting</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Angelea answers some recent questions HorseGirlTV has received about riding to hounds in America. Enjoy glimpses of the amazing Virginia countryside and follow along as we car follow a Joint meet with Old Dominion Hounds and Keswick.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep21.m4v" length="45756022" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep21.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2008 09:39:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:53</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>fox hunt, horse, horses, equine, horse tv, horse video, sport horse, interviews
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Inside Stubben North America</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Learn the basics from a world premiere saddlery</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Meet Jim Erhmann, President of Stubben North America, and learn about one of the worlds oldest and best saddle companies. Angelea travels to Stubben North America to discover what it takes to be a top saddle maker.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep22.m4v" length="77755257" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep22.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 09:39:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:52</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>saddles, stubben, horse, ride, horse tv, horse video, saddlery, interviews
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Horse Statues in Washington DC</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>The most horse statues in any city in the USA</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Washington DC is many things... the hub of our nations politics, a melting pot of individuals, a history rich area but it also is THE city with the most horse statues in our entire country. Come along for the tour of several of our favorites!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep23.m4v" length="77755257" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep23.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 09:39:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>statues, washington, dc, horse, ride, horse tv, horse video, boots, interviews
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>How To Custom Fit Your Boots</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Step by step instructions for taking professional custom boot measurements</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Not in an area where you can get professionally fitted? It's as easy as 1, 2, 3. Well there is a few more than three steps but custom fitting boot measurements are not that hard. Watch and learn from Dehner Boot Company President, Jeff Ketzler.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep24.m4v" length="64744023" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep24.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 09:39:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:06</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>boots, dress, riding, hunt, fitting, horse, horse riding, professional, interviews
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Training US Park Police Mounted Candidates</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Take a look inside the US Park Police training and meet a few of the candidates</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Ever wanted a career in law enforcement or wanted a job where you could incorporate your love of horses? Check into an exciting and rewarding career as a member of the prestigious US Park Police! HorseGirlTV supports our nations proud servicemen and women and was honored the US Park Police permitted us to witness their training this year!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep25.m4v" length="76796283" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep25.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 12:39:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>police, mounted, riding, cop, training, horse, horse riding, professional, interviews
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>PART TWO! Training US Park Police Mounted Candidates</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Take a look inside the US Park Police training and meet a few of the candidates</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Meet an experienced dressage rider US Park Police Mounted Horse Unit candidate as well as an officer from the Republic of Georgia with no prior formal riding training! Ever wanted a career in law enforcement or wanted a job where you could incorporate your love of horses? Check into an exciting and rewarding career as a member of the prestigious US Park Police! Check into an exciting and rewarding career as a member of the prestigious US Park Police! HorseGirlTV supports our nations proud servicemen and women and was honored the US Park Police permitted us to witness their training this year!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep26.m4v" length="75033028" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep26.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 09:39:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>police, mounted, riding, cop, training, horse, horse riding, professional, interviews
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>How To Tie A Stock Tie</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Actually watch, learn and try it out with us</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>You've requested it ON MULTIPLE OCCASIONS! You guys want more how to stuff and we've had several calls for stock tie help. You've asked for it and you've got it. Learn how simple it is to tie a beautiful stock tie and make your pre-tied stock obsolete!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep27.m4v" length="29344461" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep27.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, tie, stock tie, apparel, showing, jumping, dressage, dress, tack, how to
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Angelea Talks With Angelea</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>The toughest interview in HorseGirlTV history</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We have heard from our viewers on many occasions wanting to know more. This webisode, an international postcard tipped the scales and our HorseGirl faced one of her more challenging interviews to date!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep28.m4v" length="71817782" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep28.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, dressage, celebrity, interview, showing, horsegirl, girl, professional
</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>Eight Steps To Tame Your Fly Spray Practices</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Tune in on the how to for fewer flies</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>With some help from our friends at Absorbine, we were able to put together this education webisode on what to do and not to do when applying and using fly spray. Absorbine donated over 300 dollars worth of fly spray to Chester and family at the Scarlet and Gold Riding Club aboard Camp Lejeune for this great piece! Thanks Heather!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep29.m4v" length="32521478" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep29.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:13</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, insects, fly, pest, absorbine, fly spray, horsegirl, girl, professional
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Serious Competition at Super Ride VI</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet teen rider and drill team competitor, Maci Jayroe!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Super Ride VI presents the 2008 United States Equestrian Drill Championship (USEDC) at the Texas Rose Horse Park near Canton, Texas. Competitors from all over flock to Super Ride VI for a chance to win the Contest of Champions and HorseGirlTV was there to talk with teen competitor and life-long drill team rider, Maci Jayroe. Watch and learn about this amazing, cost effective and family focused sport!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep30.m4v" length="35110385" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep30.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:23</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, teen, drill team, family, rider, competition, horsegirl, girl, teen
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Basic Grooming Tips Everyone Should Know</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Tips for more effective grooming and management</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Tune in. Tack up. to learn more effective grooming and management tips. What do I need for basic grooming and horse care? What types of shampoo, conditioners, how to deter dust and debris and show touch up options. All this and more is in this episode of HorseGirlTV.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep31.m4v" length="35110385" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep31.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, grooming, cleaning, showing, care, competition, horsegirl, girl, teen
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Meet Horseman Chris Cox</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Two time Road to the Horse Champion</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Horseman, clinician, author, personality, educator! Chris Cox does it all and then some. HorseGirlTV had the honor of interviewing Chris Cox of Chris Cox Horsemanship. Chris is a two time Road to the Horse champion and all around wonderful horse person!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep32.m4v" length="80376566" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep32.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:52</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>chris cox, horseman, trainer, clinician, australian, texan, author, road to the horse
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Meet ThinLine Innovator Elaine Lockhead</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Top Saddle Pad Technology</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Angelea meets up with Elaine Lockhead, creator of the ThinLine Saddle Pad to learn about this unique, one of a kind, innovative technology!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep33.m4v" length="80376566" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep33.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>thinline, saddle, pad, saddle pad, innovative, equine, boots, girths, horse
</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Top Facility At Texas Rose Horse Park</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet Kimberly Brunson of Texas Rose Horse Park</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Texas is about all things grand and the Texas Rose Horse Park is no exception. We meet Kimberly Brunson at the Texas Rose Horse Park to learn about their facility, its events and their future plans for expansion.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep34.m4v" length="30882148" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep34.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>facility, equine, boarding, showing, events, texas</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>How To Winterize Your Horse</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Fall is upon us so be prepared</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>You're probably bringing out your winter layers, checking the fluids in your auto and turning on the heater so it's high time you think about winterizing your horse too! We got some great tips from Absorbine on how to winterize your horse and barn!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep35.m4v" length="31607462" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep35.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:42</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>groom, winter, clean, fall, horse care, absorbine</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>HOOF it Technologies</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Advancements In Horse Hoof Care</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>The folks at HOOF-it flew out to visit with Angelea and talk about innovations in horse hoof care technology. The HOOF-it people were great and Leslie was just too much fun to talk with. Angelea gets an education on repairing hooves, hoof care and high tech composite shoes. It's the way of the future!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep36.m4v" length="62999666" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep36.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>hoof, horseshoe, hoof care, trail riding, riding, hooves</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Carson Kressley, Celebrity and Horseman</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Style on and off the horse</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Infamous, magnanimous, salacious and any of the other "us-es" you can think of would describe Mr. Carson Kressley. Enjoy this charming interview with horseman, celebrity and stylist Carson Kressley. Carson began riding at an early age and his passion and drive has not only risen him to the top of the celebrity entertainment scene but likewise developed him into a skilled equestrian as well. We learn about what it takes to thrive in the horse world but also get a glimpse inside the amazing world of the Saddlebred breed!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep37.m4v" length="81928961" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep37.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2008 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:58</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>carson kressley, how to look good naked, queer eye, celebrity, hollywood</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Importance of Horse and Human Massage</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Learn the benefits of horse and human massage</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Fellow forward thinking horsewomen, Doris Rollins, LMT has known the importance of horse and rider massage therapy for years and the equestrian world is finally taken note! Doris operates her offices out of Haverhill, MA but travels to shows to work with her clientele during their events. Focusing on the balance and influence of horse to rider and rider to horse, Rollins techniques not only relax and repair but likewise envigorate for pre-performance! Watch and learn more about this interesting equine innovator and the importance of treating both humans and equines like the athletes that we are!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep38.m4v" length="52819481" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep38.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>4:52</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>massage, therapy, horse massage, equine, athlete</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Step Inside Washington International Horse Show</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Pound the pavement at WIHS with HorseGirlTV!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>An equestrian tradition since 1958, the Washington International Horse Show brings top horses and riders from the U.S. and abroad, including Olympic champions, to the nation's capital to compete for more than $415,000 in prize money and championship titles. About 500 horses participate in show jumping, hunters, equitation and dressage events during the six-day show. Special exhibitions, unique shopping in 65 boutiques and a Pony Pavilion with free pony rides round out this family-friendly show. Step inside Washington International Horse Show with Angelea and HorseGirlTV!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep39.m4v" length="30180523" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep39.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse show, wihs, washington, equine, athlete, jumper, hunter, show jumper, hunters</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>HorseGirlTV 3.0</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Happy New Year from HorseGirlTV</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>HorseGirlTV is going on year number three and only gaining momentum. We are still the leading equine-based series online today and have ramped up our line up for 2009. Watch for Olympian interviews, some serious webisodes on horse and human health, more material and options with our COMING SOON Extra Bits series plus there will be more from Angelea inside the sandbox as she steps back into the competition dressage court with her amazing Oldenburg mare! The USEF (yes, that's right... the United Stated Equestrian Federation) has honored HorseGirlTV with their Best Broadcast Media Award for 2008 and we have bigger and better plans for 2009! So keep in tuning in and tacking up with HorseGirlTV!!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep40.m4v" length="32642009" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep40.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>girl, horse girl, horsegirl, equestrian, equine, rider, horse show, olympian, angelea</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>How To Horse Shop</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>How To Horse Shop</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>FEI reiner, Mike McEntire, talks about buying horses. HorseGirlTV travels to Selma, North Carolina to meet with top FEI reining competitor and trainer, Mike McEntire. In this webisode we learn the ins and outs of how to shop for horses!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep41.m4v" length="85795382" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep41.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>8:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>buy, horse shop, shopping, buy a horse, how to horse shop, horse agent, horse broker, buying a horse</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Walking The Course With An Olympic Gold Medalist</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Walk A Grand Prix Course With Will Simpson</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Not many of us get the chance to walk a Grand Prix course. Fewer receive the ability to walk the Washington International Horse Show Grand Prix course and even far fewer receive the honor to walk it with Olympic Gold Medalist, mentor to many and all around nice guy, Will Simpson. Watch as Angelea walks with Will and pick up some notes on reading courses and the challenges course designers present. It's a good time!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep42.m4v" length="69065719" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep42.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:39</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>olympic show jumping, will simpson, show jumper, jumper, jumping course, fences, olympics</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>USEF? United States Equestrian Federation</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Chat With USEF Representative Sarah Lane</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>HorseGirlTV ventured to Ohio for the USEF Annual Convention to receive the honor of USEF Pegasus Award for Best Broadcast Media 2008. During the event, Angelea was fortunate enough to get a bit of the basics about what exactly USEF is, what they do and what cool new thing you can expect from them online in the future!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep43.m4v" length="31469137" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep43.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:55</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>usef, us equestrian federation, equestrian, federation, olympic, rider, saddlebred, reining, dressage, jumping, driving</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Meet Top Hunter Junior Champions</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Talk With The Oken Girls, Champions In Show &amp; Education!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Lucy and Lise Oken took a few minutes out of their time between working hard at their successful riding careers and studies to talk with HorseGirlTV. It's all about hard work and determination of course but these two young ladies seem to have that extra spark to make it in the big arena! Learn about their future directions and aspirations! </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep44.m4v" length="30736246" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep44.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>hunter, jumper, wihs, show jumping, hunter jumper, rider, champion, a circuit</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Horse Tail Care Basics</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Simply how to brush and care for your horses tail! </itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>HorseGirl Mail takes over this webisode as Jan from Pittsburg wants to know "How do you care for your horses tail? What's your daily routine?" Less is more with tail care basics. Watch and learn! </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep45.m4v" length="25127217" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep45.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:25</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>groom, tail, horse, clean, horse care, brush, horse tail</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Amish Built Modular Barn </title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Fabulous construction. Easy installation. Amazing barn option! </itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Jake from J and N Structures traveled down to HorseGirlTV studios in North Carolina to deliver and setup an amazing Amish built modular barn. Watch this episode to get a glimpse of how tremendously fast this great little barn was setup and ready for horses! If you're thinking of building a barn for yourself then this is the episode for you. At HorseGirlTV we did extensive research on our options for setting up a barn here at the farm and working with J and N Structures was by far one of the best decisions we made. </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep46.m4v" length="67801708" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep46.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:58</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>barn, amish, shedrow, building, farm, modular, modular barn, amish built</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Meet Miss Rodeo America 2009 </title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Not Just Fluff and Puff. Real Cowgirl! Real Inspiration! </itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>It is true, rodeo queens are not just fluff and puff, they are rough and tough and GREAT riders too. Maegan Ridley, Miss Rodeo America 2009, was so much fun to talk with and there is definitely more than just beauty and riding ability to this gal. HorseGirlTV met up with Absorbine and Miss Rodeo American in the country music capital Nashville, Tennessee. Ride along with Angelea Walkup and Miss Rodeo America 2009, Maegan Ridley for a look at what it takes to be crowned this PRCA ambassador, cowboy sport mentor and hold the title of Miss Rodeo America.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep47.m4v" length="34460453" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep47.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>queen, rodeo, america, miss rodeo, rodeo queen, cowgirl, pro rodeo</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>What Is HorseGirlTV </title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Happy Birthday HorseGirlTV </itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Two years ago today HorseGirlTV launched its pilot webisode Grooming For Anky van Grunsven and it has been a whirlwind of webisodes since. From meeting modern day cowboys still riding fence in Oregon, we relocated offices to the east coast and jet setted up to the Hamptons for champagne with eventeur, Chris Robbins. Check out the site to read more!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep48.m4v" length="22102189" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep48.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, tv, video, girl, riding, horsegirl, television</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Proper Muscle And Joint Care </title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Do not neglect proper muscle and joint care for your horse </itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Both you and your horse train hard but how often do you think about proper muscle and joint care for your horse. In this webisode, Angelea offers up some helpful hints to relieve tired or stressed muscles. Of course, it is always best to talk with your trainer or veterinarian before adding something new to your training plan.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep49.m4v" length="22102189" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep49.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, equine, athlete, muscle, health, joint, care, horse health</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Chance To Talk With Debbie McDonald </title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl meets with Debbie McDonald to talk dressage and giving back </itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Angelea had a unique moment to speak with living legend, Debbie McDonald after Brentina's retirement ceremony in Las Vegas. Ever generous with her time and energy, it was a great interview.  Not only is Debbie an amazing rider and mentor to the sport, she also gives back through her work with various charities such as her "Make A Wish" girl who's now in remission. Debbie is the upcoming celebrity speaker for this years Ride For Life.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep50.m4v" length="27050678" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep50.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:41</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>olympian, debbie mcdonald, brentina, dressage, olympics, cancer</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Horse People Giving Back </title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>PVDA Ride For Life Meet Barbara Strawson  </itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Started as a one day show, the PVDA Ride For Life has evolved to a major fundraiser to benefit breast cancer research. Many amazing people work hard to put this show and event together and one very special person was kind enough to come to HorseGirlTV's farm for an interview! Meet Barbara Strawson, international competitor, trainer and creator of the Dancing Horse Challenge!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep51.m4v" length="52873491" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep51.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>5:28</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>breast cancer, cancer, awareness, event, ride, for, life, pvda, barbara, strawson</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Fabulous And Functional Interlocking Mats </title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>The basics of installing interlocking mats </itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>If you have ever install stall mats before you know they are heavy, hard, unforgiving on your back and quite often more trouble than they are worth. We discovered the Interlocking Royal Mats at the Tractor Supply Company show in Nashville when we were out visiting with the Absorbine group. Their stall mat kit was the coolest and easiest installation of mats! Heavy duty yet easy to cut with a few passes! With the interlocking there are no edges to rub and shift when the horse moves around. We installed these mats five months ago and still there is no lifting or shifting what-so-ever. AWESOME!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep52.m4v" length="34460453" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep52.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:23</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>stall, barn, mats, rubber, interlocking, horse stall, stall mats</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Fun With Kristin And Kat Of Draper Equine Therapy </title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Tons of therapy products on the market yet here is a solid product and approach </itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Kristin Draper and Kat Wojtylak of Draper Equine Therapy flew down to the HorseGirlTV studios from Boston to talk therapy products with me (Angelea). Draper has a line of products for athletes (equine and human alike) of all ages and abilities. Made with Celliant/Holofiber, these products have been clinically proven to increase and improve circulation in the body and to deliver dramatic therapeutic benefits including relief from soreness, stiffness and swelling; increased energy; and accelerated muscle recovery after exertion. The Draper saddle pad is actually the best natural fit dressage pad I've ever put on! Watch the webisode for a bit of fun education and to see the fashion as well!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep53.m4v" length="37550151" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep53.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:39</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>equine, therapy, wraps, blanket, horse, theraputic</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Brenderup Horse Box From Brenderup Real Trailers</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Best economical and easy to use hauling horse box!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>I have been watching this company since 1999 and now 10 years later I am lucky enough to have one of my own! Brenderup Real Trailers really does have the kewlest horse box money can buy. I tow it easily with my Jeep Liberty. My mare loads like a champ. Everything about this horse box is awesome. There are tons of neat features beyond my favorites and I am sure they would be happy to send you a free DVD covering all the options so check the link below.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep54.m4v" length="48147965" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep54.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>4:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>trailer, real trailer, horse, box, van, transport</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Olympian McLain Ward</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>American show jumping competitor and olympian</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>For McLain Ward, show jumping is a family affair bringing them on the road with him. We meet up with McLain at the Washington International Horse Show in DC Verizon Center to get down and person about life as a champion, his mentor with some inspiring words for those of you out there looking to make it to the top of show jumping!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep55.m4v" length="24285683" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep55.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>olympian, jumper, jumping, show jumping, horse, olympics</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Musical Freestyle The Artist Behind The Art</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>The basics of creating and composing musical freestyle for dressage</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Frank and Cece of EquiChord join Angelea at the HorseGirlTV farm to talk musical freestyle development. Watch this webisode to learn about riding to music. It's inspiring. It's fun. Anyone can do it and enjoy riding and competing to music! A big thanks to Frank and Cece for coming down and sharing their talents with our viewers! You guys rock! Quite literally actually!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep56.m4v" length="80853120" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep56.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>musical, freestyle, kur, music, ride, dressage, anky, choreography, freestyles</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Riding To Music With EquiChord</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Part two of talking with Frank and Cece of EquiChord about musical freestyles</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This is part two in our series on musical freestyles. In this webisode we get a glimpse of the initial steps that go into creating a freestyle. We touch on beat matching, musical preferences for both the horse and human and a bit about staying on level. A big thanks to Frank and Cece for coming down and sharing their talents with our viewers! Thanks so much Frank and CeCe!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep57.m4v" length="85286056" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep57.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:35</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>musical, freestyle, kur, music, ride, dressage, anky, choreography, freestyles</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Canterwood Crest Series Author, Jessica Burkhart</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet inspiring, ambitious, talented Jessica Burkhart</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>At only 22, Jessica Burkhart is leading the way for tween horse lovers with her skillfully crafted series Canterwood Crest. Jessica flew down from NYC to talk with Angelea about a passion for horses, overcoming challenges that life hands you and the development of her writing career. We were honored to host Jessica and hope all our viewers, tween and otherwise, find her story as inspiring as we did!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep58.m4v" length="91317345" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep58.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thr, 01 Oct 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:25</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>canterwood, crest, author, tween, jessica, burkhart, best, selling, books, horse writer, equestrian series</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>What Are The Stables Like At Stal Anky van Grunsven?</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl Mail, Talk To The Pros</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Tami from Pennsylvania wants to know what the new stables are like at Anky van Grunsven. Well Tami, lets ask Sjef Janssen about the new construction!? </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/msjef_stable.m4v" length="14121781" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/msjef_stable.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>anky, train, anky van grunsven, riding, lessons, international, olympic</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Human And Horse Chiropractic</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Two professionals here to enhance human and horse sport performance</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Angelea talks with two professionals truly treating horses and humans as the athletes in which they are! Learn a bit about horse AND human chiropractic, why the equestrian and equine athlete could benefit from chiropractic work and how Dave and Wendy are moving forward as educators in the horse world! </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep59.m4v" length="51870801" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep59.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>4:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>chiropractic, horse, health, massage, natural, care, professional, sport, horse</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>How Long Does It Take To Create A Musical Freestyle?</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl Mail, Talk To The Pros</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Abbi from Camp Lejeune, North Carolina wants to know How long does it take to create a musical freestyle? Lets let a professional from EquiChord, Cece, answer this one! Thanks for your question and thanks for watching HorseGirlTV! </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/mfreestyle.m4v" length="11493486" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/mfreestyle.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>freestyle, musical, kur, musical freestyle, dressage, ride, to, music</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Talking With USEF President And Olympic Eventer David O'Connor</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet Olympian, USEF President and Top Eventer David O'Connor</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Angelea caught a few minutes to chat with Olympian, Trainer, Coach, USEF President and all around great guy, Mr. David O'Connor to talk about the World Equestrian Games for 2010, his involvement in the United States Equestrian Federation, the future of eventing and his current competition mounts. </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep60.m4v" length="69614109" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep60.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>usef, equestrian, federation, david, eventer, olympian, president</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>What's It Like Training With Anky van Grunsven?</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl Mail, Talk To The Pros</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Tammy from Washington DC wants to know... Hey HorseGirl, what is it like training with Anky? Let's let Danish rider, Bo Hostrup, answer this one! Thanks for your question and thanks for watching HorseGirlTV! </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/mbo_anky.m4v" length="11345342" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/mbo_anky.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>anky, train, ride, anky van grunsven, olympian, lessons, dressage</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Meet International Show Jumper, Georgina Bloomberg</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Georgina Bloomberg Talks About School, Showing And Juggling A Busy Life</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Angelea had the unique opportunity to sit down with international rider Georgina Bloomberg to discuss how she's able to juggle an intense school schedule at NYU, training a string of top mounts and still finding a bit of quiet personal time with her horses. </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep61.m4v" length="42216814" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep61.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>4:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>bloomberg, georgina, show jumper, jumper, olympian, hunters, rider, international</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>How Does Anky van Grunsven Stay So Fit?</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl Mail, Talk To The Pros</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Stephanie from Idado wants to know how does Anky stay so fit? Thanks for your question and thanks for watching HorseGirlTV! </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/manky_fit.m4v" length="6428932" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/manky_fit.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>anky, train, ride, anky van grunsven, olympian, lessons, dressage</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>What's The Most Profound Thing You Learned Training With Anky van Grunsven?</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl Mail, Talk To The Pros</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Michelle from Wyoming wants to know, what's the most profound thing you learned training with Anky van Grunsven? Thanks for your question and thanks for watching HorseGirlTV! </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/mang_anky.m4v" length="8543879" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/mang_anky.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:41</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>anky, train, ride, anky van grunsven, olympian, lessons, dressage</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Flying Horses With Humberto Rivera</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Angelea Talks With Horse Flight Agent, Humberto Rivera, About How To Fly</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>One might think it's a huge ordeal and while there is a certain amount of paperwork and dealings with the USDA and import country rules and regs, flying horses is NOT too hard! Angelea had an opportunity to talk with flight agent Humberto Rivera literally before taking off on her adventure to The Netherlands to train with Anky van Grunsven. </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep62.m4v" length="39176524" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep62.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:44</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>fly, horses, international, showing, transportation, flight agent</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>How Does Anky van Grunsven Fly Her Horses?</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl Mail, Talk To The Pros</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Janice from Boston wants to how Anky flies her horses? Thanks for your question and thanks for watching HorseGirlTV! </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/mliesbeth_flyinghorses.m4v" length="14441667" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/mliesbeth_flyinghorses.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>anky, train, ride, anky van grunsven, olympian, lessons, dressage</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Interview With Anky van Grunsven</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Anky van Grunsven, three time Olympic Gold Medals, clinician, rider, mom, inspiration to many</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>It goes without saying that Anky van Grunsven has been one of the top dressage riders in the world for the last decade. Her accolades include the gold medal in the 2000 Olympics with her horse Bonfire and gold in the 2004 Olympics and in the 2008 Olympics with Saliner. She dominates World Cup Dressage competition, being named the World Cup Dressage Champion eight times, in 1995, 1996, 1997, 1999, 2000, 2004, 2005, and 2006, 2008. Angelea had a unique opportunity to interview Anky while also training with her at her stable in The Netherlands.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep64.m4v" length="43440458" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep64.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>anky, anky van grunsven, grunsven, olympian, olympics, dressage, sports, horse</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Elite In Sport But Not Elitism With Dane Rawlins</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl Mail, Talk To The Pros</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Tom from Kansas wants to know how we can improve the quality of the horse industry as a whole in the United States. Perhaps we should listen to top international rider and show organizer, Dane Rawlins? Dane's brilliantly yet simply states that while we need elite in sport to constantly improve top sport riding we don't need elitism. Watch and learn from this great rider and passionate horseman! Thanks for your question and thanks for watching HorseGirlTV! </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep65.m4v" length="16321599" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep65.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>sport, horse, top sport, international rider, elite, dressage, dane, rawlins</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>International Horse Shopping For Sport Horses</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet Sport Horse Agent, Geoff Butler, And Learn About International Horse Shopping</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Meet sport horses sales agent, clinician and trainer, Geoff Butler. Geoff is huge on listening to his client's needs and wishes, trying to accommodate them. In a world full of horse companies offering sales and training, Geoff's ideals are that very few that can match his personalized approach that truly puts the clients needs first. Angelea inquires about some tough horse shopping questions and uncovers some basic how to items for horse shopping aboard!
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep63.m4v" length="66430117" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep63.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:30</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, sport, sporthorse, shop, buy, how to buy a horse</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>How Top Competition Horses Are Wrapped</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl Mail, Talk To The Pros</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Sandra from Southern California asks HorseGirlTV if we'd show the basics of how to wrap with an under wrap and polo. Sure thing Sandra! Weve asked Janine at the stable of Anky van Grunsven if she'd show us how! Thanks for your question Sandra and thanks for watching HorseGirlTV! </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep66.m4v" length="15365175" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep66.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:18</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>wrap, bandage, polo, standing wrap, horse wrap</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dentistry Without Drama With Geoff Tucker</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Geoff Tucker, DVM Equine Veterinarian Specializing In Horse Dentistry</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Dr. Tucker has been with horses professionally since 1973. He worked full time on a Thoroughbred breeding and training farm in Bedford Hills, NY. He started as a manure engineer and worked his way up to assistant farm manager. There were up to 20 horses in training and up to 100 mares foaling during the breeding season and about 10 stallions standing at stud. As the foaling manager, Dr. Tucker attended all foalings and assisted deliveries either before the vet arrived or with the help of the vet. He was also responsible for all the preventive medicine on the farm. Angelea talks with Geoff about his passion to give relieve horses and their owners through his natural, low stress methods.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep67.m4v" length="66608925" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep67.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:28</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>dentist, vet, veterinary, veterinarian, dentistry, horse, horse vet</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>GGT Footing And The Attwood Pros</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirlTV Talks With Nick Attwood Of Attwood Equestrian Surfaces About Installing GGT Footing</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Several decades of experience with equestrian surfaces, makes Nick Attwood the perfect person to talk with about producing an effective sport horse training surface. Angelea met with Nick Attwood of Attwood Equestrian Surfaces to talk about the installation of GGT, German Geo Textile, footing. GGT-Footing, a shredded textile, that stabilizes the sand particles mimicing the effect of the rooting system of turf, which has a stabilizing effect on the surrounding soil particles. GGT footing give more resilience, reduces the amount of packing and helps to hold moisture in the surface, which leads to reduced dust. The secret with GGT really is in the sand.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep69.m4v" length="54750873" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep69.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>5:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>arena, footing, sand, blend, dressage, court, riding, surface, equestrian, ggt</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Shake n Fork</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Stall Cleaning Is A Cinch With Shake'n Fork</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Many of the HorseGirlTV fans have emailed about the manure fork we've used in previous webisodes so we're opting simply to show you all how it works. It's a pretty neat fork that definitely saves on the back breaking work of stall picking. At the farm here in NC, we've been using it for over a year now and enjoy it very much. The innovator that created this fork, Joseph Berto, is located in Oregon and passionate about creating time saving and technologically advanced farm related products. We think the folks handling the Gulf Coast oil spill need to connect with him about his tarball fork to help with the clean up efforts!
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep70.m4v" length="29444627" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep70.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:28</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, clean, stall, muck, manure, bucket, fork, pitch, rake</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Innovative Drainage Options</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Angelea Chats With Woody Woodward Of Infiltrator Systems About Ag Drainage</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In the search for the perfect drainage system, HorseGirlTV found a recycled product that is easy to install as, or more, cost effective to rock and pipe called EZ Flow. That's a win-win-win situation. The EZ Flow system is designed to improve drainfield performance by eliminating the fines associated with crushed stone, and reducing compaction and embedment associated with stone. Watch as we chat with Woody Woodward of Infiltrator Systems and install arena drainage in a snap!
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep71.m4v" length="53181880" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep71.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>4:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>drain, arena, septic, drainage, water, field, lines</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>The HorseGirl Supplement, Flex Max</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl Mail: What supplement does HorseGirl use?</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Many viewers have emailed in asking about what Angelea uses around the farm for feed, forage and supplements so we decided to cover the basics of supplements. The preferred supplement around the HorseGirlTV farm is Flex plus Max because it contains everything we could want in a supplement in it so there's one bucket, one scoop and it's definitely a time saver too. The plus side is being able to feed it to the dogs as well and they love the taste as much as the horses. We use the pellets but you can get it in a powder as well. For more info on Flex plus Max you can check out Absorbine's website.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep72.m4v" length="24929507" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep72.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, rider, supplement, feeding, nutrition, absorbine</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>WEG Bronze, Silver, Gold Medallions With Bluegrass Medallions</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Chrissy Joy from Bluegrass Medallions Flies out from Lexington, Kentucky!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Chrissy Joy, spokes model for Bluegrass Medallions, flew out from Lexington, Kentucky to meet Angelea and interview for HorseGirlTV! It was great fun chatting with Chrissy who is extremely passionate about these medallions AND they brought us out a surprise! FOUR Official WEG Medallion to give away to HorseGirlTV fans! Total value is $750 and we were blown away by this generous offer! Entering to win a Bronze, Silver, Gold or Kentucky Horse Park Medallion is free and easy! Just go to the HorseGirlTV Facebook Page to find out more.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep73.m4v" length="41199348" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep73.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>WEG, World, Equestrian Games, Medallion, Gold, Silver, Bronze</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>What Is It Like Training Breeding Stallions</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl Mail: What Inspires Trainers To Work With Breeding Stallions</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Joyce Heuitink is an international rider and trainer working with Wup, a well-known Dutch stallion of Holland. HorseGirlTV caught up with Joyce in The Netherlands to ask what inspired her to work with a breeding stallion training in the art of dressage.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep74.m4v" length="8972319" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep74.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:45</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>training, breeding, stallion, wup, dutch, international, rider, dressage</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Attwood Equestrian Surfaces And Pinnacle Footing</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Learn About Attwood Equestrian Surfaces And Pinnacle Footing</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Angelea had the distinct honor of working with Attwood Equestrian Surfaces and the owner of AES took time to travel to HorseGirlTV studios to meet and interview with Angelea! Here's a bit about their highly reputable company: Attwood Equestrian Surfaces has been building quality riding arenas for over fifteen years. AES is the innovator of equine surfaces and Equation, the original dust-free footing. Their background in chemistry, construction, and manufacturing enables AES to research and create carefully balanced products that perform consistently in any climate.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep75.m4v" length="8972319" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep75.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>4:23</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>footing, arena, construction, sport horse, horses, sand, attwood, equestrian, surfaces</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dutch Rider Talks About Her Dreams For The Future</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirl Mail: What does Tawny aspire for her dressage career?</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We ask Dutch Rider and pupil of Anky van Grunsven what her dreams for the future are. Listen to what Tawny has to say!
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep76.m4v" length="11854680" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep76.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>0:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>anky, van, grunsven, avg, dutch, young rider, netherlands, dressage</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Grand Prix Trainer, Judge, and Long Time Dressage Sport Mentor, Elizabeth Madlener</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet USA Dressage Living Legend Elizabeth Madlener</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Ask and you shall receive! Fans often write in asking for HorseGirlTV to interview this or that person. A fan wrote in over the summer asking us to interview Elizabeth Madlener and here you go! Elizabeth is a well-known Grand Prix level trainer, instructor and competitor, a USEF "S" judge since 1980, USDF "L" faculty member, Dressage Today contributor, and former President and CEO of the Maryland Horse Center. Elizabeth is currently based in the Southern Maryland area, but travels frequently across the country as a clinician and judge.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep77.m4v" length="89798434" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep77.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>8:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>dressage, usa, judge, grand prix, trainer, training, sport mentor, legend</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Part II, Grand Prix Trainer, Judge, and Long Time Dressage Sport Mentor, Elizabeth Madlener</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet USA Dressage Living Legend Elizabeth Madlener</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This is part II of our fan driven webisode interview with Elizabeth Madlener! Fans often write in asking for HorseGirlTV to interview this or that person. A fan wrote in over the summer asking us to interview Elizabeth Madlener and here you go! Elizabeth is a well-known Grand Prix level trainer, instructor and competitor, a USEF "S" judge since 1980, USDF "L" faculty member, Dressage Today contributor, and former President and CEO of the Maryland Horse Center. Elizabeth is currently based in the Southern Maryland area, but travels frequently across the country as a clinician and judge.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep79.m4v" length="102920246" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep79.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>8:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>dressage, usa, judge, grand prix, trainer, training, sport mentor, legend</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Author Of The Science Of Motion, Jean Luc Cornille</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet French Olympian Jean Luc Cornille</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Jean Luc Cornille has gained worldwide recognition by applying practical science to the training of the equine athlete. Influenced by his background as a gymnast, Jean Luc deeply understands how equine training can be enhanced by contemporary scientific research. A unique combination of riding skill, training experience and extensive knowledge of the equine physiology enables Jean Luc to translate scientific insights into a language comprehensible to both horse and rider. This approach has been the trademark of his training. Meet Jean Luc and learn about his approach on HorseGirlTV.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep80.m4v" length="89192340" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep80.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>9:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>dressage, olympian, french, rider, jumper, show, jump, classical, olympic, france</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Mary Bahniuk Lauritsen, From Set To Saddle</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet Former Young Rider, Model, Trainer Mary Bahniuk Lauritsen</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Watch as we talk with such an inspiring ambitious and talented young lady, Mary Bahniuk Lauritsen about how she creatively juggles all her projects. Mary Bahniuk Lauritsen is a rider, trainer, and competitor in dressage, a model, a volunteer, a videographer and a slightly ambitious young lady. Mary is based out of her family owned farm, Cadence Farm of Harvard, Massachusetts. She has been actively competing in dressage since she was nine years old and has successfully shown up to Prix St. George. Mary is active within the sport in and out of the saddle. 
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep81.m4v" length="104013907" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep81.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>9:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>dressage, young, rider, trainer, model, usdf, sport, horse, olympic</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>HorseGirlTV Classics, Developing Your Equestrian Career</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Rewind with HorseGirlTV. What was it like to groom for Anky van Grunsven at Aachen? How to develop your career.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Educational and entertaining content is timeless which is why we're launching HorseGirlTV Classics! After producing five years of amazing equine-based content in new media we realized that some of our fan base may have never seen our early years. We take a look back to classic HorseGirlTV webisodes. What was it like grooming for Anky van Grunsven? Let's chat with Tiffany Tyler and find out. In this pilot episode of HorseGirlTV we meet former groom of Anky van Grunsen, Tiffany Tyler and learn some of Anky's grooming secrets! We catch up with Tiffany in Ashland, Oregon where she continues to develop her career in competitive equestrian sports. Tiffany plans to show this season and aspires to compete on an international level in the CDIs.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/classics-01.m4v" length="73659631" type="audio/x-m4a" /> 
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/classics-01.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, equine, equestrian, horse tv, horse video, dressage, anky, anky van grunsven, olympic, olympian</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ease Of Use Eco-Friendly Bedding</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Discover Equine Pine Boutique Bedding</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>It seems that this year is fast becoming a remembering the earth year at HorseGirlTV. With the farm studio in full swing on the East Coast, implementing and testing quality environmentally friendly products has never been easier. We modified our stable bedding solution about a year ago and have never been happier with the ease of use, decreased waste, horse happiness, quality of product and just general cool factor it's provided. With that, we want to share with you just how wonderful the boutique bedding, Equine Pine is.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep82.m4v" length="27575178" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep82.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>bedding, stable, management, horse health, care, barn, cleaning, muck, stall, boutique, equine, pine</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>HorseGirlTV Classics, Importing Horses and CEM Quarantine Facilities</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Rewind with HorseGirlTV. What you need to know about importing, CEM and secondary quarantine</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Educational and entertaining content is timeless which is why we've launched HorseGirlTV Classics! After producing five years of amazing equine-based content in new media we realized that some of our fan base may have never seen our early years. We take a look back to classic HorseGirlTV webisodes. What is involved with importing horses and secondary quarantine? Let's ask CEM facility owner, Penny Barerras and find out.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/classics-02.m4v" length="65237964" type="audio/x-m4a" /> 
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/classics-02.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>5:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, horses, horse tv, horse channel, equine, importing, cem, quarantine</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Straightforward Watering Solutions</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Arena Watering With The Rapid Rain</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We get lots of questions about how we do things around the studio and stable at HorseGirlTV and do our best to answer as many as possible via the webisodes. We have a pretty neat watering solution for arenas and pastures called the Rapid Rain. It's a simple to use, low maintenance device! Rapid Rain is manufactured in the USA which is always a big plus when we're researching products at HorseGirlTV! The Rapid Rain allows easy watering by automatically rewinding the hose and sprinkler, and shutting off when you choose. No need to move sprinklers around to different areas, or maintain a complicated and costly permanent system. Whether it's watering your yard, dust control for your horse arena, or anywhere else you need a portable watering system, there's a Rapid Rain model that does the work for you! It's definitely on our list of cool tools!
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep83.m4v" length="22615096" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep83.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:11</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>watering, arena, automated, sprinkler, rapid, rain, dressage, court, footing</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>HorseGirlTV Classics: It's Reining. It's Pouring.</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Rewind with HorseGirlTV. What is competitive reining all about?</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Educational and entertaining content is timeless which is why we've launched HorseGirlTV Classics! After producing five years of amazing equine-based content in new media we realized that some of our fan base may have never seen our early years. We take a look back to classic HorseGirlTV webisodes. Follow Angelea, as she meets with reining trainer and competitor, John Irish to learn about this competitive FEI sport that is growing in popularity. "Whoa" is given a WHOLE new meaning with this sports sliding stops!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/classics-03.m4v" length="82660120" type="audio/x-m4a" /> 
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/classics-03.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>equestrian, horse, horse tv, horse channel, horses, equine, reining, western, sliding stop, spins</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Successful Nutritional Plan</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Importance Of Understanding What You Put Inside Your Horse</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We spend hours training in the sandbox and its equally important to think about what goes inside our horses. Part of a successful training program is a successful nutritional plan. Fans ask how we do things here at HorseGirlTV and when it comes to feeding we look for three things.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep84.m4v" length="26295739" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep84.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:35</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>nutrition, horse, feed, cavalor, care, stable, management</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>High Tech Innovations In Horse Sport</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet Evin and Noah Rattner of Devonwood Competition Services</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>HorseGirlTV traveled to Portland, Oregon to visit with Evin and Noah Rattner about high tech innovations in horse sport.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep85.m4v" length="86308842" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep85.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>8:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, sport, competition, show, management, iPad, iPhone, Internet, scoring, showing</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>High Tech Innovations In Horse Sport, Part II</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Part II, Meet Evin and Noah Rattner of Devonwood Competition Services</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>HorseGirlTV traveled to Portland, Oregon to visit with Evin and Noah Rattner about high tech innovations in horse sport. Watch Part II of this great series!
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep86.m4v" length="79822909" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep86.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:44</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, sport, competition, show, management, iPad, iPhone, Internet, scoring, showing</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>The US System At Work With Jessica Rattner</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet rider, trainer, stable manager and aspiring L Candidate, Jessica Rattner</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>HorseGirlTV traveled to Devonwood Equestrian Center in Sherwood, Oregon to visit with rider, trainer, stable manager and aspiring L Candidate, Jessica Rattner, to chat about growing up with dressage in the USA. Jessica is an inspirational, hard-working young woman whos worked her way up from early childhood in the USA dressage system. Angelea was thankful to have such a wonderful interview and be able to share Jessicas passion of dressage and dressage programs with the HorseGirlTV fans.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep87.m4v" length="78149020" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep87.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>8:47</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>dressage, usdf, federation, usef, training, sport horse, mentorship, kids, riding, programs</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Innovative Riding Breeches With FITS. It's 2.0!</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>HorseGirlTV revisits a great friend to the series, Sheryl Rudolph of FITS.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>HorseGirlTV revisits a great friend to the series, Sheryl Rudolph of FITS to find out where they are at now in revolutionizing the technical apparel industry!
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep88.m4v" length="88620437" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep88.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>8:47</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>breeches, fits, riding apparel, tech apparel, dressage, eventing, show jumping</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Turning Challenging Horses Into Willing Partners</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet exercise rider, trainer, and author, Nanette Levin</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>HorseGirlTV visits with author, trainer, exercise rider and all around horse gal, Nanette Levin about her new book, and how she got started working with horses over 20 years ago.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep89.m4v" length="86787841" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep89.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>8:47</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>racehorse, racing, exercise rider, author, horse trainer, training horses</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Pro Active Maintenance To Help Your Horse In The Summer Months</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>The key to keeping your costs and stress low is proactive maintenance.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In times of uncertainty we often react by cutting corners to save money. The key to keeping your costs and stress low is proactive maintenance. This is very easily applied to the care of your horse and especially important as the weather gets warmer and you are to ride your healthy and happy horse. Here are a few tips in being proactive for keep your horse healthy and helping enjoy the warmer months!
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep90.m4v" length="23926881" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep90.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>2:19</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse, health, pro, active, maintenance, summer health, horse care, care, absorbine</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>How To Build A Jump</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Learn how to build jumps</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>HorseGirlTV gets tons of fan mail with many questions about horse management and training. This was a great question from Ludy in Arizona. Ludy asks - How do you build a jump? You'll need some materials including jump cups. Thanks for the question Ludy! Now here's your answer!
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep91.m4v" length="30653765" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep91.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:01</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>jump, jumping, show jumping, showjumping, jump standard, how to, build, sport horse</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Wild Horses Of Shackleford Banks</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Travel with HorseGirlTV to witness eastern shore wild horses</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Shackleford Banks, the southern-most barrier island in Cape Lookout National Seashore, is home to more than 110 wild horses. This is one of the few places in the eastern United States where wild horses can still be seen. Shackleford Banks is approximately nine miles long and averages less than a mile wide. It contains many habitats, unique to barrier islands, which support the horses. Come along with Angelea as she meets a Horse Wildlife Biologist and take a walk around Shackleford Banks viewing some of the wild horse island residents.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep92.m4v" length="105137669" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep92.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>10:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>wild, horse, pony, shackleford, banks, island</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Valerie Ormond And Believing In Horses</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Believing In Horses tells the story of a young girl in a military family who commits to saving unwanted horses</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Valerie spent the majority of her adult life as a Naval Intelligence Officer. The daughter of two English majors, and an English major herself, she always had a great interest in books and writing. Just prior to her retirement from the Navy, someone suggested she turn an idea she had into a book, and from there her second career began.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep93.m4v" length="62288028" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep93.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>horse book, author, horse writer, writer, writing</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>How To Fit A Blanket</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>It's not rocket science but a proper fitting blanket will keep both you and your horse happy through the winter months</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>It's all too common to see a blanket on a horse that is either too big or too small/ It's like the story of Goldilocks and the Three Bears - It doesn't work if it's too big or too small, only just right. Just right makes for a happy horse resulting in a happy horse owner.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep95.m4v" length="34499658" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep95.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>3:09</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>how to fit a blanket, blanket, rug, fit, horse clothing</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>At Home With Felicitas von Neumann-Cosel</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet an incredibly gifted rider at home on the farm in Maryland.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>HorseGirlTV traveled to Maryland to meet the team at First Choice Farm and interview the amazingly gifted trainer, Felicitas von Neumann-Cosel. Felicitas was, of course, brilliant and inspiring to chat with and furthermore we fast felt at home there as EVERYONE was so welcoming.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep96.m4v" length="79541715" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep96.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>dressage, felicitas von neumann-cosel, trainer, international, horse, olympic</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>World Leading Saddle Designer Gene Freeze</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Meet Gene Freeze of County Saddlery makers of custom fitted handmade horse saddles</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Gene has designed saddles for many of the world's leading riders, in all 3 Olympic disciplines including the current tripe Gold Medalist, Edward Gal of the Netherlands. Gene is a member of the British Society of Master Saddler's and is the Chief Saddle Fitting Instructor of the Master Saddlers Association in the US.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep94.m4v" length="45703957" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep94.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>4:28</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>saddle, dressage, show jumping, eventer, gene freeze, county saddlery, master saddler, international, edward gal</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>How To Make Angelea's Favorite Horse Show Muffin</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>How to bake super horse show muffins. Blueberr,, Coconut and Macadamia Muffins</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>These are Angelea's favorite horse show muffins as they freeze easily and individually wrapped are a quick treat to share around the tack stall but they are likewise brilliant at Sunday brunch or simply with a nice cup of coffee.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep97.m4v" length="45242380" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep97.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>4:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>muffin, bake, snack, horse show, foodie, recipe</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Talking Digestive Health With Dr. Frank Pellegrini</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>If your horse does anything other than live in the wild, you should listen to what Dr. Frank Pellegrini has to say about digestive health</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Watch and learn as Angelea talks with Frank Pellegrini DVM about digestive health and how when a horse is healthy on the inside it performs and looks better on the outside!
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep98.m4v" length="69318591" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep98.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:13</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>digestive health, nutrition, horse, colic, ulcer, hind gut, digestion, top sport, performance horse, equine health</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Reining With Jon and Seth Ingram Of Ingram Training Stable</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>We discuss reining from its development to how its evolved in the modern day and lots of things in between with talented, top, reiners Jon and Seth Ingram!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Join Angelea as she rides along with Jon and Seth to talk about the early beginnings of reining, where it has come to in the modern day, where it might be going and how you can get involved! Ingram Training Stable, is located in Loxahatchee, Florida just outside the beautiful horse village of Wellington.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep99.m4v" length="123662167" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep99.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>11:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>reining, reiner, reining horse, performance horse, quarter horse, fei reiner, western, cowboy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Meet London 2012 Olympic Para-Equestrian Dressage Hopeful, Dale Dedrick</title>
<itunes:author>Horse Girl TV</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Learn about what it takes to qualify as a para-equestrian rider and the path to the Olympics for para-equestrians.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Dale is a grade 2 due to multi-limb involvement with weakness in her legs and hands compounded by severe hand deformities. Often people never realize her disability until they see her walk with her cane.
 </itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep100.m4v" length="37904255" type="audio/x-m4a" />
<guid>http://horsegirltv.com/itunes/ep100.m4v</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>04:31</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>para-equestrian, olympics, london 2012, dressage, para-rider</itunes:keywords>
</item>
	
</channel>
</rss>