<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
		<channel> 
			<title>The CuteKid. Baby Photo Contest Gets Featured at 10 News Click</title>
				<link>http://www.thecutekid.com/</link>
					<language>en-us</language>
						<copyright>The CuteKid.</copyright>
							<description>San Diego 10News.com  covered details on how TheCuteKid.com.s baby photo contest works, evaluation process and points to the chance of getting professional exposure from the Talent and Casting Agents that act as the sites Judges. 10news.com also mentioned that every contest entrant receives a yearly subscription to Parenting. magazine. Read the entire review. </description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2007 04:55:28 EDT</pubDate>
									<itunes:author>The CuteKid.</itunes:author>
										<itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
											<itunes:category text="Kids &amp; Family"></itunes:category>
												<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
													<itunes:keywords>baby photo contest, online baby photo contest, baby contest, baby picture contest, kids photo contest, cute kids, kids photo contests, online kids photo contest, cute kids photos, cute kids contests, cutes kids online, kid photos</itunes:keywords>	
														<itunes:owner>
															 <itunes:email>thecutekid@gamil.com</itunes:email>
															 	</itunes:owner>
																	<itunes:subtitle>The Cute Kid : Baby Photo Contest Online for Cute Kids</itunes:subtitle>
																		<itunes:summary>Baby photo contest to show off cute kids. Internet's largest, most respected child photo contest. Enter the cute kid's baby photo contest today!</itunes:summary>
																		<item>
																				<title>The CuteKid. Featured by 10News.com.</title>
																						<enclosure url="http://www.thecutekid.com/video/10news_click.wmv" type="video/x-m4v" length="5"/>
																								<guid>http://www.thecutekid.com/video/10news_click.wmv</guid>
																										<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2007 22:22:32 EDT</pubDate>
																												<itunes:author>The CuteKid.</itunes:author>
																														<itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
																																<itunes:duration>1:42</itunes:duration>
																																		<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
																																				<itunes:keywords>baby photo contest, online baby photo contest, baby contest, baby picture contest, kids photo contest, cute kids, kids photo contests, online kids photo contest, cute kids photos, cute kids contests, cutes kids online, kid photos</itunes:keywords>
																																						<itunes:subtitle>The CuteKid. baby photo contest gets featured at 10 News Click </itunes:subtitle>
																																								<itunes:summary>The review conducted at San Diego 10News.com  covered details on 
																																										how TheCuteKid.com&apos;s baby photo contest works, evaluation process and points to 
																																												the chance of getting professional exposure from the Talent and Casting Agents 
																																														that act as the sites Judges. 10news.com also mentioned that every contest entrant 
																																																receives a yearly subscription to Parenting. magazine. The show described the 
																																																		prizes as &quot;amazing&quot;  and categorically mentioned that the participants are evaluated 
																																																				by selected group of entertainment industry professionals and parents. Of course, the 
																																																						biggest news is the grand prize for the CuteKid of the Year . a $25,000 College 
																																																								Tuition Fund.  &quot;The coverage shows the confidence of visitors in TheCuteKid.com and 
																																																										is testament of the value created by the contest for parents. The CuteKid. is 
																																																												committed to bring the cute kids in the fore of entertainment and modeling industry.&quot; , 
																																																														remarked Greg Byrnes, Co-Founder. </itunes:summary>
																																																														</item>	
																																																																	   
																																																																	   </channel>
																																																																	   </rss>
