<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Podcast</title>
    <link>http://www.infotech.com/research</link>
    <description>Published Podcasts</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&#169; 1998-2012 Info-Tech Research Group, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <item>
      <title>Cost Cutting Podcast: Disaster Recovery Planning</title>
      <description>DRP strategies need to meet business needs, especially in tight economic situations. This podcast provides tactical guidance on aligning DRP strategies with business priorities. Use this guidance to reach short, medium, and long-term cost-reduction targets, and save on the bottom line.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-07-08 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-disaster-recovery-planning</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-disaster-recovery-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost Cutting Podcast: E-Mail Archiving &amp; Hosting</title>
      <description>E-mail management can pose challenges for IT, especially in terms of e-discovery and managing e-mail volume. This podcast addresses these challenges, among others, and provides cost-effective solutions to overcome them. Use this tactical guidance to align e-mail management with business needs and to significantly save on the bottom line.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-07-08 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-e-mail-archiving-hosting</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-e-mail-archiving-hosting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost Cutting Podcast: Telephony &amp; Vendor Negotiation</title>
      <description>Telephony expenses can certainly add up if IT does not adopt a cost-conscious strategy. By learning to negotiate with telecom providers and optimizing mobile device use, IT can significantly impact the bottom line. Adopting a tactical telecom strategy will enable IT to effectively reach its short, medium, and long-term targets.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-07-08 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-telephony-vendor-negotiation</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-telephony-vendor-negotiation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost Cutting Podcast: Application Development</title>
      <description>Efficiently managing application development projects can be a challenge at the best of times. The cost-conscious and tactical advice in this podcast provides insight on how to develop a strategy to align app development with business-critical needs. Use this guidance to reach short, medium, and long-term cost-reduction targets, and save on the bottom line.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-06-29 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-application-development</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-application-development</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost Cutting Podcast: Network Optimization</title>
      <description>Purchasing network equipment and managing networks can be a significant source of IT expenditure. Listen to this podcast to discover tactical actions to cost-consciously procure and manage network infrastructure. Use this timely guidance to reach short, medium, and long-term targets that are aligned with IT and business needs.  </description>
      <pubDate>2009-06-29 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-network-optimization</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-network-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost Cutting Podcast: Servers &amp; Storage</title>
      <description>Server expenses can add up, but they shouldn't have to squeeze the budget. Ease the budget by cascading server hardware, extending refresh rates, and leveraging virtualization. Employ these tips and others to help the enterprise trim server costs, and save on the bottom line.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-06-29 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-servers-storage</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/cost-cutting-podcast-servers-storage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Application Development Efficiently</title>
      <description>9:27 minutes - Listen to this podcast for guidance on managing application development demand and to discover ways to optimize the actual development process.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-06-29 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/manage-application-development-efficiently</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/manage-application-development-efficiently</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ease the Budget Squeeze with Server Consolidation</title>
      <description>8:20 minutes - Listen to this podcast to discover tactics that drastically reduce server costs.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-06-29 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/ease-the-budget-squeeze-with-server-consolidation</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/ease-the-budget-squeeze-with-server-consolidation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization Save on Network Expenses</title>
      <description>7:11 minutes - Listen to this podcast to discover tactical actions to cost-consciously procure and manage network infrastructure.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-06-29 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/optimization-save-on-network-expenses</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/optimization-save-on-network-expenses</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost Cutting Podcast: Trim Microsoft Licensing Costs</title>
      <description>Microsoft licensing is a significant cost driver for most IT organizations. Finally, there's a rational approach that can be used to determine whether the organization is overspending in this area. This podcast will provide guidance for optimizing both the short-term and long-term Microsoft licensing approach.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-06-09 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/webcast-cutting-microsoft-licensing-costs</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/webcast-cutting-microsoft-licensing-costs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find the Hidden Gold in Desktop Licensing</title>
      <description>4:18 minutes - This podcast discusses how to save on desktop licensing by minimizing switching costs, dropping Software Assurance, and harnessing virtualization for the reduction of underutilized licenses.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-06-09 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/find-the-hidden-gold-in-desktop-licensing</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/find-the-hidden-gold-in-desktop-licensing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost Cutting Strategies for Workstation Savings</title>
      <description>Desktop and laptop expenditures are unavoidable, but they don't have to be painful. Listen to this series of podcasts to discover proactive tactics and advice on how to drastically reduce workstation hardware expenses. Use this guidance to reach short, medium, and long-term cost-reduction targets, and save on the bottom line.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-05-05 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/webcast-cost-cutting-strategies-for-workstation-savings</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/webcast-cost-cutting-strategies-for-workstation-savings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buying Desktop Hardware? Reduce the Pain</title>
      <description>11:02 minutes - Desktop hardware expenditures are unavoidable, but they don't have to be painful.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-05-05 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/buying-desktop-hardware-reduce-the-pain</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/buying-desktop-hardware-reduce-the-pain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cutting Costs in Helpdesk Operations</title>
      <description>Effective help desk management can potentially save IT a significant amount of time and money. The key is to develop a cost-conscious strategy that leverages help desk efforts against the never-ending crush of tickets. Use this tactical guidance to reach short, medium, and long-term cost-reduction targets, and save on the bottom line.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-04-15 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/webcast-cutting-costs-in-helpdesk-operations</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/webcast-cutting-costs-in-helpdesk-operations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to Save Time and Money? Optimize your Help Desk</title>
      <description>7:24 minutes - This podcast discusses how effective help desk management can potentially save IT a significant amount of time and money.</description>
      <pubDate>2009-04-15 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/want-to-save-time-and-money-optimize-your-help-desk</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/want-to-save-time-and-money-optimize-your-help-desk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going 'Green' Hear Why and How It's Important for Your Enterprise</title>
      <description>6:45 minutes - This podcast explores the awareness of green issues and the adoption of green technologies within the IT environment.</description>
      <pubDate>2007-12-04 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.infotech.com/research/going-green-hear-why-and-how-its-important-for-your-enterprise</link>
      <guid>http://www.infotech.com/research/going-green-hear-why-and-how-its-important-for-your-enterprise</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
