<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>

<title>The Classic Metal Show Best Of Podcast</title>

<link>http://www.classicmetalshow.com/</link>

<language>en-us</language>

<copyright>&#x2117; &amp; &#xA9; 2008 CMS, LTD &amp; Family</copyright>

<itunes:subtitle>Hail And Kill!</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:author>The Classic Metal Show</itunes:author>

<itunes:summary>The Classic Metal Show is a 6-hour, all live request show which features the best in "Classic Metal".  The show features many great features, including interviews with all the biggest stars in Classic Metal. Hosted by Neeley and Chris Akin, the show has been broadcasting since January of 1996 and grows stronger with each passing week.  Check out THE CLASSIC METAL SHOW Saturdays from 9pm to 3am EST on The CMS Radio Network, as well as our fine affiliates!  Our website is www.theclassicmetalshow.com.  The Classic Metal Show launched a 24-7 Online Classic Metal Radio Station - www.cmsradionetwork.com.  This hard rock, heavy metal, classic metal, hard rock show has featured interviews, talking metal and music from bands such as Dokken, Motley Crue, Queensryche, Slayer, Metallica, Hellfueled, Astral Doors, Tarsha, Megadeth, Lizzie Borden, Metal Church, Quiet Riot, Poison, Warrant, Def Leppard, Death Angel, Dark Angel, Seven Witches, Testament, Seven Wishes, Kick Axe, Fastway, Yngwie Malmsteen, Beatallica, Grave Digger, Manowar, Sword, 40 Ft. Ringo, Accept, AC/DC, Adriangale, Aerosmith, Alcatrazz, Aldo Nova, Alice Cooper, American Angel, American Dog, American Pearl, Anthrax, Anvil, Arcade, Armored Saint, Axel Rudi Pell, Badlands, Bar7, Belladonna, Blackeyed Susan, Black Label Society, Black N' Blue, Black Sabbath, Blaze Bayley, Blind Melon, Bon Jovi, Bonham, Brainstorm, Bret Michaels, Britny Fox, Bulletboys, Cage, Chastain, Cinderella, Cobra, David Coverdale, Damn Yankees, Dangerous Toys, Deep Purple, Dee Snider, Def Leppard, Desperado, Dio, Dirty Americans, Dream Theater, Duff McKagan, Edguy, Enuff Z'nuff, Eric Martin, Mr. Big, The Godz, Europe, Every Mother's Nightmare, Exodus, Extreme, Fastway, Fireball Ministry, Firehouse, Fozzy, Funny Money, Kix, Gamma Ray, Glenn Tipton, Gotthard, Great White, Guns N' Roses, Hades, HSAS, Halford, Hammerfall, Cans, Hanoi Rocks, Helix, House Of Lords, Hughes Turner Project, Iced Earth, Iron Horse, Iron Maiden, Keel, Iron Savior, Jack Blades, Jack Frost, Jetboy, Jizzy Pearl, Joe Lynn Turner, Joey Tempest, Josh Todd, Judas Priest, Junkyard, Kik Tracee, King Diamond, Kingdom Come, Kiss, Krokus, LA Guns, Leatherwolf, Liege Lord, Lita Ford, Living Color, Living Loud, Loudness, Love Hate, Lynch Pilson, Lynyrd Skynyrd, M3, Mad Margritt, MSG, Dave Meniketti, Metal Church, Mike Tramp, Motley Crue, Motorhead, Nashville Pussy, Murderdolls, Neil Turbin, Night Ranger, Nuclear Assault, Omen, Ozzy Osbourne, Paul Shortino, Pretty Boy Floyd, Pink Cream 69, Poison, Primal Fear, Queensryche, Quiet Riot, Rainbow, Ratt, Raven, Ray Gillen,  Rik Emmett, Sammy Hagar, Saxon, Scorpions, The Scream, Sebastian Bach, Shark Island, Silvertide, Skid Row, Slaughter, Slayer, Danger Danger, Steve Vai, Stryper, Suicidal Tendencies, Symphony X, Evergrey, Tesla, Testament, Thunder, TNT, Tracii Guns, Trouble, Twisted Sister, Tyketto, UFO, Union, Vain, Van Halen, Vicious Rumors, Brides Of Destruction, WASP, Warlock, Warrant, Warrior Soul, White Lion, Whitesnake, Widowmaker, The Wildhearts, Winger, WWIII, XYZ, Zebra. Heavy Metal Podcast, Metal Podcast, Opie and Anthony, Howard Stern, Hard Rock Podcast, Classic Rock Podcast.</itunes:summary>

<description>Airs live from 9pm-3am EST exclusively at www.theclassicmetalshow.com, and on terrestrial radio.</description>

<itunes:owner>

<itunes:name>Chris Akin</itunes:name>

<itunes:email>richwithhatred@pitriff.com</itunes:email>

</itunes:owner>

<itunes:image href="http://www.theclassicmetalshow.com/cmsmascot.gif" />

<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>

<itunes:category text="Music">

</itunes:category>

<itunes:category text="Comedy"/>


</channel>
</rss>