<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>River Trading Post Pod Network</title>
        <description>Tips, tidbits, discussion and music of interest to collectors of fine Native American Art presented by River Trading Post</description>
        <link>http://www.rivertradingpost.com</link>
        <category domain="">Native American Art, Native American</category>
        <copyright>River Trading Post 2007</copyright>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 14:28:36 -0600</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 14:16:02 -0600</pubDate>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.3.1) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.rivertradingpost.com/images/weblogob.jpg</url>
            <title>River Trading Post Pod Network</title>
            <link>http://www.rivertradingpost.com</link>
            <width>251</width>
            <height>113</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>Oneida Artist Mark Fischer Shares The Traditions of His People</title>
            <description>Oneida Artist Mark Fischer tells about the traditions of the Oneida people, their clans and their prayers.&lt;br /&gt;
Mark gave this talk to River Trading Post visitors in March 2111</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/MarkFischer.mp3</link>
            <category domain="">Discussion</category>
            <enclosure url="/Podcast/MarkFischer.mp3" length="" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">687F50C0-1CD3-470D-A91E-769565A165FF</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 14:16:02 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>River Trading Post&apos;s Joe Zeller Discusses the Indian Arts and Crafts Association</title>
            <description>In 2010, RTP&apos;s Joe Zeller was named President of the renowned IACA.  In this interview, Zeller tells how he got started in collecting American Indian Art, how River Trading Post began, and his thoughts about the Indian Arts and Crafts Association.</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/IACA%20Zeller.mp3</link>
            <category domain="">Discussion</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/IACA%20Zeller.mp3" length="" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">76FC7E86-C89F-4E91-B9CB-51F9F788930C</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 11:31:25 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>A Discussion With Renowned Navajo Jeweler Shane Hendren</title>
            <description>Navajo jeweler Shane Hendren discusses the things that influence his art, the idea of balance in Navajo culture, and his thoughts about today&apos;s market for American Indian Art.</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Shane%20Hendren%20At%20River%20Trading%20Post.mp3</link>
            <category domain="">Discussion</category>
            <enclosure url="/Podcast/Shane%20Hendren%20At%20River%20Trading%20Post.mp3" length="" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">CA689BFD-5A25-43D2-AF09-DF25DE0D25D7</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 16:07:17 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Remembering a Friend: Jimmy Shendo 1954 - 2009</title>
            <description>Jimmy Shendo was a good friend of River Trading Post.  A musician through and through.&lt;br&gt;
On a blustery, snowy Monday (December 7) in New Mexico, Jimmy&apos;s music was silenced in a tragic accident that cut his aspirations short.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Jimmy, and his group Moiety, had just been nominated for awards at the 2009 Native American Music Awards.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This program is dedicated to Jimmy, his family, his fellow musicians, and to all of Jimmy&apos;s many friends.</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Jimmy%20Shendo%20Tribute.wmv</link>
            <category domain="">Music</category>
            <enclosure url="/Podcast/Jimmy%20Shendo%20Tribute.wmv" length="" type="wmv"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1927C9D9-EB35-491B-91E4-1291EA45781B</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 9 Jan 2010 15:51:32 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Historic Toadlena Trading Post Links With River Trading Post Scottsdale.</title>
            <description>Historic Toadlena Trading Post has been around for over 100 years. During its time, it has become the center for the finest of all Navajo weavings.&lt;br&gt;
This River Trading Post Podcast gives you insights into the operation of the old trading post, and a wonderful film essay by Jane Ginn about Navajo weavings.&lt;br&gt;
Today, you can see an exceptional collection of these Navajo weavings at River Trading Post in Scottsdale, and on our River Trading Post website.&lt;br&gt;
In the meantime, we hope that you will enjoy this River Trading Post Podcast.</description>
            <link>http://www.rivertradingpost.com/toadlena.htm</link>
            <category domain="">Discussion</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Toadlenapodcast.wmv" length="110105" type="wmv"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1891C182-FF12-4AF8-B5AD-15A86C722541</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2009 16:57:43 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Artist Ed Kabotie Debut CD - Origins</title>
            <description>Ed Kabotie is a good friend ours at River Trading Post.  Ed is from both Santa Clara Pueblo and from Hopi.  His art is inspired by both of these dynamic cultures.&lt;br&gt;
Ed Kabotie is an accomplished artist, working in paintings, jewelry, pottery and carvings.&lt;br&gt;
He has just released this seven song disk, entitled &quot;Origins.&quot;  Each track was written by Ed, and he is accompanied by acoustic guitar and Native flute.&lt;br&gt;
Though contemporary in every sense, Ed&apos;s compositions reflect long held Native American tributes and beliefs.</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Ed%20Kabotie.wma</link>
            <category domain="">Music</category>
            <enclosure url="http://www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Ed%20Kabotie.wma" length="48374" type="wma"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B1BD1B4D-43D5-43A4-95C3-6F74591166AD</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 14:24:43 -0500</pubDate>
            <source url="">http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/ Ed Kabotie.wma</source>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Jimmy Shendo&apos;s Latest Album Influenced by The Eagles and Kashtin</title>
            <description>Walking the Life Road is a bit country, a bit blues, a bit traditional with a dose of influence by The Eagles and by Kashtin.
&lt;br&gt;Jemez Pueblo musician Jimmy Shendo reaches into all areas of music and styles.  His latest album, with his group Moiety, contrasts hugely to his earlier album The Town Crier, which you can listen to here on the River Trading Post Pod Network.&lt;br&gt;Shendo, and his music, have traveled extensively throughout the United States, Canada and Mexico.  And Jimmy will tell you his favorite place to perform is Hawaii.&lt;br&gt;


&lt;a href=&quot;http://myspace.com/jimmyshendo&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; &gt;&lt;br&gt;
Read more about Jimmy Shendo at Myspace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Life%20Road.mp3</link>
            <category domain="">Music</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Life%20Road.mp3" length="76639" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">551EA019-E0DD-40B2-9F08-5F4062693FC2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 11:19:11 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cliff Fragua Speaks at the Unveiling of &quot;Heart Of The Basketmaker&quot; In Illinois</title>
            <description>Schaumburg, Illinois&lt;br&gt;
November 7, 2008&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Cliff Fragua&apos;s &quot;Heart of the Basketmaker&quot; was unveiled in the Village of Schaumburg, Illinois.  The sculpture was created for the American Indian Center of Chicago, in conjunction with the Village of Schaumburg, and is on permanent display at the Indian Center&apos;s Trickster Gallery.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This short program shares Cliff Fragua&apos;s remarks during the unveiling of &quot;Heart of the Basketmaker.&quot;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Be sure to visit River Trading Post to see an extensive body of Cliff Fragua&apos;s work.</description>
            <link>http://www.rivertradingpost.com/fragua.htm</link>
            <category domain="">Discussion</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Basketmaker.wmv" length="23617" type="wmv"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">54D79672-42BD-4782-AAEB-3B93652FE65E</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 13:01:08 -0500</pubDate>
            <source url="">url=&quot;http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Basketmaker.wmv</source>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Town Crier With Jimmy Shendo - Jemez Pueblo</title>
            <description>Throughout the Pueblos of the Southwest there are many rituals and prayers for every ceremonial occasion.  These special occasions are frequently announced throughout the Pueblo by the town crier who urges all of the people to awake, open their eyes and make ready for the important occasion to come.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In this program, Jimmy Shendo, who hails from Jemez Pueblo, celebrates the Town Crier that tells the community that it&apos;s time to worship.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In the first track, Shendo asks that the Creator bestow blessings upon all the people that listen to these traditional songs.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In addition to Shendo, native flute, drums, vocals, Town Crier features Clifford Vigil Sr., Clifford Vigil, Jr., Rick Hale and Cliff Fragua.</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/The%20Town%20Crier.mp3</link>
            <category domain="">Music</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/The%20Town%20Crier.mp3" length="37069" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4501F02B-5529-434B-B24C-ECD4810E58D5</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
            <source url="">url=&quot;http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/The Town Crier.mp3&quot;  length=&quot;48446&quot;  type=&quot;mp3&quot;</source>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Rezmerized With Ryon Polequaptewa</title>
            <description>An hour of music created by Ryon Polequaptewa and recorded in his album &quot;Rezmerized.&quot;  &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
About &quot;Rezmerized&quot; Ryon says, &quot;With the heartbeat of our Mother Earth balance is restored.  Songs of strange and beautiful languages shared through various styles of repetitious harmony and melody.  From all directions of the universe and beyond together we pray.  That is the Native Way.&quot;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Ryon is donating proceeds from &quot;Rezmerized&quot; to Native Preservation.</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Rezmerized.mp3</link>
            <category domain="">Music</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Rezmerized.mp3" length="48446" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">84BD415C-9F76-4952-8459-4FBA26A8AF23</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 8 Jun 2008 16:26:34 -0500</pubDate>
            <source url="">url=&quot;http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Rezmerized.mp3&quot;  length=&quot;48446&quot;  type=&quot;mp3&quot;</source>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cliff Fragua One-On-One With Scottsdale Art Beat</title>
            <description>From River Trading Post, Scottsdale, Scottsdale Art Beat correspondent Diane Bykowski talks one on one with sculptor Cliff Fragua.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Cliff shares the special meaning of singing stone in his work, the impact of his Pueblo culture on his work, and much more.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
At the time of the interview, in May 2008, Fragua had become perhaps the most significant artist in his field...certainly one of the most important.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Cliff Fragua&apos;s work is featured at River Trading Post galleries in Chicagoland, Santa Fe and Scottsdale.</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Cliff%20Fragua.wmv</link>
            <category domain="">Discussion</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Cliff%20Fragua.wmv" length="200985" type="wmv"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C7BFE979-39D7-4BD6-8C3F-2CF2C105CB04</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 17:26:05 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Edward S. Curtis</title>
            <description>This short video essay provides insights in to photographer Edward S. Curtis, the most prolific photographer of Native American life of all time.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
His work is controversial, yet his over 40,000 photographic images provide great insight into a different time and place.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
We hope that this short program will interest you in further exploring Edward S. Curtis&apos; vast body of work.</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Edward%20Curtis%20Podcast.wmv</link>
            <category domain="">Historic</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Edward%20Curtis%20Podcast.wmv" length="36813" type="wmv"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0753530A-2DFF-47FA-A890-4A212BF4F12B</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 16:28:39 -0500</pubDate>
            <source url="">url=&quot;http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Edward Curtis Podcast.wmv</source>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ramson Lomatewama: Insights Into A Hopi Artist From KNAU Radio, Flagstaff</title>
            <description>Ramson Lomatewama is a close friend of all of us here at River Trading Post.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
While Ramson might best be know for his kachina doll carvings, he also is an educator, poet, and author.  And most recently he began the art of glassblowing.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In this podcast, we bring you a rebroadcast of KNAU radio&apos;s program that provides some great insight into our friend, and artist, Ramson Lomatewama.  &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Thanks to both KNAU and to Ramson for permission to rebroadcast this episode from KNAU&apos;s series &quot;Edge Of The Rez.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Ramson%20Lomatewama.mp3</link>
            <category domain="">Discussion</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Ramson%20Lomatewama.mp3" length="6985" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">78A2F5AF-5D2A-4587-BDE7-34B06525C046</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 7 Jan 2008 14:24:58 -0500</pubDate>
            <source url="">url=&quot;http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Ramson Lomatewama.mp3</source>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>10 Cuts From The River Trading Post Twenty Top Native American CD&apos;s.</title>
            <description>Each year, River Trading Post selects 20 Top Native American CD&apos;s to offer visitors to its three galleries.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Many are timeless, others are contemporary, and yet others are from emerging artists.  But all represent the great diversity and beauty of the music from Native American artists today.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This program shares 10 cuts that seem to be favorites of the folks at River Trading Post and our collectors.  You will hear singing, flutes and drums...and even Native American blues in the program.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Each of the CD&apos;s represented in the program is available in our Chicagoland, Santa Fe and Scottsdale galleries.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Enjoy the program.</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/RTP%202008%20Playlist.mp3</link>
            <category domain="">Music</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/RTP%202008%20Playlist.mp3" length="34462" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">DE8D4177-2CE4-4895-9A00-B0C2EEDA9479</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2007 16:25:29 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>A Harmon Percy Marble Portfolio Of American Indians</title>
            <description>Harmon Percy Marble was a prolific Native American photographer (and a mayor of Las Vegas).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Born in Nebraska in 1870, Marble owned a newspaper, sold it, and went to work for the government Indian Service in 1911.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
His assignments took him to the Navajo Reservation; he worked on the Navajo Reservation, with the Sioux tribes and with the Southern Pueblos.  He even owned a cigar store in Long Beach, California.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
While Marble&apos;s images don&apos;t have the technical quality of Edward Curtis, his work is uncontrived and natural.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
We hope you enjoy this video portfolio of Harmon Percy Marble from the River Trading Post Archive Collection.</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Harmon%20Percy%20Marble.wmv</link>
            <category domain="">Historic</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Harmon%20Percy%20Marble.wmv" length="47743" type="wmv"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">338A90C5-CEAF-4F83-926B-99E64B543BFC</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 17:20:51 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Enjoy A Two Minute Tour Of Our New Scottsdale Home</title>
            <description>The doors to the new River Trading Post Scottsdale are open and our gallery is among the very finest in all of Scottsdale.&lt;br&gt;
While our building is new and high-tech, it holds the charm,  warmth, and friendliness that has become a hallmark of River Trading Post, including a cup or two of Arbuckle&apos;s coffee.&lt;br&gt;And appreciation to Joe Ben, Jr. for his Navajo blessing on our new home.&lt;br&gt;
This is a place for people to drop in, to browse and to simply enjoy.&lt;br&gt;
We hope to see you very soon.</description>
            <link>http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/scottsdale.wmv</link>
            <category domain="http://www.rivertradingpost.com">Gallery</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/scottsdale.wmv" length="12061" type="wmv"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5EBB8539-B983-4D95-9D18-978B09DCBE33</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2007 16:41:22 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Southern Tribe Takes Us On A Southern Style Pow-Wow Journey</title>
            <description>Southern Tribe includes the descendants of many Pueblos and Nations, and the group has been featured at many leading venues, including Santa Fe Indian Market, and at River Trading Post in Santa Fe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Their album, The Journey, is a collection of original compositions inspired by the beauty of the Southwestern pow-wow landscape.  They were written by head singers Cedric Chavez and Myron Garcia, and paint a picture of their extended culture.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

As a side note, artist Andy Abeita is one of Southern Tribe&apos;s singers, and Andy&apos;s work is featured in each of the River Trading Post galleries, and on the River Trading Post website.</description>
            <link>http://www.rivertradingpost.com/images/Southern%20Tribe.jpg</link>
            <category domain="http://www.rivertradingpost.com">Music</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/The%20Journey.mp3" length="36800" type="mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B7E25428-625E-44E8-A8B0-30389188691B</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2007 15:31:41 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ryon Polequaptewa Tells Us About Five Hopi Kachina Dolls</title>
            <description>While there are many books about the Hopi Kachina Doll, there is nothing better than hearing about them from a voice of authority.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Ryon is one of today&apos;s top carvers, and in this program, he shares with us some insight into five Kachina Dolls, and the Kachinas that they represent.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Hear about the Ogre Maiden, the Mocker, the Star Chaser, the Mudhead dressed as Corn Boy, Corn Boy and Horse.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The track in this program is by Ryon and his group Blu Thunder.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
See Ryon&apos;s work at River Trading Post.</description>
            <link>http://www.rivertradingpost.com/ryon.htm</link>
            <category domain="http://www.rivertradingpost.com">Discussion</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Ryontells.wmv" length="56830" type="video/wmf"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1A46D551-7941-4CA4-BC76-A8A321779091</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2007 17:37:57 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>My Land, My People, My Work With Amelia Joe-Chandler</title>
            <description>Amelia Joe-Chandler is a teacher, a metal smith and an artist.  She was named Artist of the Year for 2006-2007 by the Indian Arts and Crafts Association.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
During her visit to our Dundee gallery, Amelia shared with our guests the influences of her Navajo heritage, her family and her land on her fabulous work today.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Enjoy this very special presentation by Amelia Joe-Chandler, and be sure to see her work at River Trading Post.</description>
            <link>http://www.rivertradingpost.com/amelia.htm</link>
            <category domain="http://www.rivertradingpost.com">Discussion</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Amelia%20Joe-Chandler.wmv" length="113514" type="video/wmf"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">25AD5192-EB90-488E-8E2E-F09363114B24</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 1 Jul 2007 13:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ryon Polequaptewa Tells About The Warrior Maiden, and Sings A Song For Us</title>
            <description>Ryon Polequaptewa is one our our favorite kachina doll carvers.  He also is a singer with Blu Thunder that is featured in the River Trading Post Pod Network.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
 In this podcast segment, Ryon tells us about Warrior Woman, the Hopi way to reach out through song, and Ryon reaching out to each of us through his song.</description>
            <link>http://www.rivertradingpost.com/images/3436.jpg</link>
            <category domain="http://www.rivertradingpost.com">Discussion</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Ryon%20Polequaptewa%20At%20River%20Trading%20Post.mp3" length="4929" type="audio/mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">CA0E3A96-8AED-42CE-AADA-F471D9CDF751</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2007 19:49:29 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Dorleen Gashweseoma Shares Moments With River Trading Post</title>
            <description>Dorleen Gashweseoma, award winning Hopi basket maker tells us about her grandmother&apos;s influence on her art, her traditional Hopi upbringing and a trip to Washington D.C.&lt;br&gt;
Dorleen&apos;s work can be found at River Trading Post galleries and on the River Trading Post Website.</description>
            <link>http://www.rivertradingpost.com/greatfinds.htm</link>
            <category domain="http://www.rivertradingpost.com">Discussion</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Dorleen%20Gashweseoma.mp3" length="8722" type="audio/mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A6014661-D137-4541-8035-45B9938D235B</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2007 17:33:52 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Blu Thunder From The Hopi Mesas</title>
            <description>Blu Thunder was formed after members of two Hopi drum groups, Blu Springs and Thunder Creek left their beloved Hopi homeland for the city to the south.  Singers from the two groups have a history of singing that spans over 10 years.&lt;br&gt;
Listen to the power of Blu Thunder drums.&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <category domain="www.rivertradingpost.com">Music</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/bluthunder.mp3" length="41826" type="audio/mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">66EF9A39-F29E-4C88-B3F7-C13771CC4702</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2007 14:39:37 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Images of Mary Elizabeth Jane Coulter, Grand Canyon Architect</title>
            <description>A short video Mary Jane Coulter&apos;s photography.  &lt;br&gt;
Coulter, architect of the Hopi House and other historic Grand Canyon buildings was inspired by the people and the land of Hopi, and greatly influenced her work.&lt;br&gt;
The video also shows you many of the images taken by Paul Coze as he documented the area for the Department of Interior.&lt;br&gt;
The images are from the photo archives of River Trading Post.</description>
            <category domain="http://www.rivertradingpost.com">Historic</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Mary%20Jane%20Coulter.wmv" length="34930" type="video/wmv"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">117DC285-E130-485D-918D-2AB0F4E2CFE3</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2007 16:36:58 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Eli Secody&apos;s Native American Church Songs</title>
            <description>Eli Secody is Navajo from Page, Arizona.  His Maternal clan is Nashtezhi Ta baa ha.  His Paternal clan is Tlogi Dine e.  &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In his Butterfly album, Secody expresses Native American Church songs with a contemporary approach.  His harmony and moving lyrics bring love and beauty into a couple&apos;s relationship.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <category domain="http://www.rivertradingpost.com">Music</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Eli%20Secody.mp3" length="16862" type="audio/mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C5ED673F-42A0-46E8-9914-FCC24E7111C4</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2007 13:31:42 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sights And Sounds Of River Trading Post</title>
            <description>Take a little trip to each of our three galleries in this program.  You will get a glimpse of what we are doing in Dundee, Santa Fe and Scottsdale as well as a look at our artists and their work.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <category domain="www.rivertradingpost.com">Gallery</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/video/Sights%20and%20Sounds%20of%20River%20Trading%20Post.wmv" length="78892" type="video/wmv"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C65A7AFB-B787-491E-92B9-B1A434486CBD</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2007 17:20:51 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Postcards Portray Native American Life</title>
            <description>During the 1950&apos;s and &apos;60&apos;s tourists visiting Indian Country were fascinated by Native American culture, and frequently purchased postcards to send back home to friends.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Many of the postcards did a great job of stereotyping the Native American.  Interestingly some also were very sensitive and well done.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This program presents a short video made up of many old postcards that are a part of the River Trading Post photo archives.&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <category domain="http://www.rivertradingpost.com">Historic</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.nativeamericanlinks.com/videos/postcardspodcast.wmv" length="32853" type="video/wmf"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">E6F61E0D-2206-4F2C-A5A6-D99AC6401475</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2007 15:47:17 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Honor The Grandmothers Part One</title>
            <description>Part One. Listen to the voices of Dakota/Lakota women elders talk about their lives during a time of struggle and survival in this special two part program that was originally produced for Minnesota Public Broadcast.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <category domain="http://www.rivertradingpost.com">Historic</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Honor%20The%20Grandmothers%20Part%20One.mp3" length="23025" type="audio/mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A9081D2A-C3DD-4161-BF3B-170E06862462</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 7 Feb 2007 17:22:29 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Honor The Grandmothers Part Two</title>
            <description>Part Two. Listen to the voices of Dakota/Lakota women elders talk about their lives during a time of struggle and survival in this special two part program that was originally produced for Minnesota Public Broadcast.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <category domain="http://www.rivertradingpost.com">Historic</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Honor%20The%20Grandmothers%20Part%20Two.mp3" length="22867" type="audio/mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9042C15D-D368-4716-9A31-3FD16E734C77</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 7 Feb 2007 17:13:38 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Contemporary Native American Musicians</title>
            <description>A look at three of today&apos;s top Native American Musicians including Rita Coolidge, Paul La Roche and Arvil Bird.&lt;br&gt;</description>
            <category domain="www.rivertradingpost.com">Music</category>
            <enclosure url="http://track.websiteceo.com/r/187326/www.rivertradingpost.com/Podcast/Contemporary%20Native%20American%20Musicians%20MP3.mp3" length="16862" type="audio/mp3"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">FEA6BD5B-4837-4D82-AB66-786007C36B14</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 7 Feb 2007 12:48:46 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
