<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/DTDs/Podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
<title> Eroticast.net - Erotic Audio - Sex Stories - Sexual How To - Porncasts</title>
<link> http://www.eroticast.net/index.php </link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>2011 Eroticast.net</copyright>
<itunes:author>Eroticast </itunes:author>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:summary>Erotic Audio Stories, Real Sex Audio</itunes:summary>
<description> High Quality Erotic Stories for Adults, Erotic Fiction, True Sex Stories</description> 
<image>
<title>Eroticast - Erotic Audio Podcast</title>
<url>http://www.eroticast.net/logo.png</url>
<link>http://www.yourdomain.com/feeds.html</link>
</image>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Eroticast</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>info@eroticast.net</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://www.eroticast.net/logo.png"/>
<itunes:category text="Sexuality"/>
<pubDate> Thu, 03 Feb 2011 00:00:00 EDT </pubDate>

<item>
<title>Phone Sex Moaning</title>
<description>In this free audio erotica file a phone sex lady gets real dirty and loud. Listen to her moan as she talks to you with music mixed over the top. She is very good with her mouth and sounds so sexy when she cries out "yes master it feels so good!"</description>
<itunes:author>Eroticast</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Phone Sex Moaning</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Phone sex operator Moans at dirty story time</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.eroticast.net/media/erotic%20audio/Moan_Phone_Issue_2.mp3" length="8038277" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.eroticast.net/media/erotic%20audio/Moan_Phone_Issue_2.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 00:20:00 EDT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:08:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>phone sex,erotica,erotic stories</itunes:keywords>

</item>

<item>
<title>Waking Up Denise</title>
<description>Should I stay or should I go now is the age old question? In this real sex audio mp3 our hot couple falls asleep after food and drinks. When our protaganist awakes at 3 AM knowing his fair maiden must return to her own castle, he gently wakes her with his hands touching her back, breasts and more until she has to mount her knight before returning home under the cover of darkness. </description>
<itunes:author>Eroticast</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Waking Up Denise</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Desnise can't stay the night but could she stay just a little longer?</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.eroticast.net/media/erotic%20audio/Waking_Up_Denise.mp3" length="12972899" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.eroticast.net/media/erotic%20audio/Waking_Up_Denise.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:15:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>real sex audio,erotica,erotic stories,sexy,hidden audio</itunes:keywords>

</item>

<item>
<title>How To Eat Pussy</title>
<description>Listen up fellas as a sultry woman explains exactly how to to use your tounge to give a woman a mind blowing orgasm. This erotic podcast covers all the fine points of cunninglus from anatomy to various techniques. A must have for all those learning how to go down on your woman in ways Cosmo wouldn't tell you. </description>
<itunes:author>Eroticast</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>How To Eat Pussy</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Learn how to give  cunninglus, another work for oral sex on a woman.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.eroticast.net/media/erotic%20audio/How_To_Eat_Pussy-Eroticast.mp3" length="5693285" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.eroticast.net/media/erotic%20audio/How_To_Eat_Pussy-Eroticast.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:07:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>cunninglus, go down on a woman, sex tips, how to, erotic radio, erotic audio</itunes:keywords>

</item>

<item>
<title>Railroad Threesome</title>
<description>With a sick boyfriend at home this hot lady goes out and finds two friends to play with.</description>
<itunes:author>Eroticast</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Railroad Threesome Erotic Story</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>With a sick boyfriend at home this hot lady goes out and finds two friends to play with.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.eroticast.net/media/erotic%20audio/Railroad_Threesome_Eroticast.mp3" length="4530000" type="audio/mp3"/>
<guid>http://www.eroticast.net/media/erotic%20audio/Railroad_Threesome_Eroticast.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>00:04:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>threesome, trio, erotic, sex, amateur story</itunes:keywords>

</item>

<item>
     <title> Best Anniversary </title>
     <description> "So what's your name, mystery lady?" I said, archly. She looked at me with a strange expression, half smiling and half what looked like longing, and suddenly leaning  towards me, she kissed me on the mouth, her lips firm and insistent, slightly open and moist... </description>
     <itunes:author> Eroticast.net </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Thu, 04 Oct 2007 1:00:00 PST </pubDate>
     <enclosure url="http://www.eroticast.net/media/audio/Best_Anniversary_Eroticast.net_Erotic_Audio_For_Adults.mp3" length="4794349" type="audio/mpeg" /> </item>

<item>
     <title> A Wonderful Night With Fi </title>
     <description> Erotic audio story with a lesbian theme. "We continued to dance, facing each other, whilst my heart beat so fast I thought I would die. The dance floor seemed to fill up even more, pushing us closer together, and making parts of our bodies brush against each other. She put a hand around my waist, looking straight in my eyes, before she leaned in, pulling me close to her and kissing me on the mouth."
</description>
     <itunes:author> Eroticast.net </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Thu, 11 Oct 2007 1:00:00 PST </pubDate>
     <enclosure url="http://www.eroticast.net/media/audio/A_Wonderful_Night_With_Fi_eroticast.net_.mp3" length="4794349" type="audio/mpeg" /> </item>
	 
<item>
     <title> How To Suck Cock  Vol #1 </title>
     <description> How to guide, one girls guide to giving a world class blowjob. Great blowjob tips or tricks that most womens magazine's won't print. Written and recorded by a woman from a womans perspective this how to guide starts off slow giving you intimate details on the art of oral sex covering all the fine points including the happy ending that will drive your man wild. 
</description>
     <itunes:author> Eroticast.net </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Thu, 18 Nov 2007 1:00:00 PST </pubDate>
     <enclosure url="http://www.eroticast.net/media/audio/how_to_suck_cock_Eroticast.net_Erotic_Audio_For_Adults.mp3" length="4992752" type="audio/mpeg" /> </item>
	 
<item>
     <title> My First Experience </title>
     <description> Erotic audio story with lesbian themes. We walked into the bedroom and closed the door behind us dropping onto the bed. I sat up as she pulled at the sarong and peeled her tight bottoms off kicking them to the floor in a tangled ball. "You have a model's body." I whispered as I had many times before, though always when she was clothed. She stood back against the wardrobe and dropped her hand to herself, moaning loudly and shaking uncontrollably. She brushed her long nails through her soft bush and went lower to open herself up with a stray finger along her slit.
</description>
     <itunes:author> Eroticast.net </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Thu, 25 Oct 2007 1:00:00 PST </pubDate>
     <enclosure url="http://www.eroticast.net/media/audio/My_First_Experience_Eroticast.net_Erotic_Audio_For_Adults.mp3" length="4794349" type="audio/mpeg" /> </item>
	 
<item>
     <title> Mary's True One Night Stands Vol #1 </title>
     <description> True Confessions! Just your typical white girl meets a black guy takes him home where they both get drunk and naked. Then what you thought was going to be normal ends up with him asking you to call him all sorts of offensive names while having sex with him hitting him, kicking him, pissing on him, and then throwing him out of your house, when the phone rings and its your boyfriend. This story might be offensive to some people, themes include interracial, cuckold, domination, humiliation, and more. While its taboo subject matter might offend some, you might get turned on, laugh, or both, to hear Mary tell her real story in her own words.

</description>
     <itunes:author> Eroticast.net </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Fri, 02 Nov 2007 1:00:00 PST </pubDate>
     <enclosure url="http://www.eroticast.net/media/audio/Marys_True_One_Night_Stands_02_eroticast.net.mp3" length="4992752" type="audio/mpeg" /> </item>	

<item>
     <title>Short Changed - Mary's True One Night Stands </title>
     <description>Public sex with a hot college guy in an open construction site along a busy street with strangers offering advice, and perhaps more. All true! Great ending! FULL STORY! 
</description>
     <itunes:author> Eroticast.net </itunes:author>
     <pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2008 1:00:00 PST </pubDate>
     <enclosure url="http://www.eroticast.net/images/stories/audio/Marys_True_One_Night_Stands_01_eroticast.net.mp3" length="4760000" type="audio/mpeg" /> </item>  
	 
</channel>
</rss>



<a href="http://www.podcastalley.com/"> My Podcast Alley feed!</a> {pca-35e2e4e2c9b4da15fa7efdf5301bc6b5}
