<?xml version="1.0"?>
	<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Beer Me Podcast</title>
		<link>http://www.beermepodcast.com/</link>
		<description>Beer talk, reviews, and more</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 5 Feb 2010 12:25:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<generator>tdscripts.com Podcast Generator</generator>		<webMaster>Jlevish@beermepodcast.com (Joshua Levish)</webMaster>
		<ttl>1</ttl>
		<item>
			<title>Beer Me Podcast 1</title>
			<description>Beer Me Podcast Episode 1</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 12:25:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast%20episode1%20final.mp3" length="21112545" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                </item>
                 <item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast 2</title>
			<description>Beer me podcast episode 2</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 12:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast%20episode%202.mp3" length="48012398" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                </item>
                 <item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast 3</title>
			<description>Beer Me Podcast Episode 3</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 12:31:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast3.mp3" length="50994151" type="audio/mpeg"/>

		 </item>
                 <item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast 4</title>
			<description>Beer Me Podcast Episode 4</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 08:54:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast4.mp3" length="36656880" type="audio/mpeg"/>

		</item>
                 <item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast 5</title>
			<description>Beer Me Podcast Episode 5, featuring Sierra Nevada Harvest Wet Hop Ale, Babe's Drunken Monk, and big plans for International Beer Day</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 10:32:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast5.mp3" length="39360357" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
                  <item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast 6</title>
			<description>Beer Me Podcast Episode 6, featuring Belzebuth, Lost Coast's Great White, and Burger King serving beer</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 08:54:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast6.mp3" length="42355807" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
 <item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast 7</title>
			<description>Beer Me Podcast Episode 7, featuring Samuel Adams Noble Pils, Spaten Optimator - finally back to the good beer!  Lots of beer talk and more.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 12:54:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast7.mp3" length="36611022" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
<item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast 8</title>
			<description>Beer Me Podcast Episode 8, featuring Deschutes Hop Trip, Meantime IPA and many wild tangents.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 4 Mar 2010 12:54:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast8.mp3" length="44984834" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
<item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast 9</title>
			<description>Beer Me Podcast Episode 9, featuring Rogue's Morimoto Soba Ale, Drake's Imperial Stout ,and discussion of Texas' crazy beer classifications</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 12:54:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/BeerMePodcast9.mp3" length="51947970" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
<item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast 10</title>
			<description>Beer Me Podcast Episode 10, Happy St. Patrick's Day to all!  The All-Guinness episode: Guinness Extra Stout, Guinness Draught, and discussion of different stouts, along with Irish Car Bombs</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 12:54:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast10.mp3" length="40503894" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
<item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 11: Hot Dogs in the Microwave</title>
			<description>This is the all-Allagash episode in which we drink the Allagash Dubbel Reserve, and Allagash Grand Cru. </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 12:54:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast11.mp3" length="42164363" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
<item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 12: The History of Beer</title>
			<description>Brett and Josh Walk you through the history of the greatest beverage of all time: Beer (did you think it would be some other beverage?) </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 12:54:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast12.mp3" length="50264409" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
<item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 13: A Taste of Cold-Filtered B.S. </title>
			<description>We are back with piss and vinegar, despite a few delays.  In this episode we are drinking He'Brew's Jewbelation 13 and Fransiskaner Hefe-weissbier, and discussing everything from the birth of Josh's son Devin Joseph to the 2010 World Beer Cup.  Crack your favorite craft beer and join us.  Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 04:24:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/BeerMePodcast13.mp3" length="59702315" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
<item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 14: This Bud's For You</title>
			<description>In this episode, we are drinking Lagunitas Wilco Tango Foxtrot, and a very special 13th anniversary ale from Firestone.  Oh, and keep in mind this episode was recorded on 4/20/2010.  Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 04:20:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast14.mp3" length="55155146" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
<item>

                                   <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 15: Up with Craft Beer, Down with Crap Beer</title>
			<description>This week Brett and Josh walk you through the battle between Macro and Micro Breweries.  We are drinking Dogfish Head's Palo Santo Marron, Aprihop, and North Coast's Old Rasputin.  We also discuss the documentary "Beer Wars."  So sit back, crack a nice brew and enjoy.  Cheers!! </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 04:20:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast15.mp3" length="66832011" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 16: Craft Beer and The American Way</title>
			<description>This week we are drinking Firestone's Solace Ale, along with Dogfish Head's 90-Minute Imperial IPA.  We discuss everything from Stone's possible European Brewery to the H.R. Bill excise tax relief for small breweries across the country.  So get your brew ready and join us for a bumpy ride through the wonderful world of beer. </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast16.mp3" length="47897942" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 17: Happy American Craft Beer Week</title>
			<description>This week we are celebrating American Craft Beer Week by drinking Victory Brewing Company's Hop Devil, Bear Republic's Racer 5 IPA and Sierra Nevada's 30th Anniversary ale(Fritz and Ken's).  Enjoy this All-American episode by grabbing your favorite American Craft Beer and drinking along with us.  Cheers!!!  </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast17.mp3" length="44430232" type="audio/mpeg"/>

			</item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 18: Getting Stoned</title>
			<description>This week we are featuring all Stone Brewing Co. beers.  We are drinking the collaborational Saison du BUFF and the Cali-Belgie.  So get off your can, go out and grab your favorite Stone beer, and drink one with us.  CHEERS!!!  </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast18.mp3" length="39652841" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                        </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 19: Activating a Window to the Cold!</title>
			<description>This week We are drinking the Coney Island Brewing Co. Albino Python and Stone's Old Guardian Barleywine.  So grab a beer, take a seat and enjoy.  CHEERS!!!!  </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast19.mp3" length="36812703" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 20: Beer School</title>
		<description> This week we are drinking Anchor's Small Beer, and New Belgium's Ranger IPA.  We discuss our trip to Temecula and our encounter with Pliny The Elder.  Brett rants about Bob Dylan and much much more enjoy.  CHEERS!!!!  </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 7 Jun 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast20.mp3" length="46137331" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 21: Canadian Bacon</title>
		<description> This week we are drinking Felinfoel Brewery Company’s Double Dragon Welsh Ale, along with Aecht Schlenkerla Rauchbier Märzen to make it an all-European episode.  We also discuss our Beer Wish List and some of the worlds oddest beers.  Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast21.mp3" length="42830125" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 22: Spicy Beer Cup</title>
		<description> In this episode we are drinking Lagunitas Hop Stoopid and Deschutes Jubel 2010.  We also discuss our first Brewing Adventure and of course the Spicy Beer Cup.  Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast22.mp3" length="52882653" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 23: Hops, malt, Hoppppps!</title>
		<description> This week join Josh and Brett as they enjoy Avery Brewing Co.'s Salvation, and Stone's 14th Anniversary Emperial IPA.  We also delve back into the wacky world of Liquor Laws and add another few brews to the Wish List.  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast23.mp3" length="49130295" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 24: Hops and Hashtags </title>
		<description> This week join Josh and Brett as they enjoy Anderson Valley Brewing Co.'s Boont Amber Ale and Bear Republic's Hop Rod Rye.  We are beat from a long Holiday Weekend so watch out!  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 5 Jul 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast24.mp3" length="48240557" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 25: Tight Pants and Cheap Beer </title>
		<description> This week Join Josh and Brett as they cross one off their wish list with Avery Brewing co's Collaboration Not Litigation Ale. They also enjoy a few Ayinger Ur-Weisse Dunkel Weizen's and talk about hipsters, Pintley.com and this week's beer news.  Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast25.mp3" length="50687485" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 26: Tea Bags and Swamp Ass </title>
		<description> This week join Josh and Brett in Hell as they mark yet another beer off there wish list.  The A/C is out and rather than throw in the towel, they push through, drinking a couple of the Mikkeller Single Hops series and Oskar Blues' Old Chub.  Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast26.mp3" length="56346583" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 27: Indian Style Session No. 1 </title>
		<description> It's Week 2 without A/C, but we soldier on and all that determination pays off well.  We finally get some Pliny the Elder on the show and make the decision to throw our show notes out the window.  So sit down on the living room floor and enjoy your favorite craft beer with us.  Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast27.mp3" length="72054051" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 28: Orval and Rodenbach </title>
		<description> We are back from the Stone Age this week, with air conditioning and great Belgian beers.  As the title implies, we are drinking Orval and Rodenbach - two historic Belgian beers.  So crack one and drink along.  Cheers!!  </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 3 Aug 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast28.mp3" length="50185013" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 29: The Real 29 </title>
		<description> Once again we are back with two amazing brews.  This time we have Russian River Supplication and The Bruery's Saison Rue.  We also came in with a bit of built-up angst and frustration so watch out for this one.  Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 9 Aug 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast29.mp3" length="105427583" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 30: Stone Round Table </title>
		<description>This week we once again explore the amazing world of Stone Brewing Co.  We do a side by side tasting of Stone's Arrogant Bastard and Oaked Arrogant Bastard, then hit the Vertical Epic 08.08.08, and the Sublimely Self-Righteous Ale.  Join us with our guest Andrew the English for this whirlwind trip through the wonderful world of Stone Brewing Co..  </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast30.mp3" length="67160498" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 31: Jeans Shorts and Baby Oil </title>
		<description>This week's episode brings us another guest: Brett's close friend Michael James.  We drink Sierra Nevada's Kellerweis and Saison DuPont.  We also dig deep into the world of hipsters, and malt liquor (Old English!) of all things.  Enjoy!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 06:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast31.mp3" length="46981167" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 32: Precious Beer Babies </title>
		<description>This week's episode brings us The Bruery's Orchard White and Sierra Nevada's Tumbler.  We talk of Josh's trip to Michigan, converting girls to beer and pumpkin ales.  We get a bit side tracked along the way so enjoy the randomness.  Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 2 Sep 2010 01:00:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast32.mp3" length="54551257" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 33: Hopsdouche.com </title>
		<description>This week's episode brings us DogFish Head's Festina Peche and Russian River's Consecration.  We talk about hop deodorant and lost abbey brews among other things.  Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 5 Sep 2010 24:00:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast33.mp3" length="47684981" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 34: Dry Sacked </title>
		<description>Jolly Pumpkin's Bam Noire and Brasserie D'Achouffe's La Chouffe (the gnome!) are the beers.  And we do some news.  But what's more important is the new trend we created in the craft beer world.  Direct all thanks to Brett's email. </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 5 Sep 2010 24:00:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast34.mp3" length="46684739" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 35: Southern California Love </title>
		<description>This week we, in honor of their domination at GABF, are drinking Lost abbey's Judgement Day and Port Brewing Co.'s Wipeout IPA. We talk about California's dominance at GABF (So Cal's dominance overall) and also dive into brewing with hot granite.  Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 20:00:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast35.mp3" length="54990085" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 36: This Bud's For Free </title>
		<description>IPAs all around, old- and new-school, light and dark.  Anderson Valley Hop Ottin and Deschutes Hop in the Dark.  And we delve into the wonderful world of beer news to find that a big brewery will be giving beer away because they can't sell it like they used to.  You get what you pay for... </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2010 20:00:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast36.mp3" length="55001087" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 37: Wet Burps and Magic Underwear </title>
		<description>Brett makes another stop at a superior bottle shop to bring to the podcast.  New Belgium/Brouwerij Frank Boon's Transatlantique Kriek and Brewery Ommegang's Three Philosophers.  We catch a buzz and then do the beer news as well. </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 23:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast37.mp3" length="55001087" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 38: Pirate Radio </title>
		<description> We are back from a small hiatus and we are taking the show on the road. We are drinking Telegraph's White ale and Stone's 10.10.10 and recording in Moreno Valley  with our guest and Brett's good friend Johnny O. Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 23:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/Beermepodcast38.mp3" length="47726568" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 39: We've Been Away For A While </title>
		<description> After some time off we are back again, Drinking some great beers from the Mid-West Courtesy of our friend Eric Wurm. Cheers!!! </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 18:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast39.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 40: Malt Liquor! </title>
		<description> Episode 40 brings with it a no-brainer: The History of Malt Liquor!  We don't drink any 40's though.  Why punish ourselves?  Instead, we dig into Eric Wurm's gift package and pull out the long-awaited Surly Furious.  Enjoy, and make sure to spill a little on the ground for the dead homies. </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2010 18:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast40.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 41: We're Ba-ack - Indian-Style! </title>
		<description> Episode Pre-party with Brett's homebrewed Witbier, followed by Avery's Maharaja Imperial IPA and then Inland Empire Brewing Company's bourbon barrel aged Coffee Porter. Josh and Brett catch up on all that has happened since the last podcast and all that is happening.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 9 Mar 2011 18:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast41.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 42: Winning with Tigerblood </title>
		<description> Let us just apologize up front for all of the Charlie Sheen-isms that will come spewing forth into your ear sockets when you listen to this week's episode.  Other than that, this one's Brett's Pliny the Younger experience and we drink a growler of Black Market Brewing Company's GABF Gold Medal-winning Rye IPA.  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 18:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast42.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 43: Midwest Beer Lightning Round </title>
		<description> Just try and keep up with us as we go through the remainder of the Midwest craft beer stash that our fan and friend Eric Wurm sent us.  6 beers in an hour is something you should look for us to do again.  Just don't blame us when we're buzzed to goofiness.  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 18:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast43.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 44: Trader Joe's Love </title>
		<description> If you don't have a Trader Joe's store near you, then you're just missing out.  Not that their beer selection is the best around, but what they contract out can be incredible and very inexpensive.  This may sound like a commercial, but really it is a hope that we can get free stuff from them.  So download and hold your breath along with us until they do.  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 18:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast44.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 45: Brett's Homebrew </title>
		<description> In the episode, Brett's Dubbel Hangover is tried by Josh for the first time, we talk about the upcoming American Craft Beer Week (May 16-22) and the Southern California Homebrewers Festival.  We then top it all off with a bottle of Stone's Lukcy Basartd (that's not a typo!) that Brett saved for Josh to try before it was all gone for the year.  What a good cousin, huh?  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 18:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast45.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 46: The Primitive Wild</title>
		<description> We were lucky enough this week to finally crack a bottle from one of our favorite breweries - Deproefbrouwerij out of Lochristi Belgium - of Flemish Primitive Wild Ale.  First, though, we begin with the Stone/Port/Green Flash Highway 78 Scotch Ale.  We also talk a little news and rejoice in the fact that we got a chance to record and that we still have so many beers in our collection that we're eager to sample.  Look for those soon, but for now, crack one of your finest and join us.  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 18:08:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast46.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 47: Beer Nerdiness</title>
		<description> Somehow, Josh and Brett get sidetracked by tech-talk and we go off the rails.  Maybe it was how good this episode's beers were: Schneider/Brooklyn's Hopfenweisse collaboration and Flying Dog's Raging Bitch Belgian IPA.  Who knows - maybe you'll learn something geeky?  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 18:08:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast47.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 48: Beer Me...QUICK!</title>
		<description> Josh has a moment and we decide to do a quick strike if for no other reason than to have a beer we haven't tried before.  And maybe to help keep us sane as well.  So Brett picked out The Bruery/Cigar City collaboration Imperial Oud Bruin called Marrón Acidifié for the special and welcome occasion.  Enjoy our first of possibly many half-episodes. </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 22:37:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast48.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 49: From Beer Humor to Genocide</title>
		<description> Yeah, Josh and Brett are in rare form as they appreciate and taste beer, regale you with tales, jokes and quotes, and end on a low note.  [Sigh] </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 22:37:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast49.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 50: Rodenbach and Cantillon</title>
		<description> Finally.  After all the talk about some of these special bottles we've been saving, we open some.  It was worth the wait.  Seriously worth it. </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 22:37:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast50.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 51: A Tale of Two Flying Dogs</title>
		<description> Brett has been a big proponent of Flying Dog's beer for a while and Josh has been needing to try it.  Today, it all comes together once again.  We delve into some of the interesting history of this brewery and the characters surrounding its creation over 20 years ago.  Find some of this ale, download the episode and join us.  And, as Dr. Gonzo said, " As your attorney, I advise you to take a hit out of the little brown bottle in my shaving kit. You won't need much, just a tiny taste." </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 16:37:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast51.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 52: Schmidy's Tavern</title>
		<description> We've finally done a year's worth of podcasts (if you listen to once a week - any more could be dangerous, so we decided to do something special: GET OUT OF THE HOUSE!  Brent Schmidman, owner of Schmidy's Tavern in Palm Desert, CA, kindly invited us to come down and do a podcast.  And then Greg Nettles, our local Stone Distribution representative, showed up!  We talk craft beer, homebrew, Stone, Beer School and harass random bar patrons (mostly the cute ones).  Beware, it was a busy Wednesday night and there is some music in the background.  Nothing we could do about that.  So to make up for it, we included some new intro and outro clips of Brett's former band, Mr. Jonez.  The intro is from "Where Did You Go?" and the outro is Brett's guitar solo from a song called "Let Me Go."  More podcasts like this to come!  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 13:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast52.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 53: Getting Around To It</title>
		<description> Josh and I, after battling various palate-debilitating illnesses, get around to opening a couple of beers and giving a new piece of recording equipment a whirl.  Sorry about the noise in advance, but we did what we could when we could.  Ringing endorsement, huh?  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 09:40:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast53.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 54: Giving The Bruery Its Due...ery?</title>
		<description> Timely episode where we take an old favorite fall seasonal of ours (Autumn Maple) and a new one (Burly Gourd) and talk about how fucking much we love The Bruery.  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 6 Dec 2011 11:29:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast54.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 55: Schmidy's Time is Here</title>
		<description> It's just after Christmas and we thought it'd be a good idea to visit our favorite local pub for another chat with owner Brent Schmidman at Schmidy's Tavern.  With the help of the lovely Megan and a few pub-goers, we drink some of Brent's fine bottle stash and talk about stuff.  And by stuff, I mean beer.  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2011 11:29:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast55.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 56: Onward and Downward</title>
		<description> The last episode at the apartment finds us opening some interesting beers and finding new favorites.  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 22:15:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast56.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 57: Back To Where It Began</title>
		<description> Josh and Brett come full circle to the place where the podcast began.  And thanks to another kind donation from our Minnesota friend, we are drinking appropriately for the occasion.  Hey, I have an idea: drink along with us!  Cheers! </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 22:15:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast57.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 58: Return of the Schmidy's</title>
		<description> Finally, our friend and fellow homebrewer Chris Anderson joins owner Brent Schmidman to talk to us about plans for making our home-pub into a juggernaut, Chris' brewing history and various stories and anecdotes about things.  In other words: we shoot the shit while drinking top-quality beer.  And, thanks to Josh, we have a new intro.  Let us know what you think! </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 8 Mar 2011 16:15:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast58.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>
<item>

                             <title>Beer Me Podcast Episode 59: Both Halves of the Globe</title>
		<description> Josh and Brett have a free moment and try Sierra Nevada's Harvest ales side by side and blended to dissect what we like best in general, and like about both beers in particular.  All the while we do are usual talking.  I'm sure you'll be delighted that this audio podcast does indeed have talking in it.  And beer.  Ready for some stuff?  Start clicking! </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 8 Mar 2011 16:15:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="http://www.beermepodcast.com/podcasts/beermepodcast59.mp3" length="44573758" type="audio/mpeg"/>

                       </item>

		</channel>
	</rss>