<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Redlands Christian Reformed Church Sermons</title>
    <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons</link>
    <description>Listen to audio sermons from the Redlands Christian Reformed Church</description>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 11:14:36 +1000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 11:14:36 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <category>Sermons</category>
    <itunes:image>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/images/churchlogo.png</itunes:image>
    <itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">
    <itunes:category text="Christianity" />
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
    <itunes:category text="Philosophy" />
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:keywords>God, Religion, Christianity, Jesus, Bible, Church, Gospel, Sermon, Spirituality, Heaven</itunes:keywords>
    <managingEditor>ryan@webdev20.com.au</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>ryan@webdev20.com.au</webMaster>
              <item>
              <title>We're Ambassadors of whom?</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120603pm.mp3</link>
              <description>3rd June 2012 PM
         - Preacher: Ryan Hemelaar
         - Bible Passage: 2 Corinthians 5:17-21
         - &lt;p&gt;Almost every nation in the world commissions certain people to be ambassadors who will represent their nation while residing in another. It's usually a job only for a select few. But the Bible speaks of all Christians being ambassadors as well, with an important responsibility, one that is even higher than representing a country on Earth. What is this responsibility? And who are we representing? This Sunday evening, we're going to explore 2 Corinthians 5:17-21 to find who we are ambassadors for and what task we have in this role.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Ryan Hemelaar)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 18:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120603pm.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120603pm.mp3" length="4964104" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>Who's most important in church?</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120603am.mp3</link>
              <description>3rd June 2012 AM
         - Preacher: Ettiene de Wilzem
         - Bible Passage: 1 Corinthians 12
         - &lt;p&gt;Everywhere we look in society we see that, as people, we arrange ourselves in certain hierarchical patterns. This is important, because without it we would find it hard to function. But what if, in a very subtle way, the importance attached to certain roles in the hierarchy extend beyond mere functionality? In other words, do we view the CEO of a company as more important in the life of the company than a 'normal' employee? Is a principal more important to a school than a teacher? Very often, if not mostly, society does view these 'higher profiles' as actually more important people in the life of the organisation than 'lower profiles'. Whether this is to be desired or not, we can ask the question: what about the church? Who are the most important people in church? As we look at 1 Corinthians 12 this Sunday we'll see what God has to say about these questions&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Ettiene de Wilzem)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 10:30:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120603am.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120603am.mp3" length="8189808" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>Is this Church?</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120527am.mp3</link>
              <description>27th May 2012 AM
         - Preacher: Jack De Vries
         - Bible Passage: 1 Corinthians 9:19-23
         - &lt;p&gt;On this Pentecost Sunday we remember the radical expansion of the early church. Jack De Vries, our denominational Ministry Development Coach, will be teaching this morning on the challenges of reaching the lost for Christ. He will challenge us to think about these questions: will you be a stumbling block or a stepping stone for unbelievers? Will you put up barriers or tear them down for the sake of the gospel? When you reach out to the unbelievers around you, will you expect that they fit into your mold? Or are you willing to change - are you willing to become like them in order to win them? Are you willing to become all things to all people so that by all possible means you might save some?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Jack De Vries)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 10:30:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120527am.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120527am.mp3" length="11398272" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>The Birth of John the Baptist</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120520pm.mp3</link>
              <description>20th May 2012 PM
         - Preacher: Josh Hartog
         - Bible Passage: 
         - &lt;p&gt;Zechariah and Elizabeth's circumstances weren't all that normal, but probably the most abnormal thing about them is how they saw God's activity in their lives and responded with praise. Tonight we're going to examine the story of John's birth and see how, like Zechariah and Elizabeth, God's salvation in Jesus Christ can transform our lives.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Josh Hartog)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 18:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120520pm.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120520pm.mp3" length="7144701" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>God Hears!</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120520am.mp3</link>
              <description>20th May 2012 AM
         - Preacher: Johann Eloff
         - Bible Passage: Galations 3:26
         - </description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Johann Eloff)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 10:30:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120520am.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120520am.mp3" length="10474060" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>Stories of God</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120513pm.mp3</link>
              <description>13th May 2012 PM
         - Preacher: Ettiene De Wilzem
         - Bible Passage: 2 Timothy 3:10-17
         - &lt;p&gt;It's that time of the year again where we stop to listen to the stories of people to whom God has revealed himself. It is in that sense that their testimonies or 'life stories' literally become 'stories of God'. Stories of how God reached out, who he put in place and what experiences led them to accept as adults the truth of the Christian faith as they profess it publicly during this service. Do not miss out on this very special occasion where we witness the hand of God in action!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Ettiene De Wilzem)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 18:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120513pm.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120513pm.mp3" length="6499560" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>God Loves Children!</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120513am.mp3</link>
              <description>13th May 2012 AM
         - Preacher: Ettiene De Wilzem
         - Bible Passage: Matthew 19:13-15
         - &lt;p&gt;When was the last time you did either of the following things: watched an animation movie, played with dolls, defeated trolls or raced toy cars with your children or grandchildren? One of the things we lose when grow older is being excited and enthused like little children over virtually anything, even empty boxes in which a refrigerator came! And while in a certain sense it is wonderful that we grow up and mature, there is also a sense in which we lose certain qualities of children that God really wants us to have! This Sunday, as we hear Jesus' exhortation on children and as we baptise a little child, we will hear more about the childlike qualities God wants us to have. Children are really welcome!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Ettiene De Wilzem)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 10:30:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120513am.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120513am.mp3" length="5336923" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>Living to Please Him</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120506pm.mp3</link>
              <description>6th May 2012 PM
         - Preacher: Ryan Hemelaar
         - Bible Passage: 2 Corinthians 5:1-10
         - &lt;p style=&quot;text-align: -webkit-left;&quot;&gt;In life, we all set goals that we'd like to reach or continue to live by. Whether it be to exercise more, do better in our studies, or simply be happy. These goals can often be the motivating factor for the things we do in life. But sometimes we can mix up which goals are the important ones. The Apostle Paul writes in 2 Corinthians about an overarching goal or aim that has a much bigger impact than losing 20 kilos. Come along this Sunday evening as we explore what this aim is by unpacking God's Word together.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Ryan Hemelaar)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 18:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120506pm.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120506pm.mp3" length="6279108" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>East of Eden</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120506am.mp3</link>
              <description>6th May 2012 AM
         - Preacher: Greg Tenni
         - Bible Passage: Genesis 3 : 21 - 4 :  26
         - &lt;p&gt;In Genesis 4 we see two developing themes. The most obvious theme is the progress of human rebellion and a movement away from God, but behind that picture we also see God at work to bring people back to Him so that sin and death do not have the final say in this world. The garden has been closed, paradise has been lost, and now we need to decide whether to continue wandering away from God, or to turn and accept the forgiveness He offers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Greg Tenni)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 10:30:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120506am.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120506am.mp3" length="9076404" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>The Lord Provides</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120429pm.mp3</link>
              <description>29th April 2012 PM
         - Preacher: Ettiene De Wizem
         - Bible Passage: Jonah 1:17 and Chapter 2
         - &lt;p&gt;Say good bye, these days are gone,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And we can't keep holding on&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When all we need is some relief&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through these hard times (Matchbox Twenty)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Ettiene De Wizem)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 18:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120429pm.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120429pm.mp3" length="6957665" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>Losing My First Love</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120429am.mp3</link>
              <description>29th April 2012 AM
         - Preacher: Bevan Burnes
         - Bible Passage: Revelation 2:1-7
         - &lt;p&gt;First century believers faced stiff opposition from political authorities determined to stop the spread of the Christian gospel. In spite of this, they were able to spread the gospel to &quot;the ends of the earth&quot;. One reason for this was a concentration on reaching cities. In Ephesus, for example, Christian leaders influenced groups of workers who not only 'turned the city upside down', but took the word inland so that &quot;all who dwelt in Asia heard the word of the Lord.&quot; (Acts 19:10). Although John sends his letters to seven churches existing at the end of the first century, the book of Revelation is an open letter to all Christians and churches, including those of us who follow Christ today. What challenges do churches and Christians face today? What words of commendation and warning might Christ say to us and His church today?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Apologies for the poor quality of the recording. We experienced some technical issues.)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Bevan Burnes)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 10:30:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120429am.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120429am.mp3" length="8349469" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>God's call of Discomfort</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120422pm.mp3</link>
              <description>22nd April 2012 PM
         - Preacher: Ettiene de Wilzen
         - Bible Passage: Jonah 1:1-4
         - &lt;p&gt;Christians mostly perceive God as a source of comfort in their lives. This is a well founded perception, since the Bible portrays God as being exactly that, especially in times when injustice and the painful effects of sin really hurts us. But, can God also be a God of discomfort? Can he be the one who calls or even steer us into incredibly uncomfortable situations where we really don't want to be? This questions receives a good answer from the story of a man in the Old Testament called Jonah...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Ettiene de Wilzen)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 18:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120422pm.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120422pm.mp3" length="5325743" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>Learn to be Wise</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120422am.mp3</link>
              <description>22nd April 2012 AM
         - Preacher: Rev Bill Wiersma
         - Bible Passage: Psalm 111
         - &lt;p&gt;The other day someone said that Christians try to please God for fear of ending up in hell if they don't. Not true.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Believers in Christ are so overcome by the fact that God's Son was willing to suffer and die on a cross for their everlasting good, that they wish to break with behaviour that destroys and instead want to live a life that honours God and that shows concern for others. In other words, Christians love because they know they are immensely loved.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Rev Bill Wiersma)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 10:30:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120422am.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120422am.mp3" length="9149652" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>The World in His Hands</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120415pm.mp3</link>
              <description>15th April 2012 PM
         - Preacher: Ettiene De Wilzem
         - Bible Passage: Jonah 1
         - &lt;p&gt;&quot;He's got the whole world, in his hands...&quot; Many of us are familiar with these words from the popular children's song. While we were children and we sing it with the actions, we must confess that the power of it doesn't really strike us unitl we're adults. Does God really hold the whole world in his hands? Does he really have the power to command the sea to calm down and it will do his bidding? Can he really cool down the heat of the sun if he wishes to? Can he control my circumstances in a way that I can see his power over them? These are all great questions that we'll consider on Sunday afternoon as we look at Jonah 1, the first in a four part series on Jonah.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (Ettiene De Wilzem)</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 18:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120415pm.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120415pm.mp3" length="6903643" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                  
              <item>
              <title>God's Presence in our Bitterness</title>
              <link>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120415am.mp3</link>
              <description>15th April 2012 AM
         - Preacher: KJ Tromp (Christian Reformed Church of Mansfield)
         - Bible Passage: Ruth 1: 1-22
         - &lt;p&gt;We often struggle with the idea of suffering in our lives and seeing the goodness of God in our lives. Sometimes we just want to give up on God, take a break from Him and do things our own way because we think it'll go a lot better that way. There was a woman in the Bible called Naomi who got dealt a pretty tough hand and on Sunday we'll have a look at how her story unfolded and how it speaks to our lives.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
              <author>office@redlandscrc.org.au (KJ Tromp (Christian Reformed Church of Mansfield))</author>
              <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 10:30:00 +1000</pubDate>
              <guid>http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120415am.mp3</guid>
              <enclosure url="http://www.redlandscrc.org.au/sermons/20120415am.mp3" length="8949449" type="audio/mpeg" /> 
            </item>
                    </channel>
			</rss>