<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
		<title>Radio Disclosure</title>
		<link>http://www.radiodisclosure.com</link>
		<language>en</language>
		<copyright>	2008 - 2009 Radio Disclosure, radiodisclosure.com</copyright>
		<itunes:subtitle>
		Radio Disclosure is a radio show that explores areas conventional media refuse to cover. It is a close up look at real life stories and documentation of the real stories behind the news. 
		</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:author>Ted Randall &amp; Matt Aaron</itunes:author>
		<itunes:summary>
		The Radio Disclosure Radio Show is focused on a wide area of subjects that range from UFO's Ghosts, The Paranormal, Hauntings, government coverups, medicine, business, ndustry and fruad. From the latest reported government cover up, alien ductions, medical problems, social problems, and the latest in the world of phenomenon. Radio Disclosure uncovers the facts and asks the questions that conventional main stream media refuses to disclose.
Radio Disclosure is hosted by Ted Randall and Matt Aaron and airs on International Shortwave and domestic radio stations.
		</itunes:summary>
		<description>
		The Radio Disclosure Radio Show is focused on a wide area of subjects that range from UFO's Ghosts, The Paranormal, Hauntings, government coverups, medicine, business, ndustry and fruad. From the latest reported government cover up, alien ductions, medical problems, social problems, and the latest in the world of phenomenon. Radio Disclosure uncovers the facts and asks the questions that conventional main stream media refuses to disclose.
Radio Disclosure is hosted by Ted Randall and Matt Aaron and airs on International Shortwave and domestic radio stations.
		</description>
		<itunes:owner>
		<itunes:name>www.radiodisclosure.com</itunes:name>
		<itunes:email>radio@radiodisclosure.com</itunes:email>
		</itunes:owner>
		<itunes:image href="http://www.radiodisclosure.com/icon/rd_icon.jpg" />
		<itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics">
						</itunes:category>
		<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:keywords>UFO,psychics, ghost, medicine, paranormal, phenomenon, hauntings, cattle mutilation, crop circles, government cover up,    </itunes:keywords>
	<image>
	<url>http://www.radiodisclosure.com/icon/rd_icon.jpg</url>
	<title>Radio Disclosure</title>
	<link>http://www.radiodisclosure.com</link>
	</image>
	<ttl>60</ttl>
	
	<item>
<title> Dr. Peter R. Breggin, MD

 
</title>
<link>http://www.radiodisclosure.com/pages/podcasts.php</link>

<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 21:00 -0700</pubDate>
<description>Peter R. Breggin M.D. conducts a private practice of psychiatry in Ithaca , New York , where he treats adults, couples, and families with children. He also does consultations in the field of clinical psychopharmacology and often acts as a medical expert in criminal, malpractice and product liability suits. Before moving to Ithaca in November 2002 he was in practice for nearly thirty-five years in Washington , DC and Bethesda , Maryland . He has written dozens of scientific articles and many professional books, including Medication Madness: The Role of Psychiatric Drugs in Cases of Violence, Suicide and Crime (2008), and is on the editorial board of several journals. In 2010 Dr. Breggin and his wife Ginger formed a new organization that continues their emphasis on bringing professional and laypersons together to share their concerns about the hazards of contemporary biological psychiatry while promoting more caring and empathic approaches to personal conflict and suffering. The new organization will sponsor an annual meeting each April in Syracuse, New York (empathictherapy.org). 

</description>
<enclosure
url="http://radiodisclosure.com/media/shows/breggin.mp3"
length="57640776" type="audio/x-mp3"/>
<itunes:duration>02:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:subtitle> Dr. Peter R. Breggin, MD

</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Peter R. Breggin M.D. conducts a private practice of psychiatry in Ithaca , New York , where he treats adults, couples, and families with children. He also does consultations in the field of clinical psychopharmacology and often acts as a medical expert in criminal, malpractice and product liability suits. Before moving to Ithaca in November 2002 he was in practice for nearly thirty-five years in Washington , DC and Bethesda , Maryland . He has written dozens of scientific articles and many professional books, including Medication Madness: The Role of Psychiatric Drugs in Cases of Violence, Suicide and Crime (2008), and is on the editorial board of several journals.  In 2010 Dr. Breggin and his wife Ginger formed a new organization that continues their emphasis on bringing professional and laypersons together to share their concerns about the hazards of contemporary biological psychiatry while promoting more caring and empathic approaches to personal conflict and suffering. The new organization will sponsor an annual meeting each April in Syracuse, New York (empathictherapy.org). 


</itunes:summary>
</item>
	<item>
<title> Nashville Physician Dr. Bailey along with Linda Moulton Howe

 
</title>
<link>http://www.radiodisclosure.com/pages/podcasts.php</link>

<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 21:00 -0700</pubDate>
<description>Nashville Physician Dr. Bailey relates  the story of a UFO in Orlinda Tennessee that he investigated.
The story he tells involves a UFO sighting along with an encounter at the location with a non human.
Emmy Award winning science reporter Linda Moulton Howe  reports on - Royal Air Force Bentwaters, Royal Air Force Woodbridge and nearby Rendlesham Forest.  Two dozen military personnel, reported unidentified aerial lights and a triangular craft between midnight on December 26th, until 5 AM on December 28th, 1980? Now, Col. Charles I. Halt, the man who was then the Deputy Base Commander at RAF Bentwaters, has gone on the record to say the lights and craft were "extraterrestrial in origin."  Also historian Richard M. Dolan has worked for ten years to produce 3-volumes about the UFO phenomenon. Vol. 2: The Cover-Up Exposed, 1973 - 1991 2009 , was released in August 2009. The third volume will be out in 2010. He comments about the British M.o.D.'s incomplete UFO file releases, 1980 RAF Bentwaters as "extraterrestrial in origin," and the power structure now controlling this planet's policies of denial about non-humans interacting with Earth.

</description>
<enclosure
url="http://radiodisclosure.com/media/shows/disclosure-09-09-09.mp3"
length="57640776" type="audio/x-mp3"/>
<itunes:duration>02:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:subtitle> Nashville Physician Dr. Bailey along with Linda Moulton Howe

</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>
Nashville Physician Dr. Bailey relates  the story of a UFO in Orlinda Tennessee that he investigated.
The story he tells involves a UFO sighting along with an encounter at the location with a non human.
Emmy Award winning science reporter Linda Moulton Howe  reports on - Royal Air Force Bentwaters, Royal Air Force Woodbridge and nearby Rendlesham Forest.  Two dozen military personnel, reported unidentified aerial lights and a triangular craft between midnight on December 26th, until 5 AM on December 28th, 1980? Now, Col. Charles I. Halt, the man who was then the Deputy Base Commander at RAF Bentwaters, has gone on the record to say the lights and craft were "extraterrestrial in origin."  Also historian Richard M. Dolan has worked for ten years to produce 3-volumes about the UFO phenomenon. Vol. 2: The Cover-Up Exposed, 1973 - 1991 2009 , was released in August 2009. The third volume will be out in 2010. He comments about the British M.o.D.'s incomplete UFO file releases, 1980 RAF Bentwaters as "extraterrestrial in origin," and the power structure now controlling this planet's policies of denial about non-humans interacting with Earth.

</itunes:summary>
</item>

	
	<item>
<title> Nuclear Physicist-Lecturer Stanton T. Friedman

 
</title>
<link>http://www.radiodisclosure.com/pages/podcasts.php</link>

<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 21:00 -0700</pubDate>
<description>Nuclear Physicist-Lecturer Stanton T. Friedman received his BSc. and MSc. Degrees in physics from the University of Chicago in 1955 and 1956. He was employed for 14 years as a nuclear physicist by such companies as GE, GM, Westinghouse, TRW Systems, Aerojet General Nucleonics, and McDonnell Douglas working in such highly advanced, classified, eventually cancelled programs as nuclear aircraft, fission and fusion rockets, and various compact nuclear powerplants for space and terrestrial applications.He became interested in UFOs in 1958, and since 1967 has lectured about them at more than 600 colleges and 100 professional groups in 50 U.S. states, 9 Canadian provinces and 16 other countries in addition to various nuclear consulting efforts. He has published more than 90 UFO papers and has appeared on hundreds of radio and TV programs including on Larry King in 2007 and twice in 2008, and many documentaries. He is the original civilian investigator of the Roswell Incident and co-authored “Crash at Corona: The Definitive Study of the Roswell Incident.” “TOP SECRET/MAJIC,” his controversial book about the Majestic 12 group, established in 1947 to deal with alien technology, was published in 1996 and went through 6 printings. An expanded new edition was published in 2005. Stan was presented with a Lifetime UFO Achievement Award in Leeds, England, in 2002, by UFO Magazine of the UK. He is co-author with Kathleen Marden (Betty Hill’s niece) of a book in 2007: “Captured! The Betty and Barney Hill UFO Experience.” The City of Fredericton, New Brunswick, declared August 27, 2007, Stanton Friedman Day. His new book “Flying Saucers and Science” was published in June 2008 and is in its 3rd printing.
</description>
<enclosure
url="http://radiodisclosure.com/media/shows/disclosure-08-26-09.mp3"
length="57640776" type="audio/x-mp3"/>
<itunes:duration>02:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:subtitle>  Nuclear Physicist-Lecturer Stanton T. Friedman

</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Nuclear Physicist-Lecturer Stanton T. Friedman received his BSc. and MSc. Degrees in physics from the University of Chicago in 1955 and 1956. He was employed for 14 years as a nuclear physicist by such companies as GE, GM, Westinghouse, TRW Systems, Aerojet General Nucleonics, and McDonnell Douglas working in such highly advanced, classified, eventually cancelled programs as nuclear aircraft, fission and fusion rockets, and various compact nuclear powerplants for space and terrestrial applications.He became interested in UFOs in 1958, and since 1967 has lectured about them at more than 600 colleges and 100 professional groups in 50 U.S. states, 9 Canadian provinces and 16 other countries in addition to various nuclear consulting efforts. He has published more than 90 UFO papers and has appeared on hundreds of radio and TV programs including on Larry King in 2007 and twice in 2008, and many documentaries. He is the original civilian investigator of the Roswell Incident and co-authored “Crash at Corona: The Definitive Study of the Roswell Incident.” “TOP SECRET/MAJIC,” his controversial book about the Majestic 12 group, established in 1947 to deal with alien technology, was published in 1996 and went through 6 printings. An expanded new edition was published in 2005. Stan was presented with a Lifetime UFO Achievement Award in Leeds, England, in 2002, by UFO Magazine of the UK. He is co-author with Kathleen Marden (Betty Hill’s niece) of a book in 2007: “Captured! The Betty and Barney Hill UFO Experience.” The City of Fredericton, New Brunswick, declared August 27, 2007, Stanton Friedman Day. His new book “Flying Saucers and Science” was published in June 2008 and is in its 3rd printing.
</itunes:summary>
</item>
	<item>
<title> Emmy Winning Science reporter Linda Moulton Howe in an exclusive interview with Ted Randall 

 
</title>
<link>http://www.radiodisclosure.com/pages/podcasts.php</link>

<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 21:00 -0700</pubDate>
<description>Emmy Winning Science reporter Linda Moulton Howe in an exclusive interview with Ted Randall talks about her beginnings as a professional reporter reporting on the unexplained.  Linda Moulton Howe is a graduate of Stanford University with a Masters Degree in Communication. She has devoted her documentary film, television and radio career to productions concerning science, medicine and the environment. Ms. Howe has received local, national and international awards, including three regional Emmys and a national Emmy nomination. Those films have included Poison in the Wind and A Sun Kissed Poison which compared smog pollution in Los Angeles and Denver; Fire In The Water about hydrogen as an alternative energy source to fossil fuels; A Radioactive Water about uranium contamination of public drinking water in a Denver suburb; and A Strange Harvest which explored the worldwide animal mutilation mystery which has haunted the United States and other countries from the mid-20th century to date. Linda has written four books: An Alien Harvest which investigates the worldwide animal mutilation phenomenon and Glimpses of Other Realities, Volumes I and II which concern U.S. military, intelligence and civilian testimonies about other forces that interact with earth life. Her fourth book, Mysterious Lights and Crop Circles, was updated in a 2nd Edition with expanded 2001 content and released in July 2002. It is an investigative report about scientific research of unusual formations in cereal crops and grasses around the world and videotapes, photographs and eyewitness descriptions of mysterious small lights associated with the enigmatic crop formations. Linda continues to write, produce and speak at national and international conferences and symposiums, including NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center. In addition to producing, reporting and editing Earthfiles.com, she also produces, writes and reports for television and radio, including segments on The Discovery Channel and weekly science, environment and earth mystery news for the nationally syndicated Clear Channel's Coast to Coast AM 
</description>
<enclosure
url="http://radiodisclosure.com/media/shows/disclosure-07-22-09.mp3"
length="57640776" type="audio/x-mp3"/>
<itunes:duration>02:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:subtitle>  Emmy Winning Science reporter Linda Moulton Howe in an exclusive interview with Ted Randall 

</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Emmy Winning Science reporter Linda Moulton Howe in an exclusive interview with Ted Randall talks about her beginnings as a professional reporter reporting on the unexplained.  Linda Moulton Howe is a graduate of Stanford University with a Masters Degree in Communication. She has devoted her documentary film, television and radio career to productions concerning science, medicine and the environment. Ms. Howe has received local, national and international awards, including three regional Emmys and a national Emmy nomination. Those films have included Poison in the Wind and A Sun Kissed Poison which compared smog pollution in Los Angeles and Denver; Fire In The Water about hydrogen as an alternative energy source to fossil fuels; A Radioactive Water about uranium contamination of public drinking water in a Denver suburb; and A Strange Harvest which explored the worldwide animal mutilation mystery which has haunted the United States and other countries from the mid-20th century to date. Linda has written four books: An Alien Harvest which investigates the worldwide animal mutilation phenomenon and Glimpses of Other Realities, Volumes I and II which concern U.S. military, intelligence and civilian testimonies about other forces that interact with earth life. Her fourth book, Mysterious Lights and Crop Circles, was updated in a 2nd Edition with expanded 2001 content and released in July 2002. It is an investigative report about scientific research of unusual formations in cereal crops and grasses around the world and videotapes, photographs and eyewitness descriptions of mysterious small lights associated with the enigmatic crop formations. Linda continues to write, produce and speak at national and international conferences and symposiums, including NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center. In addition to producing, reporting and editing Earthfiles.com, she also produces, writes and reports for television and radio, including segments on The Discovery Channel and weekly science, environment and earth mystery news for the nationally syndicated Clear Channel's Coast to Coast AM 
</itunes:summary>
</item>
	<item>
<title> Jackie Mari a Professional PSYCHIC, NumAstrologist along with Linda Moulton Howe

 
</title>
<link>http://www.radiodisclosure.com/pages/podcasts.php</link>

<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 21:00 -0700</pubDate>
<description>Emmy award winning science reporter Linda Moulton Howe with her current report for Radio Disclosure After three months of English crop formations seeming to forecast July 7, 2009, solar activity on the Sun, the most intense sunspot activity in nearly three years of an abnormally quiet sun occurred within 48 hours of July 7. Retired astrophysicist Mike Reed talks Linda about the implications.  
Jackie Mari a Professional PSYCHIC, NumAstrologist [combining Astrology with Numerology], Master Numerologist, KarmAstrologist and PERSONAL PSYCHIC CONSULTANT, GhostTALK is so very special. It's what you need to know about Ghosts, especially "bridging." We think you will be quite surprised by what you read. It's an education, a "thinker," and an opportunity to learn how to make your own "contact" with a ghost in your life. Most often they're here to help. Ghosts are real, and they can be dealt with. Who better to do it but yourself?
</description>
<enclosure
url="http://radiodisclosure.com/media/shows/disclosure-06-03-09.mp3"
length="57640776" type="audio/x-mp3"/>
<itunes:duration>02:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:subtitle>  Jackie Mari a Professional PSYCHIC, NumAstrologist along with Linda Moulton Howe


</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Emmy award winning science reporter Linda Moulton Howe with her current report for Radio Disclosure After three months of English crop formations seeming to forecast July 7, 2009, solar activity on the Sun, the most intense sunspot activity in nearly three years of an abnormally quiet sun occurred within 48 hours of July 7. Retired astrophysicist Mike Reed talks Linda about the implications.  
Jackie Mari a Professional PSYCHIC, NumAstrologist [combining Astrology with Numerology], Master Numerologist, KarmAstrologist and PERSONAL PSYCHIC CONSULTANT, GhostTALK is so very special. It's what you need to know about Ghosts, especially "bridging." We think you will be quite surprised by what you read. It's an education, a "thinker," and an opportunity to learn how to make your own "contact" with a ghost in your life. Most often they're here to help. Ghosts are real, and they can be dealt with. Who better to do it but yourself?
</itunes:summary>
</item>
	<item>
<title> Dr. Patrick Heron And Linda Moulton Howe

 
</title>
<link>http://www.radiodisclosure.com/pages/podcasts.php</link>

<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 21:00 -0700</pubDate>
<description>Emmy award winning science reporter Linda Moulton Howe with her current report on Radio Disclosure. 
A 300-foot-long, silent, triangle-shaped aircraft was seen by Challis, Idaho, hunters close to their camp trailer around 9:15 PM on September 27, 2000. Their illustrations of the mysterious triangle craft match another triangle drawing in a 1954 War Department training manual about extraterrestrial entities and technology, recovery and disposal.  
Dr. Patrick Heron was born in Dublin in 1952. When he was 24 years old, he had a "Saul on the road to Damascus" type of epiphany while reading the Bible. Thus began his Christian walk. He became interested in bible prophecy concerning the "end times" about 1996.
In 1997, his first book Apocalypse Soon was published and became a bestseller in Ireland. It entered the Irish bestsellers list after an interview with Gareth O'Callaghan, on RTE radio, who said he "read it in one sitting and was gripped." Another book The Apocalypse Generation was also a success.
There has recently been amazing interest to-date in this new book The Nephilim and the Pyramid of the Apocalypse, published by Kensington Publishing, which Patrick believes is the FIRST EVER book proving overwhelmingly who built the pyramids and why.
Patrick has a B.Sc. and M.A. in Business Studies from Trinity College, Dublin.
He also holds a Degree in Theology and recently received an Honorary Doctorate in Christian Literature from the California Pacific School of Theology, Glendale, California, as a result of the research done in his book, The Nephilim and the Pyramid of the Apocalypse (Kensington Publishing).
Dr. Heron is the Executive Producer of a TV special entitled Apocalypse and the End Times which is a Grizzly Adams production. This has been shown all over the United States and is currently available on DVD in stores nationwide.
Patrick owns and runs his own company in Dublin, Ireland, where he lives with his family. He is not associated with any particular church or denomination.
</description>
<enclosure
url="http://radiodisclosure.com/media/shows/disclosure-06-03-09.mp3"
length="57640776" type="audio/x-mp3"/>
<itunes:duration>02:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:subtitle>  Dr. Patrick Heron And Linda Moulton Howe


</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Emmy award winning science reporter Linda Moulton Howe with her current report on Radio Disclosure. 
A 300-foot-long, silent, triangle-shaped aircraft was seen by Challis, Idaho, hunters close to their camp trailer around 9:15 PM on September 27, 2000. Their illustrations of the mysterious triangle craft match another triangle drawing in a 1954 War Department training manual about extraterrestrial entities and technology, recovery and disposal.  
Dr. Patrick Heron was born in Dublin in 1952. When he was 24 years old, he had a "Saul on the road to Damascus" type of epiphany while reading the Bible. Thus began his Christian walk. He became interested in bible prophecy concerning the "end times" about 1996.
In 1997, his first book Apocalypse Soon was published and became a bestseller in Ireland. It entered the Irish bestsellers list after an interview with Gareth O'Callaghan, on RTE radio, who said he "read it in one sitting and was gripped." Another book The Apocalypse Generation was also a success.
There has recently been amazing interest to-date in this new book The Nephilim and the Pyramid of the Apocalypse, published by Kensington Publishing, which Patrick believes is the FIRST EVER book proving overwhelmingly who built the pyramids and why.
Patrick has a B.Sc. and M.A. in Business Studies from Trinity College, Dublin.
He also holds a Degree in Theology and recently received an Honorary Doctorate in Christian Literature from the California Pacific School of Theology, Glendale, California, as a result of the research done in his book, The Nephilim and the Pyramid of the Apocalypse (Kensington Publishing).
Dr. Heron is the Executive Producer of a TV special entitled Apocalypse and the End Times which is a Grizzly Adams production. This has been shown all over the United States and is currently available on DVD in stores nationwide.
Patrick owns and runs his own company in Dublin, Ireland, where he lives with his family. He is not associated with any particular church or denomination.
</itunes:summary>
</item>
	<item>
<title> Linda Moulton Howe along with Scott and Suzanne Ramsey

 
</title>
<link>http://www.radiodisclosure.com/pages/podcasts.php</link>

<pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 08:21:00 -0700</pubDate>
<description>Linda Moulton Howe presents her current report this week for Radio Disclosure? A California security guard saw the dark silhouette like the side of a nose cone in the falling space debris near Needles, California, on May 14, 2008. Four months later in August, he saw UFOs that convinced him there are vehicles above Earth that can respond to human thought.
Scott and Suzanne Ramsey have been researching the alleged crash of a UFO in Aztec New Mexico in 1948 for over 18 years! Assumed to be a hoax by UFO researcher Frank Scully, they figuring it would be an open and shut case, the Ramsey's discovered a lot more than they had bargained for. Another little known fact is that they have also done some research into the alleged ET base under the Archuleta Mesa, near Dulce New Mexico. We will be talking about some of their amazing and revealing discoveries. Visit their site at: http://www.aztec1948.com/ 
</description>
<enclosure
url="http://radiodisclosure.com/media/shows/disclosure-04-22-09.mp3"
length="57640776" type="audio/x-mp3"/>
<itunes:duration>02:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:subtitle>  Linda Moulton Howe along with Scott and Suzanne Ramsey


</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Linda Moulton Howe presents her current report this week for Radio Disclosure? A California security guard saw the dark silhouette like the side of a nose cone in the falling space debris near Needles, California, on May 14, 2008. Four months later in August, he saw UFOs that convinced him there are vehicles above Earth that can respond to human thought.
Scott and Suzanne Ramsey have been researching the alleged crash of a UFO in Aztec New Mexico in 1948 for over 18 years! Assumed to be a hoax by UFO researcher Frank Scully, they figuring it would be an open and shut case, the Ramsey's discovered a lot more than they had bargained for. Another little known fact is that they have also done some research into the alleged ET base under the Archuleta Mesa, near Dulce New Mexico. We will be talking about some of their amazing and revealing discoveries. Visit their site at: http://www.aztec1948.com/ 
</itunes:summary>
</item>
	<item>
<title> Dr. Jayson Rand on planet X and the end of the Mayan Celestial Calendar 21 December 2012. 

 
</title>
<link>http://www.radiodisclosure.com/pages/podcasts.php</link>

<pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 08:21:00 -0700</pubDate>
<description>Dr. Jason Q. Rand received his Honorary Ph.D. in the field of Energy Informative Sciences at the Academy of Energy Informative Sciences through Moscow University, Russia. His contributions in the study and pursuit of Extraterrestrial Communications, research into UFO phenomena, cosmology, and his representing the United States at The First World UFO Congress (Tucson, AZ, 1991), earned him distinctive recognition and his Doctorate from the Russian Academy of Sciences. In support of Rand's creative writing projects based on his Planet-X education and entertainment concepts, he's written three teleplays designed as television pilots for weekly series or adaptation to feature films. He travels widely, establishing close ties with his fellow UFOlogists and paranormal researchers worldwide and especially in Russia where Rand has close ties to Lt. Col. Marina Popovich and her former husband, 3-Star Army General Pavel Popovich.

</description>
<enclosure
url="http://www.radiodisclosure.com/media/shows/disclosure-03-25-09.mp3"
length="57640776" type="audio/x-mp3"/>
<itunes:duration>02:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:subtitle> Dr. Jayson Rand on planet X and the end of the Mayan Celestial Calendar 21 December 2012. 


</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Dr. Jason Q. Rand received his Honorary Ph.D. in the field of Energy Informative Sciences at the Academy of Energy Informative Sciences through Moscow University, Russia. His contributions in the study and pursuit of Extraterrestrial Communications, research into UFO phenomena, cosmology, and his representing the United States at The First World UFO Congress (Tucson, AZ, 1991), earned him distinctive recognition and his Doctorate from the Russian Academy of Sciences. In support of Rand's creative writing projects based on his Planet-X education and entertainment concepts, he's written three teleplays designed as television pilots for weekly series or adaptation to feature films. He travels widely, establishing close ties with his fellow UFOlogists and paranormal researchers worldwide and especially in Russia where Rand has close ties to Lt. Col. Marina Popovich and her former husband, 3-Star Army General Pavel Popovich.

</itunes:summary>
</item>
	
	<item>
<title>  The new wave of homelessness, unemployed families looking for work while living in tent cities.

 
</title>
<link>http://www.radiodisclosure.com/pages/podcasts.php</link>

<pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 08:21:00 -0700</pubDate>
<description>Radio Disclosure explores the new homeless in the United States. The plight of middle class American families that have lost jobs and homes, depleted savings. Now this new wave of families sweeping the nation are job hunting with no releif while living with their families in tent cities located all over the US. Zoilo Torres, the director of the Emergency Shelter Network for the Partnership for the Homeless in New York City, News from Phil Kwiatkowski of Chicago's Pacific Garden Mission and Don Worrell with the Nashville Rescue Mission.

</description>
<enclosure
url="http://www.radiodisclosure.com/media/shows/disclosure-03-19-09.mp3"
length="57640776" type="audio/x-mp3"/>
<itunes:duration>02:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:subtitle> The new wave of homelessness, unemployed families looking for work while living in tent cities.


</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Radio Disclosure explores the new homeless in the United States. The plight of middle class American families that have lost jobs and homes, depleted savings. Now this new wave of families sweeping the nation are job hunting with no releif while living with their families in tent cities located all over the US. Zoilo Torres, the director of the Emergency Shelter Network for the Partnership for the Homeless in New York City, News from Phil Kwiatkowski of Chicago's Pacific Garden Mission and Don Worrell with the Nashville Rescue Mission.

</itunes:summary>
</item>
	
<atom:link href="http://www.radiodisclosure.com/rss/radio_dis.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />		
</channel>
</rss>