<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
 
 <channel>
<ttl>60</ttl>
  <title>GIS and Location Technology</title>
  <description>Commentary on the latest trends and interesting applications in the GIS and Spatial Information Management</description>
  <link>http://www.fargeo.com</link>
  <language>en-us</language>
  <copyright>Copyright 2006-2007</copyright>
  <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 11:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
  <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2006 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
  <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
  <webMaster>info@fargeo.com</webMaster>

  <itunes:author>Farallon Geographics</itunes:author>
  <itunes:subtitle>Commentary on the latest trends and interesting applications in the GIS and Spatial Information Management</itunes:subtitle>
  <itunes:summary>No one does a better job of explaining GIS and location-based technology than the team from Farallon Geographics. Join us for our presentations and discussions on the latest trends and interesting applications in the GIS, Location Intelligence, and Spatial Information Management Industry. </itunes:summary>

  <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Farallon Geographics</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>info@fargeo.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>

<itunes:image href="http://www.fargeo.com/images/farallon_itunes.png"/>
  
<itunes:category text="Technology">
   <itunes:category text="Podcasting"/>
</itunes:category>

<item>
<title>GIS &amp; Location Technology Episode 10 - Forecasting and the Value of  Spatially-enabled Databases</title>
<link>http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_episode10.mp3</link>
<description>Spatially-enabled databases can be used to streamline decision support for resource management. This presentation describes an example that automates data interchange between a cost modeling application, GIS database, and pavement scenario manager.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_episode10.mp3" length="28759888" type="audio/mpeg" />
<category>Podcasts</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 10:30:00 -0500</pubDate>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>Spatially-enabled databases can be used to streamline decision support for resource management. An example is presented which automates data interchange between a cost modeling application, GIS database, and pavement scenario manager.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This presentation from CalGIS 2007 highlights the advantage of using enterprise GIS to support critical decisions about resource allocation for asset management by demonstrating Farallon's "Project Selection" pavement management application. This application offers a simple interface that enables GIS novices to import pavement "what if" scenarios from a pavement management program, view them on a map, and then analyze various pavement treatment decisions against budget scenarios.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>00:23:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>GIS, pavement management, streetsaver,costing,Location Technology,Intergraph,ESRI,Oracle, database, geodatabase, business,GIS server</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>GIS &amp; Location Technology Episode 9 - GIS 2.0 -  Squeezing New Value from Old GIS</title>
<link>http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_episode9.mp3</link>
<description>Decentralized databases, open source components and non-traditional visualization tools can enhance the value of an existing GIS.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_episode9.mp3" length="33216377" type="audio/mpeg" />
<category>Podcasts</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 10:20:00 -0500</pubDate>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>Decentralized databases and non-traditional visualization tools can enhance the value of an existing GIS.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This presentation from CalGIS 2007 explores innovative strategies and technologies that will enhance the value of investment in GIS. It discusses how forward-looking strategies such as decentralized databases, open source components and non-traditional visualization tools can optimize the value of GIS.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>00:27:39</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>GIS, Location Technology, Microsoft Virtual Earth, Google Earth,Oracle, database, geodatabase, business,GIS server</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>GIS &amp; Location Technology Episode 8 - Fast, Easy and Convenient -  The value proposition for Enterprise GIS mashups</title>
<link>http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_episode8.mp3</link>
<description>Google Maps, Google Earth, Microsoft Virtual Earth and other emerging technologies can be integrated with traditional GIS tools to deliver useful and targeted "enterprise mashups".</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_episode8.mp3" length="38470124" type="audio/mpeg" />
<category>Podcasts</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 10:10:00 -0500</pubDate>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>Google Maps, Google Earth, Microsoft Virtual Earth and other emerging technologies can be integrated with traditional GIS tools to deliver useful and targeted "enterprise mashups".</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This presentation from CalGIS 2007 explores how Google Maps, Google Earth, MS Virtual Earth and other emerging technologies can be integrated with traditional GIS tools such as geodatabases and ArcGIS server to deliver useful applications to broad user communities. These "enterprise mashups" promise to dramatically improve the dissemination of GIS data and analyses to people while significantly reducing the cost of deploying and maintaining GIS.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>00:32:02</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>GIS, Location Technology, Microsoft Virtual Earth, mashup, mapping,spatial,Google Earth,Oracle, database, geodatabase, business,GIS server</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>GIS &amp; Location Technology Episode 7 - The Relevance of Emerging Geospatial Technologies for IT</title>
<link>http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_episode7.mp3</link>
<description>This recent presentation discusses how organizations can leverage spatially aware databases, free mapping API's like Google Earth, and open source software like Autodesk Mapguide,  to manage data, integrate systems, and deliver compelling geospatial applications for a fraction of the cost of traditional GIS.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_episode7.mp3" length="57153743" type="audio/mpeg" />
<category>Podcasts</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 10:30:00 -0500</pubDate>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>This recent presentation discusses how organizations can leverage spatially aware databases, free mapping API's like Google Earth, and open source software like Autodesk Mapguide,  to manage data, integrate systems, and deliver compelling geospatial applications for a fraction of the cost of traditional GIS.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>IT professionals have long recognized that geodata (geographically referenced information such as parcels, streets, addresses, and aerial photographs) represent a common information asset needed across departmental and agency boundaries. Unfortunately, managing, analyzing, and publishing geodata have often required expensive and complex GIS software solutions. However, new and emerging low-cost and no-cost IT technologies now promise to take GIS out of the back-office and unlock new potential from your geodata investment. Using familiar IT tools and strategies such as databases, web services, and XML, organizations can deploy GIS solutions that leverage spatially aware relational database management systems like Oracle Express, free SOA-based mapping API's like Google Maps and Google Earth, and open source software like Autodesk Mapguide to manage data, integrate systems, and deliver compelling geospatial applications for a fraction of the cost of traditional GIS.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>00:47:36</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>GIS, Location Technology, Microsoft Virtual Earth, Google Earth,Oracle, database, geodatabase, business,GIS server</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>GIS &amp; Location Technology Episode 6 - Public mapping technology and private data: can we have the best of both worlds?</title>
<link>http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_episode6.mp3</link>
<description>With the release of the latest version of Microsoft Virtual Earth,  it is more apparent than ever, that open mapping technology can offer competitive tools for GIS professionals. We discuss when you should consider using one of these public mapping solutions, and how they can be integrated with in-house GIS data. </description>
<enclosure url="http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_episode6.mp3" length="26145347" type="audio/mpeg" />
<category>Podcasts</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 nov 2006 10:30:00 -0500</pubDate>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>Public Mapping APIs offer speed, lower development costs, and simplicity. Farallon discusses how to seamlessly transition from the regional map titling scheme in public APIs to local and detailed map tiling using enterprise GIS software and in-house GIS data.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>With the release of the latest version of Microsoft Virtual Earth,  it is more apparent than ever, that open mapping technology can offer competitive tools for GIS professionals. We discuss when you should consider using one of these public mapping solutions, and how they can be integrated with in-house GIS data.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>00:21:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>GIS, Location Technology, Microsoft Virtual Earth, Google Earth,Oracle, database, geodatabase, business,GIS server</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>GIS &amp; Location Technology Episode 5 - Why use a mashup when you already have a GIS?</title>
<link>http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_082806.mp3</link>
<description>Everyone seems to be taking an interest in mashups. Although the uses are diverse, the common thread is that they use location and maps as a theme, and they provide a simple visual interface for decision support. From a GIS perspective, when would it be desirable to use a mashup? We give an example of landslide hazard analysis in the Bay Area.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_082806.mp3" length="10286377" type="audio/mpeg" />
<category>Podcasts</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 10:30:00 -0500</pubDate>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>Mashup can be combined with back end geo-processing to offer enhanced scalability and speed along with lower cost and a more intuitive user interface.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Everyone seems to be taking an interest in mashups. Although the uses are diverse, the common thread is that they use location and maps as a theme, and they provide a simple visual interface for decision support. From a GIS perspective, when would it be desirable to use a mashup? We give an example of landslide hazard analysis in the Bay Area.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>00:20:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>GIS, Location Technology, Mashup, Google Earth,Oracle, database, geodatabase, business,GIS server</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>GIS &amp; Location Technology Episode 4 - What is a geospatially-aware database and why should you care? A first look at Oracle Spatial</title>
<link>http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_061406.mp3</link>
<description>At Farallon we receive a lot of questions about geodatabases, spatially aware databases, and in particular, about Oracle Spatial. In this episode we look at what it means for a database to be spatially-aware, and how this translates to enhanced data validity, finer control over user permissions, and easier access for web developers.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_061406.mp3" length="7932746" type="audio/mpeg" />
<category>Podcasts</category>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 June 2006 10:30:00 -0500</pubDate>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>Spatially aware databases such as Oracle Spatial can offer enhanced data validity, finer control over level of access and 
user privileges, and ease of use for web developers who are not familar with geo-coding.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>At Farallon we receive a lot of questions about geodatabases, spatially aware databases, and in particular, about Oracle Spatial. In this episode we look at what it means for a database to be spatially-aware, and how this translates to enhanced data validity, finer control over user permissions, and easier access for web developers.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>00:15:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>GIS, Location Technology, Oracle Spatial, database, Oracle, geodatabase, GIS server</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>GIS &amp; Location Technology Episode 3 - Is there such a thing as 3D GIS?</title>
<link>http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_051106.mp3</link>
<description>There is a lot of buzz around geospatial 3D right now. This is most recently highlighted by all of the news and speculation surrounding the combination of Google Earth and their free Sketchup 3D modeling software. The expanding interest in 3D and its relevance to GIS may reflect a growing fundamental change in how we work with geospatial information.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_051106.mp3" length="9199360" type="audio/mpeg" />
<category>Podcasts</category>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2006 10:30:00 -0500</pubDate>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>3D interfaces to 2D GIS vs 3D GIS. The value of modeling volumes for location mapping. 3D as the presentation technology to reduce the level of abstraction in GIS data (e.g. Google Earth).</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>There is a lot of buzz around geospatial 3D right now. This is most recently highlighted by all of the news and speculation surrounding the combination of Google Earth and their free Sketchup 3D modeling software. The expanding interest in 3D and its relevance to GIS may reflect a growing fundamental change in how we work with geospatial information.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>00:18:10</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>GIS, Location Technology, Google Earth, Virtual Earth, ESRI Arc3D, 3D, Maps, Sketchup</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>GIS &amp; Location Technology Episode 2 - Interview with Mike Tait, Director of Internet Solutions at ESRI</title>
<link>http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_032806.mp3</link>
<description>ArcWeb Services offers on demand geospatial capabilities to businesses. ArcWeb Explorer goes beyond Google Earth with backend geoprocessing, easier mashups, Flash and SVG graphics. GIS in the future will be less about mapping and more about background geoprocessing that uses SOA to integrate into business analysis.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_032806.mp3" length="19256985" type="audio/mpeg" />
<category>Podcasts</category>
<pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2006 11:30:00 -0500</pubDate>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>ESRI and Farallon discuss on demand GIS using webservices, ArcWeb Explorer vs. Google Earth, and the future of GIS in mainstream business</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>ArcWeb Services offers on demand geospatial capabilities to businesses. ArcWeb Explorer goes beyond Google Earth with backend geoprocessing, easier mashups, Flash and SVG graphics. GIS in the future will be less about mapping and more about background geoprocessing that uses SOA to integrate into business analysis.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>00:37:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>GIS, Location Technology, Google Earth, Spatial Information Management, Maps, ArcWeb, ESRI, Web Services</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>GIS &amp; Location Technology Episode 1 - Autodesk and Open Source, GIS vs. SIM, Google Earth and the GIS industry</title>
<link>http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_020806.mp3</link>
<description>Autodesk GIS Web mapping server goes open source - what this means and what is their motivation. GIS vs Spatial Information Management (SIM) - how are they different. Google Earth - why is it cool and how is it transforming GIS from the realm of specialists to mainstream IT.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.fargeo.com/podcasts/GIS_&amp;_Location_Technology_020806.mp3" length="10512729" type="audio/mpeg" />
<category>Podcasts</category>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2006 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>Autodesk GIS Web mapping server goes open source. GIS vs Spatial Information Management. The impact of Google Earth on GIS </itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Autodesk GIS Web mapping server goes open source - what this means and what is their motivation. GIS vs Spatial Information Management (SIM) - how are they different. Google Earth - why is it cool and how is it transforming GIS from the realm of specialists to mainstream IT. </itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>00:20:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>GIS, Location Technology, Google Earth, Spatial Information Management, Maps</itunes:keywords>

</item>

</channel>

</rss>