<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Nate and Di Show</title>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com</link>
<description>A Front Butt Studios Production</description>
<itunes:subtitle>A Front Butt Studios Production</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Online since April 2005, NaD is an irreverent mix of liberal comedic social commentary performed using a unique talk-reality sketch format. We call it Gonzo Reality Infotainment. 
You call it whatever you will.  

Shows will be added to the feed occasionally,  so stay subscribed!  
</itunes:summary>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>2005 Nate and Di Show</copyright>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Nate and Di</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>webmaster@nateanddi.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<image>
<url>http://www.nateanddi.com/images/HEADSHOT7SMALL.JPG</url> 
  <title>Nate and Di Show</title> 
  <link>http://www.nateanddi.com</link> 
  </image>
<webMaster>webmaster@nateanddi.com</webMaster>
<category>Humor</category>
<itunes:category text="Comedy">
</itunes:category>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>

<item>
<title>Nate and Di are back online.</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>The Nate and Di Show maybe be on hiatus, but Nate and Di are back online.  If you are interested in keeping up with their unusual antics, then visit www.nateanddi.com, and subscribe to their new feed.  This feed may be updated again at some point in the future, so stay subscribed for when we do. </description>
<itunes:subtitle>Nate and Di are back online.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>The Nate and Di Show maybe be on hiatus, but Nate and Di are back online.  If you are interested in keeping up with their unusual antics, then visit www.nateanddi.com, and subscribe to their new feed.  This feed may be updated again at some point in the future, so stay subscribed for when we do. </itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 18:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism, atheism, bible</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 88: Smokin with Jebus - the Returnisode.</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD07-13-07.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=159</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Podcastings most insane and irreverent gonzo couple have re-entered the realm of pod.  Despite the fact that the real Nate and Di stop by to whine like a couple of bleeding-heart liberals and chastise us for our blasphemous shenanigans before we even start, we are pushing the envelope on our return episode and are holding no punches.  Join us for the first time in 366 days as we pick up where we left off with some wise-ass chicanery and discover a new use for the Good Book in a response to a recent Supreme Court Decision about Jesus and our favorite sacramental herb. </description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 88: Smokin with Jebus - the Returnisode.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Podcastings most insane and irreverent gonzo couple have re-entered the realm of pod.  Despite the fact that the real Nate and Di stop by to whine like a couple of bleeding-heart liberals and chastise us for our blasphemous shenanigans before we even start, we are pushing the envelope on our return episode and are holding no punches.  Join us for the first time in 366 days as we pick up where we left off with some wise-ass chicanery and discover a new use for the Good Book in a response to a recent Supreme Court Decision about Jesus and our favorite sacramental herb.  Oh, and one last thing... if you believe for even a second that the real NaD are gonna stop us from getting on our own God-damned show, it aint gonna happen... They will be choked in their sleep if they try any of that bullshit ever again.  Thanks for listening, people.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD07-13-07.mp3" length="19238717" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2007 04:20:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:19:58</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism, atheism, bible</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 87: The Elevator Goes Up and Down</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD07-12-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=142</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>We are back. And just like an elevator ride, this one is all over the place. We join you as Di has just finished over 4 cups of coffee, so please excuse the added energy level. Today, we share tales from our month-long Hiatal Holiday from the podcast and catch everyone up with the happenings at Front Butt. Listen in as we discuss hackers, growing our garden oasis, tell you how to hatch some of your very own prehistoric beasts, welcome some new blood to The 138, and go on an elevator ride NaD-Style. The messages are also back with a vengence, so leave us one for a future show.  Dont forget, the Podcasting and Portable Media Expo is almost 2 months away, so help us make it out there by making a donation of any amount, and we will send you some shit from Front Butt. We will be back again this weekend, so listen now, while it is fresh.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 87: The Elevator Goes Up and Down</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We are back. And just like an elevator ride, this one is all over the place. We join you as Di has just finished over 4 cups of coffee, so please excuse the added energy level. Today, we share tales from our month-long Hiatal Holiday from the podcast and catch everyone up with the happenings at Front Butt. Listen in as we discuss hackers, growing our garden oasis, tell you how to hatch some of your very own prehistoric beasts, welcome some new blood to The 138, and go on an elevator ride NaD-Style. The messages are also back with a vengence, so leave us one for a future show.  Dont forget, the Podcasting and Portable Media Expo is almost 2 months away, so help us make it out there by making a donation of any amount, and we will send you some shit from Front Butt. We will be back again this weekend, so listen now, while it is fresh.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD07-12-06.mp3" length="47246786" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2006 13:01:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:49:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism, triops, prehistoric</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 86: The Ghosts That Haunt Us</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD06-06-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=140</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Not what one might expect from us on 06-06-06, but we decided to stray from the flock and totally ignore the sinister significance of the date... Instead, we share some ghosts from our past and give you this somewhat unusually formatted episode of NaD. Five Years ago last weekend, we found ourselves homeless and unemployed in the same day after the owners of a drive-in theater we were managing decided to close the doors forever. June 6 also happens to be the 80th anniversary of the first drive in theater, so join us as we take a trip down memory lane and take a tour of the Keysville Drive-In, our former home and place of business, following half a decade of total neglect. Throughout this sound-seeing tour, we discuss how we came to work for the drive-in, share a few stories about our experiences, and even tell some of the gory details of the demise of an American icon. We will Return back to a more normal show on episode 87 with a bottle of absinthe, more classic Steve Dupont, a special new correspondant, and one of our best hi-jinks ever. I apologize for the occasional iRiver audio irregularities, but we happened to be close to this place for the first time since we moved away, so neither of us could resist taking a look-see. Enjoy.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 86: The Ghosts That Haunt Us</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Not what one might expect from us on 06-06-06, but we decided to stray from the flock and totally ignore the sinister significance of the date... Instead, we share some ghosts from our past and give you this somewhat unusually formatted episode of NaD. Five Years ago last weekend, we found ourselves homeless and unemployed in the same day after the owners of a drive-in theater we were managing decided to close the doors forever. June 6 also happens to be the 80th anniversary of the first drive in theater, so join us as we take a trip down memory lane and take a tour of the Keysville Drive-In, our former home and place of business, following half a decade of total neglect. Throughout this sound-seeing tour, we discuss how we came to work for the drive-in, share a few stories about our experiences, and even tell some of the gory details of the demise of an American icon. We will Return back to a more normal show on episode 87 with a bottle of absinthe, more classic Steve Dupont, a special new correspondant, and one of our best hi-jinks ever. I apologize for the occasional iRiver audio irregularities, but we happened to be close to this place for the first time since we moved away, so neither of us could resist taking a look-see. Enjoy.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD06-06-06.mp3" length="43650517" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2006 13:01:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:45:28</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism, drive-in, theatre</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 85: Deport us please.</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD05-29-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=139</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Just in time for the post-Memorial day return to work, it is NaD 85.  Join us as we kick off our 2006 Portable Media and Podcasting Expo fundraiser, get stoned from an apple and a magnifying glass, play an awesome audio submission, discuss another concerning piece of proposed legislation in the SC State House involving possible deportation of drug users, get an outdated traffic report, and tell you what we have planned for Summer 2006.   This one is all over the place... but we will be back with more unexplainable mischief very soon, so enjoy this one while its fresh.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 85: Deport us please.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Just in time for the post-Memorial day return to work, it is NaD 85.  Join us as we kick off our 2006 Portable Media and Podcasting Expo fundraiser, get stoned from an apple and a magnifying glass, play an awesome audio submission, discuss another concerning piece of proposed legislation in the SC State House involving possible deportation of drug users, get an outdated traffic report, and tell you what we have planned for Summer 2006.   This one is all over the place... but we will be back with more unexplainable mischief very soon, so enjoy this one while its fresh.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD05-29-06.mp3" length="42459894" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2006 18:01:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:44:10</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 84: Does Privacy Have a Smell</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD05-18-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=137</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>NaD Episode 84 is hot off the press and headed directly for your ears, and for one lucky person out there, it is also going for her nose.  We start off with a humorous call Di placed to ATT consumer relations last weekend, and discuss the allegations that 3 major telecoms have turned over private phone records to the NSA.  With a follow-up call to our own telephone service provider, we cool off a bit.  Next, we switch gears and actually invade someone elses privacy, a nice stranger-lady who allowed us to get totally baked in her car without her knowing.(at least until afterwards, hehe)  We should totally apologize to Dave Slusher at EGC for bringing an all new meaning to podcast Clambakes.  NaD News sees the introduction of the new segment, The Disgusting Sex Lives of Republican Nastymen, including a hilarious clip of an abortionist insisting that he fucked goats when he grew up on a farm, a couple of pedos and a slew of other disgusting deeds you cant even imagine.  Steve Dupont exposes the underbelly of our show with an expose on our new Employee Training Tape.  To finish off, we discuss the benefits listeners receive by visiting the site, and close out with some more sage advice from Di.  So much shit on this one, we had to save 2 segments for our next installment.  So stay subscribed for that, and again, we must warn everyone, dont try this at home.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 84: Does Privacy Have a Smell</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>NaD Episode 84 is hot off the press and headed directly for your ears, and for one lucky person out there, it is also going for her nose.  We start off with a humorous call Di placed to ATT consumer relations last weekend, and discuss the allegations that 3 major telecoms have turned over private phone records to the NSA.  With a follow-up call to our own telephone service provider, we cool off a bit.  Next, we switch gears and actually invade someone elses privacy, a nice stranger-lady who allowed us to get totally baked in her car without her knowing.(at least until afterwards, hehe)  We should totally apologize to Dave Slusher at EGC for bringing an all new meaning to podcast Clambakes.  NaD News sees the introduction of the new segment, The Disgusting Sex Lives of Republican Nastymen, including a hilarious clip of an abortionist insisting that he fucked goats when he grew up on a farm, a couple of pedos and a slew of other disgusting deeds you cant even imagine.  Steve Dupont exposes the underbelly of our show with an expose on our new Employee Training Tape.  To finish off, we discuss the benefits listeners receive by visiting the site, and close out with some more sage advice from Di.  So much shit on this one, we had to save 2 segments for our next installment.  So stay subscribed for that, and again, we must warn everyone, dont try this at home.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD05-18-06.mp3" length="46563134" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 09:01:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:48:30</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 83: The Martha Stewart Morning Glory Trip</title>
<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD05-08-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=136</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>A NaD News Special Report.  Get ready for some hard-hitting journalism folks, as we follow our beat to K-Mart and purchase 30 packets of Martha Stewart Morning Glory seeds following reports that they create an LSD-like trip.   We were alerted to this story Friday by our friends at the Washington Post, who warned the world of this possible epidemic in an article by Staff Writer Theresa Vargas.  Tonight, we turn her sensationalistic story into reality right before your ears.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 83: The Martha Stewart Morning Glory Trip</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>A NaD News Special Report.  Get ready for some hard-hitting journalism folks, as we follow our beat to K-Mart and purchase 30 packets of Martha Stewart Morning Glory seeds following reports that they create an LSD-like trip.   We were alerted to this story Friday by our friends at the Washington Post, who warned the world of this possible epidemic in an article by Staff Writer Theresa Vargas.  Tonight, we turn her sensationalistic story into reality right before your ears.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD05-08-06.mp3" length="48064130" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2006 09:01:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:50:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 82: The Alpha and Omega According to Nate and Di</title>
<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD05-02-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=135</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Back again. Back again.  Sometimes, an episode develops a strong theme without us really thinking about it.  I love it when that happens.  This show is one of those, and happens to focus on Alpha and Omega, or the beginning and the end...  A year after our infamous church show, we revisit religion with an educational and entertaining lesson on the Alpha from the good book of Genesis titled Bible Bullshit Exposed after having some more of Kent Hovinds creationist hogwash shoved down our throats during a recent trip back home.  Another special report from Steve Dupont leaves us wondering what the fuck all the foreigners are saying abouts us, and we discuss a new segment coming up on NaD News.  We also scold our younger listeners for being Jr. stalkers, and take it to the Omega with a skit inspired by a recent email from an ex.  Some great tunes, a few funny voice mails, and an announcement about how you can win a NaD t-shirt, hat, and goodies bag just for making a 30-60 second promo for the show. Not as funny as the last one, but funnier than the one before that, so yeah, here it is.   Episode 83 is in the works already, and it is a riot, so we will be back before you expect it.  Subscribe, download, listen, and enjoy...  Then write and tell us about your thoughts.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 82: The Alpha and Omega According to Nate and Di</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Back again. Back again.  Sometimes, an episode develops a strong theme without us really thinking about it.  I love it when that happens.  This show is one of those, and happens to focus on Alpha and Omega, or the beginning and the end...  A year after our infamous church show, we revisit religion with an educational and entertaining lesson on the Alpha from the good book of Genesis titled Bible Bullshit Exposed after having some more of Kent Hovinds creationist hogwash shoved down our throats during a recent trip back home.  Another special report from Steve Dupont leaves us wondering what the fuck all the foreigners are saying abouts us, and we discuss a new segment coming up on NaD News.  We also scold our younger listeners for being Jr. stalkers, and take it to the Omega with a skit inspired by a recent email from an ex.  Some great tunes, a few funny voice mails, and an announcement about how you can win a NaD t-shirt, hat, and goodies bag just for making a 30-60 second promo for the show. Not as funny as the last one, but funnier than the one before that, so yeah, here it is.   Episode 83 is in the works already, and it is a riot, so we will be back before you expect it.  Subscribe, download, listen, and enjoy...  Then write and tell us about your thoughts.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD05-02-06.mp3" length="57339664" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2006 09:01:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:59:44</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Video Podcast v.1.1</title>
<link>http://media.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaDVideo04-22-06.mp4</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=134</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>We are working feverishly on the next TWO NaD episodes right now, but in the meantime, here is our first attempt at a vidcast. We recorded this on a 4 year old 15 dollar logitech quickcam, so the quality is not quite up to par, but not bad at all for the price and age of the thing. The intro is fun, plus, we give everyone a brief tour of Front Butt Studios. We produced this cast including the intro, which required quite a bit of editing, in less than 3 hours, and the actual video was made in one take that took less than 6 minutes. We are working on some cool ideas for new video projects, and I assure yall the next one will be of more substance and quality. Plus, I will also promise to back off the mic, and Di will lean in a bit and talk louder next time.  But hey, for our first experiment in video, the product is not horrible...well, too horrible.  We have had this up on our site for a few days now, and the response we got made us decide to put it on the feed for everyone else.  Enjoy.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Video Podcast v.1.1</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We are working feverishly on the next TWO NaD episodes right now, but in the meantime, here is our first attempt at a vidcast. We recorded this on a 4 year old 15 dollar logitech quickcam, so the quality is not quite up to par, but not bad at all for the price and age of the thing. The intro is fun, plus, we give everyone a brief tour of Front Butt Studios. We produced this cast including the intro, which required quite a bit of editing, in less than 3 hours, and the actual video was made in one take that took less than 6 minutes. We are working on some cool ideas for new video projects, and I assure yall the next one will be of more substance and quality. Plus, I will also promise to back off the mic, and Di will lean in a bit and talk louder next time.  But hey, for our first experiment in video, the product is not horrible...well, too horrible.  We have had this up on our site for a few days now, and the response we got made us decide to put it on the feed for everyone else.  Enjoy.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaDVideo04-22-06.mp4" length="37823796" type="audio/mp4"/>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2006 18:10:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:07:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism, video</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 81: Attack of the Imploding-Head Clones</title>
<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD04-16-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=132</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>OK... so I usually listen to each episode as it is uploading and I very seldom laugh out loud while listening to us...  I have been cracking up on this one, so consider that a seal of approval. Join us as we discuss our newfound namesakes... also referred to as clones in the show.  Next, we take you along as we rescue our parakeet Rigby, who became trapped inside of our recliner this week.  NaD news moves in a new direction with our first piece with Steve live with us on the show.  In the 2nd pet related accident in this show, our fish Gary Bibbs head imploded sometime today(It really imploded), so we honor him with a funeral right on the show.  Some new tunes, an important announcement, and a few other things round out this, the 81st episode of NaD.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 81: Attack of the Imploding-Head Clones</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>OK... so I usually listen to each episode as it is uploading and I very seldom laugh out loud while listening to us...  I have been cracking up on this one, so consider that a seal of approval. Join us as we discuss our newfound namesakes... also referred to as clones in the show.  Next, we take you along as we rescue our parakeet Rigby, who became trapped inside of our recliner this week.  NaD news moves in a new direction with our first piece with Steve live with us on the show.  In the 2nd pet related accident in this show, our fish Gary Bibbs head imploded sometime today(It really imploded), so we honor him with a funeral right on the show.  Some new tunes, an important announcement, and a few other things round out this, the 81st episode of NaD.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD04-16-06.mp3" length="34932047" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2006 17:10:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:36:23</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 80: The God Damn Long Ass Anniversary Show</title>
<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD04-08-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=128</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>One year ago, we first menaced the internet with our ramblings and strange madness. Tonight, in this special 90 minute edition, we look back over that year with the help of our listeners and podcasting friends.
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 80: The God Damn Long Ass Anniversary Show</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>One year ago, we first menaced the internet with our ramblings and strange madness. Tonight, in this special 90 minute edition, we look back over that year with the help of our listeners and podcasting friends.
</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD04-08-06.mp3" length="83939421" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2006 20:10:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>01:27:26</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 79: Mess with a Bean, Deal with the Burrito</title>
<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD04-01-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=127</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>OK, so it is not the blowout down there on 78, but it is an honest-to-Bob solid show...We are joined in the Studio by Patrick from The Charleston City Paper for this one, so we decided to let him in on a few secrets from the masters as we speak with P Dilly from the Podcast Pickle about everything from Podcating trends to The infamoud PodShow contract.  We also chat up the immigration debate with our favorite Hispandex, The Keeme himself!  NaD News continues to swerve off the beaten path with a true story about a crazy new law proposed in the SC House Of Representatives and the conclusion of Steve Duponts series, Let's Fuck with People.  The Show is also turning a year old later this week, and NaD 80 is already in the works, so leave us a voicemail or send us a message!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 79: Mess with a Bean, Deal with the Burrito</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>OK, so it is not the blowout down there on 78, but it is an honest-to-Bob solid show...We are joined in the Studio by Patrick from The Charleston City Paper for this one, so we decided to let him in on a few secrets from the masters as we speak with P Dilly from the Podcast Pickle about everything from Podcating trends to The infamoud PodShow contract.  We also chat up the immigration debate with our favorite Hispandex, The Keeme himself!  NaD News continues to swerve off the beaten path with a true story about a crazy new law proposed in the SC House Of Representatives and the conclusion of Steve Duponts series, Let's Fuck with People.  The Show is also turning a year old later this week, and NaD 80 is already in the works, so leave us a voicemail or send us a message!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD04-01-06.mp3" length="42747258" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2006 16:20:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:44:31</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 78: The Conspiracy of the Blow-job Killers</title>
<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD04-01-06a.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=126</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Our best episode EVER!  So much shit on this one I dont know where to start...You join us as Nate is caught snorting coke off of Dis ass, and then Di gives Nate a Blowjob and finishes up by getting the stripper off.  We also revisit the church from NaD 05 and piss on the pews.  Then, we switch gears and report some hard-hitting exclusive revelations by revealing the identities of the killers of both JFK and Kurt Cobain, and then tell what really happened in Roswell in 1947 and how it caused the  9/11 attacks.  Then it is back into the fun as we drive around Charleston throwing flaming bags of poop on our enemys porches!  All that and more on the 78th Episode of Nate and Di!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 78: The Conspiracy of the Blow-job Killers</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Our best episode EVER!  So much shit on this one I dont know where to start...You join us as Nate is caught snorting coke off of Dis ass, and then Di gives Nate a Blowjob and finishes up by getting the stripper off.  We also revisit the church from NaD 05 and piss on the pews.  Then, we switch gears and report some hard-hitting exclusive revelations by revealing the identities of the killers of both JFK and Kurt Cobain, and then tell what really happened in Roswell in 1947 and how it caused the  9/11 attacks.  Then it is back into the fun as we drive around Charleston throwing flaming bags of poop on our enemys porches!  All that and more on the 78th Episode of Nate and Di!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD04-01-06a.mp3" length="4532829" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2006 12:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:04:43</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism, big love, HBO </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 77: To Hell in a Handbasket</title>
<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD03-19-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=123</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>This is an unplanned wonder gem...  well, not entirely unplanned...  We had a plan, we just chose not to follow it.  We start this one off with another one of Dis increasingly strange prank calls and then we call her mom to wish her a happy birthday and get her opinion of the show and making fun of retards.(she has never heard our show, thank god.)  After a discussion with the MIL about 11 foot penises at the local sculpture show among other things, we play a special message from JC Hutchins and Satan himself.   NaD News hits home this week, with a really fucked up story about our former employer and a porn bust and Steve Dupont entertains and educates us once again with another installment of Lets Fuck With People.  Subscribe, download, listen, and laugh...  Then write and tell us about your thoughts!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD 77: To Hell in a Handbasket</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This is an unplanned wonder gem...  well, not entirely unplanned...  We had a plan, we just chose not to follow it.  We start this one off with another one of Dis increasingly strange prank calls and then we call her mom to wish her a happy birthday and get her opinion of the show and making fun of retards.(she has never heard our show, thank god.)  After a discussion with the MIL about 11 foot penises at the local sculpture show among other things, we play a special message from JC Hutchins and Satan himself.   NaD News hits home this week, with a really fucked up story about our former employer and a porn bust and Steve Dupont entertains and educates us once again with another installment of Lets Fuck With People.  Subscribe, download, listen, and laugh...  Then write and tell us about your thoughts!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD03-19-06.mp3" length="38854165" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2006 10:53:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:40:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism, big love, HBO </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 76: Conception of the Anti-Christ</title>
<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD03-11-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=121</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>OK.  Shorter episode, but we decided to drop this one early because it needs to be free, unhindered by other distractions we may create in the course of a normal show - plus Di started taking off her clothes at the end, effectively distracting the man at the mixer... Me.  We begin this one concerned that Di may indeed be with child.  In her words: The Evil One.
Listen as we take the home pregnancy test tonight - Unless youre a perv, she says. We also play some listener feedback, discuss our new satellite dish and the wonders of TIVO, and thank Blue from the Symian Syndicate for the CD he sent this week.  Subscribe, download, listen, and laugh...  Then write and tell us about your thoughts!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 76: Conception of the Anti-Christ</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>OK.  Shorter episode, but we decided to drop this one early because it needs to be free, unhindered by other distractions we may create in the course of a normal show - plus Di started taking off her clothes at the end, effectively distracting the man at the mixer... Me.  We begin this one concerned that Di may indeed be with child.  In her words: The Evil One.
Listen as we take the home pregnancy test tonight - Unless youre a perv, she says. We also play some listener feedback, discuss our new satellite dish and the wonders of TIVO, and thank Blue from the Symian Syndicate for the CD he sent this week.  Subscribe, download, listen, and laugh...  Then write and tell us about your thoughts!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD03-11-06.mp3" length="21139575" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2006 21:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:20:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism, big love, HBO </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 75: One license per shaved cat, please.</title>
<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD03-04-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=120</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>The weirdest mix of subjects we can remember on this one... Polygamy, Scatology, Letters to the editor, shaving a cat, a cabbage patch fuckme doll, and so much more.  Can you tell Di has PMS  Listen as she rants about her new foe, Letter to the Editor Meg, and plots her revenge with a research phone call to the local pet store  Never mind that she doesnt even know if this girl Meg really even has a cat.  We also kick off a fresh Censored Word Game, tell a story about our real lives, share listener feedback on the makings of green poo and a complaint that we dont thrash the religious folks so much anymore and why. Subscribe, download, listen, and laugh...  Then write and tell us about your thoughts!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 75: One license per shaved cat, please.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>The weirdest mix of subjects we can remember on this one... Polygamy, Scatology, Letters to the editor, shaving a cat, a cabbage patch fuckme doll, and so much more.  Can you tell Di has PMS  Listen as she rants about her new foe, Letter to the Editor Meg, and plots her revenge with a research phone call to the local pet store  Never mind that she doesnt even know if this girl Meg really even has a cat.  We also kick off a fresh Censored Word Game, tell a story about our real lives, share listener feedback on the makings of green poo and a complaint that we dont thrash the religious folks so much anymore and why. Subscribe, download, listen, and laugh...  Then write and tell us about your thoughts!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD03-04-06.mp3" length="33205790" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2006 21:15:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:34:31</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 74: Another Bong Bites the Dust</title>
<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD02-26-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=119</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Another dose of weird from the crazies at Front Butt!  NaD 74 was another roller coaster, you join us as Di calls the pet store to check on her constipated parakeet, Rigby.  We immediately move right along into a discussion with more scatological references than any previous edition of our show.  If this is your first time listening, we apologize for the rude introduction.  Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality were here yesterday, and Derek left us in charge of the BatPig Mobile until they return from their cruise next week.  We also daydream some about what to do with the truck, and invite listener suggestions.  Next, we test our new G-Spot bong from weedcity with less than satisfactory results.  In NaD News this week, we make a major announcement about our sponsor and remember Hunter Thompson a year after his death.  Fun show, we hope you guys enjoy it!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 74: Another Bong Bites the Dust</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Another dose of weird from the crazies at Front Butt!  NaD 74 was another roller coaster, you join us as Di calls the pet store to check on her constipated parakeet, Rigby.  We immediately move right along into a discussion with more scatological references than any previous edition of our show.  If this is your first time listening, we apologize for the rude introduction.  Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality were here yesterday, and Derek left us in charge of the BatPig Mobile until they return from their cruise next week.  We also daydream some about what to do with the truck, and invite listener suggestions.  Next, we test our new G-Spot bong from weedcity with less than satisfactory results.  In NaD News this week, we make a major announcement about our sponsor and remember Hunter Thompson a year after his death.  Fun show, we hope you guys enjoy it!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD02-26-06.mp3" length="33017385" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2006 19:36:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:34:19</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 73: Early Bird Gets the Roses of the Prophet</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD02-19-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=117</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Early for once, and another special edition show coming in the next few days! NaD 73 will go down in history as one of our favorites, we really had fun today.   Di immediately brings up my striped skin affliction she caused with a bottle of hydrogen peroxide a few nights ago, and things really dont slow down after that.  We also discuss our new pets, bibb, yaz, and bird.  Plus, we start not one, but TWO new contests tonight.  The new Censored Word Game will be up very soon and Di needs a name for her bird.  The NaD News on this episode is one of the most fun segments weve ever produced, so listen as Steve Dupont fucks with people at the IHOP in Birmingham, and we search for Roses of the Prophet Mohommad(aka Danishes) all over Charleston, including a little fucking with the local employees at the IHOP ourselves!
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 73: Early Bird Gets the Roses of the Prophet</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Early for once, and another special edition show coming in the next few days!  NaD 73 will go down in history as one of our favorites, we really had fun today.   Di immediately brings up my striped skin affliction she caused with a bottle of hydrogen peroxide a few nights ago, and things really dont slow down after that.  We also discuss our new pets, bibb, yaz, and bird.  Plus, we start not one, but TWO new contests tonight.  The new Censored Word Game will be up very soon and Di needs a name for her bird.  The NaD News on this episode is one of the most fun segments weve ever produced, so listen as Steve Dupont fucks with people at the IHOP in Birmingham, and we search for Roses of the Prophet Mohommad(aka Danishes) all over Charleston, including a little fucking with the local employees at the IHOP ourselves!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD02-19-06.mp3" length="35508423" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2006 20:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:36:55</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 72: The Flaming Panties Valentines Day Special</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD02-14-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=116</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Here it is in all its glory... NaD Episode 72. This is our most unplanned and unedited show to date, but it still rocks the Casbah due to Flaming Panty Factor.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 72: The Flaming Panties Valentines Day Special</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Here it is in all its glory... NaD Episode 72. This is our most unplanned and unedited show to date, but it still rocks the Casbah due to Flaming Panty Factor.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD02-14-06.mp3" length="29608393" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 23:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:30:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 71: Pimp Cups Overflowing with Cookie Spoons</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD02-07-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=115</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>More Weirdness than ever on this show... but also one of our longer episodes.  We kick things right off to a fresh start with a new intro and delve right into the strange as Di educates me about Pimp Cups.  We also introduce our new segment, Cartoon Mythbusters, with an experiment involving the Cookie Monster, a roll of cookie dough, a metal spoon, and a BIC lighter.  All that and much more in this nearly 50 minute show, including a new edition of NaD News with Steve Dupont, a new song from Jimmy G, and all kinds of other weird talk.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 71: Pimp Cups Overflowing with Cookie Spoons</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>More Weirdness than ever on this show... but also one of our longer episodes.  We kick things right off to a fresh start with a new intro and delve right into the strange as Di educates me about Pimp Cups.  We also introduce our new segment, Cartoon Mythbusters, with an experiment involving the Cookie Monster, a roll of cookie dough, a metal spoon, and a BIC lighter.  All that and much more in this nearly 50 minute show, including a new edition of NaD News with Steve Dupont, a new song from Jimmy G, and all kinds of other weird talk.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD02-07-06.mp3" length="45207904" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2006 18:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:47:01</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 70: The Trip, the Move, and the Panty Burgler</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD01-30-06.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=112</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Hiya. Remember us?  We used to do a podcast... Remember?  Way back, like last year? Well.  Were back again.  So watch out people!
Do many of you know a Republican truck driver who wears womens underwear? 
We do!  Episode 70 has finally arrived at your doorstep, so please answer the door before you get panty-burgled in your sleep.   Much ado about everything on this one, so many ados we had to cut it short at 40 mins and save some for another time.   Listen as we recount our move out of the shed and discuss the new house.  Hear the improved audio we discovered when the mics could finally be placed further than 6 inches from each other-   Magic!- Just Like our attempts with levitation discussed on the show.   We also finally recount our adventures at podcastercon, meeting Senator Edwards, and our bout with the cold from hell that our disease-infested roommate graciously shared with us up there.   All that, plus a true story about an uninvited visitor with some interesting habits at our shed, on this, the 1st show from our new studio!  
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 70: The Trip, the Move, and the Panty Burgler</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Hiya. Remember us?  We used to do a podcast... Remember?  Way back, like last year? Well.  Were back again.  So watch out people!
Do many of you know a Republican truck driver who wears womens underwear? 
We do!  Episode 70 has finally arrived at your doorstep, so please answer the door before you get panty-burgled in your sleep.   Much ado about everything on this one, so many ados we had to cut it short at 40 mins and save some for another time.   Listen as we recount our move out of the shed and discuss the new house.  Hear the improved audio we discovered when the mics could finally be placed further than 6 inches from each other-   Magic!- Just Like our attempts with levitation discussed on the show.   We also finally recount our adventures at podcastercon, meeting Senator Edwards, and our bout with the cold from hell that our disease-infested roommate graciously shared with us up there.   All that, plus a true story about an uninvited visitor with some interesting habits at our shed, on this, the 1st show from our new studio!  </itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD01-30-06.mp3" length="40934988" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2006 22:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:41:52</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism  </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 69: Sixty-Nine New Years Resolutions</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD12-31-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=108</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>The long-awaited episode 69 is here and is the final show for 2005!  As the neighborhood kids play with fireworks, we discuss our upcoming move out of the shed, our new jobs,  and our trip home for the holidays among other things.  Also, we give an update on Chris Wilson from nowthatsfuckedup.com.   Dont forget about podcastercon in Chapel Hill next week.  Throughout the show, we take a brief look back at the year, and make a few resolutions for 2006.   There are a few surprises mixed in as well...  69 anyone?  And finally, tonight we share our decision on a QYDJ contract with Podshow.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 69: Sixty-Nine New Years Resolutions</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>The long-awaited episode 69 is here and is the final show for 2005!  As the neighborhood kids play with fireworks, we discuss our upcoming move out of the shed, our new jobs,  and our trip home for the holidays among other things.  Also, we give an update on Chris Wilson from nowthatsfuckedup.com.   Dont forget about podcastercon in Chapel Hill next week.  Throughout the show, we take a brief look back at the year, and make a few resolutions for 2006.   There are a few surprises mixed in as well...  69 anyone?  And finally, tonight we share our decision on a QYDJ contract with Podshow.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD12-31-05.mp3" length="40934988" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2005 21:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:42:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 68: Part 1</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT1-12-17-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: Keeme, Gary from Podcast Pickle, and Sledge from I love KNIGHTS</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 68: Part 1</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: Keeme, Gary from Podcast Pickle, and Sledge from I love KNIGHTS</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT1-12-17-05.mp3" length="54630228" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2005 18:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:56:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 68: Part 2</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT2-12-17-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: Sledge, and Pk and J</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 68: Part 2</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: Sledge, and Pk and J</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT2-12-17-05.mp3" length="40927658" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2005 18:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:42:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 68: Part 3</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT3-12-17-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: Derek and Swoopy, Aaron from the Big Show, The Unharshed Mellow, and Bibb and Yaz</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 68: Part 3</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: Derek and Swoopy, Aaron from the Big Show, The Unharshed Mellow, and Bibb and Yaz</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT3-12-17-05.mp3" length="86883070" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2005 18:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>01:30:26</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 68: Part 4</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT4-12-17-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: Bibb and Yaz, Mur from GeekFu Action Grip, Jack from the KickAss Podcast, and El Nacho</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 68: Part 4</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: Bibb and Yaz, Mur from GeekFu Action Grip, Jack from the KickAss Podcast, and El Nacho</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT4-12-17-05.mp3" length="38804676" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2005 18:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:40:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 68: Part 5</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT5-12-17-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: El Nacho, SysTris, and Nlinus</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 68: Part 5</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: El Nacho, SysTris, and Nlinus</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT5-12-17-05.mp3" length="50033743" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2005 18:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:52:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 68: Part 6</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT6-12-17-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: Nlinus, JvonD, and Gabber JaW</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 68: Part 6</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Yeah, we know we said Episode 68 would include a re-cap of the live show Saturday night, but we did one better...Heres our greatest monstrosity yet, its the whole damn thing! We are flooding our feed with more than 20 podcasters chatting it up with us during five and a half hours of Podcast Party love.  In fact, it was so large, we split this episode  into 6 parts!  Special thanks to Keeme for coming on as  Co-Host and putting up with us for nearly 6 hours, and also to Oblivion for recording and uploading these for us.  Weve yet to publish one of these, so we thought the regular audience might enjoy the experience.  This is not a typical Nate and Di Show, but we hope you guys enjoy it.  Highlights from the evening include a short conversation with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality, hanging up on Bibb and Yaz again, NaD and Keeme answering the hard hitting questions from PK and J, El Nachos sister telling him not to talk to strangers and to feed his goat, and a chat with Gary Leland from the Podcast Pickle... Contstant laughter and lots more in this Special Edition of NaD.  Sorry about the occaisional Skype glitches... those things happen.  We have cleaned up the audio a bit and added some nice background grooves, so if you missed it, it sounds better than the live show - and if you made it Saturday night, listen again, cause it sounds betta still!  Thanks again to Gary and the Pickle for hosting, all of the prize donors, and of course the guests. We'll do this again very soon, promise. This part includes: Nlinus, JvonD, and Gabber JaW</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaDPodcastPartyPT6-12-17-05.mp3" length="59485898" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2005 18:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>01:01:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 67.5.25:  Pre-Party banter and other stories.</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD12-17-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=103</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Quick show to promote the Holiday Podcast Party tonight.   A few other notes, including the oral pleasure gel Di purchased from her boss.
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 67.5.25:  Pre-Party banter and other stories.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Quick show to promote the Holiday Podcast Party tonight.   A few other notes, including the oral pleasure gel Di purchased from her boss.
.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD12-17-05.mp3" length="12118548" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2005 18:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:12:33</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 67: A Mulatto at the Improv Has a Candy Cane.</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD12-11-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=101</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Back again, back again!  We apologize for the unusually long gap in episodes this week, but we had some major distractions lately...  Like a year of TV on DVD to catch up on.  We promise, it wont happen again.  Anyhow, following my failed attempt to produce a solocast to keep the feed fresh on friday, we got motivated and made our newest NaD creation - Episode 67!
We hope you enjoy, the rumor is that it tastes best with cheap wine, but its up to you on that...  Tonight, we recount a few escapades from the past week, welcome our nephew Jamal, share another NaD News segment with Steve Dupont, tell about Dis longstanding contribution to the D.A.R.E. program in SC, plus some more shit and stuff like that.  Oh.  And Di was also unusually jubilant on this one, she started the episode by taking off her clothes for no apparent reason. Fun show.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 67: A Mulatto at the Improv Has a Candy Cane.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Back again, back again!  We apologize for the unusually long gap in episodes this week, but we had some major distractions lately...  Like a year of TV on DVD to catch up on.  We promise, it wont happen again.  Anyhow, following my failed attempt to produce a solocast to keep the feed fresh on friday, we got motivated and made our newest NaD creation - Episode 67!
We hope you enjoy, the rumor is that it tastes best with cheap wine, but its up to you on that...  Tonight, we recount a few escapades from the past week, welcome our nephew Jamal, share another NaD News segment with Steve Dupont, tell about Dis longstanding contribution to the D.A.R.E. program in SC, plus some more shit and stuff like that.  Oh.  And Di was also unusually jubilant on this one, she started the episode by taking off her clothes for no apparent reason. Fun show.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD12-11-05.mp3" length="41450919" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2005 22:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:43:06</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Nates 420 Rant: Are Jesus shopping habits CNN worthy news</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/Nate420Ramble12-09-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=100</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>I have a semi-coherent  go at CNN for the really fucked up News headlines on their website today.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>Nates 420 Rant: Are Jesus shopping habits CNN worthy news</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>I have a semi-coherent  go at CNN for the really fucked up News headlines on their website today.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/Nate420Ramble12-09-05.mp3" length="9809259" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:10:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Episode 66: Dogs with shotguns will rule the earth.</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD11-30-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=98</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Well, Im nearly recovered from my bout with the Turd Flu, so heres the show already. We were all over the place as usual tonight, from grandpa shooting cute puppies during Thanksgiving dinner to Dis sister getting brainwashed by a quick-talking scamster who purports the world is only 6000 years old, this one is sure to make you cringe at least once...  
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Episode 66: Dogs with shotguns will rule the earth.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Well, Im nearly recovered from my bout with the Turd Flu, so heres the show already. We were all over the place as usual tonight, from grandpa shooting cute puppies during Thanksgiving dinner to Dis sister getting brainwashed by a quick-talking scamster who purports the world is only 6000 years old, this one is sure to make you cringe at least once...</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD11-30-05.mp3" length="37022225" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:38:30</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism  </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #65: The end is coming , Let it go!</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD11-20-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=95</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Herro, Its Nate, and I have shranty eyes... Good show tonight, I forget everything we talked about, but I know we discuss where we were a year ago, say some things to some people, play with uneccessary cenorship for a bit, share some news and a scathing report from our new correspondent Steve Dupont, discuss some holiday news and plans, salute some fallen comrades, Di begs for gifts, and close out with a great song.  Lots more inside, so listen now!
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #65: The end is coming , Let it go!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Herro, Its Nate, and I have shranty eyes... Good show tonight, I forget everything we talked about, but I know we discuss where we were a year ago, say some things to some people, play with uneccessary cenorship for a bit, share some news and a scathing report from our new correspondent Steve Dupont, discuss some holiday news and plans, salute some fallen comrades, Di begs for gifts, and close out with a great song.  Lots more inside, so listen now!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD11-20-05.mp3" length="43485963" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2005 00:18:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:45:14</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #64: Expo Wrap-up Special Edition Episode.</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD11-15-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=92</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>First of all, we want to thank Michael Haisten for making this possible and everything else he did for us this weekend. Also thanks to all of the donors who helped pay for the room and our drinks and foodstuffs.  The "regular" show is coming, but in the meantime, heres a short wrap-up and a bunch of recordings from the iRiver this weekend.  We tried to keep the "roving mic in the face" habit  at bay(figured enough of that was going on), but we caught plenty of ambient material to share.  As we said in the previous posts, the PME was a blast, and well definitely return next year in September for Expo # 2.  Dont forget PodcasterCon on January 7th, well be there too. 
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #64: Expo Wrap-up Special Edition Episode.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>First of all, we want to thank Michael Haisten for making this possible and everything else he did for us this weekend. Also thanks to all of the donors who helped pay for the room and our drinks and foodstuffs.  The "regular" show is coming, but in the meantime, heres a short wrap-up and a bunch of recordings from the iRiver this weekend.  We tried to keep the "roving mic in the face" habit  at bay(figured enough of that was going on), but we caught plenty of ambient material to share.  As we said in the previous posts, the PME was a blast, and well definitely return next year in September for Expo # 2.  Dont forget PodcasterCon on January 7th, well be there too.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD11-15-05.mp3" length="24576299" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2005 00:18:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:25:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism  </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #63: The Uh-Oh Show.</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD11-09-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=90</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>This is our last message to everyone before our big trip to the Portable Media Expo. Long show this time, a whopping 45 minutes! We walk a fine line between humor and nonsense on this one. Hear the Uh-Oh sound, some big news about the show, a commercial parody for a friend, another letter from a crazy lady, a story about our good-will hitchhiking attempts, an all new message segment, and much more! You are also invited to the shed next Wednesday for a screening of the new Robert Greenwald movie, Walmart: The High Cost of Low Prices. See some of you this wekend in Cali, we will be back next Monday with some more NaD goodness for all. 
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>Nate and Di #63: The Uh-Oh Show.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Our last message to everyone before our big trip to the Portable Media Expo. Long show this time, a whopping 45 minutes! We walk a fine line between humor and nonsense on this one. Hear the Uh-Oh sound, some big news about the show, a commercial parody for a friend, another letter from a crazy lady, a story about our good-will hitchhiking attempts, an all new message segment, and much more! You are also invited to the shed next Wednesday for a screening of the new Robert Greenwald movie, Walmart: The High Cost of Low Prices. See some of you this wekend in Cali, we will be back next Monday with some more NaD goodness for all.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD11-09-05.mp3" length="46613585" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2005 00:09:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:48:30</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #62:The not-so-spooky Halloween Spectacular.</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD10-30-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=89</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Following our most serious show ever, the silly has returned.  This is possibly the most weird and random episode yet.  Get ready for a rather sedate yet manic offering of topics including, but not limited to: pancake batter, cornflakes, myspace, our bongs new name, letters from crazy people, and aborting and/or exterminating each other.  Plus, hear some bonus conversations with some interesting surprise call-in guests.  It's kinda ironic our ftp program says "uh-oh!" every time a new show finishes uploading...  Really.  It's kinda weird.  We will have to record that so you can hear it too.
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #62: The not-so-spooky Halloween Spectacular.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Following our most serious show ever, the silly has returned.  This is possibly the most weird and random episode yet.  Get ready for a rather sedate yet manic offering of topics including, but not limited to: pancake batter, cornflakes, myspace, our bongs new name, letters from crazy people, and aborting and/or exterminating each other.  Plus, hear some bonus conversations with some interesting surprise call-in guests.  It's kinda ironic our ftp program says "uh-oh!" every time a new show finishes uploading...  Really.  It's kinda weird.  We will have to record that so you can hear it too.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NaD10-30-05.mp3" length="37488297" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:38:59</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #61: Now Thats Fucked Up and other stories.</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD10-21-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=87</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Well, thanks for the wait. One day behind shcedule, but it was worth it, we assure you. We begin with some typical Nate and Di fare,  move on to some more serious matters, and then back to our usual silliness with a musical montage we call Whatever.  The Three Branches of Republican Collapse."  This newest edition of our ever-evolving podcast features an intervew with Jeremy Morgan, webmaster of freechris.org. On Oct. 7, our friend and fellow podcaster, Chris Wilson, was arrested and charged with 300 counts of obscenity in Polk County, Florida. Chris operates a website that came to national attention when he began trading free meberships for his user-submitted amatuer photo site to troops overseas in exchange for photos from the frontlines of our war on terrorism.  Hear some details on his case and how you can help protect our rights to free speech by helping Chris.  Let us know if you do, and also send us any audio comments about this case at 361-288-3NAD.
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #61: Now Thats Fucked Up and other stories.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Well, thanks for the wait. One day behind shcedule, but it was worth it, we assure you. We begin with some typical Nate and Di fare,  move on to some more serious matters, and then back to our usual silliness with a musical montage we call Whatever.  The Three Branches of Republican Collapse."  This newest edition of our ever-evolving podcast features an intervew with Jeremy Morgan, webmaster of freechris.org. On Oct. 7, our friend and fellow podcaster, Chris Wilson, was arrested and charged with 300 counts of obscenity in Polk County, Florida. Chris operates a website that came to national attention when he began trading free meberships for his user-submitted amatuer photo site to troops overseas in exchange for photos from the frontlines of our war on terrorism.  Hear some details on his case and how you can help protect our rights to free speech by helping Chris.  Let us know if you do, and also send us any audio comments about this case at 361-288-3NAD.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD10-21-05.mp3" length="44484926" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:46:16</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #60: The Untitled Wonder Episode.</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD10-15-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=86</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Here it is! The latest and greatest insallment of weirdness from your shed-dwelling hosts. Tonight, we begin by rearraging the english language... Then things improve briefly as we thanked a very important donor and give away the podcast studio gear to a very lucky listener/donor. After that, we share a few skits, deliver a few housekeeping notes, and close out with the usual round of unusual messages and a song from one of our favorite authors.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #60: The Untitled Wonder Episode.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Here it is! The latest and greatest insallment of weirdness from your shed-dwelling hosts. Tonight, we begin by rearraging the english language... Then things improve briefly as we thanked a very important donor and give away the podcast studio gear to a very lucky listener/donor. After that, we share a few skits, deliver a few housekeeping notes, and close out with the usual round of unusual messages and a song from one of our favorite authors.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD10-15-05.mp3" length="29949258" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:31:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #59: Toss that midget over here!</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD10-07-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=85</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Our first episode following the marathon 6 hour podcast party last weekend. All around the place tonight. We discuss our plans for the Portable Media Expo, perform a few skits, ponder a strange tv show we happened upon this week, trounce on MC Hammers new religious ministry, and hear another wondrous barrage of profanity from a young listener.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #59: Toss that midget over here!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Our first episode following the marathon 6 hour podcast party last weekend. All around the place tonight. We discuss our plans for the Portable Media Expo, perform a few skits, ponder a strange tv show we happened upon this week, trounce on MC Hammers new religious ministry, and hear another wondrous barrage of profanity from a young listener.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD10-07-05.mp3" length="29046479" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:30:11</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #58: Bohemian Bible Glasses and the Surprise Orgy!</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD09-29-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=83</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Weird mood in the shed tonight.  After hearing about Tom Delays indictment, we celebrate like its 1992.  We also pay tribute to Oprah Winfreys new Opera, and write one for her to produce for us.  Dont miss Buddy Davis theory that Noah fit all the animals on the ark by bringing baby dinos aboard.  Oh, and an interesting message from the WINNER of the censored word game.  Well, thats all we can remember, but this installment must be set free upon the podosphere before we can rest, so here it is!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #58: Bohemian Bible Glasses and the Surprise Orgy!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Weird mood in the shed tonight.  After hearing about Tom Delays indictment, we celebrate like its 1992.  We also pay tribute to Oprah Winfreys new Opera, and write one for her to produce for us.  Dont miss Buddy Davis theory that Noah fit all the animals on the ark by bringing baby dinos aboard.  Oh, and an interesting message from the WINNER of the censored word game.  Well, thats all we can remember, but this installment must be set free upon the podosphere before we can rest, so here it is!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD09-29-05.mp3" length="30222714" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:31:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #57: As painful as an artificial snake bite!</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD09-22-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=82</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Tonight was a silly night... maybe more silly than we realized during the show, so we apologize in advance! Floating on the high caused by good news from the Skepticality camp, we discuss Dis cramps and her recent bout of PMS, perform a few skits,  present what is possibly our most absurd Stupid Religious Leader Statement of the Week yet, and thank our audience for the support with our new podcast venture we launched this week.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #57: As painful as an artificial snake bite!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Tonight was a silly night... maybe more silly than we realized during the show, so we apologize in advance! Floating on the high caused by good news from the Skepticality camp, we discuss Dis cramps and her recent bout of PMS, perform a few skits,  present what is possibly our most absurd Stupid Religious Leader Statement of the Week yet, and thank our audience for the support with our new podcast venture we launched this week.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD09-22-05.mp3" length="23694089" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:24:37</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD # 56: Gothic Dolphins Created the Earth</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD09-12-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=79</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>After a dismal performance by Hurricane Nate, Charleston has been threatened by another storm, Ophelia.  This podcast really has nothing to do with hurricanes, though. Tonight we share an interesting skit we call, Thats Dark, produce a new NaDSNet segment, discuss the Creation Museum that will be opening its doors soon, and update the Censored Word Game!  All this and much more jack-assery on this installment of our audio experiment we call a podcast.
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD # 56: Gothic Dolphins Created the Earth</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>After a dismal performance by Hurricane Nate, Charleston has been threatened by another storm, Ophelia.  This podcast really has nothing to do with hurricanes, though. Tonight we share an interesting skit we call, Thats Dark, produce a new NaDSNet segment, discuss the Creation Museum that will be opening its doors soon, and update the Censored Word Game!  All this and much more jack-assery on this installment of our audio experiment we call a podcast.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD09-12-05.mp3" length="24566499" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:25:31</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD # 55: Hurricane Blues and the Magic Carpet Ride</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD09-03-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=77</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>This show makes us proud to be Americans! Got some wireless gear yesterday, so Nate podcasts from the la-z-boy. Join us tonight as we discuss all this hurricane mess, question the crazy gas shortage, Sell a fabulous new product, celebrate 25 years of the Blues Brothers, thwart an attempt to steal our garbage, shave dirty words on the neighbors doggy, and introduce the theme for the Censored Word Game!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD # 55: Hurricane Blues and the Magic Carpet Ride</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This show makes us proud to be Americans! Got some wireless gear yesterday, so Nate podcasts from the la-z-boy. Join us tonight as we discuss all this hurricane mess, question the crazy gas shortage, Sell a fabulous new product, celebrate 25 years of the Blues Brothers, thwart an attempt to steal our garbage, shave dirty words on the neighbors doggy, and introduce the theme for the Censored Word Game!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD09-03-05.mp3" length="27968246" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:29:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>NaD #54: Like a Crunchy Nougat!</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-27-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=76</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Tasty like a crunchy nougat covered in chocolate syrup, its just another day at the shed. What is a crunchy nougat? We have no idea. Saw a picture once.  Episode 54 has appeared, and we like it! We discuss our recent visit to see a movie, our up-coming DragonCon trip, a new podcast, and tell how Nate almost reduced the shed to a smoldering mess recently. All this and much more on this installment of our audio experiment we call a podcast. </description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #54: Like a Crunchy Nougat!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Tasty like a crunchy nougat covered in chocolate syrup, its just another day at the shed. What is a crunchy nougat? We have no idea. Saw a picture once.  Episode 54 has appeared, and we like it! We discuss our recent visit to see a movie, our up-coming DragonCon trip, a new podcast, and tell how Nate almost reduced the shed to a smoldering mess recently. All this and much more on this installment of our audio experiment we call a podcast. </itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-27-05.mp3" length="30379226" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:31:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #53: Please stop singing! We are insane, you know!</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-23-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=75</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Upon our return from the roadtrip to see a baby, we made this! All over the place tonight. Di had a bit of trouble while handling the newborn, so we skipped out to visit with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality. Also, we play a terribly annoying yet catchy song from our childhood and some audio clips from Big Brother 6 that explains the whole reason we subjected you to the song in the first place. To top everything off, we play an interesting clip from a new podcast from here in SC. All this and maybe more. Well, definitely more.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #53: Please stop singing! We are insane, you know!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Upon our return from the roadtrip to see a baby, we made this! All over the place tonight. Di had a bit of trouble while handling the newborn, so we skipped out to visit with Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality. Also, we play a terribly annoying yet catchy song from our childhood and some audio clips from Big Brother 6 that explains the whole reason we subjected you to the song in the first place. To top everything off, we play an interesting clip from a new podcast from here in SC. All this and maybe more. Well, definitely more.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-23-05.mp3" length="31396310" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:32:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD # 52: Proud relatives of a new organism.</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-19-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=74</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Sorry, shorter show this time... This show was recorded between thunderstorms. We discuss Dis sisters new baby... our new niece, and our trip to see said baby. Also, we reminisce about favorite childhood foods and cuss up a storm with the censored word game.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD # 52: Proud relatives of a new organism.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Sorry, shorter show this time... This show was recorded between thunderstorms. We discuss Dis sisters new baby... our new niece, and our trip to see said baby. Also, we reminisce about favorite childhood foods and cuss up a storm with the censored word game.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-19-05.mp3" length="27055275" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:28:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #51: Back from the Grave with a Poo-Geyser to boot!</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-13-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=73</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>You dont think a mere bullet to the head could stop Nate and Di??? Lengthier show tonight! We are back with a vengence after a brief break. We discuss our time in the afterlife, entertain a visitor, witness a natural wonder in front of the shed, and much more!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #51: Back from the Grave with a Poo-Geyser to boot!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>You dont think a mere bullet to the head could stop Nate and Di??? Lengthier show tonight! We are back with a vengence after a brief break.  We discuss our time in the afterlife, entertain a visitor, witness a natural wonder in front of the shed, and much more!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-13-05.mp3" length="46600273" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:48:28</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #50:  Its Better to Burn Out...</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-09-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=71</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Hi everyone.  Its Corby from the Twisted Pickle Show.  Unfortunately, Nate and Di are unable to post their 50th episode...
I have taken the liberty of posting this show per their instructions. This show contains a graphic scene that is sure to go down as one of the pivotal moments in the history of their show.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #50:  Its Better to Burn Out...</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Hi everyone.  Its Corby from the Twisted Pickle Show.  Unfortunately, Nate and Di are unable to post their 50th episode...
I have taken the liberty of posting this show per their instructions. This show contains a graphic scene that is sure to go down as one of the pivotal moments in the history of their show.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-09-05.mp3" length="38364969" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:39:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD # 49: Veggie Pipe Dreams and The Waffle House Mutiny!</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-02-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=70</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Interesting experiment tonight... We recieved a suggestion from Corby to fashion smoking pipes from carrots!  To be sporting, we made it a contest! Listen to find out who is the veggie bowl champion. We also recieve a message from the closet from the Twisted Pickle himself, discuss a story involving the two waffle house employees pictured below, and tell all about why we were late with the show because of air conditioner malfunctions.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #49: Veggie Pipe Dreams and The Waffle House Mutiny!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Interesting experiment tonight... We recieved a suggestion from Corby to fashion smoking pipes from carrots!  To be sporting, we made it a contest! Listen to find out who is the veggie bowl champion. We also recieve a message from the closet from the Twisted Pickle himself, discuss a story involving the two waffle house employees pictured below, and tell all about why we were late with the show because of air conditioner malfunctions.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD08-02-05.mp3" length="34533001" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2005 00:42:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:35:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD # 48 The Smoking Keyboard episode!</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD07-28-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=69</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Now with more filling!  This one clocks in a little longer than our usual episodes.  We went out on a limb tonight after smoking the contents of our keyboard and touched on a couple of news stories, and a tale about wiping a cat's ass explosions for Corby.  We also play play a tune, share a bit of creative karaoke from Keeme, and much more!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD # 48 The Smoking Keyboard episode!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Now with more filling!  This one clocks in a little longer than our usual episodes.  We went out on a limb tonight after smoking the contents of our keyboard and touched on a couple of news stories, and a tale about wiping a cat's ass explosions for Corby.  We also play play a tune, share a bit of creative karaoke from Keeme, and much more!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD07-28-05.mp3" length="37453832" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2005 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:28:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #47 We Got a Roving Wiretap!</title>
<link>http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD07-25-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=68</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Too much to list for this edition of Nate and Di.  We have a suprise visitor, discuss our loudness, offer a public service announcement, a new editionof log and thank our listeners in the Netherlands proper.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #47 We Got a Roving Wiretap!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Too much to list for this edition of Nate and Di.  We have a suprise visitor, discuss our loudness, offer a public service announcement, a new editionof log and thank our listeners in the Netherlands proper.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD07-25-05.mp3" length="27563658" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2005 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:28:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD # 46:  A Snow Story in July!</title>
<link>http://libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD07-21-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=65</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Hey!  We're back.   Been working on some other stuff this week, sorry for the delay. Lots of goodies - New equiptment, new intros, several contests, a story, a couple of rants, we lick John and Wendy's asses, hear about Derek's spooky hotel - and much, much more!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD # 46:  A Snow Story in July!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Hey!  We're back.   Been working on some other stuff this week, sorry for the delay. Lots of goodies - New equiptment, new intros, several contests, a story, a couple of rants, we lick John and Wendy's asses, hear about Derek's spooky hotel - and much, much more!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD07-21-05.mp3" length="27666483" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2005 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:28:45</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #45: Bridging NASAs Methodone Log and the Rise of a Grunge Politician.</title>
<link>http://libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD07-17-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=62</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Were Back people! Where did we leave off? Long show today, lots to catch everyone up on. We discuss NASA, our new bridge, another weird email or two, new censored word game, and and introduce a new and improved log section. We also share a clip from a recent speaking engagement by Krist Novoselic, former bassist of Nirvana who recently became a political theory author. All this and a bag of smurfs to smoke!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #45: Bridging NASAs Methodone Log and the Rise of a Grunge Politician.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Were Back people! Where did we leave off? Long show today, lots to catch everyone up on. We discuss NASA, our new bridge, another weird email or two, new censored word game, and and introduce a new and improved log section. We also share a clip from a recent speaking engagement by Krist Novoselic, former bassist of Nirvana who recently became a political theory author. All this and a bag of smurfs to smoke!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD07-17-05.mp3" length="42483339" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2005 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:30:01</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #44: Frabbits and the septic Skeptic.</title>
<link>http://libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD07-12-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=60</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>We apologize for taking 3 days to get this one to you, and we explain in this episode why. We also introduce our new prize for the Pod Expo fundraiser, discuss the drunk show, and talk about the our turds on the floor.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #44: Frabbits and the septic Skeptic.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We apologize for taking 3 days to get this one to you, and we explain in this episode why. We also introduce our new prize for the Pod Expo fundraiser, discuss the drunk show, and talk about the our turds on the floor. </itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://libsyn.com/media/nateanddi/NaD07-12-05.mp3" length="28882325" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2005 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:30:01</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #43 This episode is one of the reasons we dont drink!</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD07-08-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=59</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Okay, we hope our parents dont hear this podcast!  Nate and Di started drinking at 10:00 AM on Friday.  After fans made demands for an episode, we made this one.   Remember this one the next time you guys bug us for a new episode on Di's Day off.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #43 This episode is one of the reasons we dont drink!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Okay, we hope our parents dont hear this podcast!  Nate and Di started drinking at 10:00 AM on Friday.  After fans made demands for an episode, we made this one.   Remember this one the next time you guys bug us for a new episode on Di's Day off. </itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD07-08-05.mp3" length="28954810" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2005 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:30:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #42: Sister Saint Reverend Di has a Friend</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD07-06-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=58</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Your usual taste of wackiness from Nate and Di on this show! Nate is almost killed by a Coke bottle. Di learns of another female St. Reverend, so we inroduce Saint Reverend Jen. We visit an interesting website, talk about corbys prize, and catch up on messages.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #42: Sister Saint Reverend Di has a friend</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Your usual taste of wackiness from Nate and Di on this show! Nate is almost killed by a Coke bottle. Di learns of another female St. Reverend, so we inroduce Saint Reverend Jen. We visit an interesting website, talk about corbys prize, and catch up on messages.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD07-06-05.mp3" length="29134571" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2005 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:30:17</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #41: The 1st Annual Controversial Cast Convention</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD07-04-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=57</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>This Independence Day we take it easy and have a conversation with one of our favorite podcasters, Soccergirl, from Soccergirl, Inc.  She asked us last week if we'd like to chat it up sometime soon, and The Fourth of July seemed quite appropriate for the show.   During our hour long conversation we talk about everything from a Haunted Nintendo on ebay to peeing on people from trees!  A truly enchanting hour of entertainment for adults ages 18+ only.
</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #41: The 1st Annual Controversial Cast Convention</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>This Independence Day we take it easy and have a conversation with one of our favorite podcasters, Soccergirl, from Soccergirl, Inc.  She asked us last week if we'd like to chat it up sometime soon, and The Fourth of July seemed quite appropriate for the show.   During our hour long conversation we talk about everything from a Haunted Nintendo on ebay to peeing on people from trees!  A truly enchanting hour of entertainment for adults ages 18+ only.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD07-04-05.mp3" length="53463738" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2005 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:55:41</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism, soccergirl </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #40: The Podcast PickleMan Roast!</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD07-01-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=56</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>After the long wait, the PickleMan finally has a new name! This episode is NSFW!
17 Podcasters Join Forces to salute the PickleMan:
Big Al and The G-Man from Two men and a Microphone
Chris and Rick from Half Hour Power Hour
Corby from the Twisted Pickle
Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality
Greg from 5 Questions.net
John and Wendy from Gabber Jaw 
Keeme from the Keeme Cast
Nate and Di from The Nate and Di Show
Phil from Bit Jobs For the Masses
Paul from Barefoot Radio
Rob from podCast 411
Soccergirl from Soccergirl, Incorporated
Join us as we roast the Podcast Pickle PickleMan like a jalepeno on a campfire, and finally reveal his new name</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #40: The Podcast PickleMan Roast!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>After the long wait, the PickleMan finally has a new name! This episode is NSFW!
17 Podcasters Join Forces to salute the PickleMan:
Big Al and The G-Man from Two men and a Microphone
Chris and Rick from Half Hour Power Hour
Corby from the Twisted Pickle
Derek and Swoopy from Skepticality
Greg from 5 Questions.net
John and Wendy from Gabber Jaw 
Keeme from the Keeme Cast
Nate and Di from The Nate and Di Show
Phil from Bit Jobs For the Masses
Paul from Barefoot Radio
Rob from podCast 411
Soccergirl from Soccergirl, Incorporated
Join us as we roast the Podcast Pickle PickleMan like a jalepeno on a campfire, and finally reveal his new name.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD07-01-05.mp3" length="30747853" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2005 16:30:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:32:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #39 06-28-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-28-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=53</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>iTunes, loose pussy surgeries, mutant hairs, and Nates officially a flasher! 
Show notes
Hey mother fuckers
iTunes
Health Class: Definition of circlage
The fuckin weird mutant hair.
Corbys Prize(Hes gonna stalk the UPS man)
Pickleman contest update
Nates a flasher!
Signing off
Karls Blanky
Messages(Hosted By Karl- With a Wheres Charlie hint)
40 up next!!! WoW! 40 podCasts!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #39 06-28-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>iTunes, loose pussy surgeries, mutant hairs, and Nates officially a flasher! 
Show notes
Hey mother fuckers
iTunes
Health Class: Definition of circlage
The fuckin weird mutant hair.
Corbys Prize(Hes gonna stalk the UPS man)
Pickleman contest update
Nates a flasher!
Signing off
Karls Blanky
Messages(Hosted By Karl- With a Wheres Charlie hint)
40 up next!!! WoW! 40 podCasts!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-28-05.mp3" length="16651712" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2005 21:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:17:20</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism, drugs </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #38: Pokies Last Stand!</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-26-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=51</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>In this episode, we pay tribute to a fallen comrade, our dedicated PC, Pokie the Pavillion. Pokie fell during her service to the Nate and Di Show as she was struck by lightning while she worked to update the website on Thursday. Pokie was laid to rest in the mouth of the Cooper River Sunday afternoon and floated out to sea. We also discuss the selfless act Charlie Watts commited when he donated his computer for our show.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #38: Pokies Last Stand</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In this episode, we pay tribute to a fallen comrade, our dedicated PC, Pokie the Pavillion. Pokie fell during her service to the Nate and Di Show as she was struck by lightning while she worked to update the website on Thursday. Pokie was laid to rest in the mouth of the Cooper River Sunday afternoon and floated out to sea. We also discuss the selfless act Charlie Watts commited when he donated his computer for our show.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-26-05.mp3" length="27733202" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2005 19:30:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:28:52</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #37 06-21-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-21-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=48</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Sister Saint Reverend Di Strikes Back!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #37 06-21-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Sister Saint Reverend Di Strikes Back!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-21-05.mp3" length="10953904" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2005 21:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:11:23</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #36 06-20-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-20-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=47</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Sister Saint Reverend Di's Inspirational Spectacular!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #36 06-20-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Sister Saint Reverend Di's Inspirational Spectacular!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-20-05.mp3" length="20039844" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2005 22:30:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:20:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD#35: 3 Days on the Hills of Atlanta in the Rain.(part 2) 06-19-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-19-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=24</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Here's the final installment from the Music Midtown Festival...?  We bring you some of the highlightsfrom our second and third day of the trip, play some interesting commercials, and catch up with a few other things.  Also, we introduce our voicemail segment with some truly bizarre calls!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD#35: 3 Days on the Hills of Atlanta in the Rain.(part 2) 06-19-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Here's the final installment from the Music Midtown Festival...?  We bring you some of the highlightsfrom our second and third day of the trip, play some interesting commercials, and catch up with a few other things.  Also, we introduce our voicemail segment with some truly bizarre calls!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-19-05.mp3" length="39407058" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2005 23:30:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:40:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #34: 3 Days on the Hills of Atlanta in the Rain.(part 1) 06-14-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-14-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=23</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>We're back, and starting to recover from the past weekend's festivities.  This is the first of two episodes from the Music Midtown Festival
in Atlanta, GA.  This first show represents less than 10 percent of the recordings we made this weekend, over 14 hours to be exact: We take you along to the press registration, getting lost, wandering around getting tore upon margaritas - and the wonderfully abundant other substances available, two performances, and a great demo from a band we met on the trip.  Part two will be available Sunday.  We'll be updating the site with more of our photos, di's notebook ramblings, our faxes from the festival,and much more.This is just the beginning of our wild chronicles of thecrazy weekend!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #34: 3 Days on the Hills of Atlanta in the Rain.(part 1) 06-14-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We're back, and starting to recover from the past weekend's festivities.  This is the first of two episodes from the Music Midtown Festival
in Atlanta, GA.  This first show represents less than 10 percent of the recordings we made this weekend, over 14 hours to be exact: We take you along to the press registration, getting lost, wandering around getting tore upon margaritas - and the wonderfully abundant other substances available, two performances, and a great demo from a band we met on the trip.  Part two will be available Sunday.  We'll be updating the site with more of our photos, di's notebook ramblings, our faxes from the festival,and much more.This is just the beginning of our wild chronicles of thecrazy weekend!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-14-05.mp3" length="34791067" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2005 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:36:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #33 06-09-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-08-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=46</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Final Daily Dose before our departure to the Midtown Music Festival.  We discuss the press room info we got today.  We are also proud to introduce The Nate and Di Store.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #33 06-09-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Final Daily Dose before our departure to the Midtown Music Festival.  We discuss the press room info we got today.  We are also proud to introduce The Nate and Di Store.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-08-05.mp3" length="13590608" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2005 02:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:13:53</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD Review 06-07-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-07-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Couldn't even bring ourselves to publish this on our website...  Sad day for music lovers.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD Review 06-07-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Couldn't even bring ourselves to publish this on our website...  Sad day for music lovers.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-07-05.mp3" length="10496691" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2005 22:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #32 06-06-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-06-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=45</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>We discuss people discussing us, and how we're totally psyched about Music Midtown.  Also, we talk about John Sinclair Radio some more and introduce the new censored word game.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #32 06-06-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We discuss people discussing us, and how we're totally psyched about Music Midtown.  Also, we talk about John Sinclair Radio some more and introduce the new censored word game.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-06-05.mp3" length="11547045" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2005 22:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:12:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #31: Nate and Di Smoke some weed</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-05-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=21</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>After last week's "Fetusode", we decided to continue to stir things up a bit with an episode on something we feel strongly about: Tokin' it up from the shed, everybody.  Join us as we share some great clips, play a few songs, and much more.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #31: Nate and Di Smoke some weed</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>After last week's "Fetusode", we decided to continue to stir things up a bit with an episode on something we feel strongly about: Tokin' it up from the shed, everybody.  Join us as we share some great clips, play a few songs, and much more.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-05-05.mp3" length="34112780" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2005 22:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:35:29</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #30 06-03-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-03-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>We recently received a request for a grocery shopping trip along with a $100.00 donation, so we pulled out all the stops to bring you the longest NaD yet!  The sound quality could be a bit better, but it's good enough, and we think it caught the "essence" of a trip to the grocery store with Nate and Di.  Thanks Ashley Taylor.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #30 06-03-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We recently received a request for a grocery shopping trip along with a $100.00 donation, so we pulled out all the stops to bring you the longest NaD yet!  The sound quality could be a bit better, but it's good enough, and we think it caught the "essence" of a trip to the grocery store with Nate and Di.  Thanks Ashley Taylor.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-03-05.mp3" length="45912440" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2005 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:46:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #29 06-02-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-02-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Watch out Folks!  Nate and Di are the MEDIA now!  We just got our press registration packet from The Music Midtown Festival in Atlanta Ga. June 10-12. Check the About Us page for pictures taken from the stage during the last White Stripes concert we attended in Atlanta, and some videos taken from a helicopter courtesy of 99X.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #29 06-02-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Watch out Folks!  Nate and Di are the MEDIA now!  We just got our press registration packet from The Music Midtown Festival in Atlanta Ga. June 10-12. Check the About Us page for pictures taken from the stage during the last White Stripes concert we attended in Atlanta, and some videos taken from a helicopter courtesy of 99X.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-02-05.mp3" length="10887175" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2005 22:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:09:45</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #28 06-01-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-01-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Weird episode tonight.  Well, weird for us...  Check out the podCast 411 interview with Adam Curry.  We discuss The interview, The Hunter Thompson Memorial, a "Rude" KFC commercial, and Di wants everyone to know she is not pregnant.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #28 06-01-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Weird episode tonight.  Well, weird for us...  Check out the podCast 411 interview with Adam Curry.  We discuss The interview, The Hunter Thompson Memorial, a "Rude" KFC commercial, and Di wants everyone to know she is not pregnant.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD06-01-05.mp3" length="11229792" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2005 20:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:11:39</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #27 05-31-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-31-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=41</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Di's pissed.  We don't know why, but she's seriously ready to explode.  Oops, she did explode.  Check it out.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #27 05-31-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Di's pissed.  We don't know why, but she's seriously ready to explode.  Oops, she did explode.  Check it out.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-31-05.mp3" length="10887175" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2005 20:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:11:19</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #26: Nate and Di Meet Us A Fetus</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-29-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=20</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Okay, we're going to admit it, maybe this episode is a little over the top, but we here at Nate and Di strive to bring you the best in journalistic integrity.  Join us as we go into the womb for a special interview you'll only find here.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #26: Nate and Di Meet Us A Fetus</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Okay, we're going to admit it, maybe this episode is a little over the top, but we here at Nate and Di strive to bring you the best in journalistic integrity.  Join us as we go into the womb for a special interview you'll only find here.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-29-05.mp3" length="18898058" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2005 17:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:19:39</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #25 05-26-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-26-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=40</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>The great BoB Election of 1996, folks.  Come with us as we travel down memory lane and discuss an infamous prank we played during our earlier years of "mischievery".  Special guests Glenn Whitt and Tim Schmidt join us to share their memories about the shenanigans.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #25 05-26-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>The great BoB Election of 1996, folks.  Come with us as we travel down memory lane and discuss an infamous prank we played during our earlier years of "mischievery".  Special guests Glenn Whitt and Tim Schmidt join us to share their memories about the shenanigans.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-26-05.mp3" length="18440775" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2005 23:30:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:19:09</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #24 05-25-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-25-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=39</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Censored word contest winner announced tonight.  We also call back the posse and discuss some changes coming soon.  Also, our weekly listener appreciation segment, and a very interesting speech closes out the show.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #24 05-25-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Censored word contest winner announced tonight.  We also call back the posse and discuss some changes coming soon.  Also, our weekly listener appreciation segment, and a very interesting speech closes out the show.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-25-05.mp3" length="13797507" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2005 22:30:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:13:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #23 05-24-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-24-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=38</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>We revisit the Lion's Den. By request, our "DVD Review episode"  We discuss a variety of things tonight, but the distraction caused by the DVD we're watching is our main topic.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #23 05-24-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We revisit the Lion's Den. By request, our "DVD Review episode"  We discuss a variety of things tonight, but the distraction caused by the DVD we're watching is our main topic.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-24-05.mp3" length="10094270" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:10:28</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #22 05-23-05</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-23-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=37</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>We discuss our interview with podCast411, a hometown newspaper article, a moronic email, update our censored word contest, and tell about Jim Morrison's miraculous resurrection.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #22 05-23-05</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We discuss our interview with podCast411, a hometown newspaper article, a moronic email, update our censored word contest, and tell about Jim Morrison's miraculous resurrection.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-23-05.mp3" length="14069874" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2005 23:50:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:14:39</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #21: Nate and Di and The Lions Den!</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-22-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=19</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>We've covered almost every other taboo subject here at Nate and Di, so this Sunday we decided to tackle SEX!  Join us for an exiting adventure at The Lion's Den.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #21: Nate and Di and The Lions Den!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We've covered almost every other taboo subject here at Nate and Di, so this Sunday we decided to tackle SEX!  Join us for an exiting adventure at The Lion's Den.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-22-05.mp3" length="31249158" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2005 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:32:32</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #20</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-21-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=36</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Solo edition today!  Nate discusses a Yale Anthropology Professor's contract renewal battle. Serious episode, and this topic is very important to us, so look for more on this story soon.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #20</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Solo edition today!  Nate discusses a Yale Anthropology Professor's contract renewal battle. Serious episode, and this topic is very important to us, so look for more on this story soon.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-21-05.mp3" length="9220670" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2005 14:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:09:33</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #19</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-20-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=35</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Daily dose for Friday May 20, 2005.  We discuss Di's trip to the dentist, fucking up the forum and website, and a special story form our adventures managing a Drive in Theater.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #19</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Daily dose for Friday May 20, 2005.  We discuss Di's trip to the dentist, fucking up the forum and website, and a special story form our adventures managing a Drive in Theater.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-20-05.mp3" length="22516874" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 22:30:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:23:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #18</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-19-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=34</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Outdoors on the roof of the shed Edition everyone...  Short show tonight, we discuss the "media extravaganza" of our day.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #18</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Outdoors on the roof of the shed Edition everyone...  Short show tonight, we discuss the "media extravaganza" of our day.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-19-05.mp3" length="72576107" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2005 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:07:33</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #17</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-18-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=33</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Strange trip tonight! We talk about Nate's first Skype call, Star Wars(Di had to),sleeping with our iRiver, a few shout outs, and more...  Number 10 Overall at the Podcast Pickle and  Number 19 at Podcast Alley Comedy category!  Thanks, Y'all!  That really encourages us.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #17</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Strange trip tonight! We talk about Nate's first Skype call, Star Wars(Di had to),sleeping with our iRiver, a few shout outs, and more...  Number 10 Overall at the Podcast Pickle and  Number 19 at Podcast Alley Comedy category!  Thanks, Y'all!  That really encourages us.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-18-05.mp3" length="23713127" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2005 23:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:24:42</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #16</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-17-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=32</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Thank audacity for the short episode tonight, it ate our first show.  So, we discuss our day.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #16</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Thank audacity for the short episode tonight, it ate our first show.  So, we discuss our day.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-17-05.mp3" length="10918109" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2005 21:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:11:22</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #15</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-16-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=31</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Rambles from who knows where tonight!  Discussions of the "lost" refrigerator interview, Di unleashes, giggles, and makes very little sense in the longest Daily Dose Yet.  Our first podcast recorded solely on our new iRiver.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #15</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Rambles from who knows where tonight!  Discussions of the "lost" refrigerator interview, Di unleashes, giggles, and makes very little sense in the longest Daily Dose Yet.  Our first podcast recorded solely on our new iRiver.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-16-05.mp3" length="19358999" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2005 22:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:20:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #14: Nate and Di Go To War!</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NateandDi_Show05-15-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=18</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>The Home Site has been attacked! The Nate and Di website has been attacked, so come with Nate and Di as we Go To War. Also, we put an interesting twist on our guess that theme song game. Join us for the best Nate and Di episode yet.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #14: Nate and Di Go To War!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>The Home Site has been attacked! The Nate and Di website has been attacked, so come with Nate and Di as we Go To War. Also, we put an interesting twist on our guess that theme song game. Join us for the best Nate and Di episode yet.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NateandDi_Show05-15-05.mp3" length="19358999" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2005 20:30:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:20:09</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #13</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-14-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=30</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Nate and Di prepare for war.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #13</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Nate and Di prepare for war.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-14-05.mp3" length="5008370" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2005 22:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:05:13</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #12</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-13-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Our listener appreciation extravaganza! We give a shout out to all of our loyal fans.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #12</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Our listener appreciation extravaganza! We give a shout out to all of our loyal fans.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-13-05.mp3" length="7170254" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2005 15:20:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:07:28</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #11</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-12-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>We discuss the strange press we've been getting lately and have an unexpected visitor. The strangest NaD yet.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #11</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We discuss the strange press we've been getting lately and have an unexpected visitor. The strangest NaD yet.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-12-05.mp3" length="8385688" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2005 20:55:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:08:44</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #10</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-11-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Nate gets a job, so we get fucked up and ramble!!!  Thanks for listening.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #10</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Nate gets a job, so we get fucked up and ramble!!!  Thanks for listening.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-11-05.mp3" length="10643714" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2005 21:55:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:11:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #09</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-10-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Some Solidarity thanks and some more evil schemes discussed! Can you guess what Nate and Di Could possibly be up to???
Send your entries to contests@nateanddi.com.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #09</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Some Solidarity thanks and some more evil schemes discussed! Can you guess what Nate and Di Could possibly be up to???
Send your entries to contests@nateanddi.com.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-10-05.mp3" length="9729219" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2005 21:20:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:10:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #08</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-09-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>We introduce the new daily podcast and discuss the crazy weekend here at the shed.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #08</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>We introduce the new daily podcast and discuss the crazy weekend here at the shed.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NaD05-09-05.mp3" length="6844303" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2005 20:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:07:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #07: Podcasters and Day-jobs Just Dont Mix!</title>
<link>http://http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NateandDi_Show05-06-05.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>That's right, it's finally here!  This is the show you've all been waiting for.  In this episode we reveal our top-secret announcement and more.  In an uncanny twist of fate, Nate was "released" from his salaried day-job this afternoon.  That  doesn't get us down, though, as we give a gut-wrenching apology to Soccergirl, take a trip to tacobell, and try to solve a troubling mystery.  Please join us as we take you on a twisted ride through our abnormal lives!</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #07: Podcasters and Day-jobs Just Dont Mix!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>That's right, it's finally here!  This is the show you've all been waiting for.  In this episode we reveal our top-secret announcement and more.  In an uncanny twist of fate, Nate was "released" from his salaried day-job this afternoon.  That  doesn't get us down, though, as we give a gut-wrenching apology to Soccergirl, take a trip to tacobell, and try to solve a troubling mystery.  Please join us as we take you on a twisted ride through our abnormal lives!</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NateandDi_Show05-06-05.mp3" length="17425196" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2005 20:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:18:09</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD #05: Nate and Di Go To Church!</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NateandDi_Show04-28-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=15</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Inspired by a recent email urging us to visit a church from a "concerned" listener who wrote us after hearing Episode 3, we decided to heed his advice and scurry right over to downtown Charleston and stop at the first church we thought looked cool.  Charleston is the "Holy City", after all, so there were many to choose from.  Our visit lasted just over 10 minutes.  Right after a  truly strange sermon, it was cut unexpectedly short when we were asked to leave by an usher.  Our trip wasn't a total loss, though. As you'll hear, we were the most joyful people in attendance!  Also, we're proud to introduce NADS-NET, The Nate and Di Shopping Network.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD #05: Nate and Di Go To Church!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Inspired by a recent email urging us to visit a church from a "concerned" listener who wrote us after hearing Episode 3, we decided to heed his advice and scurry right over to downtown Charleston and stop at the first church we thought looked cool.  Charleston is the "Holy City", after all, so there were many to choose from.  Our visit lasted just over 10 minutes.  Right after a  truly strange sermon, it was cut unexpectedly short when we were asked to leave by an usher.  Our trip wasn't a total loss, though. As you'll hear, we were the most joyful people in attendance!  Also, we're proud to introduce NADS-NET, The Nate and Di Shopping Network.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NateandDi_Show04-28-05.mp3" length="23545859" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2005 19:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:24:31</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>NaD # 04: Our Special Presidential Episode</title>
<link>http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NateandDi_Show04-24-05.mp3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nateanddi.com/?p=14</guid>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Get ready to hear podcasting history folks!  This is a very special edition of the show featuring former President Bill Clinton.  Bill arrived in town just days ago, and we sent Diana out in the field this afternoon to get an exclusive interview. Listen carefully as he discusses a wide-ranging variety of subjects.  Also, we regret to inform everyone that our new Garage Band has broken up after only 40 seconds.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>NaD # 04: Our Special Presidential Episode</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Get ready to hear podcasting history folks!  This is a very special edition of the show featuring former President Bill Clinton.  Bill arrived in town just days ago, and we sent Diana out in the field this afternoon to get an exclusive interview. Listen carefully as he discusses a wide-ranging variety of subjects.  Also, we regret to inform everyone that our new Garage Band has broken up after only 40 seconds.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://mp3.nateanddi.com/NateandDi_Show04-24-05.mp3" length="16562590" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2005 19:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:17:15</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Nate and Di Promo</title>
<link>http://www.nateanddi.com/NateAndDi_promo.mp3</link>
<itunes:author>Nate and Di</itunes:author>
<description>Promo for Nate and Di Show by Rob from podCast411.com.</description>
<itunes:subtitle>Nate and Di Promo</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Promo for Nate and Di Show by Rob from podCast411.com.</itunes:summary>
<author>webmaster@nateanddi.com</author>
<category>podcast</category> 
<enclosure url="http://www.nateanddi.com/media/NateAndDi_promo.mp3" length="397289" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2005 00:00:49 EST</pubDate>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:duration>00:00:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords> nate and di, comedy, humor, talk, sex, music, funny, politics, liberalism </itunes:keywords>
</item>


</channel>
</rss>