<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Incline Village Real Estate News - Updated Monthly</title>
<description>Updated Incline Village Sales Statistics to include: details on Residential and Condominium sales, Year to Date, by Quarter and Subdivision - Updated Monthly.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com</link>
<item>
<title>3rd Quarter of 2007, Incline Village NV Residential Homes Market</title>
<description>3rd quarter of 2007 Incline Village, NV residential homes market summary for all subdivisions and areas including: Crystal Bay Lakefront and Mill Creek real estate.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/3q2007-residential.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>3rd Quarter of 2007, Incline Village NV Residential Condo Market</title>
<description>3rd quarter of 2007 Incline Village, NV residential condo market summary for all subdivisions and areas including: The Woods and Central Incline Village condominiums.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/3q2007-condo.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>3rd Quarter of 2007, Incline Village NV Residential PUD Market</title>
<description>3rd quarter of 2007 Incline Village, NV residential pud market summary for all subdivisions and areas including: The Championship and Incline Village Golf Course homes.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/3q2007-pud.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Residential Home Sales Incline Village, NV, 2005</title>
<description>Residential Home Sales market summary for all subdivision and areas of Incline Village in 2005. Incline residential property  statistics include: number of properties for sale and average listing price.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/residential-sales05.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Condo Sales Incline Village, NV, 2005</title>
<description>Residential condo Sales market summary for all subdivision and areas of Incline Village in 2005. Incline condo property statistics include: number of properties for sale and average listing price.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/condo-sales05.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>PUD Sales for Incline Village, NV, 2005</title>
<description>PUD Sales market summary for all subdivision and areas of Incline Village in 2005. Incline residential pud property statistics include: number of properties for sale and average listing price.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/pud-sales05.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Incline Village Residential Homes Market - 2nd Quarter 2007</title>
<description>2nd quarter 2007 Incline Village residential homes market summary for all subdivision and areas including: Woods, Lakeview and Lakefront.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/2007secondquarter-residential.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Incline Village Residential Condos Market - 2nd Quarter 2007</title>
<description>2nd Quarter 2007 Incline Village Residential Condos market summary for all subdivision and areas including: Jennifer, Upper and Lower Tyner and Ponderosa.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/2007secondquarter-condo.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Incline Village Residential PUD Market - 2nd Quarter 2007</title>
<description>2nd Quarter 2007 Incline Village Residential PUD market summary for all subdivision and areas including: Apollo, Mountain and Championship Golf Course.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/2007secondquarter-pud.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Incline Village Residential Condos Market Price Summary - 2004</title>
<description>2004 Incline Village Residential Condos market summary for all subdivision and areas: number of listings, average listing price, and median listing price.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/2004-condo-summary.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Incline Village Residential PUD Market Price Summary - 2004</title>
<description>2004 Incline Village Residential PUD market summary for all subdivision and areas: number of listings, average listing price, and median listing price.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/2004-pud-summary.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Incline Village Residential Homes Market Price Summary - 2004</title>
<description>2004 Incline Village Residential Homes market summary for all subdivision and areas: number of listings, average listing price, and median listing price.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/2004-residential-summary.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Incline Village Residential PUD Market - First Quarter 2007</title>
<description>2007 Incline Village Residential PUD - First Quarter market info: number of listings, average listing price, and median listing price.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/inclinevillage-pud1stquarter07.htm</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Incline Village Residential Condos Market - First Quarter 2007</title>
<description>2007 Incline Village Residential Condos - First Quarter market info: number of listings, average listing price, and median listing price.</description>
<link>http://www.ttahoe.com/inclinevillage-condos1stquarter07.htm</link>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>