<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><?xml-stylesheet href="http://www.blogger.com/styles/atom.css" type="text/css"?><feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:openSearch='http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/' xmlns:georss='http://www.georss.org/georss' xmlns:gd='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005' xmlns:thr='http://purl.org/syndication/thread/1.0'><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11380613</id><updated>2012-04-12T14:32:04.518-07:00</updated><title type='text'>The New Bankruptcy Law - 2005</title><subtitle type='html'>Keep up to date on the new bankruptcy law.  President Bush signed the new bankruptcy code into law on April 20th, 2005. We have 180 days to file under the old law before the new one takes effect.</subtitle><link rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#feed' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://new-bankruptcy-laws.blogspot.com/feeds/posts/default'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11380613/posts/default'/><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://new-bankruptcy-laws.blogspot.com/'/><link rel='hub' href='http://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/'/><author><name>Jeff Mathias, Bankruptcy Attorney</name><uri>http://www.blogger.com/profile/00585556775969216881</uri><email>noreply@blogger.com</email><gd:image rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#thumbnail' width='27' height='32' src='http://www.mathiaslaw.com/art/mathias.jpg'/></author><generator version='7.00' uri='http://www.blogger.com'>Blogger</generator><openSearch:totalResults>3</openSearch:totalResults><openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex><openSearch:itemsPerPage>25</openSearch:itemsPerPage><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11380613.post-111825066641417683</id><published>2005-06-08T10:02:00.000-07:00</published><updated>2005-06-08T10:18:30.640-07:00</updated><title type='text'>Important Bankruptcy Law Changes Looming</title><content type='html'>&lt;style type="text/css"&gt;
&lt;!--
.style1 {
 font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif;
 font-size: 12px;
}
.style3 {font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px; font-weight: bold; }
--&gt;
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt; Every Iowa attorney should be aware of important upcoming changes to the bankruptcy code. &amp;nbsp; President Bush has signed the new bankruptcy law and it takes effect on Monday, October 17 th , 2005. &amp;nbsp; The Bankruptcy Clerk advises the electronic filing system may be down for updates that weekend resulting in cases filed after Friday being dated for Monday, so the effective last day to file under the existing law may be Friday, October 14 th . &amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not a Bankruptcy Attorney? &amp;nbsp; Read On &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Many Iowa attorneys may be surprised to learn that the Bankruptcy Abuse Prevention and Consumer Protection Act of 2005 (BAPCPA) imposes advertising and disclosure requirements on attorneys who may never file a bankruptcy case. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; If for example, as dissolution counsel, you notice that your client may benefit from filing bankruptcy, you may be inclined to tell them relief is available and assure them they will be able to keep their home and car. &amp;nbsp; You may advise them in general terms of what sorts of debt can be discharged prior to referring them to bankruptcy counsel. &amp;nbsp; Giving such compensated advice is “bankruptcy assistance” within the new code and makes you a “debt relief agency”. &amp;nbsp; As such, you must include the following disclaimer in all advertising: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align="center" class="style1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are a debt relief agency . &amp;nbsp; We help people file for &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align="center" class="style3"&gt;bankruptcy relief under the Bankruptcy Code. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Additionally, within three business days of giving advice to a client considering bankruptcy, you must provide them with a detailed disclosure that includes advice that they do not need to hire an attorney for bankruptcy. &amp;nbsp; Depending on the complexity of the client's case, some bankruptcy attorneys wonder if such advice would be considered malpractice. &amp;nbsp; You must also execute a contract with the client within 5 days, with contents prescribed by the code. &amp;nbsp; The ABA strongly lobbied against these provisions but was rebuffed by Congressional leadership who insisted that passage depended on no amendments being approved. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Over the State Median Income: The Means Test &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The new means test is designed to force some debtors with income over the state median to file a repayment plan under Chapter 13 instead of a full discharge under Chapter 7. &amp;nbsp; First, you must apply strict expense caps intended for IRS tax collection cases. &amp;nbsp; After these caps and other allowances have been applied to each expense category, the remaining income is added together to establish whether the client is able to make payments under Chapter 13. &amp;nbsp; BAPCPA ignores the fact that debtors may not actually have much of this money left over each month. &amp;nbsp; Further, there is no exemption from the means test for debtors who fail in a Chapter 13. &amp;nbsp; These folks will apparently fall into a “no man's land” where they will be ineligible for Chapter 7 due to the means test, and unable to complete a Chapter 13 because the payments are not realistic. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reasonable Investigation Requirement &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; BAPCPA requires a reasonable investigation by counsel into the circumstances upon which the petition and other pleadings are based and permits the Court to assess attorney fees and costs upon debtors counsel personally for dismissal or conversion costs when a Chapter 7 does not succeed. &amp;nbsp; Although some bankruptcy attorneys are actually forming third party entities to investigate their clients, our United States Trustee tells me he feels that as a rule, Iowa attorneys are already performing a reasonable investigation. &amp;nbsp; Doubtless those attorneys who need to improve their case preparation will be more apt to, given the risk of paying out of pocket if a case is dismissed or converted. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Provisions &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; “Current Income” for the purposes of the means test is the average income for the prior six months, raising the question of what will happen where the bankruptcy is spurred by job loss. &amp;nbsp; Actual notice to creditors is not sufficient if not provided to a specific creditor address. &amp;nbsp; Many more documents must be filed including pay stubs for the past 60 days. &amp;nbsp; Where a debtor fails to file any of many required documents, the case is automatically dismissed. &amp;nbsp; Attorneys who fail to file any document on time or comply with each provision of the disclosure requirements may have to refund their entire fee to the client. &amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; There is a presumption under the new law that debtors cannot afford a reaffirmation where the reaffirmed debt would cause expenses to exceed income. &amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;Although the court can approve such reaffirmations, it is unclear how many hearings are possible given current resources or how such a presumption can be overcome. &amp;nbsp; There is a new bright line rule that marital debt is not discharged in Chapter 7. &amp;nbsp; For debtors over the state median income, creditors are allowed to bring motions to dismiss based on abuse or bad faith demonstrated by a totality of the circumstances. &amp;nbsp; Previously the standard was “substantial abuse”. &amp;nbsp; Debtors must complete credit counseling and budgeting classes although they may be available online. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; BAPCPA was drafted by the credit industry after they succeeded in scuttling the recommendations of the bipartisan National Bankruptcy Review Commission. &amp;nbsp; It's too early to know what the precise impact of BAPCPA will be. &amp;nbsp; The National Association of Consumer Bankruptcy Attorneys (www.nacba.org) is working double time to help Iowa members come up to speed as fast as possible. &amp;nbsp; Doubtless the bench, bar, clerks &amp;amp; trustees will work hard to make the system work as well as possible for Iowa debtors and creditors. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="style1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;*A 1998 graduate of Southern Methodist University School of Law in Dallas, West Des Moines attorney Jeff Mathias limits his practice to consumer bankruptcy and can be contacted at jeff@mathiaslaw.com. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="blogger-post-footer"&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/tracker/11380613-111825066641417683?l=new-bankruptcy-laws.blogspot.com' alt='' /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://new-bankruptcy-laws.blogspot.com/feeds/111825066641417683/comments/default' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11380613&amp;postID=111825066641417683' title='12 Comments'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11380613/posts/default/111825066641417683'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11380613/posts/default/111825066641417683'/><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://new-bankruptcy-laws.blogspot.com/2005/06/important-bankruptcy-law-changes.html' title='Important Bankruptcy Law Changes Looming'/><author><name>Jeff Mathias, Bankruptcy Attorney</name><uri>http://www.blogger.com/profile/00585556775969216881</uri><email>noreply@blogger.com</email><gd:image rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#thumbnail' width='27' height='32' src='http://www.mathiaslaw.com/art/mathias.jpg'/></author><thr:total>12</thr:total></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11380613.post-111756105451097499</id><published>2005-05-01T10:37:00.000-07:00</published><updated>2005-06-02T10:13:53.920-07:00</updated><title type='text'>The New Bankruptcy Law - April 2005</title><content type='html'>&lt;p&gt;President Bush signed the new bankruptcy code into law on April 20th, 2005.&amp;nbsp;We have 180 days to file under the old law before the new one takes effect.&amp;nbsp;So the last day to file under the old law is in mid October, 2005.&lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;p align="center"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Warning:&amp;nbsp;Do not wait until October to file your bankruptcy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
                    If you do it may be impossible to find any attorney who can file your case on time.&amp;nbsp;We expect to be extremely busy at that time.&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;tr align="left" valign="top"&gt;
                &lt;td colspan="2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Bankruptcy Law Summary &lt;/b&gt;(&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2005/04/20/pf/bankruptcy_bill/index.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Read CNN article on the New Bankruptcy Law&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;/tr&gt;
              &lt;tr align="left" valign="top"&gt;
                &lt;td width="255"&gt;&lt;h3 align="center"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Current Bankruptcy Law&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;Eligible for Ch 7 if your expenses meet or exceed &lt;i&gt;current&lt;/i&gt; income&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;td width="75%" bgcolor="#CCCCCC"&gt;&lt;h3 align="center"&gt;&lt;u&gt;New Bankruptcy Law&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;Not eligible for Ch 7 if your income is over the state median income and you can pay at least $100 monthly. &lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;May not be eligible for bankruptcy for 6 months after job loss.&lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;p align="right"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.census.gov/hhes/income/histinc/h08.html"&gt;Read US Census Median Income Figures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
              &lt;/tr&gt;
              &lt;tr align="left" valign="top"&gt;
                &lt;td width="255"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your actual expenses are ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;td width="75%" bgcolor="#CCCCCC"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Strict IRS collection guidelines dictate how much you can spend on home, car etc.
                  &lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;p align="right"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.irs.gov/businesses/small/article/0,,id=104793,00.html"&gt;Read IRS Home Guidelines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;p align="right"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.irs.gov/businesses/small/article/0,,id=104627,00.html"&gt;Read IRS Food and Other Guidelines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
                    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
              &lt;/tr&gt;
              &lt;tr align="left" valign="top"&gt;
                &lt;td width="255"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Affordable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;td width="75%" bgcolor="#CCCCCC"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new law requires attorneys to certify The accuracy of your petition.&amp;nbsp; More attorney time and expense will be involved.&amp;nbsp; Attorney fees will increase. The filing fee also increases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
              &lt;/tr&gt;
              &lt;tr align="left" valign="top"&gt;
                &lt;td width="255"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actual notice to creditors Ok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;td width="75%" bgcolor="#CCCCCC"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strict notice requirements allow creditors to continue collecting against you after filing bankruptcy even if they know about your bankruptcy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
              &lt;/tr&gt;
              &lt;tr align="left" valign="top"&gt;
                &lt;td width="255"&gt;&lt;p&gt;No classes required&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;td width="75%" bgcolor="#CCCCCC"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two classes required&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
              &lt;/tr&gt;
              &lt;tr align="left" valign="top"&gt;
                &lt;td width="255"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not required to provide tax return to creditors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
                &lt;td width="75%" bgcolor="#CCCCCC"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Required on request. &lt;br&gt;
  Failure = mandatory dismissal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
              &lt;/tr&gt;
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Features of the New Bankruptcy Law:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;ol start=1 type=1&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;The new law will deny Chapter 7 relief to people with more than the state median income and more than minimum discretionary income. Debtors who cannot file a Chapter 7 bankruptcy will have to file under Chapter 13 and pay a lot more in attorney fees and pay back up to 100% of their debt. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;If you are forced into a Chapter 13 but later cannot make the payments your case will be dismissed, and you may not be eligible for any form of bankruptcy. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;Allowable expenses are based on IRS collection guidelines, not your actual expenses. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;Income calculations for your bankruptcy would be based on your past six-month&amp;rsquo;s income. &amp;nbsp;Hence, if you lose your job, you could be ineligible for bankruptcy for six months since the Court would consider your old income as current income. Creditors will have a strong incentive to take your property quickly, before you become eligible for relief. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;Attorney certification requirements will require more attorney time and expense;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;You can exempt one radio, one TV and one VCR.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;You will have to attend credit counseling class and a personal financial management course. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;You will have to file your tax returns with your bankruptcy, making them a part of the public record. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;Fewer types of debt are discharged under the new law. Example: Debt ordered paid in a divorce decree. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;The new law does not stop landlord eviction. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;Creditors can continue to collect against you if you do not send them notice at their preferred address even if they have actual notice of your bankruptcy. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;The new law is replete with technical requirements designed to trigger automatic dismissal of the case.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ol&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iowa Senator Charles Grassley&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://grassley.senate.gov/"&gt;http://grassley.senate.gov/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt; was the principal force behind the new law.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
              &lt;![if !supportEmptyParas]&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;![endif]&gt;
&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;We expect to be very busy toward the end of the sixth month grace period.&amp;nbsp; It may be impossible to find an attorney who can accept your case late in the grace period and get it filed in time as we expect to have record high demand.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;![endif]&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="blogger-post-footer"&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/tracker/11380613-111756105451097499?l=new-bankruptcy-laws.blogspot.com' alt='' /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://new-bankruptcy-laws.blogspot.com/feeds/111756105451097499/comments/default' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11380613&amp;postID=111756105451097499' title='0 Comments'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11380613/posts/default/111756105451097499'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11380613/posts/default/111756105451097499'/><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://new-bankruptcy-laws.blogspot.com/2005/05/new-bankruptcy-law-april-2005.html' title='The New Bankruptcy Law - April 2005'/><author><name>Jeff Mathias, Bankruptcy Attorney</name><uri>http://www.blogger.com/profile/00585556775969216881</uri><email>noreply@blogger.com</email><gd:image rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#thumbnail' width='27' height='32' src='http://www.mathiaslaw.com/art/mathias.jpg'/></author><thr:total>0</thr:total></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11380613.post-111056903905777881</id><published>2005-04-03T11:08:00.000-07:00</published><updated>2005-06-08T10:15:12.286-07:00</updated><title type='text'>The New Bankruptcy Law - March 2005</title><content type='html'>&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" color=darkgreen&gt;Article Published by Jeff Mathias, Bankruptcy Attorney &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://mathiaslaw.com"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mathiaslaw.com/template-art/logo.jpg" border="0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mathiaslaw.com/bankruptcy_mp3/mp3maker_IN_2005_5-6.mp3"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mathiaslaw.com/art/clip1_u.jpg" border="0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.mathiaslaw.com/bankruptcy_mp3/V2.mp3"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.mathiaslaw.com/art/clip_long_u.jpg" border="0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="3" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" color=darkblue&gt;March 11, 2005 - Senate Passes New Bankruptcy Legislation &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" color=darkblue&gt;A bankruptcy overhaul bill the Senate passed by a 74-25 vote on Thursday would require people with incomes above a certain level to pay credit-card charges, medical bills and other obligations under a court-ordered bankruptcy plan. This is the biggest rewrite of bankruptcy laws in 27 year. Below is a summary of the changes. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current Bankruptcy Law&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Eligible for Ch 7 if your expenses meet or exceed &lt;i&gt;current&lt;/i&gt; income&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Your actual expenses are ok&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Affordable&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Actual notice to creditors Ok&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;No classes required&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Not required to provide tax return to creditors&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Bankruptcy Law&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Not eligible for Ch 7 if your income is over the state median income and you can pay at least $100 monthly. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;May not be eligible for bankruptcy for 6 months after job loss.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;blockquote&gt;
              &lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;font size="1"&gt;Read US Census Median Income Figures&lt;u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
              &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.census.gov/hhes/income/histinc/h08.html"&gt;&lt;font size="1"&gt;http://www.census.gov/hhes/income/histinc/h08.html&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/blockquote&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" align="left"&gt;Strict IRS collection guidelines dictate how much you can spend on home, car etc.&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;blockquote&gt;
              &lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;font size="1"&gt;Read IRS Home Guidelines&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;font size="1"&gt;&lt;br&gt;
              &lt;a
href="http://www.irs.gov/businesses/small/article/0,,id=104793,00.html"&gt;http://www.irs.gov/businesses/small/article/0,,id=104793,00.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;font size="1" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Read IRS Food and Other Guidelines&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
              &lt;a
href="http://www.irs.gov/businesses/small/article/0,,id=104627,00.html"&gt;http://www.irs.gov/businesses/small/article/0,,id=104627,00.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/blockquote&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" align="left"&gt;The new law requires attorneys to certify The accuracy of your petition.&amp;nbsp; More attorney time and expense will be involved.&amp;nbsp; Attorney fees will increase. The filing fee also increases.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif" align="left"&gt;Strict notice requirements allow creditors to continue collecting against you after filing bankruptcy even if they know about your bankruptcy.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Two classes required&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Required on request. &lt;br&gt;
    Failure = mandatory dismissal.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Features of the New Bankruptcy Law:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt; &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;ol start=1 type=1&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;The new law will deny Chapter 7 relief to people with more than the state median income and more than minimum discretionary income. Debtors who cannot file a Chapter 7 bankruptcy will have to file under Chapter 13 and pay a lot more in attorney fees and pay back up to 100% of their debt. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;If you are forced into a Chapter 13 but later cannot make the payments your case will be dismissed, and you may not be eligible for any form of bankruptcy. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Allowable expenses are based on IRS collection guidelines, not your actual expenses. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Income calculations for your bankruptcy would be based on your past six-month&amp;rsquo;s income. &amp;nbsp;Hence, if you lose your job, you could be ineligible for bankruptcy for six months since the Court would consider your old income as current income. Creditors will have a strong incentive to take your property quickly, before you become eligible for relief. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Attorney certification requirements will require more attorney time and expense;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;You can exempt one radio, one TV and one VCR.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;You will have to attend credit counseling class and a personal financial management course. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;You will have to file your tax returns with your bankruptcy, making them a part of the public record. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Fewer types of debt are discharged under the new law. Example: Debt ordered paid in a divorce decree. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;The new law does not stop landlord eviction. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Creditors can continue to collect against you if you do not send them notice at their preferred address even if they have actual notice of your bankruptcy. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
              &lt;li style='color:black;mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:
     auto;mso-list:l0 level1 lfo1;tab-stops:list .5in'&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;The new law is replete with technical requirements designed to trigger automatic dismissal of the case.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ol&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iowa Senator Charles Grassley&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://grassley.senate.gov/"&gt;http://grassley.senate.gov/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt; was the principal force behind the new law.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
                  &lt;![if !supportEmptyParas]&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;![endif]&gt;
  &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2" face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;We expect to be very busy toward the end of the sixth month grace period.&amp;nbsp; It may be impossible to find an attorney who can accept your case late in the grace period and get it filed in time as we expect to have record high demand.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;


&lt;a href="http://www.blogarama.com/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.blogarama.com/images/button.gif" border=0 alt="Blogarama - The Blog Directory"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
                  &lt;![if !supportEmptyParas]&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;![endif]&gt;
  &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
  &lt;![if !supportEmptyParas]&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;![endif]&gt;
  &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
  &lt;![if !supportEmptyParas]&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;![endif]&gt;
  &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
  &lt;![if !supportEmptyParas]&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;![endif]&gt;
  &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;
  &lt;![if !supportEmptyParas]&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
  &lt;![endif]&gt;
  &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="blogger-post-footer"&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/tracker/11380613-111056903905777881?l=new-bankruptcy-laws.blogspot.com' alt='' /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://new-bankruptcy-laws.blogspot.com/feeds/111056903905777881/comments/default' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11380613&amp;postID=111056903905777881' title='1 Comments'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11380613/posts/default/111056903905777881'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11380613/posts/default/111056903905777881'/><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://new-bankruptcy-laws.blogspot.com/2005/04/new-bankruptcy-law-march-2005.html' title='The New Bankruptcy Law - March 2005'/><author><name>Jeff Mathias, Bankruptcy Attorney</name><uri>http://www.blogger.com/profile/00585556775969216881</uri><email>noreply@blogger.com</email><gd:image rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#thumbnail' width='27' height='32' src='http://www.mathiaslaw.com/art/mathias.jpg'/></author><thr:total>1</thr:total></entry></feed>