<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<webMaster>Domonic Rini</webMaster>
		<managingEditor>Domonic Rini</managingEditor>
		<copyright>Maximum Threshold Radio Show 2007-2008</copyright>
		<language>en</language>
		<title>MAXIMUM THRESHOLD RADIO SHOW http://maximumthreshold.net</title>
		<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;catid=13&amp;Itemid=32</link>
		<description>MAXIMUM THRESHOLD RADIO SHOW: Is an internet radio show dedicated to presenting up and coming hard rock bands and current successful bands as well as interviews, news and music reviews.

Give this show a listen and pass us around to your friends. Click HERE to check out the Maximum Threshold Show international website. We are addictive and so is the music that we present for your listening pleasure. So crank those speakers and crack open a cold one and give us a listen and check out these bands.

Please get involved in this site and post in the forum at Maximum Threshold Forum with your comments and recommendations.

Remember that there are "No Limits To MAXIMUM THRESHOLD"

Please visit our website at MAXIMUMTHRESHOLD.NET </description>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<generator>Jitbit RSS Feed Creator</generator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 14:22:37 -0400</pubDate>
		<image>
			<title>Maximum Threshold Radio Show Archives http://maximumthreshold.net</title>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;catid=13&amp;Itemid=32</link>
			<url>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/images/comprofiler/98_464a0b9ad771c.jpg</url>
		</image>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD RADIO SHOW #43 It was a FREEVIL Night! http://maximumthreshold.net</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">This week's show was a blast. No interviews, just some awesome music, some wacky news and of course the Billboard Top 10. Watch the video stream of the show. It was an overall funny show. I rank it pretty high. Give it a listen. 

Music played: Freevil, Black Tractor, Meltdown, 3SO - 30 Seconds Out, Phanatos, Sunless Daze, Blackwater, BroknStone and much more!!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=90</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 14:22:37 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">  	  MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #42 The absolute best in Hard Rock / Metal music and music news http://maximumthreshold.net </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Dom and Dan rip out some new news in music and some really wild (Funny) news (Fairly Odd News) from around the world. Music news included: Megadeth, Steve Smyth, MT Tour 07'-08', 
Music played: El Sid, Freevil, Black Tractor, Michael Santos, Sunless Daze</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=88</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 14:22:31 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD.NET #41 MARKUS ALLEN CHRISTOPHER - MISS CRAZY </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Interview with Markus Allen Christopher, lead guitarist/vocalist for the San Francisco hard rock/metal band Miss Crazy. This was a funny, news educated show and had some really good stories. Music played: Suicide Circus, Forget to Remember, Overload, Sangata, BroknStone, Monster Madhouse, Piggy D. Remembering Never, Color Blind Aggression, Miss Crazy, Destructor, King Diamond, Blackwater, Meltdown, Sunless Dayz, Big Nasty, Michael</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=87</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 14:22:21 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #40 Radio Cult / Brian Van Meter interview </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Music News: Led Zeppelin, Doro tour US, Rob Zombie Halloween US Tour dates with Ozzy, Slash and Dave Mustaine, VH1 new show, Iron Maiden Various news, Music played: Freevil, Miss Crazy, Brian Van Meter, Alexx Calise, Color Blind Aggression, Suicide Circus, Black Tractor, Cardona, and much much more!!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=85</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2007 16:55:28 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #39 w/ BOBAFLEX.' MIKE STEEL AND ROB ZOMBIE'S - PIGGY D T</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">The show consisted of a massive interview with Bobaflex's lead guitarist Mike Steele and a hearty interview with the bass player for Rob Zombie and his solo project Evacuation Plan. 
Music news: Looney Tunes destroyed in fire, Smashing Pumpkins, Scorpions (Rudolph Shenker) / Bill Corgan, Rob Zombie's movie Halloween and new movie deal, Raven, Buckcherry, Led Zeppelin bootlegger, new Slayer Mastodon Lamb of God Unholly Alliance DVD release, Rock of Love, Sebastian Bach's Celebrity Rap Superstar, CBGB Hilly Kristal dies, Black Sabbath reunion, Lynch Box, Nikki Sixx, Billboard Top Top 

Music Played: Piggy D, Freevil, Suicide Circus, Broknstone, Groove Pipe, Justin Emord, and a whole lot more!!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=83</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #38 MEGADETH, ATREYU, AND WHOLE MUCH MORE!~</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">This was your meat and potato show, straight up hard rock and metal music and this weeks news 

Music played: Diecast, Suicide Circus, Brain Van Meter, Black Tractor, Entheogen, Featured on Fridays, Groove Pipe, Miss Crazy, Overloaded, Radio Cult, Color Blind Aggression, Santagata, Justin Emord, Freevil</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=71</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #37 W/ GEORGE LYNCH (Dokken/Lynch Mob) , JONATHAN KITA (Diecast), Carlos Cavaso (Quiet Riot, 3 Legged Dog, Hollywood All Starz), Horror Actress Lilith Stabs</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Jonathan Davis talks gaming and Guitar Hero, Robert Plant auctions off an acoustic guitar, Metallica voted Sweden's most popular concert, Slayer - Tom Araya - says they don't do anything controversial anymore, Billboard Top 10. Music played: Diecast, Justin Emord, Sweaty Johnson, Trigger Point, Color Blind Aggression, Lilith Stabs, 3 Legged Dog, Freevil, Suicide Circus and much more!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=68</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #36 ROCKSTAR CAGE MATCH W/ OZZY, EDDY VAN HALEN, RONNIE JAMES DIO, MARILYN MANSON VS SLAYER PLUS MUCH MORE: http://maximumthreshold.net</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Maximum Threshold Show takes to the show on the road, this time to cover the Rockstar Death Cage Match featuring: Tag Team fight w/ Eddie Van Halen and Eddie Money vs Eddie Vetter and Eddie Ojeda (Dubbed the Battle of the Eddie's), Ozzy vs Joe Cocker, Ronnie James Dio vs Gene Simmons, Marilyn Manson vs the entire band Slayer (featured death match), Special fight 50 Cent vs Flava Flav and Snoop Dogg in a handicap match. (Listen to the show for winners!!) 

Music news: Bumblefoot, Joe Elliot (Def Leppard), Get Thrashed Director,Rush, Drowning Pool tour dates, Bruce Kulik solo record, Exodus new songs, LA Guns Love/Hate Faster Pussycat members perform at Erotic Ball, Iced Earth new video, The Cult: new songs, Slash, Venom, Nikki Sixx, Van Halen tour dates, Paul Stanley emmy award, Zakk Wylde, Dave Mustaine (We called Dave), Mijovi lawsuit, Anthrax, Chris Caffery, Billboard Top 10 
Music Played: Freevil, Baghead, Color Blind Aggression, Faces of March, Eldimur Krimm, Trigger Point, El Sid, Suicide Circus, Evolocity, Rebel Girl, Radio Cult, Overloaded, Eddie Ojeda, and much much more 3 hour show!!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=67</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 16:09:31 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #35 w/JUSTIN EMORD &amp; ROB WERTHNER (HOT ACTION COP)  </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">This is an explosive show with Justin Emord, and Rob Werthner. Justin talks about the happenings at the Summer NAMM 2007. Rob Werthner discussed what Hot Action Cop has been up to. 

Music news: Marilyn Manson lawsuit, Pogo, Korn - Terry Bozzio, Heavy Metal Doesn't Belong In Mesa, Councilman Says, Gene Simmons Family Jewels' To Premiere In Canada With Three-Hour Mini-Marathon, MARILYN MANSON Calls Former Bandmate's Allegations 'Ridiculous, LIFE OF AGONY Drummer Seeks Musicians For New Project, SLAYER's KERRY KING Says Band Will Not Do Any More Touring This Year,STATIC-X Going For A 'Harder And More Metallic' Approach, KILLSWITCH ENGAGE: ADAM DUTKIEWICZ To Leave VANS WARPED TOUR, GODSMACK Might Launch Acoustic Tour In November, WARPED TOUR Organizer Apologizes To SHARON OSBOURNE For OZZFEST Remarks,ROB ZOMBIE: Live Album Track Listing Revealed, SCORPIONS: More North American Tour Dates Announced, Billboard Top 10. 

Music played: Black Tractor, Stymeed, John Macaluso, Freevil, Eldrimur Krimm, Suicide Circus, Color Blind Aggression, El Sid, Hot Action Cop, Justin Emord and much much much more!!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=66</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #34 - UNPLUGGED SHOW!!</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">This week's show is might different than any other show that has previously been on Maximum Threshold. This is the "unplugged" show, in which all it is, is news, no commercials, no music, just straight info, and its short! 

Music News: Dream Theater signs with Roadrunner,FREDDIE MERCURY, JIMI HENDRIX Top Supergroup Poll, PAUL DI'ANNO: I'm Not The Right Guy For The ANTHRAX Singer Job,LED ZEPPELIN: Double-CD Collection, Reissue Of 'The Song Remains The Same' Due In November, DOWN: New Album,DORO, SAXON, W.A.S.P., U.D.O. Confirmed For Germany's HEAVY CHRISTMAS MEETING,JIMMY PAGE Testifies In Bootlegging Trial,PETER CRISS: 'I'm A Kid Inside And The Music Keeps Me Young',GUNS N' ROSES Guitarist Sings 'Knockin' On Heaven's Door' In Japan,IRON MAIDEN, DRAGONFORCE Songs Added To 'Guitar Hero III,BAM MARGERA Brings Scandinavian 'Sleaze Rock' To The States ,HENRY ROLLINS Says War In Iraq 'Never Was A Good Idea,MATT SORUM Says New METALLICA Songs Are 'Sick' And 'Crazy Fast' With Lots Of 'Tempo Changes,Soilwork,JUDAS PRIEST, IRON MAIDEN, MOTÖRHEAD, SLAYER Tracks Featured On 'Heavy Metal Box',Rocklahoma Sets Stage for 2008,James Hetfield Dicusses The Band's Current Setlist, The New Album And "Master Of Puppets,Billboard Top 10</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=65</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #33 Metallica / Megadeth Warchest / Ozzfest / Rocklahoma MUSIC NEWS AND NEWS http://maximumthreshold.net  </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Music News: Megadeth "Warchest", Metallica - James Hetfield St Anger didn't work,Ozzfest no show, Tenafly Viper (Mushroomhead/Chimaira, Marilyn Manson,Korn covers album,Jimi Hendrix SG on display,Thin Lizzy,Firehouse, Dokken on Christmas Album, Alter Bridge new album,Testament sold out show,Robert Plant,Rocklahoma video pics on maximumthreshold site,Nikki Sixx Heroine Diaries,G&amp;R Reunion,Bon Jovi energy drink?, Billboard Top 10,Marcus Henderson Guitar Hero 3, Queensryche Acoustic Set, Rush conert earnings, 

Music played: El Sid, John Macaluso, Bad Side, Trigger Point, Master of Luxury, Evolocity, King Diamond, Hot Action Cop, Suicide Circus, Color Blind Aggression, Destructor, Justin Emord, Alexa Vetere, Ronny North,Black Tractor, Freevil,Eldemur Krimm (Black Fog), and much more.</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=64</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #32 INTERVIEW W/ NATHAN -SHROUD OF DISORDER, MUSIC NEWS AND NEW MUSIC http://maximumthreshold.net  </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Music News: Anthrax- Corey Taylor may be new singer (Slipnot/Stone Sour), Sebastian Bach / Metal Mike' PainMuseum, Mary Friedman new Ibanez model, Znowhite new release "All Hail To Thee", Velvet Revolver #2 Billboard Chart, Brett Michaels First Eipisode of Rock of Love to air, Guitar Hero's Marcus Henderson, Exodus tour with Vicious Rumors, Brian "Head" Welch book, Smashing Pumpkins, Rocklahoma Steven Adler to join Bang Tango, James Hetfield was not detained at UK Airport, Slash in Guitar Hero's Legends of Rock, MEgadeth tour dates 2007, Queensryche new double best of CD Sign of the Times: The Best of Queensryche, Nikki Sixx - free concert, Amy Lee and new lineup, The Simpsons new CD called Testify, John Popper off drug charges, George Michaels fined $250,000, Billboard Top 10. 

Music played: Suicide Circus, Color Blind Aggression, Eldemur Krimm, House of Heroes, Jericho 7, Black Tractor, Justin Emord, Freevil, Domonic, Remember Never,Terminal.</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=63</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2007 16:20:21 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #31 HOT MUSIC NEWS AND MUSIC http://maximumthreshold.net  </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Music News: Gidget Gein new record/tour, Peter Criss new record, Van Halen - Wolfigang tour, Metallica - setlist, Live Earth Concert coverage, Robert Plant denies Led Zeppelin reunion, Alic Cooper, Raven / Anvil / Destriuctor show, Eddie Van Halen post rehab, Def Leppard setlist- Vivian Campbell, Ozzy Walk of Fame news, UDO tour news, Queensrych - Geoff Tate and Mike Stone part in charity ride, Nikki Sixx Heroine Diaries preview, Megadeth with White Lion reunion news, Testatment new record signs deal with Nuclear Blast Records, and Billboard Top 10. 

Music played: Giget Gein, Freevil, Evolocity, Vicious Rumors, Eddie Ojeda, Trigger Point, Color Blind Aggression, Hot Action Cop, Destructor,</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=62</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #30 - SCARLETT POMERS, JAK PARIS, AARON - EVOLOCITY, JOHN MACALUSO http://maximumthreshold.net  </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Powerhouse show with much talent! Scarlett talked about the organizations, acting and rocking out on stage, Jak Paris spoke about his new record and "Chains" and Minarik Guitars as well as recording, Aaron spoke about touring, recording and history of Evolocity, Johnny Mac spoke about being a drummer with his new record and all the friends he had on it, and was really funny (A must listen to) Music news: Dio not wanting to do another Black Sabbath album, Project Revolution - bring the pyro!, Gidget Gein coming on the show next week, Sepultura guitaris swallows tv remote control battery, Marilyn Manson's unauthorized biography "Long Road ouf of Hell, Joey Vera filling in for Jim Sheppard of Nevermore, John Petrucci and Mike Portnoy discuss the songwriting process, Soilwork - new record, Death Angel- Oegueda tears eyeball, Rage Against The Machine tour, Mike Wead launches Probulator, King Diamond postpones European tour due to back problem, Get Thrashed movie, and much more!! 

Music played: Gidget Gein, Evolocity, John Macaluso, Crimson Heart, Alexx Calise, Scalera, Color Blind Aggression, Radio Cult, King Diamond, and much much much more!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=61</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #29 W/ EDDIE OJEDA (TWISTED SISTER), NICOLE -CRIMSON HEART, JUSTIN EMORD</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Music News: Ozzy Osbourne new video "The Big One's", Paul Stanley DVD, Ozzy Osbourne sells house to Christina Aguilara 10.9 million. Contest: Justin Emord won autographed CD of Hot Action Cop. Paul Stanley new DVD 

Music Played: Freevil, John Macaluso, Justin Emord, Eddie Ojeda, Black Tractor, Crimson Heart, Mower, Color Blind Aggression, and a whole bunch more!! Listen to the show 2:50 mins.</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=60</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">  	 MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #28 DORA PESCH, ADMIRAL NO BEARD- SWASHBUCKLE, AND PKS http://maximumthreshold.net </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #28 Doro Pesch, Admiral NoBeard of Swashbuckle, and PKS Music News: Joe Perry Aerosmith, Heaven and Hell new video online, Kiss offering Fans chance to vote on setlist, POD and their new record "When Angels Serpents Dance", Marilyn Manson new video "Heart Shaped Glasses", Godsmack member saves Drowning woman, Rush "Snakes and Arrows" and concert set list, Vinnie Vincent Invasion video, Ozzfest ticket. King Diamond "Give Me Your Soul... Please", Billboard Top 10 Albums</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=59</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #27 TAYLOR OF TRIGGER POINT http://maximumthreshold.net</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Interview: Taylor of the Ca. Metal / Hardcore band TRIGGER POINT Music News: Eddie Trunk &amp; Don Jamieson and myspace, Marilyn Manson shoots down My Chemical Romance, Slayer &amp; Marilyn Manson tour info, Paris Hilton and her jail time, Scarlett Pomers, New York Dolls Coney Island Show, Smashing Pumpkins show with new guitarist, Dan Spitz solo and twins boys Brendan Allen Spitz, Harptallica, Avenged Sevenfold A7X, Call In from Chris from UNN, Guns N Roses Chinese Democracy, and much much more! 

Music Played: Swashbuckle, Scalera, Trigger Point, Justin Emord, Don Moore, Kate Rigg, Piggy D and the Evacuation Plan, Alex Skolnick (Western Sabbath Stomp), Color Blind Aggression "Down in a Hole", Domonic "Melodic Murder", Synasis, and much more!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=58</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #26: INTERVIEW ALEX SKOLNICK (AST, TESTAMENT) AND RONNY NORTH http://maximumthreshold.net  </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Interview with Alex Skolnick and Ronny North: Alex spoke in regards to Testament recording and his solo works, Ronny North is on for an encore performance is indeed our household rocker! 

Music played: Alex Skolnick (Western Sabbath Stomp), Piggy D, Ronny North, Trigger Point, Justin Emord, Color Blind Aggression, Freevil (Deathblow), Swashbuckle (Walk the Plank), Dissolute, and much more. 

Music News:Nikki Sixx's The Heroine Diaries, Guitar Hero Encore: Rocks the 80's, Post rehab Eddie Van Halen to be featured in the 8/07 Guitar World, Ozzfest and how you can be on stage with Ozzy, Black Rain enters the charts as #3, The Cult signs record deal with Roadrunner Records, Poker w/ Motley Crue, Marilyn Manson, Joe Perry and Sanjaya Malakar, Kelly Clarkson, Silverchair's new record Young Modern, LA Guns tour dates, Fast Eddie Clark Anthology, Billboard Top 10 And various funny news, Strippers for thesis credit!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=57</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #25: Chris Caffery (Savatage, Trans Siberian Orhcestra &amp; CC) &amp; Cookie Cutter Girl http://maximumthreshold.net  </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Music News: Chris Caffery- Pins and Needles, Slayer Biography "Slayer: The Reign of the Planet's Heaviest Band", American Idol &amp; Joe Perry (Sanjaya Malakar, Kelly Clarkson), Venom Scandinavian tour dates, Faster Pussycat, Alice Cooper "Decades of Porn Party", Evenescence new lineup (Amy Lee), Billboard Top 10 (Linkin Park)</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=55</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #24 W/ Lemmy Kilmister, Danny B. Harvey, Tomas of Freevil http://maximumthreshold.net</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Lemmy and Danny discussed the tour with The Head Cat as well as the new guitars that they use by Minarik Guitars. Tomas Andersson from the Swedish band Freevil give an update to the band. Music news: New King Diamond Give me your soul... Please. "Never Ending Hill", Rainbow reunion, Amy Lee marriage, Brian "Head" Welch book signing dates, new Slayer merchandise, CCDeville 80's Fes,t Ozzy on Jimmy Kimmel Live, Gidget Gein signs with Amped Records, Rush review, GNR, Kevin DuBrow, Omazing Grace song, and the Billboard top 10. 

Music Played: Freevil, The Head Cat, Cookie Cutter Girl, Chris Caffery, Gods Guns &amp; Glory, King Dianond, Sunless Daze, Don Moore, and much much more!!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=53</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">  	 MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #23 WK 5/14 Interview w/ Kyle of Proximity Grey http://maximumthreshold.net </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Interview with Kyle Preston, guitarist for the band Proximity Grey. Music news: Brintey Spears, Rush "Snakes and Arrows", Chevelle equipment stolen, Samshing Pumpkins picks stolen, Montley Cruise, Vince Neil Skyler Neil golf outing, Thin Lizzy &amp; Queensryche tour, Amy Lee of Evanescence ties the knot, Joe Satriani, K.K. Downing, Dave Mustaine may run for office, American Idol Lakisha Jones axed from the show, Les Paul, and the billboard top 10 Chart, and of course Minarik Guitars promotion.</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=50</link>
			<pubDate>05/12/07</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #22 wk 5/7 / Interview SCALERA &amp; EUPHORIA http://maximumthreshold.net</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Music News: Nikki Sixx book, Minarik Guitars Inferno and Lotus, Velvet Revolver &amp; Alice In Chains show, James Hetfield honors Sammy Hagar, maximumthreshold.net updates, Linkin Park listening party, Cocaine Energy Drink, Billboard Top 10 Music: Proximity Grey, Euphoria, Color Blind Aggression, Alexx Calise, Sundaze Day 9, Chris Caffery, Denata and whole bunch more!!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=48</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #21 MUSIC NEWS WEEK OF 4/30  </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #21 MUSIC NEWS WEEK OF 4/30 Music News: Jello Biafra gave a political speech in Toledo, OH USA in regards to his ideas and plans for the war in Iraq as well as political direction (no music was mentioned). Dan was there on the scene to obtain the information and gives us the haps on the event. Twisted Sister added to Rocklahoma, Ozzy's Black Rain will have a special item inside the CD, Dowload Festival, Billboard Top 10, Minarik Guitars - Lotus and Inferno, Saxon Biff Byford video, Poison and Ratt concert news, Guns N Roses, MaximumThreshold.net , American Idol, and much more! 

Music played: Gods Guns &amp; Glory, Denata, Alexx Calise, Color Blind Aggression, Baghead and much more Contact us at : dom@maximumthreshold.net or dan@maximumthreshold.net</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=47</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #20 week 4/23 / Interview w/ Eric Antonik guitarist - Audiblethread  </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Music News: Alex Lifeson, Ozzy's new release "Black Rain", Ozzfest, Mark St. John Kiss response, Dowload concert, Mercury Records come-back, Rocklahoma, Vince Neil MotleyCruise, Interview with Eric Antonik, guitarist for the band Audiblethread. 

Music played: Denata, Audiblethread, Alexx Calise, Black Tractor, LA Guns, Chris Caffery, Split Nixon, Morality Check and more.</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=45</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #19 WEEK 4/16 -Interview w/ Comedian Don Jamieson &amp; Bald Freak recording artist, Joe Milazzo- Black Pig</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #19 WEEK 4/16 -Interview w/ Comedian Don Jamieson &amp; Bald Freak recording artist, Joe Milazzo- Black Pig MUSIC NEWS: ROCKLAHOMA, Ozzy's new release Black Rain, Dave Mustaine ebay DV8R LTD, Cocaine Energy Drink, Korn - new drummer, Billboard Top 10. 

Music: Gods Guns &amp; Glory, Color Blind Aggression, Black Pig, Cellbound, Black Tractor, Audiblethread, Nevermore, Dan singing the song TUNA,</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=32</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #18 Week 4/9 Interview w/ Jason Kelly / Angel Cardona / Alexx Calise</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">MUSIC NEWS: Mark St. James death, Lamb of God, Ozzy, Rocklahoma Festival, Tracii Guns, Minarik Guitars, Extreme, Stephen Hoffman, and a whole lot more!! 

Music by: Gods Guns and Gllory, Audiblethread, Domonic, Color Blind Aggression, More, Jason Kelly, Cardona, Burning Vegas, Alexx Calise, and much much more!! 4 hour show!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=20</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW Hard Rock/Metal #14 Interview with Cliff the vocalist of Dry Kill Logic and the CA guitarist Ronny North  </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Cliff discusses the progress of DKL and the new record. Ronny North discussed his new record, upcoming tour and guitar info. Great interviews! News to include: Van Halen, Eddie Van Halen back in rehab, David Lee Roth and VH tour/Induction ceremony, Billboard Top 10, Black Sabbath / Heaven &amp; Hell and much much much more. 

Music to include: Morality Check, Stymeed, Ronny North, Dry Kill Logic, The Ohio Sky and many more a 3 1/2 hour show packed with music and alot of news.</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=11</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #17 HARD ROCK/METAL / w BUMBLEFOOT OF GNR, MARCUS HENDERSON OF GUITAR HERO AND THE CINCI METAL BAND BLACK TRACTOR  </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">nterview with the lead guitarist of Guns N Roses, Ron Thal AKA Bumblefoot, The lead guitarist for the Playstation game Guitar Hero, Marcus Henderson and Gregg from the Cinci metal band Black Tractor. 

Music News: White Lion (Mike Tramp &amp; Vito), The Kinks, The Black Eye Peas (DUI), Heaven and Hell, Static-X, Quiet Riot &amp; Def Leppard tour dates, Evenescence, American Idol, Smashing Pumpkins, Rage Against The Machine, Judas Priest, Scorpions, Billboard Top 10 Rock Albums for the week and a whole lot more. 

Music played: Burning Vegas, Black Tractor, Audiblethread, Drenalin, Rusted Out, Ronny North, Crossroads, and who whole lot more. 3 hour show</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=21</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW #11 W/ LA Guns TRACII GUNS</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Interview with LA Guns- Tracii Guns: Tracii discusses the European Tour, evolution of his career, new music by LA Guns and technical aspects of being a musician. Music to include: LA Guns, Color Blind Aggression, American Rust, The Ohio Sky, Cardona, Living Stereo, Morality Check and much more hard rock/metal!</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=23</link>
			<pubDate>
			</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">  	 MAXIMUM THRESHOLD #10 W/ RUDY SARZO / MORALITY CHECK (RON) &amp;1 EYED BRIAN http://maximumthreshold.net </title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">FEATURED INTERVIEW WITH RUDY SARZO, EXCLUSIVE NEWS IN REGARDS TO HIS BOOK (OFF THE RAILS), DETAILS IN REGARDS TO RANDY RHOADS, INTERVIEW WITH THE KEYBOARDIST FOR THE CLEVELAND METAL BAND "MORALITY CHECK", AND A SPECIAL CALL IN FROM 1 EYED BRI FROM "THE DOMINION". Music to include Morality Check and 2nd Half.</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=24</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title xmlns="New item">MAXIMUM THRESHOLD SHOW - Hard Rock/Metal #7 INTERVIEW W/ STEVE SMYTH OF NEVERMORE</title>
			<description xmlns="This is a sample item in a feed, created by Jitbit RSS Feed Creator. NOTE: this item description should be edited.">Interview with Steve Smyth of Nevermore, Dragonlord and Vicious Rumors. Music to include: Nevermore, Dragonlord, Vicious Rumors, Antikythera, Domonic, Color Blind Aggression, The Broadview Gutters, American Rust, and Ronny North</description>
			<link>http://www.maximumthreshold.net/index.php?option=com_weblinks&amp;task=view&amp;catid=13&amp;id=26</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
