<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">

<channel>
<title>Today's Middle Level Educator</title>
<link>http://www.nmsa.org/Publications/TodaysMiddleLevelEducator/tabid/1409/Default.aspx</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2007-2010 by National Middle School Association</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle>A podcast series from National Middle School Association</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Today's Middle Level Educator, a podcast series produced by National Middle School Association, is the place to hear conversations, interviews, and commentaries from middle level practitioners, leaders, and experts.</itunes:summary>
<description>Today's Middle Level Educator, a podcast series produced by National Middle School Association, is the place to hear conversations, interviews, and commentaries from middle level practitioners, leaders, and experts.</description>
<itunes:keywords>nmsa, middle school, middle level, middle grades, young adolescents, education, teaching, teachers, principals</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:owner>
	<itunes:name>National Middle School Association</itunes:name>
	<itunes:email>webmaster@nmsa.org</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:image href="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/nmsa.png" />
<itunes:category text="Education">
<itunes:category text="K-12" />
</itunes:category>
<itunes:category text="Education">
<itunes:category text="Higher Education" />
</itunes:category>

	<item>
		<title>Active Learning for the Creative Classroom</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Mary Henton, manager of the Middle School Portal Two, talks with Cally Stockton, author of Minds and Motion: Active Learning for the Classroom.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>They discuss various activities from the book Minds and Motion: Active Learning for the Creative Classroom.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Mary Henton, manager of the Middle School Portal Two, talks with Cally Stockton, author of Minds and Motion: Active Learning for the Classroom.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep40.mp3" length="20811621" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep40.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>21:40</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>Minds and Motion, middle school, middle level, middle grades, education, Cally Stockton, student motivation, motivate students, active learning, classroom activities</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Motivating Young Adolescents</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director for NMSA, is joined by Kim Campbell, classroom teacher and member of the NMSA Site-Based Services Speakers Cadre. Jack and Kim share ideas about student motivation and the role of the classroom teacher.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>They discuss practical ways to motivate the young adolescent.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director for NMSA, is joined by Kim Campbell, classroom teacher and member of the NMSA Site-Based Services Speakers Cadre. Jack and Kim share ideas about student motivation and the role of the classroom teacher. They discuss practical ways to motivate the young adolescent.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep39.mp3" length="19324508" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep39.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>20:07</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, education, Kim  Campbell, student motivation, motivate students, motivate young adolescents, classroom motivation</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Building Positive Relationships with Your Students</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Join Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director for NMSA, and Howard Ormond, principal and member of the NMSA Site-Based Services Speakers Cadre, for a discussion on specific strategies to motivate young adolescents.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>They examine the importance of building positive relationships with your students and how teachers can truly impact the lives of young adolescents.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Join Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director for NMSA, and Howard Ormond, principal and member of the NMSA Site-Based Services Speakers Cadre, for a discussion on specific strategies to motivate young adolescents. They examine the importance of building positive relationships with your students and how teachers can truly impact the lives of young adolescents.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep38.mp3" length="18273141" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep38.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>19:02</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, education, Howard Ormond, student motivation, relationships with your students, teacher</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>School Uniforms: Jeans or Jackets?</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>The impact of school uniforms is an issue that affects schools, parents, and students alike. Join Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director, and Ms. Ernie Rambo as they focus on this timely topic.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Ernie is a classroom teacher in Las Vegas, Nevada, and has been directly involved with the implications of the uniform issue. Jack and Ernie examine the advantages and disadvantages of school uniforms and talk about questions the teachers might have regarding the uniform issue and how to address students concerns.</itunes:summary>
		<description>The impact of school uniforms is an issue that affects schools, parents, and students alike. Join Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director, and Ms. Ernie Rambo as they focus on this timely topic. Ernie is a classroom teacher in Las Vegas, Nevada, and has been directly involved with the implications of the uniform issue. Jack and Ernie examine the advantages and disadvantages of school uniforms and talk about questions the teachers might have regarding the uniform issue and how to address students concerns.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep37.mp3" length="16735256" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep37.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>17:25</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, education, Ernie Rambo, uniforms, school uniforms</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Connecting the Dots - NMSA09 Preview</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director of NMSA, talks with Rita Pierson about her upcoming speech at the NMSA09 Annual Conference in Indianapolis, Indiana.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Rita shares her thoughts on what topics she will cover as the Teacher Luncheon speaker. Rita's vast knowledge in staff motivation, poverty issues, and school climate make Rita a must hear speaker.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director of NMSA, talks with Rita Pierson about her upcoming speech at the NMSA09 Annual Conference in Indianapolis, Indiana. Rita shares her thoughts on what topics she will cover as the Teacher Luncheon speaker. Rita's vast knowledge in staff motivation, poverty issues, and school climate make Rita a must hear speaker.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep36.mp3" length="6885215" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep36.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>7:10</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, education, Rita Pierson, nmsa09</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>The Culture of Formative Assessment</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>In this second part of a two-part discussion about formative assessment, Kate Garrison, Manager of Products and services for Professional Development with Measured Progress, discusses the culture of formative assessment.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>In this second part of a two-part discussion about formative assessment, Kate Garrison, Manager of Products and services for Professional Development with Measured Progress, discusses the culture of formative assessment.</itunes:summary>
		<description>In this second part of a two-part discussion about formative assessment, Kate Garrison, Manager of Products and services for Professional Development with Measured Progress, discusses the culture of formative assessment.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep35.mp3" length="20781521" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep35.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>21:38</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, education, formative assessment, Cate Garrison, Catherine Garrison, assessment, summative assessment, classroom assessment</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>The Evolution of Advisory</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Bob Spear and Jack Berckemeyer discuss the importance of advisory in the middle school.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>They also examine how advisory has changed over the last several years with the impact of the No Child Left Behind Act and other mandates. This episode provides schools and individuals with a sense of understanding the importance a quality advisory program brings to any great middle school.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Bob Spear and Jack Berckemeyer discuss the importance of advisory in the middle school. They also examine how advisory has changed over the last several years with the impact of the No Child Left Behind Act and other mandates. This episode provides schools and individuals with a sense of understanding the importance a quality advisory program brings to any great middle school.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep34.mp3" length="18195819" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep34.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>18:57</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, Bob Spear, advisory, advisory programs</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Single Sex Classrooms</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Ever wonder about the issues regarding the single sex classroom? Jack Berckemeyer, National Middle School Association assistant executive director, and Judith Baenen, editor of NMSA's The Family Connection, take on this hot topic!</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Judith shares her knowledge of the single sex classroom and why it has become such a huge issue. The conversation also examines the differences between how girls learn versus boys and what teachers can do to address those distinctions.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Ever wonder about the issues regarding the single sex classroom? Jack Berckemeyer, National Middle School Association assistant executive director, and Judith Baenen, editor of NMSA's The Family Connection and member of the Site-Based Services Speakers Cadre, take on this hot topic! Judith shares her knowledge of the single sex classroom and why it has become such a huge issue. The conversation also examines the differences between how girls learn versus boys and what teachers can do to address those distinctions.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep33.mp3" length="15275120" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep33.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>15:54</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, Judith Baenen, classroom, single sex classroom, gender</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>The Students are SOAR-ing</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Kim Campbell, a classroom teacher and member of the NMSA Site-Based Services Cadre, talks about the SOAR program with NMSA's Assistant Executive Director, Jack Berckemeyer.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>The SOAR program has been used at Kim's school to help deal with the achievement gap. Jack and Kim share practical ways to introduce SOAR and provide concrete examples of the program's impact in the lives of young adolescents.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Kim Campbell, a classroom teacher and member of the NMSA Site-Based Services Cadre, talks about the SOAR program with NMSA's Assistant Executive Director, Jack Berckemeyer. The SOAR program has been used at Kim's school to help deal with the achievement gap. Jack and Kim share practical ways to introduce SOAR and provide concrete examples of the program's impact in the lives of young adolescents.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep32.mp3" length="10227427" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep32.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>10:39</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, Kim Campbell, SOAR, achievement gap</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Formative Assessment: Debunking the Myths</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Formative assessment is a verb, not a noun. A process whereby students and teachers maintain ongoing conversation about learning, formative assessment is key to student achievement.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Kate Garrison, manager of products and services for professional development with Measured Progress, debunks 5 myths about formative assessment in the first of this 2-part discussion.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Formative assessment is a verb, not a noun. A process whereby students and teachers maintain ongoing conversation about learning, formative assessment is key to student achievement. Kate Garrison, manager of products and services for professional development with Measured Progress, debunks 5 myths about formative assessment in the first of this 2-part discussion.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep31.mp3" length="20370587" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep31.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>21:13</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, assessment, formative assessment, student achievement, Catherine Garrison, Kate Garrison</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Student Voice and Student Choice</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>In this episode, Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director for National Middle School Association, talks with middle level expert and member of the NMSA Site-Based Services Speakers Cadre Nancy Doda on the issues of student motivation.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Nancy shares information about the power of student choice and the impact of allowing students to have a voice in the classroom.</itunes:summary>
		<description>In this episode, Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director for National Middle School Association, talks with middle level expert and member of the NMSA Site-Based Services Speakers Cadre Nancy Doda on the issues of student motivation. Nancy shares information about the power of student choice and the impact of allowing students to have a voice in the classroom.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep30.mp3" length="21219474" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep30.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>22:06</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, Nancy Doda, student motivation, student voice, classroom, student involvement, student</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Building Community and Business Relationships</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Join Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director for National Middle School Association, and Dr. Santo Pino as they discuss the importance of community involvement and business partnerships within the school.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Jack and Santo also share ideas on ways to involve businesses in your school and the issues and concerns schools might experience.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Join Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director for National Middle School Association, and Dr. Santo Pino as they discuss the importance of community involvement and business partnerships within the school. Jack and Santo also share ideas on ways to involve businesses in your school and the issues and concerns schools might experience.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep29.mp3" length="13897168" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep29.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>14:28</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, Santo Pino, community involvement, business partnerships</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Cyber-Citizenship for Young Adolescents</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Jill Spencer, a member of the NMSA Site-Based Services Speakers Cadre, has a discussion about cyber citizenship and its issues with Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director for National Middle School Association.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Jill explains what it means to be a good cyber citizen in today's day and age. She elaborates on appropriate actions for young adolescents when dealing with technology, and shares some great examples for classroom teachers to use.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Jill Spencer, a member of the NMSA Site-Based Services Speakers Cadre, has a discussion about cyber citizenship and its issues with Jack Berckemeyer, assistant executive director for National Middle School Association. Jill explains what it means to be a good cyber citizen in today's day and age. She elaborates on appropriate actions for young adolescents when dealing with technology, and shares some great examples for classroom teachers to use.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep28.mp3" length="19583503" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep28.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>20:23</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, middle grades, Jill Spencer, cyber-citizenship, cyber citizen, technology</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Voices of Teens: Writers Matter</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Michael Galbraith and Bob Vogel, authors of the new books Voices of Teens: Writers Matter and Voices of Teens: In Their Own Words tell NMSA director of publications April Tibbles how they engaged, even empowered, students through reflective writing.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Together, Michael and Bob crafted a magical program for the middle school classroom based on Erin Gruwell's Freedom Writer's Diary.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Michael Galbraith and Bob Vogel, authors of the new books Voices of Teens: Writers Matter and Voices of Teens: In Their Own Words tell NMSA director of publications April Tibbles how they engaged, even empowered, students through reflective writing. Together, Michael and Bob crafted a magical program for the middle school classroom based on Erin Gruwell's Freedom Writer's Diary.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep27.mp3" length="11763905" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep27.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>12:15</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, writing, voices of teens, Michael Galbraith, Bob Vogel, reflective writing, Freedom Writer's Diary</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Podcasts and the Science Classroom</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Todd Williamson, a 7th grade science teacher who employed student-created podcasts to enrich a science unit on human body systems.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Todd explains how producing the podcasts helped students improve science, literacy, and technology skills and understanding.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Todd Williamson, a 7th grade science teacher who employed student-created podcasts to enrich a science unit on human body systems. Todd explains how producing the podcasts helped students improve science, literacy, and technology skills and understanding.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep26.mp3" length="20883356" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep26.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 3 Oct 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>21:45</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teacher, students, podcast, classroom technology, technology, Todd Williamson</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Wikis in the Classroom</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Erica Roberts, interviewed by Mary Henton, NMSA director of integrated media initiatives.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>When Erica used wikis as the format for an annual social studies curriculum project, her students were engaged and learned.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Erica Roberts, interviewed by Mary Henton, NMSA director of integrated media initiatives. When Erica used wikis as the format for an annual social studies curriculum project, her students were engaged and learned.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep25.mp3" length="20883356" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep25.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>21:45</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teacher, students, wiki, classroom technology, technology, Erica Roberts</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Bridge Building with Skype</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Bill Ivey, interviewed by Mary Henton, NMSA director of integrated media initiatives.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Bill tells the story and shares insights about how students in his humanities class, in Massachusetts, used Skype to collaborate and learn with students in New York City.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Bill Ivey, interviewed by Mary Henton, NMSA director of integrated media initiatives. Bill tells the story and shares insights about how students in his humanities class, in Massachusetts, used Skype to collaborate and learn with students in New York City.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep24.mp3" length="18984150" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep24.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 5 Sep 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>19:46</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teacher, students, skype, classroom technology, technology, Bill Ivey</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Questions from the Undergrads</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features three middle school principals taking questions from undergraduate students.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>At the April 2008 gathering of the Collegiate Middle Level Association, students preparing to teach in the middle grades had an opportunity to pose questions to three seasoned middle school principals.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features three middle school principals taking questions from undergraduate students. At the April 2008 gathering of the Collegiate Middle Level Association, students preparing to teach in the middle grades had an opportunity to pose questions to three seasoned middle school principals.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep23.mp3" length="22440672" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep23.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>23:22</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teacher, new teacher, CMLA</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Transitioning from Life as a College Student to Classroom Teacher</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Kathy Hunt Ullock, educational consultant and member of the National Middle School Association Site Based Services cadre, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Kathy and Jack offer advice to the new teacher and discuss the importance of establishing a support system.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Kathy Hunt Ullock, educational consultant and member of the National Middle School Association Site Based Services cadre, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director. Kathy and Jack offer advice to the new teacher and discuss the importance of establishing a support system.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep22.mp3" length="18627212" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep22.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 1 Aug 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>19:24</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teacher, new teacher, Kathy Hunt Ullock</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Building Professional Relationships</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Ross Burkhardt, former teacher, past president of National Middle School Association, and a member of NMSA's Site Based Services cadre talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Ross and Jack talk about building professional relationships within the school.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Ross Burkhardt, former teacher, past president of National Middle School Association, and a member of NMSA's Site Based Services cadre talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director. Ross and Jack talk about building professional relationships within the school.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep21.mp3" length="18847059" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep21.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>19:37</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teacher, new teacher, Ross Burkhardt</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Practical Matters for the New Teacher</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Sherrel Bergmann, middle level educator and consultant, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Sherrel and Jack share concrete, practical suggestions for the new teacher. They also comment on steps to build safe, respectful relationships in the classroom.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Sherrel Bergmann, middle level educator and consultant, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director. Sherrel and Jack share concrete, practical suggestions for the new teacher. They also comment on steps to build safe, respectful relationships in the classroom.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep20.mp3" length="23289129" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep20.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 3 Jul 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>24:15</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teacher, new teacher, classroom, Sherrel Bergmann</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Understanding Young Adolescents</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Kenneth Brighton, intereviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>A middle school teacher for two decades, Kenneth is currently a professor at Johnson State College specializing in middle level education and adolescent development. This show discusses his book, Coming of Age: The Education &amp; Development of Young Adolescents.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Kenneth Brighton, intereviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications. A middle school teacher for two decades, Kenneth is currently a professor at Johnson State College specializing in middle level education and adolescent development. This show discusses his book, Coming of Age: The Education &amp; Development of Young Adolescents.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep19.mp3" length="9817887" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep19.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>10:13</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, young adolescents, adolescent development, Coming of Age, Kenneth Brighton</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>A Principal's Perspective: Supporting the First Year Teacher</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Walt Grebing, consultant and former middle level principal, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Walt and Jack discuss what principals are looking for during the interview process and tips on how to adjust to your new school environment.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Walt Grebing, consultant and former middle level principal, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director. Walt and Jack discuss what principals are looking for during the interview process and tips on how to adjust to your new school environment.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep18.mp3" length="17977286" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep18.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>17:53</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teachers, teacher preparation, new teacher, Walt Grebing, teacher interview, teams</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Thoughts on Pre-Service Preparation</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Judy Brough, professor of middle level education and consultant, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Judy and Jack talk about pre-service teacher education and reflective classroom practice.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Judy Brough, professor of middle level education and consultant, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director. Judy and Jack talk about pre-service teacher education and reflective classroom practice.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep17.mp3" length="17168117" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep17.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>17:53</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teachers, teacher preparation, new teacher, Judy Brough</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Reflections of a First-Year Teacher</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Nancy Feigenbaum, intereviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Nancy, a successful reporter for 14 years and a first-year teacher at age 41, shares her experiences in her first year of teaching. This show discusses her book, More Than I Ever Imagined: A First-Year Teacher's Discoveries.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Nancy Feigenbaum, intereviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications. Nancy, a successful reporter for 14 years and a first-year teacher at age 41, shares her experiences in her first year of teaching. This show discusses her book, More Than I Ever Imagined: A First-Year Teacher's Discoveries.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep16.mp3" length="7021322" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep16.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 2 May 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>7:18</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teachers, new teacher, Nancy Feigenbaum</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Organizing for Success</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Debbie Silver, middle level educator and consultant, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Debbie and Jack offer ideas and concrete suggestions to help the new teacher organize for success.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Debbie Silver, middle level educator and consultant, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director. Debbie and Jack offer ideas and concrete suggestions to help the new teacher organize for success.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep15.mp3" length="23900186" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep15.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>24:53</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teachers, new teacher, classroom management, Debbie Silver</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Supporting the New Teacher</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Dave Shepard, a former middle level principal, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Dave and Jack talk about identifying a good teaching candidate, and offer advice to the new teacher about first steps in classroom management and student motivation.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Dave Shepard, a former middle level principal, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director. Dave and Jack talk about identifying a good teaching candidate, and offer advice to the new teacher about first steps in classroom management and student motivation.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep14.mp3" length="20877087" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep14.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>21:44</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teachers, new teacher, hiring, classroom management, student motivation</itunes:keywords>
	</item>


	<item>
		<title>The War Against Bullying</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Charlene Giannetti and Margaret Sagarese, intereviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Charlene and Margaret are recognized experts on young adolescent behavior. This episode discusses the publication Keep Cliques and Bullies from Invading Your School, and provides useful information on dealing with this issue.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Charlene Giannetti and Margaret Sagarese, intereviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications. Charlene and Margaret are recognized experts on young adolescent behavior. This episode discusses the publication Keep Cliques and Bullies from Invading Your School, and provides useful information on dealing with this issue.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep13.mp3" length="16283715" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep13.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>16:57</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, bully, bullies, cliques</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>The School and Familly Connection</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Judith Baenen, middle level professor and educator, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Judith and Jack talk about building relationships with parents and families, pre-service course work, suppporting new teachers, and maintaining a sense of humor.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Judith Baenen, middle level professor and educator, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director. Judith and Jack talk about building relationships with parents and families, pre-service course work, suppporting new teachers, and maintaining a sense of humor.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep12.mp3" length="20272718" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep12.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>21:07</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teachers, new teacher, teacher preparation, parents, family</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>On Being a New Teacher</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Nick Toombs, a second year teacher in Denver, CO, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Nick shares some of his experiences as a new teacher and talks about the preparation necessary for the first interview and the difference between his first and second years of teaching.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Nick Toombs, a second year teacher in Denver, CO, talking with Jack Berckemeyer, NMSA assistant executive director. Nick shares some of his experiences as a new teacher and talks about the preparation necessary for the first interview and the difference between his first and second years of teaching.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep11.mp3" length="19610670" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep11.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>22:25</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, teachers, new teacher, teacher preparation, teacher interview</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Book Study for Staff Development</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Gail Heinemeyer, former middle school principal, talking with NMSA directors Jack Berckemeyer and Mary Henton.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>The conversation focuses on the advantages of staff participation in a book study on This We Believe: Successful School for Young Adolescents. Gail also offers advice to leverage data for student achievement.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Gail Heinemeyer, former middle school principal, talking with NMSA directors Jack Berckemeyer and Mary Henton. The conversation focuses on the advantages of staff participation in a book study on This We Believe: Successful School for Young Adolescents. Gail also offers advice to leverage data for student achievement.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep10.mp3" length="10516715" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep10.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>10:57</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>middle school, middle level, staff development, teachers, This We Believe, professional development, student achievement</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Expressions from the Middle</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features winning student podcasts from the 2007-2008 edition of Expressions from the Middle.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Expressions from the Middle is an online feature of Month of the Young Adolescent that celebrates young adolescents by showcasing student creative projects from around the world.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features winning student podcasts from the 2007-2008 edition of Expressions from the Middle. Expressions from the Middle is an online feature of Month of the Young Adolescent that celebrates young adolescents by showcasing student creative projects from around the world.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep9.mp3" length="11987513" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep9.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>12:29</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>moya, middle school, middle level, middle grades, young adolescents, students</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>The Bright Middle Schooler</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Carol Ann Tomlinson, interviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Carol is a recognized expert on gifted and talented students, meeting the needs of all students, and differentiated learning. This show discusses Carol's recent book Smart in the Middle Grades: Classrooms That Work for Bright Middle Schoolers. Carol offers some insights about working with high ability and high potential students.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Carol Ann Tomlinson, interviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications. Carol is a recognized expert on gifted and talented students, meeting the needs of all students, and differentiated learning. This show discusses Carol's recent book Smart in the Middle Grades: Classrooms That Work for Bright Middle Schoolers. Carol offers some insights about working with high ability and high potential students.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep8.mp3" length="12688848" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep8.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>13:13</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>Carol Ann Tomlinson, middle school, students, gifted students, talented students, differentiated learning</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Successful Advisory Programs</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Sue Thompson and John Niska, interviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Together they discuss NMSA's newest professional development kit, Launching a Successful Advisory Program. The show highlights the importance of authentic advocacy and advisory programs, while John and Sue share their experiences.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Sue Thompson and John Niska, interviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications. Together they discuss NMSA's newest professional development kit, Launching a Successful Advisory Program. The show highlights the importance of authentic advocacy and advisory programs, while John and Sue share their experiences.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep7.mp3" length="9012479" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep7.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2007 08:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>9:23</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>Sue Thompson, John Niska, middle school, advisory, advisory program, advocacy</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>High Ability, High Potential Students</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Susan Rakow, Ph.D., interviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Dr. Rakow is assistant professor in Curriculum and Gifted Education at Cleveland State University and has 30 years experience teaching middle school and gifted students. Susan talks about meeting the needs of all students, including those with high ability and high potential.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Susan Rakow, Ph.D., interviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications. Dr. Rakow is assistant professor in Curriculum and Gifted Education at Cleveland State University and has 30 years experience teaching middle school and gifted students. Susan talks about meeting the needs of all students, including those with high ability and high potential.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep6.mp3" length="11832032" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep6.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2007 11:30:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>12:19</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>Susan Rakow, middle school, students, gifted students, high ability students, high potential students</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Pointers for Principals, How to Hire the Best Teachers</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Ed Vittardi, interviewed by Mary Henton, NMSA director of integrated media initiatives.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Ed is currently working with NMSA as a facilitator for the Summer Leadership Institute. He is also a very successful principal in Ohio and serves on the Ohio Middle School Board. He shares his insights about finding and interviewing candidates for teaching positions.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Ed Vittardi, interviewed by Mary Henton, NMSA director of integrated media initiatives. Ed is currently working with NMSA as a facilitator for the Summer Leadership Institute. He is also a very successful principal in Ohio and serves on the Ohio Middle School Board. He shares his insights about finding and interviewing candidates for teaching positions.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep5.mp3" length="14690455" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep5.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2007 13:30:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>15:18</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>Ed Vittardi, middle school, teacher, principal, interview, teacher interview, interview tips</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Interview Tips for Teachers</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Gail Heinemeyer, interviewed by Mary Henton, NMSA director of integrated media initiatives.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Gail is currently a principal in Pennsylvania and is a facilitator for NMSA's Summer Leadrship Institute. Gail provides practical interviewing tips and helpful information for aspiring teachers.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Gail Heinemeyer, interviewed by Mary Henton, NMSA director of integrated media initiatives. Gail is currently a principal in Pennsylvania and is a facilitator for NMSA's Summer Leadrship Institute. Gail provides practical interviewing tips and helpful information for aspiring teachers.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep4.mp3" length="11913534" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep4.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2007 10:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>12:24</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>Gail Heinemeyer, middle school, teacher, interview, teacher interview, interview tips</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Interview Tips for Principals</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Santo Pino, interviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Santo has more than 40 years experience in education at all levels and is a facilitator for the NMSA Leadership Institute. His vast knowledge of middle level issues makes him an excellent resource for invaluable advice for aspiring and experienced principals preparing for an interview.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Santo Pino, interviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications. Santo has more than 40 years experience in education at all levels and is a facilitator for the NMSA Leadership Institute. His vast knowledge of middle level issues makes him an excellent resource for invaluable advice for aspiring and experienced principals preparing for an interview.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep3.mp3" length="7341897" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep3.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2007 13:30:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>7:38</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>Santo Pino, middle school, principal, interview, principal interview, interview tips</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Bloom's Taxonomy in the Classroom</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Sandra Schurr, interviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Sandra is the director of the National Resource Center for Middle Grades/High School Education at the University of South Florida. Sandra discusses the publication, Ignite Student Intellect and Imagination in Mathematics. Today's show provides practical strategies for bringing rich activities based on Bloom's Taxonomy to the classroom.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Sandra Schurr, interviewed by April Tibbles, NMSA director of publications. Sandra is the director of the National Resource Center for Middle Grades/High School Education at the University of South Florida. Sandra discusses the publication, Ignite Student Intellect and Imagination in Mathematics. Today's show provides practical strategies for bringing rich activities based on Bloom's Taxonomy to the classroom.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep2.mp3" length="11312091" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep2.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 11:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>11:47</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>Sandra Schurr, middle school, Bloom's taxonomy, Ignite, classroom activities</itunes:keywords>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Democratic Classroom</title>
		<itunes:author>National Middle School Association</itunes:author>
		<itunes:subtitle>Features Mark Springer and two of his students, interviewed by April Tibble, NMSA Director of Publications.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Mark is a teacher at Radnor Middle School (Radnor, PA) and the author of Soundings: A Democratic, Student-Centered Education. Mark facilitates the development of student-generated, interdisciplinary curriculum.</itunes:summary>
		<description>Features Mark Springer and two of his students, interviewed by April Tibble, NMSA Director of Publications. Mark is a teacher at Radnor Middle School (Radnor, PA) and the author of Soundings: A Democratic, Student-Centered Education. Mark facilitates the development of student-generated, interdisciplinary curriculum.</description>
		<enclosure url="http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep1.mp3" length="11347617" type="audio/mpeg" />
		<guid>http://www.nmsa.org/portals/0/media/podcast/TMLE_ep1.mp3</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 12:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		<itunes:duration>11:49</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>Mark Springer, middle school, interdisciplinary curriculum, curriculum</itunes:keywords>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>


