<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
   <rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/DTDs/Podcast-1.0.dtd"  version="2.0">
     <channel>
       <title>Family Health Radio</title>
       <itunes:author>Family Health</itunes:author>
       <link>http://fhradio.org</link>
       <description>A daily series of 2 1/2 minute radio programs heard on over 250 radio stations.Providing practical, easy-to-understand, honest 
health information on common health problems and the latest health care developments. A production of The WOUB Center For Public Media. And 
supported by the Osteopathic Community</description>
      <itunes:subtitle>Information to help you lead a healthy lifestyle </itunes:subtitle>
     <itunes:summary>A daily series of 2 1/2 minute radio programs heard on over 250 radio stations.Providing practical, easy-to-understand, 
honest health information on common health problems and the latest health care developments. A production of The WOUB Center For Public 
Media. And supported by the Osteopathic Community. Online at fhradio.org</itunes:summary>
     <copyright>2011 Ohio University</copyright>
     <itunes:owner>
     <itunes:name>Family Health Radio</itunes:name>
     <itunes:email>bilski@fhradio.org</itunes:email>
     </itunes:owner>
     <itunes:image rel="image" href="http://fhradio.org/images/FH_LOGO_POD.jpg">Family Health Radio</itunes:image>
     <image>
     <url>http://fhradio.org/images/FH_LOGO_SM_POD.jpg</url>
     <title>Family Health Radio</title>
     <link>http://fhradio.org</link>
     </image>
     <category>Health</category>
     <itunes:category text="Science &amp; Medicine">
          <itunes:category text="Medicine"/>
     </itunes:category>
<itunes:category text="Health">
          <itunes:category text="Fitness &amp; Nutrition"/>
     </itunes:category>
<itunes:category text="Health">
          <itunes:category text="Self-Help"/>
     </itunes:category>
	<lastBuildDate> Thu, 31 May 2012  14:35:00 EST </lastBuildDate>
<item>
	<title> Diabetic foot problems </title>
	<itunes:author>Family Health</itunes:author>
	<author>Family Health Radio 2011 Ohio University</author>
	<description>Why do people with diabetes need to be especially concerned about their feet? Many people with diabetes have 
	problems with the nerves in their feet.  That means they may not feel pressure points on the bottoms of their feet, and because they 
	are also likely to have problems with blood circulation they're especially prone to skin breakdown, foot ulcers, and more serious foot 
	problems.  Left untreated, these problems may even necessitate amputation.  More than twenty-thousand amputations are performed 
	every year on people with diabetes. Script Number: 32216 For archived Family Health programs visit fhradio.org. </description>
	<itunes:summary>Why do people with diabetes need to be especially concerned about their feet? Many people with diabetes have 
	problems with the nerves in their feet.  That means they may not feel pressure points on the bottoms of their feet, and because they 
	are also likely to have problems with blood circulation they're especially prone to skin breakdown, foot ulcers, and more serious foot 
	problems.  Left untreated, these problems may even necessitate amputation.  More than twenty-thousand amputations are performed 
	every year on people with diabetes. Script Number: 32216 For archived Family Health programs visit fhradio.org. </itunes:summary>
	<link>  http://fhradio.org/MP3/32216.mp3 </link>
	<pubDate> Mon, 28 May 2012  00:00:00 EST </pubDate>
	<enclosure url="http://fhradio.org/MP3/32216.mp3" length="" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:duration>2:30</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Diabetic foot problems Family Health Information Osteopathic</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
	<title> CT scans for kids </title>
	<itunes:author>Family Health</itunes:author>
	<author>Family Health Radio 2011 Ohio University</author>
	<description>Do American children receive too much radiation from medical imaging tests? Americans today receive more radiation 
	from medical imaging procedures like x-rays and CT scans that ever before. Approximately seven million CT scans are performed on 
	children every year in the U.S., and that number is rising by about ten percent each year.  Although x-rays emit very little radiation, CT 
	scans emit much more -- the equivalent of almost 100 x-rays per scan -- and some experts believe that they raise the risk for cancer,
	 especially among children. Script Number: 32217 For archived Family Health programs visit fhradio.org. </description>
	<itunes:summary>Do American children receive too much radiation from medical imaging tests? Americans today receive more 
	radiation from medical imaging procedures like x-rays and CT scans that ever before. Approximately seven million CT scans are 
	performed on children every year in the U.S., and that number is rising by about ten percent each year.  Although x-rays emit very 
	little radiation, CT scans emit much more -- the equivalent of almost 100 x-rays per scan -- and some experts believe that they raise 
	the risk for cancer, especially among children. Script Number: 32217 For archived Family Health programs visit fhradio.org. 
	</itunes:summary>
	<link>  http://fhradio.org/MP3/32217.mp3 </link>
	<pubDate> Tue, 29 May 2012  00:00:00 EST </pubDate>
	<enclosure url="http://fhradio.org/MP3/32217.mp3" length="" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:duration>2:30</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>CT scans for kids Family Health Information Osteopathic</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
	<title> Fast walkers </title>
	<itunes:author>Family Health</itunes:author>
	<author>Family Health Radio 2011 Ohio University</author>
	<description>Can you predict someone's life span based on how fast they walk?  We tend to use images of speed when talking about
	 the health of older adults.  We describe a hearty older relative as having "a spring in her step," or express concern about an ailing 
	friend, who is "starting to slow down".  A report recently published in the Journal of the American Medical Association may lend 
	scientific support to these ideas. Script Number: 32218 For archived Family Health programs visit fhradio.org. </description>
	<itunes:summary>Can you predict someone's life span based on how fast they walk?  We tend to use images of speed when talking 
	about the health of older adults.  We describe a hearty older relative as having "a spring in her step," or express concern about an 
	ailing friend, who is "starting to slow down".  A report recently published in the Journal of the American Medical Association may lend 
	scientific support to these ideas. Script Number: 32218 For archived Family Health programs visit fhradio.org. </itunes:summary>
	<link>  http://fhradio.org/MP3/32218.mp3 </link>
	<pubDate> Wed, 30 May 2012  00:00:00 EST </pubDate>
	<enclosure url="http://fhradio.org/MP3/32218.mp3" length="" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:duration>2:30</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Fast walkers Family Health Information Osteopathic</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
	<title> Information about Salvia </title>
	<itunes:author>Family Health</itunes:author>
	<author>Family Health Radio 2011 Ohio University</author>
	<description>What is the salvia drug, and what are the health risks involved with its use? Interest in the not-yet-illegal drug called 
	salvia has sky-rocketed, largely due to a leaked internet video showing pop star Miley Cyrus smoking the herb.  The New York Times 
	reported that shortly after the Cyrus video appeared, Google searches for salvia jumped by about 600 percent. Script Number: 32219 
	For archived Family Health programs visit fhradio.org. </description>
	<itunes:summary>What is the salvia drug, and what are the health risks involved with its use? Interest in the not-yet-illegal drug called 
	salvia has sky-rocketed, largely due to a leaked internet video showing pop star Miley Cyrus smoking the herb.  The New York Times 
	reported that shortly after the Cyrus video appeared, Google searches for salvia jumped by about 600 percent. Script Number: 32219 
	For archived Family Health programs visit fhradio.org. </itunes:summary>
	<link>  http://fhradio.org/MP3/32219.mp3 </link>
	<pubDate> Thu, 31 May 2012  00:00:00 EST </pubDate>
	<enclosure url="http://fhradio.org/MP3/32219.mp3" length="" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:duration>2:30</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Information about Salvia Family Health Information Osteopathic</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
	<title> Stop smoking drugs </title>
	<itunes:author>Family Health</itunes:author>
	<author>Family Health Radio 2011 Ohio University</author>
	<description>Are there prescription drugs that can help you quit smoking -- and do they work? Addiction works in funny ways.  While
	 one person might be able to quit smoking cold turkey and never look back, another person tries to quit countless times, to no avail.  
	The cravings cause extreme discomfort, distraction and irritability, as well as physical symptoms like headaches, stomach pain and 
	soreness in the mouth. Script Number: 32220 For archived Family Health programs visit fhradio.org. </description>
	<itunes:summary>Are there prescription drugs that can help you quit smoking -- and do they work? Addiction works in funny ways.  
	While one person might be able to quit smoking cold turkey and never look back, another person tries to quit countless times, to no 
	avail.  The cravings cause extreme discomfort, distraction and irritability, as well as physical symptoms like headaches, stomach pain 
	and soreness in the mouth. Script Number: 32220 For archived Family Health programs visit fhradio.org. </itunes:summary>
	<link>  http://fhradio.org/MP3/32220.mp3 </link>
	<pubDate> Fri, 01 Jun 2012  00:00:00 EST </pubDate>
	<enclosure url="http://fhradio.org/MP3/32220.mp3" length="" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:duration>2:30</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Stop smoking drugs Family Health Information Osteopathic</itunes:keywords>
</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
