<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/DTDs/Podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>-- Invitrogen Live Science Enhanced Podcasts --</title>
  <link>http://www.invitrogen.com/livescience</link>
  <description>FREE Bioscience seminars delivered to your iPod</description>
  <language>en-us</language>
  <copyright>&#xA9;2005 Invitrogen Ltd</copyright>
  <docs>http://www.invitrogen.com</docs>
  <managingEditor>Invitrogen Live Science Team</managingEditor>
  
  <itunes:category text="Science"></itunes:category>
  <itunes:keywords>invitrogen science life science stem cells bioscience webinar seminar livescience</itunes:keywords>
  <itunes:image>http://www.invitrogen.com/downloads/ivgn_logo.jpg</itunes:image>

  <image>
    <url>http://www.invitrogen.com/downloads/ivgn_logo.jpg</url> 
    <title>FREE Invitrogen bioscience seminars delivered to your iPod</title> 
    <link>http://www.invitrogen.com</link> 
    <description>Invitrogen Live Science</description> 
    <width>144</width> 
    <height>144</height> 
  </image>

  <item>
    <title>Martin Wisher and Alex Miller: EU Regulatory Controls for the Use of Bovine Sera</title>
    <link>http://www.invitrogen.com/livescience</link>
    <description>Dr Martin Wisher and Alex Miller B.Sc.(hons.) discuss the EU Regulatory Controls for the Use of Bovine Sera</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.invitrogen.com/downloads/WISHERpod.m4b"  length="25004672" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2005 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
	<itunes:keywords>Martin Wisher Alex Miller Regulatory Controls Bovine Sera Invitrogen Live Science</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>  

  <item>
    <title>Mathias Uhlen: Human Protein Map</title>
    <link>http://www.invitrogen.com/livescience</link>
    <description>A Human Protein Atlas for Normal and Cancer Tissues</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.invitrogen.com/downloads/UHLENpod.m4b"  length="45300112" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2005 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
	<itunes:keywords>Mathias Uhlen Human Protein Map Invitrogen Live Science</itunes:keywords> 
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Miodrag Stojkovic: Embryonic Stem Cells</title>
    <link>http://www.invitrogen.com/livescience</link>
    <description>Derivation, Growth, and Nuclear Transfer of Human Embryonic Stem Cells</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.invitrogen.com/downloads/MIODRAGpod.m4b"  length="47896560" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2005 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
	<itunes:keywords>Miodrag Stojkovic Embryonic Stem Cells Invitrogen Live Science</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Steve Bustin: Quantification of mRNA</title>
    <link>http://www.invitrogen.com/livescience</link>
    <description>Appropriate quantification of mRNA in Human Tissue</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.invitrogen.com/downloads/BUSTINpod.m4b"  length="58673296" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2005 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
	<itunes:keywords>Stephen Steve Bustin Quantification of mRNA Invitrogen Live Science</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
    
  <item>
    <title>Matthew Baker: Nucleic Acid Purification</title>
    <link>http://www.invitrogen.com/livescience</link>
    <description>Invitrogen launched an exciting new products based on the patent-protected ChargeSwitch nucleic acid purification technology earlier this year. Invitrogens new ChargeSwitch technology can be used with either DNA or RNA in a range of formats, and includes simple manual purification of a few samples as well as high throughput automated applications. ChargeSwitch requires just three simple steps to extract nucleic acids from a wide variety of sources, including bacteria, tissues, blood, forensic sample and buccal cells, and excels on small sample sizes. Unlike other DNA/RNA purification methods, ChargeSwitch is 100 percent water-based and does not need hazardous or caustic chemicals, which are known to compromise the efficiency of many downstream processes such as PCR and their absence in ChargeSwitch-based protocols, can offer significant performance benefits.</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.invitrogen.com/downloads/BAKERMpod.m4b"  length="44763216" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2005 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
	<itunes:keywords>Matthew Baker Nucleic Acid Purification Invitrogen Live Science</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Thomas Joos: Protein Microarrays</title>
    <link>http://www.invitrogen.com/livescience</link>
    <description>Thomas Joos discusses Protein Microarrays.</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.invitrogen.com/downloads/JOOSpod.m4b"  length="48953824" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2005 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
	<itunes:keywords>Thomas Joos Protein microarray Invitrogen Live Science </itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
    <title>Dr Renaud Vincentelli: Recombinant Protein Expression</title>
    <link>http://www.invitrogen.com/livescience</link>
    <description>Research Leader CNRS, Molecular Transport and Signalling and Structural Genomics Research Group, Marseille, France.</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.invitrogen.com/downloads/VINCENTpod.m4b"  length="48953824" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2004 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
	<itunes:keywords>Dr Renaud Vincentelli Recombinant Protein Expression Invitrogen Live Science </itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
    <title>Dr Rene Ketting: Gene Silencing RNAI</title>
    <link>http://www.invitrogen.com/livescience</link>
    <description>Dr Ketting is a Senior Scientist working with Prof Dr Plasterk at the Netherlands Institute for Developmental Biology in Utrecht.</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.invitrogen.com/downloads/KETTINGpod.m4b"  length="48953824" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2004 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
	<itunes:keywords>Thomas Joos Protein microarray Invitrogen Live Science </itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
    <title>Dr Michael Taussig: Protein Arrays</title>
    <link>http://www.invitrogen.com/livescience</link>
    <description>Dr Taussig is Head of the Technology Research Group: Display of protein libraries for selection and evolution of individual members, and their application in isolation of antibodies, generation of protein arrays and discovery of protein-protein interactions. He is also Chairman of the European Science Foundation programme on Integrated Approaches to Functional Genomics: Its aim is to promote the development of functional genomics in Europe through activities such as workshops, training courses, a large scale Euroconference and an informative website.</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.invitrogen.com/downloads/TAUSSIGpod.m4b"  length="48953824" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2004 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
	<itunes:keywords>Dr Michael Taussig Protein Arrays Invitrogen Live Science </itunes:keywords>
  </item>

</channel>
</rss> 
