<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Hex the Dex</title>
<description>British podcast championing new electronic/dance tunes, breaks, bootlegs and remixes. With presenters Dave and Dave! Enjoy!</description>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com</link>
<image>
       <url>http://www.hexthedex.com/images/hex_300x300.jpg</url>
       <title>Hex the Dex</title>
       <link>http://www.hexthedex.com</link>
</image>
<itunes:image href="http://www.hexthedex.com/images/hex_300x300.jpg"></itunes:image>
<itunes:summary>"Outstanding and original!" British comedy and breakbeat podcast... Yes, you heard it right, comedy and breaks!</itunes:summary>
<itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
<language>en-gb</language>
<itunes:category text="Comedy"></itunes:category>
<itunes:category text="Music"></itunes:category>
<itunes:owner>
              <itunes:name>Dave, Dave &amp; Dom</itunes:name>
              <itunes:email>dave@hexthedex.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:keywords>Comedy,music,breakbeat,breaks,echaskech,dave and dave,good,funny,uk,electronica,dance music,chat,amusing</itunes:keywords>
<item>
  <title>Platters That Matter - Hex The Dex - March 2012</title> 
  <description>
  	Lorraine Kelly on your window? You need to get that checked. We can't stand her, and neither can Missy. The freak. Take a two hour stroll through the minds of a couple of Daves, with the comforting hand of Dom to lead the way. You won't regret it, unless of course you are seafood intolerant.
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://hexthedex.com/shows/Platters_That_Matter_HexTheDex_March2012.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://hexthedex.com/shows/Platters_That_Matter_HexTheDex_March2012.mp3" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
  <guid>http://hexthedex.com/shows/Platters_That_Matter_HexTheDex_March2012.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Seize Pie Potato - Hex The Dex - Feb 2012</title> 
  <description>What do they say? Good morning or afternoon or evening to you
prospective listener and welcome to this text description of a
podcast. This show is as meaty as it is silly, it is as silly as a
sausage and as sausagy as gay porn. That’s right, gay porn..what of
it? You can’t curry love…that’s what they say. Enjoy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://hexthedex.com/shows/Seize_Pie_Potato_HexTheDex_Feb2012.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://hexthedex.com/shows/Seize_Pie_Potato_HexTheDex_Feb2012.mp3" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://hexthedex.com/shows/Seize_Pie_Potato_HexTheDex_Feb2012.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
  <title>A View To A Grill - Hex The Dex - Dec 2011</title> 
  <description>What do they say? Good morning or afternoon or evening to you
prospective listener and welcome to this text description of a
podcast. This show is as meaty as it is silly, it is as silly as a
sausage and as sausagy as gay porn. That’s right, gay porn..what of
it? You can’t curry love…that’s what they say. Enjoy.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://hexthedex.com/shows/A_View_To_A_Grill_HexTheDex_Dec2011.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://hexthedex.com/shows/A_View_To_A_Grill_HexTheDex_Dec2011.mp3" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://hexthedex.com/shows/A_View_To_A_Grill_HexTheDex_Dec2011.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Woo Yeah - Hex The Dex - Oct 2011</title> 
  <description>Where else can you go for meat bands, nuclear Sinatras, pcp olympics, and 2 tunes featuring the 'woo yeah' guy? Nowhere.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2011 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Woo_Yeah-HexTheDex-11_10_16.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Woo_Yeah-HexTheDex-11_10_16.mp3" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Woo_Yeah-HexTheDex-11_10_16.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
  <title>The Godfather - Hex The Dex - Apr 2011</title> 
  <description>Hex the Dex is back where it started,  in podcast form. Uncut,uncensored and in breathtaking dead-central super-sounding mono. All of the fun with all of the not fun still there too. It’s literally less but seems like more. Beatable value on a shoestring budget doesn’t get more less than this. It’s still quite funny though and there’s some good beats. Why not give it a wiz.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 29 APR 2011 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Godfather_HexTheDex_Apr2011.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Godfather_HexTheDex_Apr2011.mp3" length="57397248" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Godfather_HexTheDex_Apr2011.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>The Tumnus Conundrum 2 - Hex The Dex - Oct 2010</title> 
  <description>OK, fair play. The first part of this Tumnus Conundrum programme contained few, if any references to Narnia or Mr Tumnus or indeed a Conundrum. Fear not hardy and tolerant listener for this part 2 programme does have all the right places in the right bits. For example Mr Tumnus is mentioned repeatedly in an unfolding conundrum scenario, very much in keeping with the original programme title, The Tumnus Conundrum. WARNING: Fans of the timid faun known as Mr Tumnus my wish to avoid listening due to Tumnuicide.</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Tumnus_Conundrum_2_HexTheDex_Oct2010.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Tumnus_Conundrum_2_HexTheDex_Oct2010.mp3" length="43986944" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Tumnus_Conundrum_2_HexTheDex_Oct2010.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>The Tumnus Conundrum - Hex The Dex - Oct 2010</title> 
  <description>BACK! If you like big backs then you are in luck, coz we are massively back in a huge way. Sorry for the neglect podcasterz, it wont happen again. This show if crammed to the gullet with all the usual meaningless dross and disposable nonsense that just passes for borderline entertainment in our half lived lives. The Hex The Dex silly car is revved and ready, lets off-road…..in Narnia.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2010 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Tumnus_Conundrum_1_HexTheDex_Oct2010.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Tumnus_Conundrum_1_HexTheDex_Oct2010.mp3" length="59834368" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Tumnus_Conundrum_1_HexTheDex_Oct2010.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Bumschlaken - Hex The Dex - May 2010</title> 
  <description>Who, tell me, who? Just who, would sand a monkey for fun. And I don't mean throw sand in the monkeys face, though that would be bad enough. No. Who would take some sandpaper, starting with a course grain, and set about a blameless simian with the intention of giving him a lovely smooth finish? Who? Only someone extremely bored, that's who. Don't let it be you. Listen to this megabig-double-size show forthwith. WARNING: Actual show may appear shorter due to time flying when you're having fun. Not a guaranteed cure for monkey sanding syndrome. Contains nuts. People with bladder weakness should probably be ashamed of themselves.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Bumschlaken_HexTheDex.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Bumschlaken_HexTheDex.mp3" length="95379456" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Bumschlaken_HexTheDex.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>The Dogs - Hex The Dex Live 3pm Apr 18th 2010</title> 
  <description>Like the man with the world record for having the highest sperm count, this show is creaking at the seams and begging to be released. Its dog content is higher than any previous Hex, a stunning 80 percent. The Robert Mugabe count is off the scale, and if you like tedious towel-folding robots, then boy is this the podcast for you.</description> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 3 May 2010 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://hexthedex.com/shows/The_Dogs_1-HexTheDex-18_04_10.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://hexthedex.com/shows/The_Dogs_1-HexTheDex-18_04_10.mp3" length="59326464" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://hexthedex.com/shows/The_Dogs_1-HexTheDex-18_04_10.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Hoovers 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm Mar 28th 2010</title> 
  <description>Yes, more lovely bandwidth! Thank you wise benefactor. Now witness the power of this fully operational battle-podcast. KablooooooOOOooooMMM! ---WARNING: There has been a great disturbance in the Force, as if millions of voices cried out in terror, and were suddenly silenced. WARNING ENDS.---</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hoovers_2-HexTheDex-28_03_10.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hoovers_2-HexTheDex-28_03_10.mp3" length="54607872" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hoovers_2-HexTheDex-28_03_10.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Hoovers 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm Mar 28th 2010</title> 
  <description>Yikes! Whenever we post a new show all of our bandwidth gets eaten in a couple of days. The cause of this problem is a phenomena known as popularity. We have thus-far avoided popularity by excluding entertaining content, being irritating berks and through a combined strategy of ineptitude and laziness. Sadly our efforts have failed. We are popular. Please, please, dear listener, if you want to listen to future episodes of Hex the Dex then don't listen to this one. Ta.</description> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 6 Apr 2010 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hoovers_1-HexTheDex-28_03_10.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hoovers_1-HexTheDex-28_03_10.mp3" length="54349824" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hoovers_1-HexTheDex-28_03_10.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Bystanders 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm Feb 14th 2010</title> 
  <description>Bystanders, TW*TS more like. Hello and welcome to this podcast description text. Throughout this sentence I'll be explaining the purpose of this sentence and then towards the end telling you that this is a good choice of podcast. I’ll thank you for listening and then invoke a cheery farewell.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Bystanders_1-HexTheDex-14_02_10.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Bystanders_1-HexTheDex-14_02_10.mp3" length="63754240" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Bystanders_1-HexTheDex-14_02_10.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Caught In A Trap 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm Jan 10th 2010</title> 
  <description>As Public Enemy quite rightly point out, Elvis was a hero to most. Now, we too celebrate his memory by imagining The King crawling naked over a carpet of primed mousetraps. Respect due. </description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Caught_In_A_Trap_2-HexTheDex-10_01_10.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Caught_In_A_Trap_2-HexTheDex-10_01_10.mp3" length="70041600" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Caught_In_A_Trap_2-HexTheDex-10_01_10.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Caught In A Trap - Hex The Dex Live 5pm Jan 10th 2010</title> 
  <description>They tried to stop us but we were too strong, too many, too silly. They tried to stop us but we had too little to lose, and we smelled unusually.  Live from a concrete bunker in London's war-torn Hackney district comes the sound of hope. There will always be a show. Hex the Dex will never be slain. Stirring stuff, huh? You may notice that this edition of Hex The Dex sounds a little gritty. Please accept our apologies but we had to broadcast it using an old umbrella, a record player, a circular saw blade, a light bulb, and Gertie's Speak and Spell. Try to enjoy it anyway. Lovely love from us.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Caught_In_A_Trap_1-HexTheDex-10_01_10.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Caught_In_A_Trap_1-HexTheDex-10_01_10.mp3" length="48287744" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Caught_In_A_Trap_1-HexTheDex-10_01_10.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Popacappin' - Hex The Dex Live 5pm Dec 13th 2009</title> 
  <description>Bend over. Dave has got a cap, and he wants to pop it in something. Then you can try and sit down, relax, make a cup of tea and a Mr Kipling Urinal Cake and have an exceedingly good time listening to Hex The Dex.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Popacapin-HexTheDex-13_12_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Popacapin-HexTheDex-13_12_09.mp3" length="44290048" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Popacapin-HexTheDex-13_12_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Malelophant 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm Nov 8th 2009</title> 
  <description>What? News, stories, suits, autocue, serious voice, massive tragedy, ehhhhhh? Has Hex really gone rolling news or is it simply a lame-ass Day Today rip-off? Yes. WARNING: This show contains weak vegetable based rapping.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Malelophant_2-HexTheDex-08_11_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Malelophant_2-HexTheDex-08_11_09.mp3" length="44290048" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Malelophant_2-HexTheDex-08_11_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Malelophant 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm Nov 8th 2009</title> 
  <description>We were on a quest, yes that was it, a magical quest. The quest we were on is the reason for our long absence. We went missing, but now we are back, HooT! HooT! HooT! Sorry about that. Right where were we……ahh yes, talking total arse-bilge, playing the breaks and generally hooning about. Your normal transmission will now resume. Godspeed.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Malelophant_1-HexTheDex-08_11_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Malelophant_1-HexTheDex-08_11_09.mp3" length="46764032" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Malelophant_1-HexTheDex-08_11_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Owls Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Apr 26th 2009</title> 
  <description>Owl stretching time continues! Actually I can't even remember why this show was called Owls! There is certainly not a single mention of an owl in this part two bit. It had something to do with dirty egg holes I think but that's not important anymore. Probably best to treat this as a stand alone listening experience and forget all about those filthy owls for now. This show features some hot stuff (coming through) including: a massive mice off, canned fish, DIY tips and a very confusing intro designed to disorient any soon-to-be-disappointed owl fans. Enjoy. HooT! HooT!</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 3 Jun 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Owls_2-HexTheDex-26_04_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Owls_2-HexTheDex-26_04_09.mp3" length="47677440" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Owls_2-HexTheDex-26_04_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Owls Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Apr 26th 2009</title> 
  <description>Whatever you do, don't go into the barn. If you don't have a barn then consider yourself very lucky. If you are already in the barn then don't look behind you. It's Owls! All the usual Hex the Dex fun in this show, there's killer breaks, a DubStep DebAcle, Lady Gaga gets some grief, we rhyme Nationality with Irrationality and hear about Enid Blyton's lesser know children's book, The Evil Nine. Bonk!</description> 
  <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Owls_1-HexTheDex-26_04_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Owls_1-HexTheDex-26_04_09.mp3" length="56991744" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Owls_1-HexTheDex-26_04_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Moose On Da Loose Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Apr 12th 2009</title> 
  <description>Well it's about bloody time! We finally travel back to the future, our future that is, not yours. It’s your NOW, you can tell because you’re reading this at the moment. Unless you’re in the future (yours and ours) remembering reading this once (in the future past.) Either way you are NOW and we are THEN doing a show for you NOW. Geddit? Good. This show has stuff in it, including our Crucify this Famous Guy competition and a story about a soapy man. Or is he? Soapy? I love you. Or will I?</description> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Moose_On_Da_Loose_2-HexTheDex-12_04_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Moose_On_Da_Loose_2-HexTheDex-12_04_09.mp3" length="48377856" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Moose_On_Da_Loose-HexTheDex_2-12_04_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Moose On Da Loose Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Apr 12th 2009</title> 
  <description>In a dystopic and crime ridden woodland, a terminally wounded moose is saved by the government and returns to the herd as a powerful laser-antlered cyborg, but will he fit in or is he doomed to stomp alone on an eternal quest for juice? All that and thumping great tunes, the dubstep debacle and Dom's balloon knot. Silly Billies.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Moose_On_Da_Loose-HexTheDex-12_04_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Moose_On_Da_Loose-HexTheDex-12_04_09.mp3" length="50892800" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Moose_On_Da_Loose-HexTheDex-12_04_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Integrity Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Mar 22nd 2009</title> 
  <description>Dude! You did it again, you downloaded our podcast, you rock! Seriously man we love it so much when you download our podcast, it makes us all happy inside like a blowie and steak day. Anyhoo, please find enclosed several unacceptable conversations including Joseph Fritzle talk, some badass breaks, a mighty mince off and a fiendish Google Street View review. Up your ears for 4 whole years, it’s Hex the Dex.</description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Integrity_2-HexTheDex-22_03_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Integrity_2-HexTheDex-22_03_09.mp3" length="45027328" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Integrity_2-HexTheDex-22_03_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Integrity Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Mar 22nd 2009</title> 
  <description>If Michael J Fox was a power tool then which one would he be? Are Icelanders born in kit form? Is Dom secretly funny? Who reads these show descriptions anyway? Do you? It's just me typing this to myself isn't it? Well? This show features some excellent tunes, some tasteless conversation and the answers to some questions. Please post a hello on our forum at hexthedex.com if you read this. Just so I know you're there. Please.This sounds pathetic now doesn't it? I'm so lonely.</description> 
  <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Integrity_1-HexTheDex-22_03_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Integrity_1-HexTheDex-22_03_09.mp3" length="60518400" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Integrity_1-HexTheDex-22_03_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Animal Snax Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Feb 8th 2009</title> 
  <description>Picture yourself, laid back, stretched out, frosty cocktail in hand, submerged in a warm rock pool by the ocean. Tendrils of seaweed tickle your toes. Mmmmmm…pleasant for sure, but missing something perhaps? Some sexy company? Well why not try a prawn? Yes, that’s right a prawn, your ideal date for areas where sea and land overlap a bit. Try it. Do a prawn. They love it. All that plus some superbreaky choonz, a magnificent mince-off and a Puma with a Satsuma.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Animal_Snax_2-HexTheDex-08_02_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Animal_Snax_2-HexTheDex-08_02_09.mp3" length="59097088" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Animal_Snax_2-HexTheDex-08_02_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Animal Snax Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Feb 8th 2009</title> 
  <description>Bong...Britain has been buried under boggling boganers.  Bong...Dave found on top of a hill at sunrise in his little gym shorts.  Bong...Animals all over the world are ravenous for snacks.  Bong...Christian Bale very reasonably goes ape.  Bong...Pleasing breakbeat music found.  Hex The Dex - news alchemists tinkering with the golden egg of fact.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Animal_Snax_1-HexTheDex-08_02_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Animal_Snax_1-HexTheDex-08_02_09.mp3" length="60091347" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Animal_Snax_1-HexTheDex-08_02_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Mind Peepers Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Jan 25th 2009</title> 
  <description>Would you like to buy a nazi mankini? Well obviously, who wouldn’t? Here is a show featuring chatting men and banging music. If you don’t like either or both elements then consider this an exercise in EXTREME tolerance. Please also go to breakspoll.com and vote for Hex the Dex as best radio show. Ta muchly, Laters.</description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Mind_Peepers_1-HexTheDex-25_01_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Mind_Peepers_1-HexTheDex-25_01_09.mp3" length="57532416" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Mind_Peepers_1-HexTheDex-25_01_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Battenberg Bass Bait Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Jan 11th 2009</title> 
  <description>We're here to save morris dancing, lets be quite clear about that. This most derided form of English folk dance is not, as some people contend, "Totally gay beyond all belief." So please stop saying it is. It quite often involves sticks for example, which are very very manly. So there. OK, so the inclusion of tinkling bells, limp-wristed hankie waving and ludicrous prancing may excuse your misguidedness but, from now on, DO consider yourselves better informed. All that and great tunes for a better life. Prance! Go on.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Battenberg_Bass_Bait_2-HexTheDex-11_01_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Battenberg_Bass_Bait_2-HexTheDex-11_01_09.mp3" length="64692224" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Battenberg_Bass_Bait_2-HexTheDex-11_01_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Battenberg Bass Bait Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Jan 11th 2009</title> 
  <description>Congratulations. You'd be surprised how many peeps plow straight into the listening experience without taking the time to read this little textual nugget. Perhaps they think they'll understand well enough without guidance. Perhaps they fear that the electric frisson of surprise will be lost to a careless spoiler contained here. Perhaps they are the sort of person deserving nothing but pity for their premature-jizz-prone aural proclivity. Numpties. WARNING: This show contains the concept of a cow being trebucheted into a wind turbine. Who would do such a thing? Not Jimmy Carr, that's for sure. Happy New Year Old Beans.</description> 
  <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Battenberg_Bass_Bait_1-HexTheDex-11_01_09.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Battenberg_Bass_Bait_1-HexTheDex-11_01_09.mp3" length="61890560" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Battenberg_Bass_Bait_1-HexTheDex-11_01_09.mp3</guid> 
</item>
<item>
  <title>Stocking Filler - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Dec 25th 2008</title> 
  <description>Yo babes! Happy Chrimbo, and all manner of festive jazz in your area.
This bonus HextheDex is the best stocking filler since golden legs, in which we get digested by the mighty Sarlacc for a thousand years, we present a Which guide to stunt cockery and a mince off so mincey it’s mincier than the minciest mince pie since records began! Seasons beatings peeps. HooT!</description> 
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate> 
  <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Stocking_Filler-HexTheDex-25_12_08.mp3</link> 
  <author>dave@hexthedex.com</author> 
  <enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Stocking_Filler-HexTheDex-25_12_08.mp3" length="87560192" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure> 
  <guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Stocking_Filler-HexTheDex-25_12_08.mp3</guid> 
  </item>
<item>
<title>Naughty Swarm Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Nov 23rd 2008</title>
<description>Balloomania grips the show as we take to the French skies with Jean-Claude Van Damme, we review Dave’s collection of Santa costumes, we investigate the legal career of Judge Reinhold and the Burka-Doppelganger Skive-Scam. All that and an exclusive live Echaskech track. Hex the Dex, the sonic mind-slug.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Naughty_Swarm_2-HexTheDex-23_11_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Naughty_Swarm_2-HexTheDex-23_11_08.mp3" length="62353408" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Naughty_Swarm_2-HexTheDex-23_11_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Naughty Swarm Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Nov 23rd 2008</title>
<description>Chillax dude, the ants are respectin’ and if the ants are respectin’ then we’re golden. Welcome to the buzziest episode of Hex the Dex ever, Doms’s insect diorama is teaming with Rasta crickets, socialist insects and HM the Queen Bee is laying for England. Meanwhile Dave has railway issues, there’s massive Orbital news and those pesky pirates are back. Down your street and up your ears since the dawn of time, it’s Hex the Dex.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Naughty_Swarm_1-HexTheDex-23_11_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Naughty_Swarm_1-HexTheDex-23_11_08.mp3" length="55238656" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Naughty_Swarm_1-HexTheDex-23_11_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mr Rascal Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Nov 9th 2008</title>
<description>Avast, me hearties! Welcome to the one and only, official, accept-no-substitutes, Hex the Dex, where things have taken a turn for the uber-minced. Fans of good taste will be disappointed as we discuss dolphin suicide and stunt-pimped euthanasia. Meanwhile, will someone please bring me the Dirty Sanchezed head of Gillian McKeith!</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Mr_Rascal_2-HexTheDex-09_11_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Mr_Rascal_2-HexTheDex-09_11_08.mp3" length="49610752" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Mr_Rascal_2-HexTheDex-09_11_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mr Rascal Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Nov 9th 2008</title>
<description>He’s just a rascal, a Mr Rascal! Barack Obama seems cool but can he pee in the presence of a US Marine? No? Better head for the military hidey-hole then. Meanwhile, Dom rides a rollercoaster and screams like a girl, Dave rides his high horse right-out-a-town and Other Dave coughs up a kitten. It’s all here as well as exclusive tracks from reputable artists. Hex the Dex, i’n’it!?</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Mr_Rascal_1-HexTheDex-09_11_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Mr_Rascal_1-HexTheDex-09_11_08.mp3" length="50049024" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Mr_Rascal_1-HexTheDex-09_11_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>G Monastic Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Oct 12th 2008</title>
<description>Need a new warehouse? Then come on down to Warehouse Warehouse where the warehouse King will sell you a minter. Also on special offer, it's Butt Chocolate served by a tinkling troll man. Still want more? Try this: Caving hamsters, Dog Hair champagne, Dom’s camel toe and THE BACON TREE JOKE. Hex the Dex, never knowingly oversold!</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/G_Monastic_2-HexTheDex-12_10_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/G_Monastic_2-HexTheDex-12_10_08.mp3" length="62488576" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/G_Monastic_2-HexTheDex-12_10_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>G Monastic Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Oct 12th 2008</title>
<description>Devastatin’ Dave the golden giggler is away but fear not, ably clambering into his size 13s is louche dandy G-Money. G is Dom’s bandmate in Echaskech and what he doesn’t know about being soave, sophisticated and generally debonair isn’t worth knowing. So ladies, watch out lest you be vocally depantiefied! Chat includes Dial M for Mute Button and The Task Bar Channel. Music features broken beats of the finest choosing. Hex The Dex, it’s fantastic monastic magic!</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/G_Monastic_1-HexTheDex-12_10_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/G_Monastic_1-HexTheDex-12_10_08.mp3" length="53280768" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/G_Monastic_1-HexTheDex-12_10_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Salad Dressing Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Sep 28th 2008</title>
<description>The fun continues here in part 2.  We've got pirate talk, monkey zeitgeist, facebook poking alternatives, ED209 vs Scout Walker, boosting, Dave's laughing farmer decapitation fears and all sorts of other balls. The 'mince off' is possibly a step too far but what the hell, it is certainly IS mincey. Hex the Dex, bring the noise boys.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Salad_Dressing_2-HexTheDex-28_09_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Salad_Dressing_2-HexTheDex-28_09_08.mp3" length="53592064" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Salad_Dressing_2-HexTheDex-28_09_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Salad Dressing Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Sep 28th 2008</title>
<description>Paul Newman is dead, but will he live on in our hearts and salads? We find out plus the best way to build a secret mountain base; how not to pull a scouser; two girls one houses of parliament; super hairy super mole infestations; and the War Games Paradox. Plus some awesome fresh breaks. Hex the Dex, smells like a whole bucket-o-good to us, mmmmmmm.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Salad_Dressing_1-HexTheDex-28_09_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Salad_Dressing_1-HexTheDex-28_09_08.mp3" length="48701440" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Salad_Dressing_1-HexTheDex-28_09_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Over Hung Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Sep 14th 2008</title>
<description>Cephalalgia is what doctors call a headache, but headache is three letters shorter than cephalalgia, which means that we win. Not that that does us any good at all in this, part two of the show. Our hangovers continue to throb and meaningless bum-dribble cascades from our lantern-jawed durr-faces. Pity us listener, lest you become us and repent you heartless memory. Hex the Dex, up your ears since ages ago.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Over_Hung_2-HexTheDex-14_09_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Over_Hung_2-HexTheDex-14_09_08.mp3" length="54145024" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Over_Hung_2-HexTheDex-14_09_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Over Hung Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Sep 14th 2008</title>
<description>Drinking too much causes hangovers. Not drinking enough causes boredom and social exclusion! So-wot-ya-gonna-do? Hmmmm? Our advice is DO drink too much but never ALL the time and for christsakes DON’T ever EVER dance to ‘Hips Don't Lie’ by Shakira! EVER! We DID drink too much before this show. Did we get away with it? You be the judge. We have Bestival news, audio boots(TM), hearty tunes and slamming headaches. Yum-it-up.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Over_Hung_1-HexTheDex-14_09_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Over_Hung_1-HexTheDex-14_09_08.mp3" length="56557568" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Over_Hung_1-HexTheDex-14_09_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gary Glitter Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Aug 24th 2008</title>
<description>Found in this show is: Mole rat chat, One Flew Over the Rainbow, Film advice, Olympic fakery planning, a massive fiver, a giant dookie and the most pretentious joke in world history. Missing from this show is: one BMX bicycle formally owned by a tw..err..Dom. All the tunes with none of the mixing, it’s Hex the Dex.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Gary_Glitter_2-HexTheDex-24_08_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Gary_Glitter_2-HexTheDex-24_08_08.mp3" length="49233920" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Gary_Glitter_2-HexTheDex-24_08_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gary Glitter Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Aug 24th 2008</title>
<description>Gary Glitter is cockney rhyming slang for shi…ah, hello there! This show has all the answers but we’ve lost the questions so you’ll have work it out backwards. Here are the answers: Frogs. PORGs. Buddhists. Garry Glitter being torn limb from limb by a gang of marauding toddlers. And, new from Hex the Dex productions, The Secret Bastard. Plus muchos solid tunes for all you beat junkies out there. This show is part of a multipack and should not be sold separately.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Gary_Glitter_1-HexTheDex-24_08_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Gary_Glitter_1-HexTheDex-24_08_08.mp3" length="54034432" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Gary_Glitter_1-HexTheDex-24_08_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cheese Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Aug 10th 2008</title>
<description>The cheesy chat continues along with lady spanking, Olympic hope, Cornish landing craft, Tranny racing, The Mince Off, What makes you cry? And cuddly jet pack pick me up! All that and a tonne of awesome beats. Hex the Dex, your mighty servant.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2008 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Cheese_2-HexTheDex-10_08_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Cheese_2-HexTheDex-10_08_08.mp3" length="55754752" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Cheese_2-HexTheDex-10_08_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cheese Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST Aug 10th 2008</title>
<description>What is the point of cheese? Is it just chewy rotten milk or is there more to it than that? What is the best cheese to rave with? What’s wrong with Edam? It’s madE backwards, that’s what. Yes this show features cheese, both figurative and literal so tuck in to the stinking melty goodness.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Cheese_1-HexTheDex-10_08_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Cheese_1-HexTheDex-10_08_08.mp3" length="54034432" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Cheese_1-HexTheDex-10_08_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Leggy Ginger Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST July 27th 2008</title>
<description>It’s part two of that Hex show with world famous stand up comedian Michael Legge in it. You know, the one with lots a bonza tunes jostling for position amid a veritable smorgasbord of silly chat. Oh come now, you must remember? No? WINDOW LICKER! w00t! w00t! w00t! (Sorry, I was very tired when I wrote this and there's really no excuse for those w00ts. My bad.)</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2008 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Leggy_Ginger_2-HexTheDex-27_07_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Leggy_Ginger_2-HexTheDex-27_07_08.mp3" length="59310080" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Leggy_Ginger_2-HexTheDex-27_07_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Leggy Ginger Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST July 27th 2008</title>
<description>HEX: One Dave, another Dave and a Dom, so it has been thus far. Yet must we expect it always? Use CAUTION conjecture laden listener, lest ye be vexed, for one Dave is missing. BEWARE, for in his stead sits a growling gnashing troll by the name LEGGE, mirthsayer and seriousness-banisher of old. FEAR HIM…..Translation: Due to a long held appointment with a field Dave is absent from this show and has therefore been temporarily replaced by lovely stand-up comedian Michael Legge. Enjoy the Davelessness and EXSPERMINATE!</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Leggy_Ginger_1-HexTheDex-27_07_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Leggy_Ginger_1-HexTheDex-27_07_08.mp3" length="60129280" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Leggy_Ginger_1-HexTheDex-27_07_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blunty Hole Part 2 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST July 13th 2008</title>
<description>So it turned out that James Blunt not only rhymed with, but in fact was a…ah, hello and welcome to part two of the show. This half is chock full of goodness with intelligent chat and slamming tunes. Subjects include the ahead of his time racial integrity of Morph from Take Hart, wet handed American lady talk, Grunty gym man and, well you know, all the usual balls really. Hounding your ears since 2005, it's Hex the Dex!</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2008 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Blunty_Hole_2-HexTheDex-13_07_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Blunty_Hole_2-HexTheDex-13_07_08.mp3" length="60489728" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Blunty_Hole_2-HexTheDex-13_07_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blunty Hole Part 1 - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST July 13th 2008</title>
<description>James Blunt rhymes with…ah, hello there! Welcome to a whole new format in Hex the Dex show formats. Instead of one super-massive two hour monstrosity we are going to split every show into two and stagger the release. Part one here contains a steaming heap of quality material, including: Is a window better than TV? What’s up with string? Stylophone attack! The ant that cried butter mountain! And, yes, a review of James Blunt at Glastonbury. Enjoy the silly my lover!</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Blunty_Hole_1-HexTheDex-13_07_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Blunty_Hole_1-HexTheDex-13_07_08.mp3" length="51544064" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Blunty_Hole_1-HexTheDex-13_07_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cow Bell - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST June 22nd 2008</title>
<description>WARNING! This show features a loose cow bell in the hands of an idiot and as such should not be listened to by anyone with a cow bell allergy or general bovine clang intolerance. What the hell are cow bells for anyway? Finding cows? Maybe. Also this is the first show description to feature a text emoticon ;o) see. Enjoy the sounds old friend.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Cow_Bell-HexTheDex-22_06_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Cow_Bell-HexTheDex-22_06_08.mp3" length="114016256" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Cow_Bell-HexTheDex-22_06_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lager Omm - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST June 8th 2008</title>
<description>Science is a noble field worthy of considered respect. Feel your frustration mount therefore, as we halfass our way through a Hex the Dex science experiment! With the research underway we also find time to discuss Poop-Howitzers, Circular Parties, Porcelain Buses and Hugh Hefner’s sexy brain transplant. Hex in full pseudoscientific effect baby, yeah!</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Lager_Omm-HexTheDex-08_06_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Lager_Omm-HexTheDex-08_06_08.mp3" length="117522432" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Lager_Omm-HexTheDex-08_06_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Willy Island - Hex The Dex Live 5pm BST May 25th 2008</title>
<description>Hello. It has been a very eventful month at the Breakbeat Castle, we left Purple Radio's Saturday afternoon slot and joined NSB Radio's Sunday 5-7BST afternoon slot. So does this mean choral music and ecclesiastical ramblings? You betcha evil ass it doesn't! No fear! It's a case of meet the new Hex, same as the old Hex, in other words the usual puerile banter with your old friends Dave, Dave and Dom. This week the good ship Hex sets sail for Willy Island!</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Willy_Island-HexTheDex-25_05_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Willy_Island-HexTheDex-25_05_08.mp3" length="99479552" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Willy_Island-HexTheDex-25_05_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Philatelator - Hex The Dex Live 2pm GMT Apr 26th 2008</title>
<description>Warning! Do not listen if you are operating heavy machinery.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Philatelator-HexTheDex-26_04_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Philatelator-HexTheDex-26_04_08.mp3" length="103989376" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/The_Philatelator-HexTheDex-26_04_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Like a Chicken - Hex The Dex Live 2pm GMT Apr 12th 2008</title>
<description>If your name is Madonna then this show probably isn't for you. Everyone else hop aboard the mirth bus, ding-ding! Dave has been to Dublin with nary a thought for causality. Back in London Dave has been on a trip of his own...down the stairs. It's a lap dancing, dog racing, gladiatorial happy-fest of a show. Just watch out for the bad fairy!</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2008 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/LikeAChicken-HexTheDex-12_04_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/LikeAChicken-HexTheDex-12_04_08.mp3" length="103481344" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/LikeAChicken-HexTheDex-12_04_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Poo Inspectors - Hex The Dex Live 2pm GMT Mar 29th 2008</title>
<description>Get out of China, Tibet.  Or is it that China should get out of Tibet?  Stand by for some incisive political debate on Hex The Dex.  Dom is back, Dave has bought some fresssshhhhhh breaks, other Dave has bought some Buckfast and we put on our Rock Hands (twice).  Plus, some scat chat, the Happy Times, Dom gives birth and Dave flicks his switch.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Poo_Inspectors-HexTheDex-29_03_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Poo_Inspectors-HexTheDex-29_03_08.mp3" length="102122309" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Poo_Inspectors-HexTheDex-29_03_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>AsparaguWizzer - Hex The Dex Live 2pm GMT Mar 15th 2008</title>
<description>Welcome to Hex the Dex with Dave and Dave and......Oh no, where's Dom? Is he lost forever? Will the Dave's manage on their own? Is the good ship Hex missing a captain or a cabin boy? Who can foretell? If only we had some asparagus. The only show you never knew you always wanted to hear, Hex the Dex LIVE, Yip!</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/AsparaguWizzer-HexTheDex-15_03_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/AsparaguWizzer-HexTheDex-15_03_08.mp3" length="87834624" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/AsparaguWizzer-HexTheDex-15_03_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Crab Future - Hex The Dex Live 2pm GMT Mar 1st 2008</title>
<description>Dave has been to Berlin and come back convinced that Germans are actually rather lovely people, not the jackbooted Jerries you might have thought. Sadly Germany's gain is France's loss as Dave risks international relations again with more of the ill informed xenophobic claptrap that is fast becoming his trademark. In other exclusive news Heather Mills McCartney might be a gold-digger! Hear our shock revelation. Plus great tunes for your modern life. All here on Hex the Dex LIVE baby, Yeah!</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Crab-Future-HexTheDex-01_03_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Crab-Future-HexTheDex-01_03_08.mp3" length="115163136" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Crab-Future-HexTheDex-01_03_08</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Panda Style - Hex The Dex Live 2pm GMT Feb 16th 2008</title>
<description>Pandas don't like to do the nasty, but when they do, ooooh, its NASTY.  This is Hex the Dex but like NEVER before...we are LIVE! All the ridiculous and offensice chat, but without the comfortable safety net of a post show edit. Hear how we manage to offend not just the whole of Southeast Asia and China, but also Jeremy Beadles grieving family and almost all non-english ethnic groups. If Purple Radio has a licence, it won't have it for long!</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Panda-Style-HexTheDex-18_02_08.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Panda-Style-HexTheDex-18_02_08.mp3" length="75841536" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Panda-Style-HexTheDex-18_02_08.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Jan_08_Iceland.mp3</title>
<description>It is not a Hex really, this show,  it has no breaks and Other Dave is eerily absent. How can we do a show without chuckler Dave, the golden giggler? And without our beloved breaks? Surely that is impossible. Well fear not because stepping up to the mic in place of Dave comes a worthy contender, Andy G / G Money. Journey with us as we recount tails of our recent marvelous mystical Icelandic adventure. Clungortunity Ahoy!</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2008 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Jan_08_Iceland.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Jan_08_Iceland.mp3" length="102780601" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Jan_08_Iceland.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex December 07 (3) - Happy Perinterval</title>
<description>Hello and merry perineum of Christmas to you. This is a no holds barred rip snorting festive stonker of a show. Joining the boys in the studio is legendary breaks supremo, DJ High Eight, the all conquering CEO of ReConnect Records. Also Dave cooks up a fantastic Christmas roast, Dom ponders Victorian graffiti and Dave provides culinary commentary. A party for your ears? Yes.</description>
<pubDate>30 Dec 2007 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Dec_07_Happy_Perinterval.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Dec_07_Happy_Perinterval.mp3" length="69140480" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Dec_07_Happy_Perinterval.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex December 07 (2) - Paintballs Of Steel 2</title>
<description>WAR, what is it good for...hmmmm...well it seems quite a lot of things actually, hear our full report. Plus the sad conclusion to our paintball battle, Terry Wogans todger, conical head gear and your face in meat dot com. Just a few of the strange delights on offer in this hootie mack of a show.</description>
<pubDate>20 Dec 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Dec_07_Paintballs_Of_Steel_2.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Dec_07_Paintballs_Of_Steel_2.mp3" length="58523648" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Dec_07_Paintballs_Of_Steel_2.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex December 07 (1) - Paintballs Of Steel</title>
<description>War is hell, but to be fair that really only applies to end bit when you get shot, before that its a laugh. Dave, Dave and Dom load paintball guns and go deep behind enemy lines for...err...actually they never really figure that out due to the fog of war and their short attention spa...oh look a bird box. Join the boys for that plus gynecological Facebook pics, Thundercats outtakes, Dave blowing a postmodern fuse and a whole lot more.</description>
<pubDate>7 Dec 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Dec_07_Paintballs_Of_Steel.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Dec_07_Paintballs_Of_Steel.mp3" length="58007552" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Dec_07_Paintballs_Of_Steel.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex November 07 (1) - Moby Dave</title>
<description>The extraordinary tail of one mans struggle with obesity and his fight not to be covered in foil, suspended from the ceiling and spun around like some hideous juddering glitter ball, the campest and funniest air safety announcement in history, the horrific boyjoy sexborg Miss Piggy and the K9 Doggle, all this a more could be in your ears. Do it.</description>
<pubDate>15 Nov 2007 23:59:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Nov_07_Moby_Dave.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Nov_07_Moby_Dave.mp3" length="63700992" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Nov_07_Moby_Dave.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex October 07 (1) - The Funkstrom</title>
<description>Hello. Time for more informative sounds from Hex The Dex. Not only do we have some fine fine tunes, including a world podcast exclusive (possibly 2), we have some authentic Canadian input, Dave's successful date tips, a Bang Face review, party news, drunken Germans and forum peeps thanks. Go on, give it a listen...</description>
<pubDate>10 Oct 2007 23:59:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Sept_07_Dr_Hux.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Oct_07_The_Funkstrom.mp3" length="55973243" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Oct_07_The_Funkstrom.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex September 07 - Dr Hux</title>
<description>Wow! It's more tunes and chat in another Hex the Dex. Is stupid Bill stupid Cosby stupid? Televisions - have they lost some of their analogue charm? We delve into the whole "are poorly performed regional accents actually racist?" can of worms. Is Castro is still alive? What is it with Michael Stipe and Oranges? On a more serious note, there is a sensitively handled discussion about the "Base" method of sexual reporting. And if you make it right to the end....sorry!</description>
<pubDate>05 Sep 2007 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Sept_07_Dr_Hux.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Sept_07_Dr_Hux.mp3" length="41375526" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Sept_07_Dr_Hux.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex August 07 - Ladyboat Glitterboy</title>
<description>Hello. Hugo has gone, so it is back to Dave, Dave and Dom to inform you about the hot topics gripping todays global news feeds: Mirrored boat radio broadcasts, forum filth, ladies with chaps, debatable bootlegs, DJ theorums and a very funky small man. Plus the usual smattering of top quality tunes. Sold to you...for free.</description>
<pubDate>29 Aug 2007 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Aug_07_Ladyboat_Glitterboy.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Aug_07_Ladyboat_Glitterboy.mp3" length="47393314" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Aug_07_Ladyboat_Glitterboy.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex July 07 - Breakheart</title>
<description>How do you dress like old school beat meisters Altern8? Is Tiny Dancer an excuse for Elton John to exist? What does a real Scotsman sound like? Do Daleks rave? What would we put on our rider lists if we were ever in the position to have one? Yup, we are back and not a lot has changed! Apart from this time we play some of our favourite tunes from the past.</description>
<pubDate>01 Aug 2007 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_July_07-Breakheart.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_July_07-Breakheart.mp3" length="68390912" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_July_07-Breakheart.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex June 07 - Chocolate</title>
<description>Not a show for the easily offended this. In fact, if you are easily offended then you can fcuk off, because this really is not for you. The braver listener will enjoy puerile tails of Glasturbation, worm control, chocolate scheiza, money monkeys and the police. Plus some fat tunes naturally.</description>
<pubDate>04 Jul 2007 01:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_June_07-Chocolate.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_June_07-Chocolate.mp3" length="63930368" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_June_07-Chocolate.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex May 07 - Ski Sunday</title>
<description>We get off to an unexpectedly Austrian start this week with Franz Klammer. We have one in the front and two in the back, which is distracting to say the least. A guess the DJ contest...its probably Hi8 judging by the number of mentions he gets in the show. And all the frickin breaks and fun you can handle. Ouch.</description>
<pubDate>31 May 2007 01:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_May_07-Ski_Sunday.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_May_07-Ski_Sunday.mp3" length="61019483" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_May_07-Ski_Sunday.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex Apr 2007 (2) - Wow and Flutter</title>
<description>Here at Hex The Dex we have decided it is officially Summer, so expect summer tunes, picnic planning tips, alternative uses for Coleslaw, hydro-electric bass pumps and Owls.</description>
<pubDate>24 Apr 2007 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate> <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_Apr_07_(2)-Wow_and_Flutter.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_Apr_07_(2)-Wow_and_Flutter.mp3" length="50687520" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid> http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_Apr_07_(2)-Wow_and_Flutter.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title> Hex Apr 2007 (1) - May Contain Funk</title>
<description> After six weeks hard toil Dave is back and so is the show. We are so happy to be back on the mic that we indulge our love of beer to the max. Oh well at least the ensuing mess is peppered with magnificent breakbeat tunes. Beard maladies, soft metal history, prophylactic shock and much much more. May indeed contain funk. We were drunk.</description>
<pubDate>14 Apr 2007 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate> <link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_Apr_07_(1)-May_Contain_Funk.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_Apr_07_(1)-May_Contain_Funk.mp3" length="48029696" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid> http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_Apr_07_(1)-May_Contain_Funk.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex Feb 2007 - Badland Ninjas</title>
<description>Location. Location. Location...and this time its not Dave and Dave's flat. We go on a day trip to Dom's new studio facility where we try out a new tool for the show...the anecdote list. Topics relating to mice, fur clad chinese ladies, March 8th, flammable human adverts, tree graffiti, alfresco dancing women and rhino keepers crop up. Plus the tunes. Always the tunes...</description>
<pubDate>22 Feb 2007 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Feb_2007-Badland_Ninjas.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Feb_2007-Badland_Ninjas.mp3" length="75944768" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Feb_2007-Badland_Ninjas.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex Jan 2007 - Dedication</title>
<description>A monster nine, yes nine, fresh tunes in a show dedicated to James Brown, albeit rather loosely. What would you borrow from the library of random chance? What wood is best for constructing a bass proof shed? Who has the manliest robot voice? The answers to these questions plus more enthralling nonsense await the brave listener.
</description>
<pubDate>26 Jan 2007 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Jan_2007-Dedication.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Jan_2007-Dedication.mp3" length="69664768" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Jan_2007-Dedication.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex Best of 2006 Mix</title>
<description>To get you through the dark days of January, here is Hex The Dex's "Best tunes we played last year according to Dave" mix. Hope you enjoy...even if it wasn't mixed by Dom as he was up a mountain, so in the spirit of Christmas past, and because he has a Santa outfit, Dave had to give it a go!
</description>
<pubDate>05 Jan 2007 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_The_Dex_Best_of_2006_Mix.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_The_Dex_Best_of_2006_Mix.mp3" length="121813240" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_The_Dex_Best_of_2006_Mix.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex Dec 2006 - Xmas Special</title>
<description>Eight chunky tunes, seven swear words, six sausages, five frozen fowl, four fancy hats, three strange men, two called Dave and a Dom covered in graaaaaeeeaaavy. Happy Christmas Friends.
</description>
<pubDate>24 Dec 2006 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Dec_2006-Xmas_Special.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Dec_2006-Xmas_Special.mp3" length="58458112" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Dec_2006-Xmas_Special.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex November 2006 (2) - Van Higher.mp3</title>
<description>Come with us on a whistle-stop tour of central London in a hired white van. The magisterial presence of HRH Queen Elisabeth II makes this the most regal podcast in history. Also featured are Tony Blair, The Archbishop of Canterbury, Hugh Grant, James Blunt (What an absolute bast*rd), an actual dong from Big Ben and a hoop of hope. Plus seven awesome tunes. Vans rule!
</description>
<pubDate>25 Nov 2006 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Nov_2006_(2)-Van_Higher.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Nov_2006_(2)-Van_Higher.mp3" length="65159168" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Nov_2006_(2)-Van_Higher.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex November 2006 (1) - Charlie</title>
<description>Will History remember us? If so, then it will state that in this show we covered the first Moon landing, Scouts with military support and Bergerac. All washed down with some liquor and the best tunes we could find. It's also Halloween and Dom has gone missing....</description>
<pubDate>05 Nov 2006 10:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Nov_2006_(1)-Charlie.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Nov_2006_(1)-Charlie.mp3" length="64651264" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Nov_2006_(1)-Charlie.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex October 2006 (2) - MaccaAttack</title>
<description>Normal service is resumed as we cover B-Boy head accessories, the Tenby tragedy, Dave's new adventures in the "babe pen" and after weeks of intricate legal tit for tat we can announce the winner of the Full Metal Jacket competition.</description>
<pubDate>20 Oct 2006 10:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Oct_2006_(2)-Maccattack.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Oct_2006_(2)-Maccattack.mp3" length="64651264" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Oct_2006_(2)-Maccattack.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex October 2006 - Special Part Two</title>
<description>1...2......1...2...Check...Check...HELLO and hold on for part two of our Audio Test Broadcast. Think of it as flipping an audio bird to our little thieving f**k friend. Dave goes shopping for his Mum's birthday pressie, Dom makes an unpleasant sound, Dave witnesses youth crime in action and take cover for back to back Pendulum madness.</description>
<pubDate>09 Oct 2006 11:20:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-October_2006_Special_Part_Two.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-October_2006_Special_Part_Two.mp3" length="44400640" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-October_2006_Special_Part_Two.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex October 2006 - Special Part One</title>
<description>Testing....Testing....Hello everybody. This is a Hex The Dex Audio Test Broadcast. Following the unforunate incident involving our equipment and a thieving F**K, Hex The Dex returns to air with a 2 part "New Equipment Test" special. It's different...but the same. WARNING: Caution is advised due to boss tunage.</description>
<pubDate>01 Oct 2006 22:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-October_2006_Special_Part_One.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-October_2006_Special_Part_One.mp3" length="37191680" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-October_2006_Special_Part_One.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex September 2006 (1) - Moooo</title>
<description>Funeral turnout low? Involved in an embarrassing situation involving your mother, a security official and some personal improvement apparatus? Concerned about Tea consumption? Hex The Dex is back to help you with these, and other, every day dilemmas. Plus the finest fresh breaks we could find.</description>
<pubDate>01 Sep 2006 17:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Sep_2006_(1)-Moooo.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Sep_2006_(1)-Moooo.mp3" length="49248000" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Sep_2006_(1)-Moooo.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex August 2006 (2) - The Jeff</title>
<description>As Britain shrugs of the fear of terrorist fluid, the boys have only one concern. Nerd Off! Dave and Dom slug it out for the title of Ultimate Nerd. A precautionary tail for nut fans. Intelligent Fruit Flies, we have the facts. And a track from Echaskech recorded live at the Big Chill festival. Sweet.</description>
<pubDate>16 Aug 2006 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Aug_2006_(2)-The_Jeff.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Aug_2006_(2)-The_Jeff.mp3" length="53248000" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Aug_2006_(2)-The_Jeff.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex August 2006 (1) - Hard Boiled</title>
<description>Want to stage a fair fight between a Shark and a Bear? Want to know how long to boil Dom for before he is just right? Want to listen to some Grade A adulation? Well, listen to this and we'll tell you how.</description>
<pubDate>01 Aug 2006 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Aug_2006_(1)-Hard_Boiled.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Aug_2006_(1)-Hard_Boiled.mp3" length="45613056" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_Aug_2006_(1)-Hard_Boiled.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex July 2006 (2) - Cruise Control</title>
<description>Dave has been and gone and hired a boat, be afraid. Other Daves rubber fetish comes to a sticky end. Dom goes to a gay disco. Hex the Dex, a show featuring normal balanced chaps. No really.</description>
<pubDate>18 Jul 2006 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_July_2006_(2)-Cruise_Control.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_July_2006_(2)-Cruise_Control.mp3" length="48431104" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_July_2006_(2)-Cruise_Control.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex July 2006 (1) - Girls</title>
<description>We really cant apologize enough for this show. It pushes the envelope of decency, adheres the stamp of shame and posts itself to its own bottom. Sorry again. Told you.</description>
<pubDate>02 Jul 2006 01:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_July_2006_(1)-Girls.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_July_2006_(1)-Girls.mp3" length="47939584" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_July_2006_(1)-Girls.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex June 2006 (2) - That's No Moon</title>
<description>Can your Granny be a work of art? Is Cliff Richard a nice chap or a potty mouthed blackguard? How hard is a Chihuahua? Why all the questions? Why Not?</description>
<pubDate>16 Jun 2006 00:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-June_(2)-That's_No_Moon.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-June_(2)-That's_No_Moon.mp3" length="47513600" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-June_(2)-That's_No_Moon.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex June 2006 (1) - When Animals Attach (Phil Collins)</title>
<description>Dom returns just in time to help with the Hex The Dex When Animals go Wrong round up. Bears, badgers, rocket powered cows and cooperative chickens are all covered. And Phil Collins pops in and does a lot of good work for charity.</description>
<pubDate>04 Jun 2006 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_June_2006_(1)-Phil_Collins.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_June_2006_(1)-Phil_Collins.mp3" length="44859392" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_June_2006_(1)-Phil_Collins.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex May 2006 (2) - Spin Cycle</title>
<description>Hex The Dex offers a special celebrity guest the chance to redeem themselves from their own pitiful failure. We go onderground for some mine news and discuss possibly the World's greatest hissy fit. Plus the usual breaks and beats.</description>
<pubDate>16 May 2006 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_May_2006_(2)-Spin_Cycle.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_May_2006_(2)-Spin_Cycle.mp3" length="4725461" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_May_2006_(2)-Spin_Cycle.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex May 2006 (1) - H.U.G.S.</title>
<description>More banter and breaks from Hex The Dex. Hugging strangers, Druids, Scientology and Mr. Mange Tout get blinded our spotlight of ill informed chat. We also have a brand new competition for you, and we delve into the murky world of the profane. Go on, give it a go.</description>
<pubDate>02 May 2006 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-May_(1)-H.U.G.S..mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-May_(1)-H.U.G.S..mp3" length="49625974" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-May_(1)-H.U.G.S..mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex April 2006 (2) - Emergency Broadcast Message</title>
<description>DON'T PANIC! Hex The Dex is here with all the information YOU need to know about Bird Flu. What is it? How did it get here? Can you eat a hamburger with a pencil? Do Truffles cry Mayonnaise? How do you lure a Swan to a remote French farmhouse? If you want answers to these questions, then this is the show for you.</description>
<pubDate>01 Apr 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-April_(2)-Emergency_Broadcast_Message.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-April_(2)-Emergency_Broadcast_Message.mp3" length="49625974" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-April_(2)-Emergency_Broadcast_Message.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex April 2006 (1) - Springy</title>
<description>Has Spring Sprung in London? The results are in. And for our beloved British Bobbies its a case of two wheels good, eight wheels bad. Can you fit England up the Amazon? Only sideways it seems. Oh, and do you know the way to Uluru? Streuth mate!</description>
<pubDate>01 Apr 2006 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_April_2006_(1)-Springy.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_April_2006_(1)-Springy.mp3" length="42960787" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_April_2006_(1)-Springy.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex March 2006 (2) - 2nd 1st Birthday Show</title>
<description>The birthday celebrations continue as we attempt to battle our SODding melancholy. Luckily we succeed with some excellent tunes, some hard liquor and talk of Dave's lint scam. Failed sponsorship deals, rollerskates, London Cabbie annoyance tactics, feline civic responsibilities and rutting neighbours all help lift the gloom too. And Dom leaves (again).</description>
<pubDate>15 Mar 2006 23:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_The_Dex-March_2006_(2).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_The_Dex-March_2006_(2).mp3" length="47087716" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_The_Dex-March_2006_(2).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex March 2006 (1) - 1st Birthday Show</title>
<description>Happy Birthday Hex The Dex. In celebration we continue our study into stupid cops vs stupid crims, more US Military animal tampering and George Michael, if you're listening, give Dave a call. Although, if you are Tom Cruise, please don't.</description>
<pubDate>4 Mar 2006 22:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-March_2006_(1).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-March_2006_(1).mp3" length="41708612" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-March_2006_(1).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex February 2006 (2) - Valentines Day Massacre</title>
<description>It's the Hex The Dex Valentines Day breakbeat love in....Dave gets you in the mood with his views on Valentines Day. Criminals or Police - who's the stoopidist? We have an interview with the legendary Torveld Strap and will Dave fall for Dave and Dom's practical joke?</description>
<pubDate>15 Feb 2006 22:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-February_2006_(2).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-February_2006_(2).mp3" length="43493687" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-February_2006_(2).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex February 2006 (1) - Magic Beans</title>
<description>There she blows! Dave and Dave harpoon another excellent selection of breakbeat blubber for your science needs. Dom goes AWOL down in Acapulco, or somewhere, and Dave pleads for your Breakspoll votes.</description>
<pubDate>2 Feb 2006 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-February_2006_(1).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-February_2006_(1).mp3" length="43493687" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-February_2006_(1).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex January 2006 (2) - Plague!!</title>
<description>Dom is taken gravely ill but the Daves aren't convinced. Are you? More brand spanking new breakbeat of the cutting edge variety, glued together with chat that is, as usual, nonsensical. Self-aware potatoes jostle for position with England greatest shame, Morris dancers...</description>
<pubDate>19 Jan 2006 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-January_2006_(2).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-January_2006_(2).mp3" length="48814592" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-January_2006_(2).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex January 2006 (1) - Live Spectacular</title>
<description>We kick of 2006 with a special "Live" edition of Hex The Dex. There's Christmas Gift analysis, Alien musical accompanyment, Tat quiz and a plea for Sean to come home. Plus some tunes we like.</description>
<pubDate>5 Jan 2006 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-January_2006_(1).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-January_2006_(1).mp3" length="58814592" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-January_2006_(1).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex 2005 Xmas Cracker</title>
<description>Buoyed by the now legendary culinary success of his Xmas dinner, Dom turns his attention to the decks to craft an hour of the finest breaks that have been heard on Hex The Dex in 2005. It's the tunes without the chat. Happy Christmas from Hex The Dex.</description>
<pubDate>24 Dec 2005 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_The_Dex_2005_Xmas_Cracker.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_The_Dex_2005_Xmas_Cracker.mp3" length="58814592" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_The_Dex_2005_Xmas_Cracker.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex December 2005 (2) - Happy F*cking Christmas</title>
<description>Kaboom! The biggest festive explosion in peacetime europe. Suitably dark breaks for the holidays and roast turkey on pseudoephedrine. And no-one died.</description>
<pubDate>16 Dec 2005 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-December_2005_(2).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-December_2005_(2).mp3" length="56417455" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-December_2005_(2).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex December 2005 (1) - We Loved Techno</title>
<description>This time on Hex The Dex: "I love Techno" totally-pro travelogue, instant listener requests, Dave's directors cut of Titanic, tat quiz rule change and a bit of special wee leaks out. Oh, and some more fine tunes.</description>
<pubDate>30 Nov 2005 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-December_2005_(1).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-December_2005_(1).mp3" length="56417451" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex-December_2005_(1).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex November 2005 (2) - Techno Aftermath</title>
<description>Dave, Dave and Dom battle through savage fatigue in order to bring you a show of fine breakbeat music, another quality competition and a some special news for all you Radiohead fans out there.</description>
<pubDate>15 Nov 2005 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_November_2005_(2).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_November_2005_(2).mp3" length="42403000" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_November_2005_(2).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex Promo 1 - www.hexthedex.com</title>
<description>If you think the show deserves it then promote it... This handy attachable promo will fit on most emails and will earn you respect and adoration from friends and casual aquaintances alike!</description>
<pubDate>30 Oct 2005 19:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/brainstorm.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/brainstorm.mp3" length="2259008" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/brainstorm.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex November 2005 (1) - Witch Watch Wrap Up</title>
<description>Witch Watch West concludes, cheese sweats, pyrotechnic anarchy and another chance to win authentic London tat.</description>
<pubDate>31 Oct 2005 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_November_2005_(1).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_November_2005_(1).mp3" length="41259008" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_November_2005_(1).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex October 2005 (2) - Witch Watch One</title>
<description>Crack squirrels, witch watching and a very unpleasant reference to Daves buttocks. No really, it'll make you want to puke.</description>
<pubDate>17 Oct 2005 23:40:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_October_2005_(2).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_October_2005_(2).mp3" length="36470926" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_October_2005_(2).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex October 2005 (1) - Projectile Knees</title>
<description>Engine room disaster, lazer guided dart dolphins and Dom chooses his own special birthday tunes</description>
<pubDate>1 Oct 2005 19:09:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_October_2005_(1).mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_October_2005_(1).mp3" length="48138926" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_October_2005_(1).mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex Septemeber 2005</title>
<description>Featuring James Earl Jones as Darth Vader, special laser offer, ultra-miniturised nano-rastas and muppets, ALWAYS with the muppets!</description>
<pubDate>2 Sep 2005 16:09:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_September_2005.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_September_2005.mp3" length="48138926" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_September_2005.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex August 2005</title>
<description>Coaster and Gibb, if either of you two people who constitute our audience are easily offended, look away. If you have not heard this before then expect to laugh hard with a slightly bewildered look on your face. Also, tasty tunes, chosen by Dave, because its his birthday.</description>
<pubDate>1 Aug 2005 17:16:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_August_2005.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_August_2005.mp3" length="50517541" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_August_2005.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex July 2005</title>
<description>Spin classes, elephant stuffing and all the other highlights from glastonbury, skillfully interwoven with breakbeat music from the UK.</description>
<pubDate>12 Jul 2005 19:16:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_July_2005.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_July_2005.mp3" length="50517541" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_July_2005.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex June 2005</title>
<description>Summer's here, and the muppets are back and some of Jim Hensons Creations are mentioned too! Ha Ha! Expect humour consistantly as good as that, and filthy UK breakbeat too, with your hosts Dave and Dave</description>
<pubDate>29 May 2005 19:16:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_June_2005.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_June_2005.mp3" length="60170825" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_June_2005.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex May 2005</title>
<description>Warning: Do not listen to this if; you have the head of a horse, you are Dom, you hate breakbeat music, or you have any kind of self respect.</description>
<pubDate>3 May 2005 19:16:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_May_2005.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_May_2005.mp3" length="74100000" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_May_2005.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex April 2005</title>
<description>Dave leaves the show and has Dom got a terminal illness that means he can't carry on? Surely this show can't be falling apart on only the second show? Of course not, we build a virtual Dave whilst the real Dave escapes custody of the law by farting in a police-dog's face. It only makes sense in this, the stoopidest show playing the latest breaks and beats from the UK and anywhere else that can do it as well!</description>
<pubDate>9 Apr 2005 11:13:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_April_2005.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_April_2005.mp3" length="70213070" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_April_2005.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hex the Dex March 2005</title>
<description>Today we try to come up with a name for the show, and Dave talks about a friend of a friend called Jade with a muppet for a nose.</description>
<pubDate>18 Mar 2005 11:13:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_March_2005.mp3</link>
<author>dave@hexthedex.com</author>
<enclosure url="http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_March_2005.mp3" length="70213070" type="audio/x-mpeg"></enclosure>
<guid>http://www.hexthedex.com/shows/Hex_the_Dex_March_2005.mp3</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>