<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://www.urbancastradio.com/Feeds/UrbanCast.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>UrbanCast Radio</title>
    <link>http://www.urbancastradio.com</link>
    <description>From Hip Hop to Neo Soul. UrbanCast Radio aims to give independent and unsigned acts an opportunity to get heard! Tune in every week for music thats &quot;Fresh 2 Death!&quot;</description>
    <generator>Feeder 1.2.3.1 http://reinventedsoftware.com/feeder/</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>UrbanCast Radio</copyright>
    <managingEditor>Info@urbancastradio.com (Silence)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2006 08:58:51 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2006 08:58:51 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Podcasts</category>
    <item>
      <title>Volume VII: UrbanCast Radio 06/28/06</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>DROPS!</p>
Aight here is the MP3 version of the show for all the listeners out there that don't have iTunes or an iPod! Y'all know I have love for you and I always got ya bizaack na'mean!
<p>We need drops!! LOL</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2006 16:16:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/VolumeVII.mp3" length="52251483" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-vii-urbancast-radio-062806-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume VII: UrbanCast Radio 06/28/06 Enhanced</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>You have some explaining to do Mr. Sea!</h1>
What up, what up! It's your host Mr. Sea and I'm back with volume 7. I've been away handling bizness and now I have returned to supply you with the greatest hits from the unsigned indie marketplace. It's the holiday period and trust you will not be dissappointed.
<p>As always enjoy the holidays and be safe. Enclosed you find the enhanced version of Volume V. This of course is for all the iTunes users out there. Remember to take advantage of what the enhanced version has to offer, such as view pictures of the artists and go to their respective web sites.
</p>
<p>Don't forget to <a href="http://www.urbancastradio.com/wordpress/2006/06/29/urbancast-volume-vii/" target="_self">Vote or Die</a></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2006 02:46:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/VolumeVII.m4a" length="53530895" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-vii-urbancast-radio-062806</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume VI: UrbanCast Radio 03/13/06</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>OnTop TV</h1>
In case you haven't noticed a new addition has been added to the web site. You can now watch the latest music videos thanks to OnTop TV. Just scroll down to the Media Center section of the site. Your going to need the latest edition of Windows Media Player and a Broadband internet connection for it to work properly. Enjoy!
<p>We are in the process of collecting music videos from the Artist's. If you are an artist or you know an artist that is not currently signed, send in their videos and it could be possibly added to our very first video cast. Be a part of history and send them in now!</p>
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2006 23:42:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/VolumeVI.mp3" length="53209448" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-vi-urbancast-radio-031306-enhanced-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume VI: UrbanCast Radio 03/13/06 Enhanced!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>Heeeeee's Bizaaaaack!!!</h1>
What Up! It's your host Mr. Sea and I'm back from my extended sabbatical! Truthfully speaking, we had faulty equipment and we just had to suck it up an invest in some real ish. Coming up with the CAPITAL was a problem, but now we back stronger than ever! Enclosed you find the enhanced version of Volume V. This of course is for all the iTunes users out there. Remember to take advantage of what the enhanced version has to offer, such as view pictures of the artists and go to their respective web sites.
<p>Don't forget to <a href="http://www.urbancastradio.com/wordpress/2006/03/14/urbancast-volume-vi/" target="_self">Vote or Die</a></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2006 21:27:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/VolumeVI.m4a" length="54503949" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-vi-urbancast-radio-031306-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume V: UrbanCast Radio 01/23/06 Enhanced!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>Volume V Enhanced...</h1>
Enclosed you find the enhanced version of Volume V. This of course is for all the iTunes users out there. Remember to take advantage of what the enhanced version has to offer, such as view pictures of the artists and go to their respective web sites.
<p>Don't forget to <a href="http://www.urbancastradio.com/wordpress/2006/01/23/urbancast-volume-v/" target="_self">Vote or Die</a></p>
<p>Until the next show, peace and blessings!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2006 21:22:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/volumeV.m4a" length="54062944" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-v-urbancast-radio-012306-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume V: UrbanCast Radio 01/23/06</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>This Just In: Africa Is A Country!!!!!</h1>
Hey it's your host Mr. Sea with another volume of UrbanCast Radio. I would like to start off by wishing everyone a <b>Happy New Year!</b>. As always this episode is filled with tracks from talented artists such as, Deshara Renee, JayCi, K-Diamondz, Street Lotto, Kertasy etc.
<p>You must be wondering how the title came about. I traveled to the beautiful continent of Africa in December but during the podcast I referred to it as a country... I know, I know silly mistake. Well now I have to deal with being made fun for the rest of the week, hey I guess that's the price you pay...<p> ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2006 19:39:20 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/VolumeV.mp3" length="51783895" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-v-urbancast-radio-012306</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume IV: UrbanCastRadio 12/19/05 Enhanced</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<b>Happy Holidays...Volume IV Enhanced Is Here!!!</b>
<p>Enclosed you will find the enhanced version of Volume IV. This is for all the iTunes users out there.</p> 
<p>Don't forget to <a href="http://www.urbancastradio.com/wordpress/2005/12/19/urbancast-volume-iv/" target="_self">Vote or Die</a></p>
<p>So far no one has voted for their favorite songs from the previous podcasts... Hmmm I wonder why? No idea, I guess our host Mr. Sea will be choosing his favorite songs from the podcasts for the best of show!</p>
Until the next show, peace and blessings!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2005 00:06:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/volumeIV.m4a" length="55706032" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-iv-urbancastradio-121905-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume IV: UrbanCastRadio 12/19/05</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>Get Well Real Quick Yarah!!!</h1>
Hey it's your host Mr. Sea with another volume of UrbanCast Radio. As always it's packed with talented artists such as R-Style, Fam 1st, Street Lotto, Kardiak etc.
<p>This show is dedicated to Yarah Bravo, who is currently under the weather. Yarah is very talented musician who has the drive and ambition needed to get anywhere in this behemoth of an industry! Yarah we wish u a speedy recovery...</p>
<img src="http://www.urbancastradio.com/Photos/Yarah.jpg" alt="Yarah Bravo" title="Yarah Bravo" height="300" width="284" align="middle" /> ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2005 22:13:56 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/VolumeIV.mp3" length="52177614" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-iv-urbancastradio-121905</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume III: UrbanCastRadio 12/06/05 Enhanced</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>Volume III Enhanced!</h1>
Here is the enhanced version of Volume III. If you use iTunes, you definitely want this version. From iTunes you will be able to view photos of the artist's and go to their respective websites. 
<p>If you are an artist, please go to the blog and read the latest tip which provides information on how to get your music to XM radio for their new channel dedicated to unsigned artists! Take a look you will not be disappointed.</p>
<p>Don't forget to <a href="http://www.urbancastradio.com/wordpress/2005/12/06/urbancast-volume-iii/" target="_self">Vote or Die</a></p>
Until next week, peace and blessings!
]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2005 01:46:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/volumeIII.m4a" length="62473920" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-iii-urbancastradio-120605-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume III: UrbanCastRadio 12/06/05</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>Uhmmmm!</h1>
Hey it's me again, your host Mr. Sea! Here is the latest addition of our "UrbanCast". It's packed with talented artist's such as Raymu, Jaaz, Rich Medina, Big Sty etc.
<p>As I was listening to the show I realized that I said "Uhmmmm" countless times! Being that I didn't go to Broadcasting school, I guess that's ok. If you have a problem with it then come see me!</p>
<p>As usual we are still working out the kinks, but I must say we are almost there. It seems like every week something new comes up. This week was volume.</p>
<p>Please vote for your favorite track of this "UrbanCast" in order to do so please go to the corresponding blog and post a comment. Remember in order to cast your vote you must be registered!
<a href="http://www.urbancastradio.com/wordpress/2005/12/06/urbancast-volume-iii/" target="_self">Vote or Die</a></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2005 22:13:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/VolumeIII.mp3" length="60577344" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-iii-urbancastradio-120605</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume II:UrbanCast Radio 11/26/05 Enhanced!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>iTunes!</h1>
We have finally made onto iTunes! Hopefully this will help us achieve our goal of getting the music heard. To celebrate we have made an enhanced AAC pdocast for iPod owners with color screens to enjoy. Also if you listen via iTunes you will also be able to view pictures of the artists and click on the links to their respective websites. I hope you enjoy this additional feature, if you have any questions or comments please do not hesitate to contact us via e-mail.

<p>dont forget to <a href="http://www.urbancastradio.com/wordpress/2005/11/26/urbancast-volume-ii/" target="_self">Vote or Die</a></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2005 01:26:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/volumeII.m4a" length="52236064" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-iiurbancast-radio-112605-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume II: UrbanCast Radio 11/26/05</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>Finally!</h1>
I know I know, you guys could not wait to get the second addition of the "UrbanCast"! Well here it is...
<p>The Show is loaded with hot tracks from artists such 8th Wonder, Hakim, Krunch, Yuns plus many more.</p>
<p>I have been able to work out some of the kinks give or take a few, so please continue to bear with us. As always feel free to e-mail us or give us a shout out. Check out our Odeo Channel: <a href="http://odeo.com/claim/feed/66e8f69c221116cc">Our Odeo Channel</a> (odeo/66e8f69c221116cc)</p>
<p>Please vote for your favorite track of this "UrbanCast" in order to do so please go to the corresponding blog and post a comment. Remember in order to cast your vote you must be registered!
<a href="http://www.urbancastradio.com/wordpress/2005/11/26/urbancast-volume-ii/" target="_self">Vote or Die</a></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2005 00:56:07 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/VolumeII.mp3" length="50591877" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-ii-urbancast-radio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume 1: UrbanCast Radio 11/9/05</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>It's About Time!</h1>
Ok, after much anticipation the "UrbanCast" has finally been completed! This show has sizzling tracks from artists such as Talonted, Adonis Star, Coco Dupree plus many more.
<p>There are still minor kinks to the show so please bear with us. We would love to hear your opinion of the show and any suggestions you may have. Feel free to e-mail us or insert your comment in the Shout Box.
Please vote for your favorite track of this "UrbanCast" in order to do so please go to the corresponding blog and post a comment. Remember in order to cast your vote you must be registered!
<a href="http://www.urbancastradio.com/wordpress/2005/11/08/first-podcast/" target="_self">Vote or Die</a></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2005 15:38:06 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3?http://www.urbancastradio.com/Enclosures/UrbanCastI.mp3" length="53043059" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">volume-1-urbancast-radio-11905</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UrbanCast To Go Live!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h1>The Little Company That Could!</h1>
It's been a long time coming but UrbanCast Radio is about to go live. In order to make this an enjoyable experience for all our visitors we are making every effort t make sure all the glitches in the system are non existent.
<p>The purpose of UrbanCast Radio is to provide a medium for unsigned artist's in Hip-Hop, R&B, Rap, Spoken Word and Neo Soul etc to get their music heard. Every week we will provide you with an "UrbanCast" for your listening pleasure.</p>
<p>If you are an artist with quality music please feel free to send us your music and we will gladly put it on our show. But remember we are also trying to make this an enjoyable experience for the listener as well so we can't guarantee placement of your track on the show.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2005 17:09:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">urbancast-to-go-live</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>