<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--rss version="2.0"-->
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
 
<channel>
  <title>CMEcorner2go: Hepatitis B</title> 
   <!--link>http://www.cmecorner.com/podcast/hep_05/index.htm</link--> 
    <link>http://www.cmecorner.com/programs.asp?ProductID=322&amp;audience=Physicians</link>
  <category>Medicine</category> 
	<itunes:category text="Education">
	<itunes:category text="Science &amp; Medicine" />
	</itunes:category>

  <itunes:author>CMEcorner.com</itunes:author> 
  <itunes:summary>Welcome to cmecorner2go, an educational service of CME Corner (cmecorner.com). Earn CME (continuing medical education) credit by participating in this FREE audio podcast on chronic Hepatitis B (HBV). This program provides CME credit for physicians, physician assistants (PA), nurses, and nurse practitioners (NP). cmecorner2go is dedicated to providing quality medical education for health care professional. Please visit us online at www.cmecorner.com. </itunes:summary>
  <description>Welcome to cmecorner2go, an educational service of CME Corner (cmecorner.com). Earn CME (continuing medical education) credit by participating in this FREE audio podcast on chronic Hepatitis B (HBV). This program provides CME credit for physicians, physician assistants (PA), nurses, and nurse practitioners (NP). Please visit us online at www.cmecorner.com.</description> 
  <webMaster>cmecorner@medcommedia.com</webMaster> 
  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2006 08:00:00 EST</pubDate> 
  <image>
  <title>CME CORNER 2go logo</title> 
  <url>http://www.cmecorner.com/podcast/hep_05/cme2go_hep.jpg</url> 
  <!--link>http://www.cmecorner.com/podcast/hep_05/index.htm</link--> 
  <link>http://www.cmecorner.com/programs.asp?ProductID=322&amp;audience=Physicians</link>
  
  <description> Welcome to CME Corner 2go, a FREE CME (Continuing Medical Education) podcast service for doctors, physician assistants (PA), nurses, nurse practitioners (NP), and pharmacists. Earn continuing education credit (CME, AAFP, AAPA, CE, and CNE) by participating in this FREE podcast on chronic Hepatitis B. CME Corner is dedicated to providing quality medical education for health care professionals. Please visit us at www.cmecorner.com to view our full selection of CME and CE programs and podcasts.</description> 
  </image>
  <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit> 

  
  <item>
  <title>This program has expired. Please visit CMEcorner.com for more podcasts</title> 
  <link>http://www.cmecorner.com/podcast/expired.pdf</link>
   <itunes:author>cmecorner.com</itunes:author> 
  <description>This is the PDF workbook. Click on the link and it should open in your browser with Adobe Acrobat Reader. Complete and print the test for continuing education credit.</description> 
    <!--category>Education</category--> 
  <category>Medicine</category> 
	<itunes:category text="Science &amp; Medicine">
	<itunes:category text="Medicine" />
	</itunes:category>
   <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2006 08:00:00 EST</pubDate> 
  <itunes:keywords>
CME, continuing medical education, medical education, continuing education, credit, diabetes, DM, insulin, medicine, nursing, pharmacist, nurse, physician, pharmacy, NP
</itunes:keywords>
  <enclosure url="http://www.cmecorner.com/podcast/expired.pdf" length="2395749" type="application/pdf" /> 
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.cmecorner.com/podcast/expired.pdf</guid> 
  </item>
  </channel>
  </rss>
