<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>Mutation Comedy -- Improvisational, Sketch, and Strange</title>
<atom:link href="http://teammutation.com/podcast.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
<description>'Mutation Comedy' is an ad-lib comedy and audio editing team that has been making audio skits since 1990. The Mutation team is back at it fresh in 2006. We have three new albums: 'Empirical Aquariums', 'Carpet of Capricorn', and 'The Jolly Golden Goose'. The Mutation team has a strong work ethic producing new material for their fans, never leaving them without new skits and shows to sink into. With heavy influences from such BBC greats as Rowan Atkinson, Jennifer Saunders, Stephen Fry, the Monty Python crew, and league of Gentlemen - the frolicking silliness of this U.S. comedy team presents an alternative to the modern anti-intellectual.</description>
<link>http://www.teammutation.com</link>

<image>
<url>http://www.teammutation.com/paranoid.JPG</url>
<title>Mutation Comedy -- The new age of improvisational, sketch and stand-up Comedy</title>
<link>http://www.teammutation.com</link>
<width>144</width>
<height>101</height>
</image>

<item>
<title>Jolly Golden Goose Part 1</title>
<description>Skits include Martha Stewart, Bon Jovi Senior Citizen, Jo Kamel Philantropist, Blonan the Barbarian and a look at Adultery.</description>
<link>http://www.teammutation.com</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.teammutation.com/podcasts/Jolly_golden_goose.mp3" length="800" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 00:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Do The Knuckle Drag</title>
<description>
Team Mutation reports on the latest markets and fetish capitalism. The team then dredges up an old interview, banned from PBS, with John Lennon and Big Bird. Team Mutation then goes to Amsterdam Holland to report on the Bongs-R-US festival. A look at the latest in bong technology.</description>
<link>http://www.teammutation.com</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.teammutation.com/podcasts/Do_the_knuckle_drag.mp3" length="855" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 00:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Easter_oh_Nein</title>
<description>
In celebration of Easter 2009, the Mutation Comedy Crew Cast a Pod.  The episode starts with the contemplation of revelatory scripture, Ancient Tibetian egg-hunting, Life during the Tudor era of England. We then present a documentary on the Barbershop Quartet who went into sketch comedy, and ending on the true story of the career that started in the 1930'cartoon... Woody Woodpecker.</description>
<link>http://www.teammutation.com</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.teammutation.com/podcasts/Easter_oh_nein.mp3" length="957" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 00:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bobbies_and_Cops-Mutation_Comedy</title>
<description>
A BBC radio episode on the difference between crime in the U.K. compared to crime in the U.S.A.  A forum with a U.S. Officer and a British Bobbie.</description>
<link>http://www.teammutation.com</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.teammutation.com/podcasts/Bobbies_and_Cops-mutation.mp3" length="300" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 00:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Sassafras_Sawdust_A</title>
<description>
Part A of A/B in a 2009 session titled:  'Sassafras Sawdust'.  Includes: Solutions for a snoring Dog, Aliens learn the welfare state, culinary show experiences futility, pole dancing 101 meets postmodernism, Legal marijuana in quantity, Wrestling star Rick Flair gets married with digression, and orifice expansion as a new model for making skits.  </description>
<link>http://www.teammutation.com</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.teammutation.com/podcasts/Sassafras_Sawdust_A.mp3" length="901" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 00:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Young_Marilyn_Monroe</title>
<description>
Mr. Monroe helps his eager daughter in a career move</description>
<link>http://www.teammutation.com</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.teammutation.com/podcasts/Young_Marilyn_Monroe.mp3" length="213" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 00:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Mutation Radio - Empirical Aquariums Part A</title>
<description>
The First Podcast of 2009, with more to come very soon.  This Show contains 'Locks of Luck Hairstyling Salon', 'Sunday Paper', 2 'Of Chemical Bondage' episodes,
and 'Pink Lady Gym'.</description>
<link>http://www.teammutation.com</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.teammutation.com/podcasts/empirical_aquariums_a.mp3" length="1781" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 00:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

  </channel>
  </rss>