<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel>
  <title>Interstate Travel Weather Page</title>
  <link>http://www.bridalweather.com/travelweather.html</link>
  <description>Audio weather forecasts for major US Interstates.  An Interactive US map to click on.</description>
  <item>
    <title>Interstate 95 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I95.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-95.  Temperature forecasts, radars, and and Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I95.mp3" length="1084200" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Interstate 90 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I90.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-90.  Temperature forecasts, radars, and and Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I90.mp3" length="1351914" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
   <item>
    <title>Interstate 85 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I85.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-85.  The Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Typically no longer than a minute and a half.  Longer in serious weather.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I85.mp3" length="1476597" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
   <item>
    <title>Interstate 84 Weather </title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I84.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-84.  The Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Typically no longer than a minute and a half.  Longer in serious weather.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I84.mp3" length="2062482" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
   <item>
    <title>Interstate 80 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I80.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-80.  Temperature forecasts, radars, and and Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I80.mp3" length="1064184" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
   <item>
   <title>Interstate 75 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I75.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-75.  Temperature forecasts, radars, and and Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I75.mp3" length="1267680" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Interstate 70 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I70.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-70.  Temperature forecasts, radars, and and Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I70.mp3" length="1128402" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Interstate 65 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I65.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-65.  Temperature forecasts, radars, and and Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I65.mp3" length="1476597" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
   <item>
   <title>Interstate 55 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I55.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-55.  The Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Typically no longer than a minute and a half.  Longer in serious weather.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I55.mp3" length="1476597" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Interstate 40 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I40.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-40.  Temperature forecasts, radars, and and Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I40.mp3" length="1246413" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Interstate 35 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I35.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-35.  The Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Typically no longer than a minute and a half.  Longer in serious weather.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I35.mp3" length="1476597" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
   <item>
   <title>Interstate 25 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I25.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-25.  The Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Typically no longer than a minute and a half.  Longer in serious weather.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I25.mp3" length="1476597" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Interstate 20 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I20.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-20.  The Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Typically no longer than a minute and a half.  Longer in serious weather.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I20.mp3" length="1046670" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
   <item>
   <title>Interstate 15 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I15.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-15.  The Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Typically no longer than a minute and a half.  Longer in serious weather.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I15.mp3" length="2032458" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Interstate 10 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I10.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-10.  The Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Typically no longer than a minute and a half.  Longer in serious weather.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I10.mp3" length="1335651" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Interstate 5 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I5.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-5.  Temperature forecasts, radars, and and Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I5.mp3" length="1317720" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Interstate 4 Weather</title>
<link>http://www.bridalweather.com/I4.html</link>
    <description>Get daily weather forecasts for the entire length of I-4.  The Audio weather cast starts automatically playing.  Typically no longer than a minute and a half.  Longer in serious weather.  Updated daily or every other day if the forecast is on!</description>
    <enclosure url="http://www.bridalweather.com/I4.mp3" length="1476597" type="audio/mpeg" />
  </item>
</channel></rss>