<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
  <channel>
    <title>Ollie Style</title>
    <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
    <description>Pinoy Podcast




</description>
    <language>en-ph</language>
    <generator>podOmatic RSS Generator</generator>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 06:35:43 GMT</pubDate>
    <itunes:keywords>ad,ads,adverstiser,alaala,araw,arawaraw,ascap,asian,astig,attila,audio,australia,bading,banda,bands,baso,bobo,bomb,boys,bulaga,burat,business,call,center,comedy,contact,de,diet,dyip,eat,eheads,files,filipino,filscap,free,gago,gag&#225;,girls,globe,hataw,hostess,how,hun,interview,jeep,jeepney,joey,kanta,kantutan,kid,korn,krung,krungkrung,kupal,learn,leon,manila,mega,metro,music,negosyo,new,ofw,ollie,open,ortigas,pasig,personal,philippines,phone,pilipino,pinas,pinay,pinoy,podcast,podcasts,poea,radio,rock,sched,scholarship,sex,shedule,show,smart,sop,sotto,style,tagalog,taguig,talk,tamaraw,tarantado,tarsier,to,totoy,turat,vic,willy,words,yahoo,zelda</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>RADIO SHOW Listen to this Pinoy Podcast! Pakinggan mo! A Show that tackles Filipino life </itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Ollie Style</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>olliestyleradioshow-at-gmail[dot]com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
    <itunes:image href="http://assets.podomatic.net/mymedia/thumb/26126/600x600_604067.bmp"/>
    <itunes:author>Ollie Style</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Pinoy Podcast




</itunes:summary>
    <atom:link type="application/rss+xml" rel="self" href="http://ollie.podomatic.com/rss2.xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 13 - Alaska</title>
      <description>This episode is all about Alaska

http://olliestyle.blogspot.com
www.olliestyleradioshow.us.tt</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2008-02-28T17_30_53-08_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2008-02-28T17_30_53-08_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 01:30:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2008-02-29</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>13,alaska,episode</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="14589830" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2008-02-28T17_30_53-08_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>999</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>This episode is all about Alaska

http://olliestyle.blogspot.com
www.olliestyleradioshow.us.tt</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US 101 Part 2 - How to Easily Get A Job In a Call Center, Survive, and Be Promoted - Ollie Style Radio Show Episode 12</title>
      <description>This episode is about Alabama...

http://olliestyle.blogspot.com
http://getpaidtoblog.tk
http://freearticlesblog.tk
http://hotelclubs.tk
http://medicalalarms.tk
http://olliestyle.co.nr
http://olliestyleradioshow.tk
http://freearticles.tk
http://pinoypodcaster.tk
http://noypiscandals.tk
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-09-18T14_35_36-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-09-18T14_35_36-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 21:35:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-09-18</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>alaba,call,cente,jobs</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="14427004" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-09-18T14_35_36-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>990</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>This episode is about Alabama...

http://olliestyle.blogspot.com
http://getpaidtoblog.tk
http://freearticlesblog.tk
http://hotelclubs.tk
http://medicalalarms.tk
http://olliestyle.co.nr
http://olliestyleradioshow.tk
http://freearticles.tk
http://pinoypodcaster.tk
http://noypiscandals.tk
</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US 101 Part 1 - How to Easily Get A Job In a Call Center, Survive, and Be Promoted - Ollie Style Radio Show Episode 11</title>
      <description>Pinoy Podcaster - Ollie Style - Episode 11 
www.olliestyleradioshow.tk

Holidays and Special Events in the USA

www.olliestyleradioshow.tk</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-07-27T11_47_35-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-07-27T11_47_35-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2006 18:47:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-07-27</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>101,business,call,center,comedy,filipino,interviews,job,learn,music,negosyo,new,ofw,personal,philippines,pilipino,pinay,pinoy,podcast,radio,sex,show,tagalog,talk,us</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="24475648" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-07-27T11_47_35-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>1529</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>Pinoy Podcaster - Ollie Style - Episode 11 
www.olliestyleradioshow.tk

Holidays and Special Events in the USA

www.olliestyleradioshow.tk</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Easily Get a Job in A Call Center, Survive and Be Promoted-[How to Get Hired by Being Obvious] Part 4</title>
      <description>If you want a drink of water, do you hire a focus group or pick up the Yellow Pages? No. You go to the kitchen, fill a glass and drink. You take the shortest route to fill your need. 
The path is obvious, right? 
Your job search is the same way. The formula for success can be obvious, if you take the time to look at how others have found employment before you. 
Here are three ways to find work faster by &quot;being obvious.&quot; 
Obvious Tip #1: Follow Up With Employers
You can't get hired if employers don't know you exist. 
So, if you're sending out resumes with no response, or going to interviews without getting job offers, you need to follow up better with employers. Because you may have fallen off their radar. 
Know this: getting hired may be your #1 priority, but it may rank around #459 in the mind of a busy employer. That means you can't depend on them to call you back. It's up to you to take action. 
You have to follow up. 
But as many as 90% of job seekers FAIL to do so, according to my observations and those of hiring experts like Elizabeth Laukka, National Recruiter for Minneapolis-based Wells Fargo Home Mortgage. 
&quot;It so rare to receive a thank-you note or follow-up phone call that these really stand out for me. I get them from around 10-20% of the people I interview,&quot; says Laukka. 
And what if you don't have an address to send a thank-you letter to? 
&quot;I would absolutely give my mailing address to candidates who wanted to drop something in the mail -- all they have to do is ask,&quot; says Laukka. 
Obvious Tip #2: Don't Alienate People Who Can Help You 
In this age of Palm Pilots, Day Planners and other organizational gizmos, there's no excuse for not staying on top of the details in your job search. 
Example: I agreed last month to write a resume free of charge for one local man. He replied once to the three emails I sent him. And he never did return my phone call. 
I figure he's either been hired (and no longer needs a resume) or can't keep track of his phone and email messages. In either case, he won't be getting my help. 
Here's the reality: the people most able to help you find a job are busy. And they're mentally keeping score of how quickly and professionally you respond to their emails and phone calls. 
So it behooves you to treat everyone you meet in your job search with courtesy. Respect their time. Return their phone calls. And they will champion you with hiring managers. 
Obvious Tip #3: Ask For The Job 
OK. I saved the best for last. That's because if I had put this tip first, I would have scared half of you away by now. 
Let me explain. 
Any successful job search all boils down to two simple facts. You must: 
1. meet the right hiring authority, and
2. convince that person to hire you. 
It follows that, the more hiring authorities you can meet, the faster you'll find work. 
So, why don't more people just introduce themselves to prospective employers and ask for a job? Is this method too obvious? Frightening? 
I don't know. 
But I do know one thing. If you do this right, you will get hired. Fast. 
Here's an example shared by Claire Nelligan, from the WorkForce Center in Minneapolis. 
&quot;I knew a job seeker who wanted work as a baker. We wrote his resume and was going to mail it. But I asked him to put on his business clothes and walk the resume in to his top three prospective employers,&quot; says Nelligan. 
Nelligan told him: &quot;Ask for the manager. Introduce yourself. Tell them you want to work there. Tell them that you appreciate they are busy, and quickly share what value you would bring to their organization. Give them the resume and tell them you will call to set up a convenient time to answer any questions they may have about how your skills could meet their needs.&quot; 
What happened next? 
&quot;He was interviewed on the spot and left with a job offer,&quot; says Nelligan. 
Now, can you expect to walk into Trump Tower, ask to meet The Donald and get a job offer as his next apprentice? Probably not. But you can tweak this method to match your personality and ask to meet almost any hiring authority you choose, so long as you're persistent and professional. 
Now, go out and make your own luck! 
Article by Kevin Donlin, President of Guaranteed Resumes. Since 1996, Guaranteed R&#233;sum&#233;s has provided resume, Internet resume, cover letters and job searches for clients in all 50 states and 23 countries. To download a Free Job Search Kit and learn more, visit http://www.gresumes.com 


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-07-12T11_33_17-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-07-12T11_33_17-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2006 18:33:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-07-12</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>business,call,center,comedy,filipino,interviews,job,learn,music,negosyo,new,ofw,personal,philippines,pilipino,pinay,pinoy,podcast,radio,sex,show,tagalog,talk</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="24967168" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-07-12T11_33_17-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>1560</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>If you want a drink of water, do you hire a focus group or pick up the Yellow Pages? No. You go to the kitchen, fill a glass and drink. You take the shortest route to fill your need. 
The path is obvious, right? 
Your job search is the same way. The formula for success can be obvious, if you take the time to look at how others have found employment before you. 
Here are three ways to find work faster by &quot;being obvious.&quot; 
Obvious Tip #1: Follow Up With Employers
You can't get hired if employers don't know you exist. 
So, if you're sending out resumes with no response, or going to interviews without getting job offers, you need to follow up better with employers. Because you may have fallen off their radar. 
Know this: getting hired may be your #1 priority, but it may rank around #459 in the mind of a busy employer. That means you can't depend on them to call you back. It's up to you to take action. 
You have to follow up. 
But as many as 90% of job seekers FAIL to do so, according to my observations and those of hiring experts like Elizabeth Laukka, National Recruiter for Minneapolis-based Wells Fargo Home Mortgage. 
&quot;It so rare to receive a thank-you note or follow-up phone call that these really stand out for me. I get them from around 10-20% of the people I interview,&quot; says Laukka. 
And what if you don't have an address to send a thank-you letter to? 
&quot;I would absolutely give my mailing address to candidates who wanted to drop something in the mail -- all they have to do is ask,&quot; says Laukka. 
Obvious Tip #2: Don't Alienate People Who Can Help You 
In this age of Palm Pilots, Day Planners and other organizational gizmos, there's no excuse for not staying on top of the details in your job search. 
Example: I agreed last month to write a resume free of charge for one local man. He replied once to the three emails I sent him. And he never did return my phone call. 
I figure he's either been hired (and no longer needs a resume) or can't keep track of his phone and email messages. In either case, he won't be getting my help. 
Here's the reality: the people most able to help you find a job are busy. And they're mentally keeping score of how quickly and professionally you respond to their emails and phone calls. 
So it behooves you to treat everyone you meet in your job search with courtesy. Respect their time. Return their phone calls. And they will champion you with hiring managers. 
Obvious Tip #3: Ask For The Job 
OK. I saved the best for last. That's because if I had put this tip first, I would have scared half of you away by now. 
Let me explain. 
Any successful job search all boils down to two simple facts. You must: 
1. meet the right hiring authority, and
2. convince that person to hire you. 
It follows that, the more hiring authorities you can meet, the faster you'll find work. 
So, why don't more people just introduce themselves to prospective employers and ask for a job? Is this method too obvious? Frightening? 
I don't know. 
But I do know one thing. If you do this right, you will get hired. Fast. 
Here's an example shared by Claire Nelligan, from the WorkForce Center in Minneapolis. 
&quot;I knew a job seeker who wanted work as a baker. We wrote his resume and was going to mail it. But I asked him to put on his business clothes and walk the resume in to his top three prospective employers,&quot; says Nelligan. 
Nelligan told him: &quot;Ask for the manager. Introduce yourself. Tell them you want to work there. Tell them that you appreciate they are busy, and quickly share what value you would bring to their organization. Give them the resume and tell them you will call to set up a convenient time to answer any questions they may have about how your skills could meet their needs.&quot; 
What happened next? 
&quot;He was interviewed on the spot and left with a job offer,&quot; says Nelligan. 
Now, can you expect to walk into Trump Tower, ask to meet The Donald and get a job offer as his next apprentice? Pr(continued)</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Easily Get A Job in a Call Center, Survive and Be Promoted [Job Interview ] Part 3</title>
      <description>Job Interview [continued]

15.) Do you own a life insurance policy? 
16.) Do you have a savings plan? 
17.) Are you in debt? 
18.) How large is your visa bill? 
19.) Do you pay off your charge card bills every month? 
20.) Have you ever been refused a bond? 
21.) Do you have a valid driver's license? 
22.) Have you ever had a driver's license revoked? Why? 
23) Are you a Team Player? 
24 ) You look like a person &quot;on the ball&quot; Where do you see yourself in time period - 1 year, 2 years etc? 
25) How do you see yourself fitting in our organization? 
As previously mentioned most interviewers have little or no originality in their Interview skills and procedures. All they generally do is copy the standard questions that have been commonly asked. Little originality if at all. The trick is to plan and anticipate your answers to the se &quot;vital&quot; questions in order that you past muster in order to get the job and income involved. 
Standard practice is to have 3 interviews 
1) Interview one is the first step - basic screening 
2) Interview 2 is a bit more serious - You have passed step one - If they are thorough they may have called your references 
3) Interview 3 is usually by a team or another member of the &quot;team&quot; A more senior person or even just another person in the organization will interview you. Although the reason for this will be claimed to be to add in additional expertise and experience into this vital hiring procedure the real reason is to spread the responsibility so that no one person can be blamed if &quot;you don't work out &quot;. 
Remember none of these questions need be answered by you. However you take the risk of offending the interviewer (and their interview skills and thus ending your chances for employment and income from that firm). Note that a number of the questions may be totally incongruous , that is inconsistent and incompatible. Best not to laugh. For example the interviewer may ask if you are a self starter, take responsibility and make your own decisions and then ask leading questions To ask if find out if you are the type that always follows company procedure without question. Or they may ask questions to verify that you always consider the company's needs and wants as most important and then ask questions to verify that &quot;That a customer should never question the company's policy on returns or extended warranties&quot;. When the interviewer goes to great length to explain that the company has a great focus for &quot; team players&quot; it is not a good idea to point out that being a &quot; team player &quot; is not always a good thing. That the interview questions have focused on identifying you as a &quot; self starter who takes charge&quot;. And besides that it is true that the Sept 11 hijackers were &quot; good Team Players&quot;. Lastly two points - One very intelligent manager's hiring guideline was that when he took out a serious candidate to lunch he watched if the candidate salted his soup before tasting it. The manager wanted people in his organization who checked things out before jumping to act. If you get an interviewer who asks original thought provoking questions in your interview take quick note. For example if the manager asks a question such as &quot;It is 4:55 pm. A customer is considering buying an expensive item which the store has had on hand for some time and has not sold. The customer is very interested in this item. Has phoned their spouse for their ok. The phone call is going to be returned for approval at 5:15. What do you do?&quot; Take note - this is a very smart person in an organization which may well be very good to work for. 

Shaun Stevens www.aceemploymentservices.net call_kirk@hotmail.com 
About the Author

http://olliestyle.co.nr

About the Author
Shaun Stevens Senior Marketing Consultant Ace Employment Services Winnipeg Experience in Marketing in the Employment , Human Resources and Training Fields. Experience in Self Help , Training and Assessment as well as Government Corrections Area

http://olliestyle.co.nr

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-07-06T09_46_02-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-07-06T09_46_02-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2006 16:46:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-07-06</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>business,call,center,comedy,filipino,interviews,job,learn,music,negosyo,new,ofw,personal,philippines,pilipino,pinay,pinoy,podcast,radio,sex,show,tagalog,talk</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="21536768" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-07-06T09_46_02-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>1346</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>Job Interview [continued]

15.) Do you own a life insurance policy? 
16.) Do you have a savings plan? 
17.) Are you in debt? 
18.) How large is your visa bill? 
19.) Do you pay off your charge card bills every month? 
20.) Have you ever been refused a bond? 
21.) Do you have a valid driver's license? 
22.) Have you ever had a driver's license revoked? Why? 
23) Are you a Team Player? 
24 ) You look like a person &quot;on the ball&quot; Where do you see yourself in time period - 1 year, 2 years etc? 
25) How do you see yourself fitting in our organization? 
As previously mentioned most interviewers have little or no originality in their Interview skills and procedures. All they generally do is copy the standard questions that have been commonly asked. Little originality if at all. The trick is to plan and anticipate your answers to the se &quot;vital&quot; questions in order that you past muster in order to get the job and income involved. 
Standard practice is to have 3 interviews 
1) Interview one is the first step - basic screening 
2) Interview 2 is a bit more serious - You have passed step one - If they are thorough they may have called your references 
3) Interview 3 is usually by a team or another member of the &quot;team&quot; A more senior person or even just another person in the organization will interview you. Although the reason for this will be claimed to be to add in additional expertise and experience into this vital hiring procedure the real reason is to spread the responsibility so that no one person can be blamed if &quot;you don't work out &quot;. 
Remember none of these questions need be answered by you. However you take the risk of offending the interviewer (and their interview skills and thus ending your chances for employment and income from that firm). Note that a number of the questions may be totally incongruous , that is inconsistent and incompatible. Best not to laugh. For example the interviewer may ask if you are a self starter, take responsibility and make your own decisions and then ask leading questions To ask if find out if you are the type that always follows company procedure without question. Or they may ask questions to verify that you always consider the company's needs and wants as most important and then ask questions to verify that &quot;That a customer should never question the company's policy on returns or extended warranties&quot;. When the interviewer goes to great length to explain that the company has a great focus for &quot; team players&quot; it is not a good idea to point out that being a &quot; team player &quot; is not always a good thing. That the interview questions have focused on identifying you as a &quot; self starter who takes charge&quot;. And besides that it is true that the Sept 11 hijackers were &quot; good Team Players&quot;. Lastly two points - One very intelligent manager's hiring guideline was that when he took out a serious candidate to lunch he watched if the candidate salted his soup before tasting it. The manager wanted people in his organization who checked things out before jumping to act. If you get an interviewer who asks original thought provoking questions in your interview take quick note. For example if the manager asks a question such as &quot;It is 4:55 pm. A customer is considering buying an expensive item which the store has had on hand for some time and has not sold. The customer is very interested in this item. Has phoned their spouse for their ok. The phone call is going to be returned for approval at 5:15. What do you do?&quot; Take note - this is a very smart person in an organization which may well be very good to work for. 

Shaun Stevens www.aceemploymentservices.net call_kirk@hotmail.com 
About the Author

http://olliestyle.co.nr

About the Author
Shaun Stevens Senior Marketing Consultant Ace Employment Services Winnipeg Experience in Marketing in the Employment , Human Resources and Training Fields. Experience in Self Help , Training and Assessment as well as Government Corrections Area

http:(continued)</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Easily Get A Job in a Call Center, Survive and Be Promoted [Job Interview ] Part 2</title>
      <description>Standard Interview Questions on Personal and Family: 

1.) What are your parents' occupations? 
2.) Do you live with your parents? 
3.) Do you own or rent your home? 
4.) How far do you live from this company? 
5.) Do you speak a foreign language especially French or Spanish? 
6.) How much time do you spend with your family ? 
7.) In your opinion, what makes a happy? marriage 
8.) Who is the boss in your family? 
9.) Is your spouse employed? Will there be a conflict ? 
10.) What contributed to your divorce? What have you learned from this experience? 
11.) Describe your relationship with your children. 

12.) What child care arrangements have been made 
for your children? 
13.) Do you keep and follow a personal budget? 
14.) Do you balance your chequebook on a regular basis? 

http://olliestyle.co.nr

About the Author
Shaun Stevens Senior Marketing Consultant Ace Employment Services Winnipeg Experience in Marketing in the Employment , Human Resources and Training Fields. Experience in Self Help , Training and Assessment as well as Government Corrections Area

http://olliestyle.co.nr

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-07-05T18_07_25-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-07-05T18_07_25-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2006 01:07:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-19</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-07-06</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>[job,],be,business,call,center,comedy,easily,filipino,get,in,interview,job,learn,music,negosyo,new,ofw,personal,philippines,pilipino,pinay,pinoy,podcast,promoted,radio,radiohow,sex,show,survive,tagalog,talk,to</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="29227008" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-07-05T18_07_25-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>1826</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>Standard Interview Questions on Personal and Family: 

1.) What are your parents' occupations? 
2.) Do you live with your parents? 
3.) Do you own or rent your home? 
4.) How far do you live from this company? 
5.) Do you speak a foreign language especially French or Spanish? 
6.) How much time do you spend with your family ? 
7.) In your opinion, what makes a happy? marriage 
8.) Who is the boss in your family? 
9.) Is your spouse employed? Will there be a conflict ? 
10.) What contributed to your divorce? What have you learned from this experience? 
11.) Describe your relationship with your children. 

12.) What child care arrangements have been made 
for your children? 
13.) Do you keep and follow a personal budget? 
14.) Do you balance your chequebook on a regular basis? 

http://olliestyle.co.nr

About the Author
Shaun Stevens Senior Marketing Consultant Ace Employment Services Winnipeg Experience in Marketing in the Employment , Human Resources and Training Fields. Experience in Self Help , Training and Assessment as well as Government Corrections Area

http://olliestyle.co.nr

</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Easily Get A Job in a Call Center, Survive and Be Promoted  [Job Interview ] Part 1</title>
      <description>[CLICK THE PLAY BUTTON BELOW TO LISTEN TO THIS PODCAST]

Episode Summary [Ollie Style Radio Show]

Job Interview Basics Discussion, 
Tips on job interviews.  Part 1

Job Interview Basics : Personal Questions 
[read on the &quot;Ollie Style Radio Show&quot;]

Of all the questions you'll be asked, personal and family ones appear to be the most &quot;statistical.&quot; For this reason, most jobseekers answer them in a &quot;static&quot; way, with &quot;name, rank, and serial number.&quot; They're also often emotionally charged, since interviewers ask about personal perils, family feuds, and status symbols. Therefore, rehearsing your lines is particularly important, since what you say is as important as what you convey. While most of the questions in this area have only marginal value in determining your qualifications to perform a specific job, you must get past them so you can get down to business with the interviewer. That's why they're called KO factors. Wrong answers will knock you out in Round 1; right ones will keep you in the ring for a while. Personal and family items are invariably at the top of resumes, on the front of application forms, and at the beginning of interview checklists. Since these are the &quot;cue cards&quot; used in the actual interview, expect the questions in Act 1, Round 1. &quot;First impressions really count&quot; (and they really do to overworked people who are interviewing), this is your chance to shine. Most film critics will tell you they lock into a review within five minutes. If they watch longer, it's either to enjoy the show or to justify their negative rating. That's why lawyers often see judges writing their decisions from the bench soon after the opening statements. Yours will, too. Your judge is overworked. Then greet the interviewer with the Magic Four Hellos: 
1.) Smile. If you can't fake it, just think about how lucky the interviewer is to be meeting you. 
2.) Direct eye contact. If it's too much for you, look at the bridge of the interviewer's nose. 
3.) Introduce yourself. Say, &quot;Hi, I'm (first name) (last name). It's a pleasure meeting you.&quot; 
4)A firm but gentle handshake. Rehearse. No live shark; no dead flounder. 
Then, once you're &quot;on the road&quot;. Head for the chair on your favored side (right if you are right-handed, etc.) If you're ambidextrous, you can take center stage. Just be sure there's a chair behind you. Stand there until you're asked to be seated. Basically most managers copy their bosses training, style and procedures (or lack thereof). There is little originality in interview questions. The same questions are repeated in interviews ad infinitum. The problem is that once you are hired all your wonderful traits are forgotten. It simply becomes &quot;You had better work your ass off or you will lose your job.&quot; 


About the Author
Shaun Stevens Senior Marketing Consultant Ace Employment Services Winnipeg Experience in Marketing in the Employment , Human Resources and Training Fields. Experience in Self Help , Training and Assessment as well as Government Corrections Area</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-07-03T13_54_22-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-07-03T13_54_22-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2006 20:54:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-07-03</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>call,center,don,favis,interview,job,manny,manolo,paquiao</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="34639872" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-07-03T13_54_22-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>2164</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>[CLICK THE PLAY BUTTON BELOW TO LISTEN TO THIS PODCAST]

Episode Summary [Ollie Style Radio Show]

Job Interview Basics Discussion, 
Tips on job interviews.  Part 1

Job Interview Basics : Personal Questions 
[read on the &quot;Ollie Style Radio Show&quot;]

Of all the questions you'll be asked, personal and family ones appear to be the most &quot;statistical.&quot; For this reason, most jobseekers answer them in a &quot;static&quot; way, with &quot;name, rank, and serial number.&quot; They're also often emotionally charged, since interviewers ask about personal perils, family feuds, and status symbols. Therefore, rehearsing your lines is particularly important, since what you say is as important as what you convey. While most of the questions in this area have only marginal value in determining your qualifications to perform a specific job, you must get past them so you can get down to business with the interviewer. That's why they're called KO factors. Wrong answers will knock you out in Round 1; right ones will keep you in the ring for a while. Personal and family items are invariably at the top of resumes, on the front of application forms, and at the beginning of interview checklists. Since these are the &quot;cue cards&quot; used in the actual interview, expect the questions in Act 1, Round 1. &quot;First impressions really count&quot; (and they really do to overworked people who are interviewing), this is your chance to shine. Most film critics will tell you they lock into a review within five minutes. If they watch longer, it's either to enjoy the show or to justify their negative rating. That's why lawyers often see judges writing their decisions from the bench soon after the opening statements. Yours will, too. Your judge is overworked. Then greet the interviewer with the Magic Four Hellos: 
1.) Smile. If you can't fake it, just think about how lucky the interviewer is to be meeting you. 
2.) Direct eye contact. If it's too much for you, look at the bridge of the interviewer's nose. 
3.) Introduce yourself. Say, &quot;Hi, I'm (first name) (last name). It's a pleasure meeting you.&quot; 
4)A firm but gentle handshake. Rehearse. No live shark; no dead flounder. 
Then, once you're &quot;on the road&quot;. Head for the chair on your favored side (right if you are right-handed, etc.) If you're ambidextrous, you can take center stage. Just be sure there's a chair behind you. Stand there until you're asked to be seated. Basically most managers copy their bosses training, style and procedures (or lack thereof). There is little originality in interview questions. The same questions are repeated in interviews ad infinitum. The problem is that once you are hired all your wonderful traits are forgotten. It simply becomes &quot;You had better work your ass off or you will lose your job.&quot; 


About the Author
Shaun Stevens Senior Marketing Consultant Ace Employment Services Winnipeg Experience in Marketing in the Employment , Human Resources and Training Fields. Experience in Self Help , Training and Assessment as well as Government Corrections Area</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Revive Your Sex Life Today!</title>
      <description>[CLICK THE PLAY BUTTON BELOW TO LISTEN TO THIS PODCAST]

How to Revive Your Sex Life Today!   
By: Sarah Brindisi [read on the &quot;Ollie Style&quot; Show]


Has your sex life been a bit neglected lately? Its not like you don't care but well, it's just finding the time and energy. It seems impossible some days because there's work and cleaning and working out and grocery shopping and cooking dinner, laundry, kids, family commitments, friends, ironing! When you do get horizontal you pass out within minutes. Or you're not in the mood. Or you just can't be bothered. Soon enough a month has passed and you can't remember the last time you had sex. And when was the last time you kissed your partner and I mean really kissed them, not just a polite peck? 

Or maybe you've just fallen into a rut. You have sex in the same place at roughly the same time each week and do the same things. Routine is good for things like brushing your teeth but it shouldn't come into your sex life when variety and excitement are crucial elements in making it fulfilling.

If this sounds like you and you want to kickstart your sex life back into well, life, then read on. 

1. Be spontaneous 
The element of surprise can be very seductive. Take a shower together, surprise your partner with a long passionate kiss when they are expecting to just graze lips, buy some new lingerie and wear it. 

2. Get healthy
Eating well and regular exercise put you in better touch with your body and that inner healthy glow not only makes you look more attractive but gives you heaps of energy and makes you feel more vibrant and alive.

3. Be affectionate 
If you haven't had sex for awhile then it may be better to build up slowly to get back into the groove. Instead of trying to go from a standing start to racing speed, ease your way back into the physical by touching when you can and by being considerate with each other. Touch when you talk. Stop to kiss when you walk past each other in the hallway. Trail your finger along their shoulder as they sit reading a magazine. Snuggle on the couch in front of your favorite movie. 

4. Be sensual
Give your partner a peppermint foot bath when they get home from a busy day. Massage their hands, scalp, back - wherever takes your fancy (if you don't know how to massage, don't think about it, just do what feels good). Or try a lighter touch by using a feather or silk scarve to trail along the length of your partner.

5. Be encouraging when your partner does something you like 
Even if you've been together a long time your partner doesn't always know what you like and even if they do it doesn't hurt to tell them once in awhile. Say what you like and why you like it, if they have more information you never know what they may come up with to please you.

6. Read your partner an erotic bedtime story 
The mind is crucial in any attempt to resuscitate your sex life. It needs to be turned on first and the body will follow. There is some great erotic fiction around or you could try Nancy Friday for stories about other people's sexual fantasies.

7. Have fun 
When was the last time you laughed together? Put on your favourite track and dance. Or buy the music that was popular when you first got together and play that for a trip down memory lane over dinner. Take a midnight dip. 

8. Write a sexy letter 
If you can't tell your partner what you really want them to do to you, then writing it down is a great alternative. It lets you be as specific as you like without feeling like your face is going to turn tomato red and gives your partner time to process what you've said and get into the mood (if you need help putting your letter together try visiting www.loveyouletters.com for easy-to-us love templates).

9. Experiment
Learn a new technique together. Try a romantic weekend away. Or you could try a sex toy from one of the many on offer. If you always have sex lying down then try standing or sitting. If you're always on top then try switching things around.

10. Focus on the now
When you do get down to it, it is crucial that you focus on exactly what it is you are doing. To do this you must stop the chatter within your own head. Don't worry that you forgot to pick up the drycleaning, or how you need to call your mother about her birthday, or the fact that you're out of cereal. Leave all that stuff to later. Much later. Chances are it won't seem nearly so important once you're done.


http://olliestyle.co.nr</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-30T21_30_30-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-30T21_30_30-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2006 04:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-07-01</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>business,call,center,comedy,filipino,how,learn,life,music,negosyo,new,ofw,personal,philippines,pilipino,pinay,pinoy,podcast,radio,revive,sex,tagalog,to,today,your</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="28061696" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-06-30T21_30_30-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>1753</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>[CLICK THE PLAY BUTTON BELOW TO LISTEN TO THIS PODCAST]

How to Revive Your Sex Life Today!   
By: Sarah Brindisi [read on the &quot;Ollie Style&quot; Show]


Has your sex life been a bit neglected lately? Its not like you don't care but well, it's just finding the time and energy. It seems impossible some days because there's work and cleaning and working out and grocery shopping and cooking dinner, laundry, kids, family commitments, friends, ironing! When you do get horizontal you pass out within minutes. Or you're not in the mood. Or you just can't be bothered. Soon enough a month has passed and you can't remember the last time you had sex. And when was the last time you kissed your partner and I mean really kissed them, not just a polite peck? 

Or maybe you've just fallen into a rut. You have sex in the same place at roughly the same time each week and do the same things. Routine is good for things like brushing your teeth but it shouldn't come into your sex life when variety and excitement are crucial elements in making it fulfilling.

If this sounds like you and you want to kickstart your sex life back into well, life, then read on. 

1. Be spontaneous 
The element of surprise can be very seductive. Take a shower together, surprise your partner with a long passionate kiss when they are expecting to just graze lips, buy some new lingerie and wear it. 

2. Get healthy
Eating well and regular exercise put you in better touch with your body and that inner healthy glow not only makes you look more attractive but gives you heaps of energy and makes you feel more vibrant and alive.

3. Be affectionate 
If you haven't had sex for awhile then it may be better to build up slowly to get back into the groove. Instead of trying to go from a standing start to racing speed, ease your way back into the physical by touching when you can and by being considerate with each other. Touch when you talk. Stop to kiss when you walk past each other in the hallway. Trail your finger along their shoulder as they sit reading a magazine. Snuggle on the couch in front of your favorite movie. 

4. Be sensual
Give your partner a peppermint foot bath when they get home from a busy day. Massage their hands, scalp, back - wherever takes your fancy (if you don't know how to massage, don't think about it, just do what feels good). Or try a lighter touch by using a feather or silk scarve to trail along the length of your partner.

5. Be encouraging when your partner does something you like 
Even if you've been together a long time your partner doesn't always know what you like and even if they do it doesn't hurt to tell them once in awhile. Say what you like and why you like it, if they have more information you never know what they may come up with to please you.

6. Read your partner an erotic bedtime story 
The mind is crucial in any attempt to resuscitate your sex life. It needs to be turned on first and the body will follow. There is some great erotic fiction around or you could try Nancy Friday for stories about other people's sexual fantasies.

7. Have fun 
When was the last time you laughed together? Put on your favourite track and dance. Or buy the music that was popular when you first got together and play that for a trip down memory lane over dinner. Take a midnight dip. 

8. Write a sexy letter 
If you can't tell your partner what you really want them to do to you, then writing it down is a great alternative. It lets you be as specific as you like without feeling like your face is going to turn tomato red and gives your partner time to process what you've said and get into the mood (if you need help putting your letter together try visiting www.loveyouletters.com for easy-to-us love templates).

9. Experiment
Learn a new technique together. Try a romantic weekend away. Or you could try a sex toy from one of the many on offer. If you always have sex lying down then try standing or sitting. If you're always on(continued)</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Secret Ways to Show Your Love to Your Partner </title>
      <description>PLS. CLICK THE PLAY BUTTON BELOW.

Five Secret Ways to Show Your Love to Your Partner    
By: Trent Brownrigg  (Read on the Ollie Style Show)

There are many ways to express love to your partner other than quoting the actual words &quot;I Love You.&quot; Usually the fire in relationships dies down after a while and the feeling of your heart pounding with the excitement of being with your significant other is not felt nearly as often, or even at all. 

So, how do we get back that love, passion and warm feeling that wraps around us and penetrate our thoughts in the beginning of a relationship? 

Many say actions speak louder than words so below I have listed 5 secrets of seduction to help you show your partner how much you truly love them: 

1. Flirt 

This is a light-hearted seduction with the intent of conveying love! Why not send a sexy text message or email while you are at work? This reminds the other person that you are thinking about him or her. It also increases the intensity of love so that you actually look forward to seeing each other when you return home from work. 

2. Candles 

According to Feng Shui, the seduction candle is red and the ingredients are musk, patchouli, pine, cedar and juniper. This secret of seduction can put back the romance in your relationships. Why not fill your room with scented candles and turn off the lights just to relax in each others arms? The extra effort goes a very long way! 

3. Food 

It is said that &quot;the way to a man's heart is through his stomach,&quot; however this is also thought to be the secret of successful seduction of women too. Show your love by setting up a surprise dinner for two. Add flowers, soft music and incense to create a seductive love nest. Aphrodisiac foods such as oysters, chili, chocolate, figs, honey and walnuts are said to aid in the stimulation of your loved ones hormones. 

4. Love Letters and Poems 

Why not leave a love note for your loved one? This can be posted in the bathroom or kitchen before you leave to work. You could also leave a nice love poem under the pillow so that your partner finds this at night before bedtime or first thing in the morning. Or send a hand written love letter to their work address. This will stir up the feeling of love in the privacy of your bedroom as well as in your relationship. Inspiration can be taken from music or love poem books. 

5. Get Away 

There can be a lot of distractions in your relationship such as work or children. There are many short vacations available for the weekend or just for a day. You may arrange a trip to the Health Spa or a Hotel so that you are in a different environment than usual where you can both relax and concentrate on each other.

Using the five techniques above to show your significant other just how much you truly love them will certainly spice up your love life, strengthen your relationship, and keep you and your partner happy for years to come! Article Source: http://www.articledashboard.com  About the author: 

Do you have someone you want to share your feelings with? Find Love Poems and Love Letters to express how you feel at www.sweet-love-poems.com


listen  to other podcasts of Ollie Style at http://ollie.podomatic.com
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-28T12_55_42-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-28T12_55_42-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2006 19:55:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-06-28</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>filipino,love,ollie,partner,pinas,pinay,pinoy,sex,style</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="20428800" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-06-28T12_55_42-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>1276</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>PLS. CLICK THE PLAY BUTTON BELOW.

Five Secret Ways to Show Your Love to Your Partner    
By: Trent Brownrigg  (Read on the Ollie Style Show)

There are many ways to express love to your partner other than quoting the actual words &quot;I Love You.&quot; Usually the fire in relationships dies down after a while and the feeling of your heart pounding with the excitement of being with your significant other is not felt nearly as often, or even at all. 

So, how do we get back that love, passion and warm feeling that wraps around us and penetrate our thoughts in the beginning of a relationship? 

Many say actions speak louder than words so below I have listed 5 secrets of seduction to help you show your partner how much you truly love them: 

1. Flirt 

This is a light-hearted seduction with the intent of conveying love! Why not send a sexy text message or email while you are at work? This reminds the other person that you are thinking about him or her. It also increases the intensity of love so that you actually look forward to seeing each other when you return home from work. 

2. Candles 

According to Feng Shui, the seduction candle is red and the ingredients are musk, patchouli, pine, cedar and juniper. This secret of seduction can put back the romance in your relationships. Why not fill your room with scented candles and turn off the lights just to relax in each others arms? The extra effort goes a very long way! 

3. Food 

It is said that &quot;the way to a man's heart is through his stomach,&quot; however this is also thought to be the secret of successful seduction of women too. Show your love by setting up a surprise dinner for two. Add flowers, soft music and incense to create a seductive love nest. Aphrodisiac foods such as oysters, chili, chocolate, figs, honey and walnuts are said to aid in the stimulation of your loved ones hormones. 

4. Love Letters and Poems 

Why not leave a love note for your loved one? This can be posted in the bathroom or kitchen before you leave to work. You could also leave a nice love poem under the pillow so that your partner finds this at night before bedtime or first thing in the morning. Or send a hand written love letter to their work address. This will stir up the feeling of love in the privacy of your bedroom as well as in your relationship. Inspiration can be taken from music or love poem books. 

5. Get Away 

There can be a lot of distractions in your relationship such as work or children. There are many short vacations available for the weekend or just for a day. You may arrange a trip to the Health Spa or a Hotel so that you are in a different environment than usual where you can both relax and concentrate on each other.

Using the five techniques above to show your significant other just how much you truly love them will certainly spice up your love life, strengthen your relationship, and keep you and your partner happy for years to come! Article Source: http://www.articledashboard.com  About the author: 

Do you have someone you want to share your feelings with? Find Love Poems and Love Letters to express how you feel at www.sweet-love-poems.com


listen  to other podcasts of Ollie Style at http://ollie.podomatic.com
</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tips For Attracting Women</title>
      <description>This is a good episode!!!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-27T15_56_12-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-27T15_56_12-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2006 22:56:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-06-27</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>boy,dating,girl,sex,tips,woman</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="21817344" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-06-27T15_56_12-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>1363</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>This is a good episode!!!</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discussion about breasts, X rated films, and vagina</title>
      <description>&#160;sex, vigina, breasts, x rated films, porn, chicharon bulaklak</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-26T22_30_22-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-26T22_30_22-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2006 05:30:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-06-27</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>breasts,bulaklak,chicharon,films,porn,rated,sex,vigina</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="3061888" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-06-26T22_30_22-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>382</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>&#160;sex, vigina, breasts, x rated films, porn, chicharon bulaklak</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st  podcast</title>
      <description>1st podcast with brian, richard, and joel in the QA lab.... 
hehehe</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-23T13_06_13-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-23T13_06_13-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2006 20:06:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2011-05-16</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-06-23</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1622144" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-06-23T13_06_13-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>405</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>1st podcast with brian, richard, and joel in the QA lab.... 
hehehe</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vasectomy </title>
      <description>discussion about vasectomy with jc, qa ric, mike, joel, brian, and ollie

PLEASE LISTEN TO OUR FIRST PODCAST TOO...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-23T17_41_37-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-23T17_41_37-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2006 00:41:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-06-24</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>sex,vasectomy</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1310848" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-06-23T17_41_37-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>327</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>discussion about vasectomy with jc, qa ric, mike, joel, brian, and ollie

PLEASE LISTEN TO OUR FIRST PODCAST TOO...</itunes:summary>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st  podcast</title>
      <description>1st podcast with brian, richard, and joel in the QA lab.... 
hehehe</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-23T13_06_13-07_00</guid>
      <comments>http://ollie.podomatic.com/entry/2006-06-23T13_06_13-07_00</comments>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2006 20:06:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <dcterms:modified>2008-06-18</dcterms:modified>
      <dcterms:created>2006-06-23</dcterms:created>
      <link>http://ollie.podomatic.com</link>
      <dc:creator>Ollie Style</dc:creator>
      <itunes:keywords>call,center,pinoy,sex,superman</itunes:keywords>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1622144" url="http://ollie.podomatic.com/enclosure/2006-06-23T13_06_13-07_00.mp3"/>
      <itunes:duration>405</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:summary>1st podcast with brian, richard, and joel in the QA lab.... 
hehehe</itunes:summary>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
