<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[EliteCastingNetwork.com Audition Notices]]></title>
	<description><![CDATA[EliteCastingNetwork.com Audition Notices]]></description>
	<link>http://auditions.elitecastingnetwork.com</link>
	<atom:link href="http://elitecastingnetwork.com/rss/notices.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<ttl>25</ttl>
	<image>
		<title><![CDATA[EliteCastingNetwork.com Audition Notices]]></title>
		<url>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/ssc.png</url>
		<link>http://auditions.elitecastingnetwork.com</link>
	</image>

	<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Female Models]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Female_Models__324</link>
	<description><![CDATA[This is an opening for attractive models who are looking for excellent and long term work. I am currently shooting for the launch of a private upscale adult website that showcases beautiful women of all ethnicity.

Details:

1) Must be between the ages of 18-28 

2) Must be open to taking tastefully done lingerie/nude/semi-nude photos/video.

3) The shoot will be a combination of photos and video.

4) The pay is a flat fee of $500-$1000 and will last approximately 1-2 hours.

5) If done well, it can turn into a long term opportunity.

6) Must be in physically fit condition.

7) Race does not matter.

8) Must submit at least two full body photos via email, the sexier the better as the photos you submit will be the deciding factor for selection.

Positions are limited, I'm only looking for 5 models at this time. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Female_Models__324</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Catalogue MAGAZINE launching]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Catalogue_MAGAZINE_launching</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Catalogue MAGAZINE launching Male and female needed for a catalog magazine,photo shoot with a designer who wants to update her online catalog. After you have had your professional shoot, you are then given the opportunity to have a full spread in new mag .You will then receive an online editorial with a story about you (the model) in the Magazine, as well as your images from the shoot. This is a great opportunity for aspiring models, actors/actresses who would like to get some more exposure. Producers, agencies, casting directors are all apart of this magazine and may take you on for their next big project. Interested applicant should kindly send 1 head shot and 1 full body shoot, no topless/nude pictures . Must be 18 years and above. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Catalogue_MAGAZINE_launching</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Web Cam Models Wanted]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Web_Cam_Models_Wanted_4</link>
	<description><![CDATA[WEBCAM MODELS HIRING TODAY!! GIRLS, GUYS, OR COUPLES -- WORK FROM HOME!!!
Recruiting webcam models for the largest and best network of adult websites, with over 5 million visitors per day
Attractive females, males, or couples wanted, you must be 18 and over, friendly,couteous, open minded and enjoys being in front of the camera
Webcam models can work as little or asmuch as they like. Must have a private place to work, a webcam, computer, and high-speed internet
Payments are weekly for the previous week worked, and we offer payments by check, direct deposit, Payoneer, Alert Pay, or Paxum
Please send your most recent photo (Non-Nude), as well as your availability]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Web_Cam_Models_Wanted_4</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[My Strange Addiction]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/My_Strange_Addiction_18</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Do you have a friend or family member suffering from a strange addiction? It's hard to watch someone you love battle an addiction, especially when that baddiction seems strange, unusual and completely unstoppable. The major docu series profiles those suffering from addictions that may seem unusual, but nonetheless, very harmful and challenging. We allow friends and family members to discuss the addiction in a safe and controlled environment and then offer help to those suffering from an addiction. 

If you have someone in your life that is ingesting or smelling something dangerous or engaging in odd behavior that is damaging their quality of life, please contact us so we can help.]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/My_Strange_Addiction_18</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Documentary]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Documentary_945</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Filmmaker searching for an attractive female nymphomaniac. Needed for a documentary film project. Must have minimal (willing to try) acting skills. Must be able to travel to the city upon request. This is a paying job. Send photos, information that makes you relevant to this casting and contact information or call us]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Documentary_945</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[CASTING: SINGLE DADS]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/CASTING_SINGLE_DADS_1</link>
	<description><![CDATA[CASTING SINGLE DADS NATIONWIDE: New Reality Series looking for single fathers between the ages 25-45 with a great story. Email your story, contact info and photo]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/CASTING_SINGLE_DADS_1</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[TV TALK]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_TALK_7</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
TV TALK: CHEATED ON?? WANT TO CATCH HIM/HER IN THE ACT?

***ALL NON-NYC GUESTS GET FREE: PLANE TICKET TO/FROM NEW YORK CITY, CENTRALLY-LOCATED HOTEL, CAR SERVICE, MEAL MONEY, HAIR & MAKE-UP!***

HIT NATIONAL TV TALK SHOW THAT SPECIALIZES IN CONFLICT RESOLUTION IS LOOKING FOR GUESTS THAT BELIEVE THEIR SIGNIFICANT OTHERS ARE CHEATING AND WANT TO CATCH HIM/HER IN THE ACT WITH THE HELP OF A PRIVATE EYE OR HIGH-TECH SPY GADGETS! ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_TALK_7</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[On Air Talent]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/On_Air_Talent_5</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
AXSLive - "Fiercely Independent"

The world's music and pop culture voice beginning July 2012...

Breaking new ground.

We are looking for on air "Leads" in Atlanta. We want you to take us into the story LIVE, into the music LIVE, into the event LIVE every time, EVERY day.
We are taking LIVE TV in a different direction.

If you are an actor or comedian with strong improv skills bring it on!

Radio personalities - you handle live all day long, we are open to you!

Bloggers, Vloggers, if you are passionate and have the ability to handle yourself on camera and bring the story to the screen LIVE - talk to us!

If you are professional and passionate about what you do let us know, show us what you want the world to see - musicians, artists, fashion designers, chefs, performers, trendsetters, entertainers - everyone with a strong voice may have a place at AXSLive.

Help us create something new. We're looking for contributors at all levels, in all disciplines to be part of a team that creates a new way of bringing music, arts, entertainment and popular culture to all platforms.

Become part of the AXSLive adventure.

EOE. Good benefits. All submissions must be electronic and include the following: small head shot, short bio, links to reels, full resume and credits and professional references. Please note the CITY you are applying for in the subject line. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/On_Air_Talent_5</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[TV show]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_show_1490</link>
	<description><![CDATA[CHANCE OF A LIFETIME FOR ONE LUCKY FAMILY!

THE CASTING FIRM and a MAJOR CABLE NETWORK
is going to take one lucky family on an adventure and give them a LIFE CHANGING PRIZE as only Hollywood can dream up!! 

This is one of those shows where the producers give away SOMETHING HUGE and watch the family spend it or experience it! 

YOU COULD BE THAT FAMILY THIS TIME!! Here is what we are looking for...

A family that...
HAS NEVER traveled outside the USA (mexico and canada ok!)
Enjoys typical American pastimes.... like hunting, fishing, baseball games, camping, church, little league, BBQ's etc. 
Is OUTGOING 
Has at least 2 boys AGES 18-25 (they can be nephews or cousins)

PLEASE REFER FAMILIES YOU KNOW!! 

Please submit the following info and I will give you a call with more details! 

NAME
AGES OF FAMILY MEMBERS
PHONE
PHOTO
CITY YOU LIVE
please answer the following questions...
BRIEFLY tell me a little about your family.
Have you ever traveled outside the USA. If so, to where and why?
Do you believe America is the best country?
Do you have extended family (aunts uncles nieces nephews) that would participate on the show if selected? If so how old are they?
How many boys ages 18-25 are in your family?]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_show_1490</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[TV SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_SHOW_1489</link>
	<description><![CDATA[($50) TV SHOW: LOOKING FOR TEENS AND ADULTS WHO WANT TO CONFRONT THEIR BULLIES!

NATIONAL TALKSHOW IS LOOKING FOR TEENS AND ADULTS WHO HAVE BEEN BULLIED FOR ANY REASON TO APPEAR ON OUR PROGRAM.

IF YOU HAVE BEEN HARRASSED BECAUSE OF YOUR WEIGHT, PERSONALITY OR SEXUAL ORIENTATION AND WANT TO CONFRONT YOUR BULLY WE WANT TO TALK TO YOU.

THIS IS FOR A TAPING IN NEW YORK CITY ON FRIDAY, JUNE 15. NON-NEW YORK CITY GUESTS TRAVEL ON THURSDAY, JUNE 14.

WE'RE LOOKING FOR ENERGETIC, OUTGOING, AND DYNAMIC PEOPLE!]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_SHOW_1489</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[PROMO JOBS]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/PROMO_JOBS</link>
	<description><![CDATA[PREMIER MODELING AGENCY IS CURRENTLY HIRING MALE AND FEMALE MODELS BETWEEN THE AGES OF 21 TO 35 TO HELP PROMOTE THE COMPANY BY HELPING US PASS OUT FLYERS FOR THE COMPANY TO POTENTIAL MODELS AT COLLEGES, EVENTS, MALLS, AND VARIOUS NIGHTCLUBS IN THE ATLANTA AREA.
THE PAY STARTS AT $15.00 AN HOUR AND INCREASES AS YOU CONTINUE TO WORK OR THE COMPANY. YOU WILL GET PAID CASH THE SAME DAY YOU WORK.

*NO EXPERIENCE NEEDED.

*TO APPLY SEND YOUR PICTURE, AGE, AND CONTACT INFO ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/PROMO_JOBS</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Casting for Feature Film]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Casting_for_Feature_Film__2</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ATTENTION ALL PLUS SIZED TALENT and OTHERS. AUDITIONS ARE BEING HELD FOR THIS FILM. PLEASE CONTACT BY EMAIL HEADSHOT AND RESUME. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Casting_for_Feature_Film__2</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[CASTING]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/CASTING_9961</link>
	<description><![CDATA[CASTING: GSN's "AMERICAN BIBLE CHALLENGE"

Calling all Bible enthusiasts: GSN (Game Show Network) and the creators of "Extreme Makeover: Home Edition" are looking for you! 

We are casting for GSN's "The American Bible Challenge," a new game show hosted by Jeff Foxworthy. We're looking for lively individuals in teams who want to win money for their favorite charity. 

IF YOU HAVE A PASSION FOR THE BIBLE AND LOVE COMPETITION, THIS IS THE PERFECT GAME SHOW FOR YOU!

We're looking for teams of three who have competitive spirits, great personal testimonies, a general knowledge of pop culture -- and, of course, you have to know your Bible!

Come celebrate your faith, have fun with your friends and show off your Bible knowledge!!!

Email us and include the following: 
Name, 
Age, 
Contact info,
City,
Jobs
2 current photos. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/CASTING_9961</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[HIT TV TALK SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/HIT_TV_TALK_SHOW_10</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
HIT TV TALK SHOW: LOOKING FOR FIANCES IN A FEUD OR WANT TO CONFESS!

***ALL NON-NYC GUESTS GET FREE: PLANE TICKET TO/FROM NEW YORK CITY, CENTRALLY-LOCATED HOTEL, CAR SERVICE, MEAL MONEY, HAIR & MAKE-UP!***

HIT NATIONAL TV TALK SHOW THAT SPECIALIZES IN CONFLICT RESOLUTION IS LOOKING FOR GUESTS THAT ARE ENGAGED, BUT ARE FIGHTING SO MUCH THEIR MARRIAGE IS IN JEOPARDY!

IF YOUR BIG DAY MAY BE A BIG BUST ALL BECAUSE OF A BIG DISPUTE WITH YOUR FIANCE, LET US HELP YOU RESOLVE YOUR PROBLEMS!

Also looking for:

GUESTS WHO WANT TO CONFESS SOMETHING TO THEIR FIANCES BEFORE THEY GET HITCHED!

HAVE A SECRET EATING AT YOU AND NEED TO GET IT OFF YOUR CHEST BEFORE YOU WALK DOWN THE AISLE? COME TO US AND LET US HELP YOU WORK IT OUT!]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/HIT_TV_TALK_SHOW_10</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[TV SHOW GUEST]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_SHOW_GUEST_1</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ARE YOU SICK OF YOUR BOYFRIEND (OR GIRLFRIEND) TALKING TO HIS EX??!!!
WANT RELATIONSHIP HELP FROM AN EXPERIENCED EXPERT ON A NATIONALLY-SYNDICATED TV SHOW WITH YOUR PARTNER?]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_SHOW_GUEST_1</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[We Need Real People]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/We_Need_Real_People_3</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Topic #1 -- "How Far Would You Go To Get a 2nd Chance?!"
Would you suck on a stranger's toe, run outside naked, or get a tattoo of their name on your face just to get them back?? If you would do ANYTHING to get them back you could be a guest! If you or someone you know are so desperate to have a second chance with the person you lost, we want to help rekindle the lost love. Our producers are looking for crazy in love guests to help. 
Write to us with the subject line: "2nd Chance" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem. 
*** If you know someone who could fit this story, give us their name and phone number and if they make it to air we will write you a check! ****


Topic #2 -- "Reality Check: What He Really Thinks About You!"
Are you a woman that needs to get to the bottom of what he really thinks? Whether you are in a relationship or desperately trying to be in one with him, we want to help show you want he REALLY THINKS! Our producers are ready to get to the bottom of it with help from our experts. 
Write to us with the subject line: "Reality Check" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem. 
*** If you know someone who could fit this story, give us their name and phone number and if they make it to air we will write you a check! ****



Topic #3 -- "Bedroom Wars"
Has the sex become lame and boring? Are you or your mate constantly complaining about the dry lovemaking? Do you want to spice it up in an extreme way? Our producers want to help address these bedroom nightmares you could be having with help from our experts. 
Write to us with the subject line: "Bedroom Wars" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.
*** If you know someone who could fit this story, give us their name and phone number and if they make it to air we will write you a check! ****


Topic #4 -- "They Hate My Odd Mate"
Do your friends or family think you can do WAY better than who you are with?? Maybe they complain about their weight, clothing style or attitude? Our producers want to help change their minds with a 1-minute makeover that will get them off your back.
Write to us with the subject line: "Odd Mate" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.
*** If you know someone who could fit this story, give us their name and phone number and if they make it to air we will write you a check! ****


Topic #5 -- "I Would Do Anything To Be Liked By Them"
How far would you go to be liked by a person or a group? Do you or someone you know have problems with "mean" girls or guys? Have you been asked to do an extremely gross or embarrassing thing? Are you fed-up with the way your friends are treating people? Write to us with the subject like: "Anything To Fit In"
Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.
*** If you know someone who could fit this story, give us their name and phone number and if they make it to air we will write you a check! ****
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/We_Need_Real_People_3</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[TV CASTING]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_CASTING__11</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Have you been dreaming about your big day since you can remember, and you're ready to put those plans in place?
Are you planning your dream wedding, while still searching for your dream guy? 

Maybe you're extremely ambitious, and believe you can do anything when you set a deadline and put your mind to it. Maybe you're of a more spiritual mindset and believe that by putting your positive energy into action, the universe will yield your desired results. 

Whatever your story, we want to follow you on your journey! 

CASTING NEW DOCU-SERIES FOR MAJOR CABLE NETWORK
We are looking for dynamic, attractive single women who are determined to find Mr. Right and make their wedding dreams come true -- and they are taking steps to make it happen!]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_CASTING__11</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Adult Film Female Casting]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Adult_Film_Female_Casting</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Empire Films South is always interested in contracting with new talent who meet our strict criteria. You must be over the age of 18, caucasian, extremely good looking, intelligent and graceful; previous experience is not required. Empire Films South employs the services of top professionals, models, actresses, adult film stars and sensual massage professionals.

You must love to travel and have no restriction on your ability to travel. Inner beauty is of the utmost importance. In addition it is important that you are comfortable in all social situations and you can carry your self with confidence and class at all times.

If you feel you meet this criteria and are an aspiring female 18 to 27 years old and have a good camera presence or have ever thought of starting a career in the adult industry, then we would like to speak to you. Empire Films South is 100% professional, discreet, serious and confidential. This is a perfect opportunity for those that want to do something fun and exciting in addition to their regular job, for the college student or for anyone that wants to try something different.

Bio Requirements&#8232;
You are asked to provide a short bio as part of your application. Please provide details about your experience, goals, reasons for applying, or any other relevant information. Please err on the side of providing more info rather than less. Also, don't make it sound like a personal ad.

Provide 4 Different Photos (or more!)&#8232;
At least four photos are required for applications. No duplicates, re-crops, or manipulations of the same image. 

Quality Images Required&#8232;
We want quality images here. Your photos must be judged to be of sufficient quality. 

No Fakes&#8232;
We take copyright laws very seriously here. If your photos or profile appear to be the work of someone else, you will be denied. This includes fake tear sheets, advertisements, and magazine covers using existing trademarks.

Model Requirements

Show Us Your Face
&#8232;Your portfolio must show your face clearly. 

Show Us All of You
&#8232;Please include at least 1 full length body shot. Nudes not required. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Adult_Film_Female_Casting</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Daytime TV Show]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Daytime_TV_Show_4</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Daytime TV Show looking for experienced court stringers looking to visit court houses a few times a week looking for small claims. Rate negotiable - gas and mileage will be compensated. 
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Daytime_TV_Show_4</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[MODELS NEEDED]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/MODELS_NEEDED_4792</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Red Town Boutique is looking to expand its business presence five models are needed for this assignment.
Per Diem and travel arrangements will be provide if necessary.
Please provide a recent photo and body measurements.
Compensation is based upon experience.]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/MODELS_NEEDED_4792</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Baby Mama Drama?]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Baby_Mama_Drama_2</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
TV SHOW NOW CASTING- ***BE A GUEST ON A NATIONAL TELEVISION SHOW**** Are you a baby maker and proud of it?

Are women begging to have your baby?

Need help on how to respond to women who want to be the mother of your child?

Have you fathered three or more children with different baby mamas?

Are you God's gift to women?

Do you have multiple babies and still think you are the marrying kind?

We want to know!]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Baby_Mama_Drama_2</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[We Need Real People]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/We_Need_Real_People_</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Topic #1 -- "How Far Would You Go To Get a 2nd Chance?!"
Would you suck on a stranger's toe, run outside naked, or get a tattoo of their name on your face just to get them back?? If you would do ANYTHING to get them back you could be a guest! If you or someone you know are so desperate to have a second chance with the person you lost, we want to help rekindle the lost love. Our producers are looking for crazy in love guests to help. 
Write to us with the subject line: "2nd Chance" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.


Topic #2 -- "Reality Check: What He Really Thinks About You!"
Are you a woman that needs to get to the bottom of what he really thinks? Whether you are in a relationship or desperately trying to be in one with him, we want to help show you want he REALLY THINKS! Our producers are ready to get to the bottom of it with help from our experts. 
Write to us with the subject line: "Reality Check" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.


Topic #3 -- "Bedroom Wars"
Has the sex become lame and boring? Are you or your mate constantly complaining about the dry lovemaking? Do you want to spice it up in an extreme way? Our producers want to help address these bedroom nightmares you could be having with help from our experts. 
Write to us with the subject line: "Bedroom Wars" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.

Topic #4 -- "They Hate My Odd Mate"
Do your friends or family think you can do WAY better than who you are with?? Maybe they complain about their weight, clothing style or attitude? Our producers want to help change their minds with a 1-minute makeover that will get them off your back.
Write to us with the subject line: "Odd Mate" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.

Topic #5 -- "I Would Do Anything To Fit It"
How far would you go to be liked? Do you or someone you know have problems fitting into a certain social group or organization? Maybe in order to join or fit in they make you do extremely gross or embarrassing things in order for you to prove yourself. Our producers want to hear your story and meet the people that make you try so hard to fit in. 
Write to us with the subject line: "Anything To Fit In" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.

ALL GUESTS ARE GIVEN AN ALL EXPENSE PAID TRIP TO NYC, includes:
-Round trip travel to New York City
-Accommodations at one of our Manhattan hotels
-Hair/Make-up
-Plenty of food]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/We_Need_Real_People_</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Actor Actresses]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Actor_Actresses_1</link>
	<description><![CDATA[TV Commercial Producer need Hispanic, African, Indian, Middle Eastern, Asian and White actors and actresses for international flavored TV Commercial..Send Photo Must have your own clothing representing your ethnicity]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Actor_Actresses_1</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Series]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Series_66</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Are you a gay or lesbian individual who needs help revealing your sexual identity to your loved ones?

Do you live everyday feeling trapped in your skin?

Do you fear how society and/or your loved ones might react if they knew your true sexual identity?

If so, come be a part of our docu-series, where together with a licensed therapist you can sit down with your loved ones and reveal your sexual identity. 

By being a part of this docu-series you can help to free many other LGBT individuals who struggle everyday keeping their true sexual identity hidden from their loved ones.

BE COURAGEOUS!

!!!Take part in a MOVEMENT in your LGBT community!!!

"It is ok to feel fear, as long as you don't let fear stop you"]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Series_66</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[MTV CASTING]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/MTV_CASTING_1968</link>
	<description><![CDATA[MTV - NOW CASTING - "I HAVE A SECRET ONLINE PROFILE"

Are you currently using a fake profile on sites or phone apps like Facebook, Twitter, OkCupid, TextPlus, Blendr, Grindr, Tumblr, Plenty of Fish, etc?? Has someone fallen for your online alter-ego?

Do you spend hours talking or texting with someone you met online? Are you afraid to meet them because you haven't 
been completely honest?

Are you in a long distance relationship with someone you've never actually met in person? Have you been holding 
something back from them... are you keeping a secret?

Do you make excuses for not meeting in person because you've been avoiding telling them something? Are
you afraid they won't accept you for who you really are?

Do you have a talent for creating believable fake profiles but have gotten in too deep?

Are you currently using a fake profile to get to know someone you have a crush on... or to keep track of an ex or someone your ex left you for?

Do you need help figuring out the best way to finally tell them the truth? Are you looking for a safe way to explain
yourself and reveal the real you?

Everyone has a story to share... If ANY of these scenarios sound like you or someone you know, then MTV wants to hear your story! We're here to offer support and guidance along the way.]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/MTV_CASTING_1968</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Hair Salon seeks models]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Hair_Salon_seeks_models_1</link>
	<description><![CDATA[National Hair Salon seeks models $1100



Guys, Late Teens to early 30's talent. Normal, real, everyday should not be commercial looking. Variety of hair types and lengths.

Females / All Ethnicities /17 -- 35 Variety of hair types and lengths.

Note if selected you will be required to have hair styled for shoot, may include trimming, color.

Rate $1100

Location: NYC, out of town talent encouraged to apply if selected travel and expenses will be paid.

We are looking for new faces that are serious about getting their career started.



Please send a couple recent photos along with name, phone number
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Hair_Salon_seeks_models_1</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[TRAVEL CHANNEL SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/_TRAVEL_CHANNEL_SHOW_1</link>
	<description><![CDATA[You saved up all year for this vacation, but secretly you're hoping for a trip that will take you beyond the same old, same old........ Game for something better?!? 'TRIP FLIP' -- the new Travel Channel series, will put the zing back into your vacation & flip your trip head over heels! You will experience NASHVILLE the way it SHOULD be seen, not on a tour bus, but off-the-beaten track. . ..visiting the coolest spots in town (including the CMA Festival), finding the city's hidden gems that only the locals know about. This is truly a once-in-a-lifetime experience you do not want to miss!

Contact Tina  for more info & and come along for the ride of a lifetime! ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/_TRAVEL_CHANNEL_SHOW_1</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[DOCU-SERIES]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/DOCUSERIES_56</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you pregnant and hiding it? If you are due before SEPTEMBER 1, you could share your story on national television and help other women in the same situation. Email us your name, age, due date, location, photo and a summary of why you are secretly pregnant. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/DOCUSERIES_56</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/SHOW_8590</link>
	<description><![CDATA[NATIONAL TALK SHOW LOOKING FOR GUESTS!!!

FREE ROUND-TRIP AIRFARE, FREE HOTEL, MONEY FOR FOOD, HAIR, MAKE-UP AND WARDROBE INCLUDED!!!!

WANT A LIE DETECTOR TEST FOR FREE??? LET US HELP YOU!!!! CONTACT:


Is the woman in your life abusive? Want to confront and demand she get help? Contact us today!

Want to be reunited with a loved one who abandoned you? Want to know why they left and where they have been hiding? If so, contact Bill today!

Are you in love with someone outside your race? Does your family hate your mate because of race? 

Is your own mother a deadbeat mom? Do you want to confront her and let her know she needs to step up, own what she did and make it right? If so, contact the Bill Cunningham show today!

Are you a teen mom raising your child alone because your son or daughter's father is a deadbeat? Want Bill's help getting your child's deadbeat dad to step up, pay child support, and be a father? If so, contact Bill today!!

Are you a wife who has the WORST husband in America? Want Bill's help? Contact us today!!]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/SHOW_8590</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Female Talent]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Female_Talent_36</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Seven Senses Productions is seeking female talent for the growing adult video industry in Atlanta. If you are 18+years old and have a good camera presence, then we would like to speak to you. 
This is a perfect opportunity for those that want to do something fun and exciting in addition to their regular job, for the college student or for anyone that wants to try something different.
No experience is necessary; If you are interested, please send along a few pictures.
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Female_Talent_36</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[TV SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_SHOW_1488</link>
	<description><![CDATA[TV TALK SHOW: SPITEFUL BREAK-UPS/HAS YOUR EX POSTED NUDE PHOTOS OF YOU OR TRIED TO EMBARRASS YOU ONLINE?

- NATIONALLY SYNDICATED TV TALK SHOW IS LOOKING FOR DYNAMIC, OUTGOING, AND ENERGETIC PEOPLE WHO WANT TO CONFRONT THE PERSON THAT POSTED NUDE PHOTOS OF THEM ONLINE! 

- DO YOU HAVE AN EX OR FRIEND THAT BETRAYED YOUR TRUST BY POSTING PRIVATE PHOTOS THAT YOU SENT HIM/HER ONLINE AFTER YOU BROKE UP?

- DO YOU WANT TO CONFRONT AN EX WHO EMBARRASSED YOU IN PUBLIC OUT OF SPITE, BY LYING, POSTING, OR SPREADING RUMORS AFTER A BREAK UP?

- DID YOU TRY TO GET REVENGE ON AN EX BY PUBLISHING NUDE OR PRIVATE PICTURES OF THEM ONLINE AND NOW YOU WANT TO APOLOGIZE?
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_SHOW_1488</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[CASTING]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/CASTING_9960</link>
	<description><![CDATA[NY BASED HIT NATIONAL TV TALK SHOW IS LOOKING FOR SEVERELY OBESE WOMAN WHO ARE HAVING CONFLICT WITH THEIR BEAUTIFUL MOMS! 

( REFERRAL FEE OF $50 FOR ANYBODY YOU RECOMMEND WHO ENDS UP ON THE SHOW)

TV SHOW IS CASTING PEOPLE NOW!

DO YOU OR SOMEONE YOU KNOW....

-STRUGGLE WITH OBESITY AND ARE CONSTANTLY BEING PUT DOWN BY THEIR BEAUTIFUL MOM OR SISTERS?
-A YOUNG WOMEN BETWEEN THE AGES OF 18 AND 28 WHO ARE 400LBS PLUS AND ARE AT ODDS WITH SOMEONE ABOUT THEIR WEIGHT
-ARE YOU A BEAUTIFUL MOM WHO IS AT ODDS WITH HER OUTRAGEOUSLY OBESE DAUGHTER BECAUSE SHE CAN'T LOSE WEIGHT?
-DO YOU HAVE A MOTHER DAUGHTER RELATIONSHIP ISSUE BECAUSE OF WEIGHT?
- DO YOU WANT TO STOP FIGHTING WITH YOUR MOM OR DAUGHTER OVER YOUR WEIGHT?

***WE WILL GIVE YOU THE HELP YOU NEED TO START SHEDDING THE POUNDS AND THE TOOLS TO GET ALONG WITH YOUR MOM OR YOUR DAUGHTER. WE ARE LOOKING FOR PEOPLE WITH BIG PERSONALITIES WHO ARE NOT AFRAID TO VOICE THEIR OPINION!

$$$ LOST WAGES PAID- FREE TRIP TO NYC--FREE FLIGHTS HOTEL AND MEAL MONEY, PLUS COUPLES COUNSELING INCLUDED ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/CASTING_9960</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[TV]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_139</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
***IF YOU REFER ANY GUESTS WE CHOOSE, YOU WILL GET A $50 REFERRAL FEE!***

HIT NATIONAL TV TALK SHOW THAT SPECIALIZES IN CONFLICT RESOLUTION IS LOOKING FOR GUESTS THAT HAVE BEEN CHEATED ON WHILE THEY WERE AWAY FROM HOME. . .

OR. . .

PEOPLE WHO HAVE BUSTED CHEATERS ON VIDEO TAPE!

OR. . .

PEOPLE WHO BELIEVE THEIR SIGNIFICANT OTHERS ARE CHEATING AND WANT A PRIVATE EYE TO CATCH HIM/HER IN THE ACT!

IF YOU WERE IN THE MILITARY, ON THE ROAD TRUCKING, WORKING ON AN OIL RIG, ON A LONG-HAUL FISHING BOAT, OR AWAY FROM HOME FOR AN EXTENDED PERIOD OF TIME FOR ANY REASON. . .AND YOUR SIGNIFICANT OTHER CHEATED ON YOU WHILE YOU WERE AWAY. . .WE WANT TO HEAR FROM YOU!

OR. . .

IF YOU CAUGHT YOUR SIGNIFICANT OTHER ON VIDEOTAPE CHEATING ON YOU, OR YOU WERE BUSTED ON VIDEOTAPE CHEATING ON YOUR SIGNIFICANT OTHER, WE ALSO WANT TO HEAR FROM YOU!

OR. . .

YOU BELIEVE YOUR SIGNIFICANT OTHER IS CHEATING ON YOU AND YOU'D LIKE A P.I. TO CATCH HIM/HER IN THE ACT. . .]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_139</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[NEW TV SHOW!]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/_NEW_TV_SHOW_11</link>
	<description><![CDATA[CHANCE OF A LIFETIME FOR ONE LUCKY FAMILY!

THE CASTING FIRM and a MAJOR CABLE NETWORK
is going to take one lucky family on an adventure and give them a LIFE CHANGING PRIZE as only Hollywood can dream up!! 

This is one of those shows where the producers give away SOMETHING HUGE and watch the family spend it or experience it! 

YOU COULD BE THAT FAMILY THIS TIME!! Here is what we are looking for...

A family that...
Does NOT travel outside of the USA very often 
Enjoys typical American pastimes.... like hunting, fishing, baseball games, camping, church, little league, BBQ's etc. 
Is OUTGOING 
Has at least one boy AGES 18-25 (they can be nephews or cousins)

PLEASE REFER FAMILIES YOU KNOW!! 

Please submit the following info and I will give you a call with more details! 

NAME 
AGES OF FAMILY MEMBERS
PHONE
 PHOTO
 CITY YOU LIVE
please answer the following questions...
BRIEFLY tell me a little about your family.
Have you ever traveled outside the USA. If so, to where and why?
Do you believe America is the best country?
Do you have extended family (aunts uncles nieces nephews) that would participate on the show if selected? If so how old are they?
How many boys ages 18-25 are in your family?
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/_NEW_TV_SHOW_11</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/SHOW__28</link>
	<description><![CDATA[CASTING: GSN's "AMERICAN BIBLE CHALLENGE"

Calling all Bible enthusiasts: GSN (Game Show Network) and the creators of "Extreme Makeover: Home Edition" are looking for you! 

We are casting for GSN's "The American Bible Challenge," a new game show hosted by Jeff Foxworthy. We're looking for lively individuals and teams who want to win money for their favorite charity. 

IF YOU HAVE A PASSION FOR THE BIBLE AND LOVE COMPETITION, THIS IS THE PERFECT GAME SHOW FOR YOU!

We're looking for teams of three who have competitive spirits, great personal testimonies, a general knowledge of pop culture -- and, of course, you have to know your Bible!

Come celebrate your faith, have fun with your friends and show off your Bible knowledge!!!

Email us and you must include the following: Name, age, contact info, and 2 current photos. Tell us about why you love learning the Bible! Please provide teammates name, ages, contact info, and their relationship to you. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/SHOW__28</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[NEW FAMILY DINNER TV SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/NEW_FAMILY_DINNER_TV_SHOW</link>
	<description><![CDATA[LOOKING FOR RECENTLY BLENDED FAMILIES (within the last year) WHO WANT AND NEED HELP GETTING THEIR FAMILIES TOGETHER!

Are you struggling to make your TWO FAMILIES ONE?
Is there CONSTANT FIGHTING between the two sets of KIDS? 
Do you feel DISCONNECTED from each other?
Need some HARMONY???

Believe it or not, having consistent FAMILY DINNER CAN HELP!

Powderhouse Productions, in association with the non-profit The Family Dinner Project, is looking for RECENTLY BLENDED FAMILIES from all walks of life who NEED the help and support of experts in putting their families back together!

Families that are chosen for this MAJOR CABLE NETWORK TV SHOW will be COMPENSATED and SUPPLIED with everything they need to jumpstart their family dinner experience: recipes, activities, expert advice, groceries and more.

Having dinner together as a family CAN CHANGE EVERYTHING!

If you and your family are interested in being considered for this project PLEASE CONTACT US FOR DETAILS ASAP! ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/NEW_FAMILY_DINNER_TV_SHOW</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Hit TV Show]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Hit_TV_Show_45</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Topic #1 -- "Parents Who Cross The Line"
Are you and your spouse at odds over how to raise your kids? Do you get criticized for the way you discipline your kids? Do you know someone who allows their children to have party, drink, or have sex at home? Are you upset with the way someone in your family is raising their kids? If so, we want to hear your story. . .
Write to us with the subject line: "Extreme Parents" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.


Topic #2 -- "I Would Do Anything To Fit It"
How far have you gone to fit in with a group? Do you or someone you know have problems fitting into a certain social groups, clubs, gangs? Do you know someone who will do anything to fit in and you want to confront them? Have you had to perform extreme acts or tasks to be a part of a group? Do you want to confront someone who made you perform a extreme task, and still didn't accept you? If you want to share your story. . . 
Write to us with the subject line: "Anything To Fit In" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.


Topic #3 -- "Reality Check: What He Really Thinks About You!"
Have you ever said, " I have no idea what my man thinks"? Do you really want to know what's on your man's mind? Does your man talk in circles? Do you feel like your woman never let's you get a word in, or doesn't understand you? We are looking for couples who want to break down the wall of communication! If you are ready to really get your point across. . .. 
Write to us with the subject line: "Reality Check" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.


Topic #4 -- "How Far Would You Go To Get a 2nd Chance?!"
Do you want a second chance at love? Are you willing to jump out a plane, get a tattoo or eat something gross to prove your love? If you would do ANYTHING to get them back you could be a guest! If you or someone you know are so desperate to have a second chance with the person you lost, we want to help rekindle the lost love. Our producers are looking for crazy in love guests to help. 
Write to us with the subject line: "2nd Chance" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.



Topic #5 -- "Contest: Special Talents!"
Do you have a special talent? Can jump rope with spaghetti? Or sing Opera in drag? Or maybe even blow fire from your nose? Do you want to confront anyone that thinks you're crazy or that doesn't even call it a talent? We want to showcase your most special talents on our show and prove to them that it is talent! Our producers are looking for guest with special talents!. Write to us with the subject line: "Special Talents" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.


Topic #6 -- "Look-a-Likes! Who Do You Think You Are?!"
Do you or someone you know look so much like a celebrity that it is causing problems in your life? Are you a look-a-like and your partner is feud up with you pretending to be someone else? If you know anyone that is either obsessed with being a look-a-like or hates being a look-a-like, we want to hear your story! 
Write to us with the subject line: "Look-a-Like" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.


Topic #7 -- "Twins, Triplets & Quads At War!"
Do you having double, triple or quadruple trouble with your identical twin siblings?? Maybe you are tired of being blamed and confused for the things they have done. If you are at odds with your identical siblings, we want to hear your story. 
Write to us with the subject line: "Identical Sibling Rivalry" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.

Topic #8 -- "Groupies & Baller Followers"
Are you or someone you know a proud and infamous baller groupie?? Do they follow ball players all around the country trying to catch their interest and if lucky, get pregnant!? Are you upset because your friend is chasing men for the wrong reason? If you're ready to confront a friend or loved one about the groupie ways, we want to hear your story. Write to us with the subject line: "Groupies" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.

Topic #9 -- "Bedroom Wars"
Are you bored with your sex life? Are you or your mate constantly complaining about too much sex, not enough sex, or lame sex? Do you want to spice it up in the bedroom, but want some help? If you're a couple that his ready to talk about sex, we want to hear your story. 
Write to us with the subject line: "Bedroom Wars" to be considered. Include phone numbers for direct contact and a brief line about your problem.]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Hit_TV_Show_45</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[REALITY SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/_REALITY_SHOW_49</link>
	<description><![CDATA[We are casting Single Dads for a new reality series. Fathers between the ages 25-45 please send your great Single Dad story and PICTURE! 

Thank you!! ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/_REALITY_SHOW_49</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[REALITY SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/_REALITY_SHOW_48</link>
	<description><![CDATA[TV REALITY SHOW COMING TO HOT-ATLANTA! 
TV SHOW LOOKING FOR SINGLE 
WOMEN AGES 25-35 ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/_REALITY_SHOW_48</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Campaign]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Campaign_8</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Express Web Campaign $400
Express trendsetters with the latest in women and men's clothing seek male/female for upcoming 
fall/winter web campaign. Clothing laid-back enough for lounging at home but great for a night out on the town. 
Petite to tall welcome to apply. Ages 18yrs-25ish No experience necessary but must have great camera presents. 
Travel paid, shoot date early June. Submit your best picture, resume or best contact number to: 
(Serious applicants only!) Good Luck! ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Campaign_8</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[REALITY SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/REALITY_SHOW_763</link>
	<description><![CDATA[TV REALITY SHOW COMING TO HOT-ATLANTA! 
TV SHOW LOOKING FOR SINGLE 
WOMEN - TWINS, TRIPLETS, ETCs - AGES 25-35 
]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/REALITY_SHOW_763</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[TV REALITY SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_REALITY_SHOW_20</link>
	<description><![CDATA[TV REALITY SHOW COMING TO HOT-ATLANTA! 
TV SHOW LOOKING FOR SINGLE 
WOMEN AGES 25-35 

IF YOU'RE LOOKING TO MEET, DATE AND MAYBE FALL IN LOVE WITH AN ELIGIBLE BACHELOR NEW TO ATLANTA... ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/TV_REALITY_SHOW_20</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[something dangerous]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/something_dangerous</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Casting Call: Are you ingesting something dangerous and need help?

A documentary series is currently looking for individuals who are ingesting dangerous, non-food items to share their story and receive professional treatment.

This series allows individuals that have uncontrollable urges to eat, drink and consume non-food items the chance to discuss their addiction in a safe and comforting manner.

If you or someone you know is ingesting:
-	wood
-	metal
-	magnetic material
-	cleansers 
-	hair / beauty products
-	toxic chemicals
-	other items not listed 

Please reach out to us. We can help! 

Many undetected medical conditions can cause individuals to want to consume non-food items. Our team of professionals can help you get your life and your health back on track!]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/something_dangerous</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Free Thinking Families]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Free_Thinking_Families</link>
	<description><![CDATA[LOOKING FOR FAMILIES IN THE ATLANTA AREA WHO ARE AGNOSTIC/ATHEIST OR FREE THINKERS!!

Major cable network is looking for outgoing & outspoken non-religious families in the Atlanta area to star in a brand new documentary TV series.

We are especially interested in families with children who would be willing to share with and learn from other families.

All types of families are encouraged to apply (traditional, non-traditional, single parents, same sex, etc.)

If you've ever thought your family should be on TV now's your chance. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Free_Thinking_Families</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Interview subjects needed]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Interview_subjects_needed_1</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Atlanta area author/producer is interested in interviewing persons who have suffered setbacks (unemployment, home foreclosure, bankruptcy) during the economic crisis of the last few years (The Great Recession). 
Interview sessions will be a minimum of one hour long and will be used as source material for a book and possible documentary. The sessions may be conducted either in person or by phone. ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Interview_subjects_needed_1</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Adult films]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Adult_films_144</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Recruiting GUYS for an Adult Website 

We only want to work with the best and our starting pay for male models is $2,000.00 for a 2 day production. 

If you think you have what it takes, send your pictures (face and body please) to 
the email address provided above, include a contact number and I will get back to you to discuss further details. 

Models should: 
-Have NO previous experience in the adult industry! 
-Have six-pack abs 
-Ages 18-35ish
-Have an athletic/muscular body 
-Be very handsome 

I look forward to discussing booking you to work with us soon!]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Adult_films_144</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Athletic Models Needed]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Athletic_Models_Needed_11</link>
	<description><![CDATA[TalentSoup is casting for athletic models (and all you buff actors) for a print shoot shooting in Atlanta
All talent must be signed up in TalentSoup to be submitted. 
It's fast and free. Go to www.talentsoup.com/signup and follow the directions.

The search is constrained to within 100 miles of Atlanta so if you are outside that area, simply change your address to Atlanta, GA to be included in the casting.

Pro Webcomp talent are paid $2000 for a booking, Entry (free account) are paid $1600.

Your Webcomp portfolio must include shots of you in athletic gear. The client needs to see your body and movement in your photos.
If you are in the Soup and fit the criteria, you'll be submitted automatically as always!]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Athletic_Models_Needed_11</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[NAT'L TV SHOW]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/NATL_TV_SHOW_142</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Divorce Court is looking for married couples on the verge of divorce, feuding couples that have been living together for at least 3 years or recently divorced couples. 
If you are a great talker, and want to bring your story to our show, please call us. Both sides have to participate. 
If you appear on the show, we will pay $570 per litigant, and we will fly you out and pay for your hotel in Los Angeles (some restrictions apply). ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/NATL_TV_SHOW_142</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[Models]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Models_301742</link>
	<description><![CDATA[If you are an aspiring female 18 years of age or older and have ever thought of starting a career in the adult industry, well look no further!
Here's the first step you need to take to get into the adult industry. We are 100% professional, discreet, serious and confidential. To set up an interview please text us with your name, number, age, picture (no nudes please) and something about your self at 4045743670 (only text messages) and we will give u a call. U can also e-mail me at crazyocu gmail
Must be :
18 years of age or older
Opened minded
 Professional
Discreet
Serious
We have two ways of conpensation 
1. Pay per video ( different prices apply)
2. 10000 visits $100 for the rest of your life! (base on terms and conditions)

We storage the videos UNTIL you decide to publish them (max 5 years) ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/Models_301742</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[rizfilms]]></title>
	<link>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/rizfilms</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Me And My Husband
short film: 30 min 

Mother Role: 38-50 yrs old, willing to do nude screen.

best friend female Role : 35:50 yrs old,  also nude screen.

Father Role: 45-50 

daughter Role 18-23 yrs old. willing to do nude screen

boyfriend Role18-23yrs old. nude screen 

location: staten island
filming days; 3 days
will pay for your traveling and food .
camera: canon 5d ]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 22:18:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<guid>http://elitecastingnetwork.com/auditions/rizfilms</guid>
</item>

	
</channel>
</rss>