<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Copcast</title>
    <link>http://copcast.net</link>
    <description>Welcome to CopCAST, the voice behind the badge.  Join your host Rich Schumaker and his friends for a weekly podcast for cops - by cops.  Each week we get together to discuss cop and tech news.</description>
    <generator>Feeder 1.5.10(880) http://reinventedsoftware.com/feeder/</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2008 RLS Enterprises, Inc.</copyright>
    <managingEditor>talkback@copcast.net</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>talkback@copcast.net (RLS Enterprises, Inc.)</webMaster>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 05:55:50 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 22:13:02 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Talk Radio</category>
    <category>Education</category>
    <image>
      <url>http://copcast.net/images/copcast3.png</url>
      <title>CopCAST</title>
      <link>http://copcast.net</link>
      <width>100</width>
      <height>100</height>
      <description>CopCAST Logo</description>
    </image>
    <atom:link href="http://copcast.net/copcast.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <itunes:author>Rich Schumaker</itunes:author>
    <itunes:subtitle>CopCAST - The Voice Behind the Badge</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>Welcome to CopCAST, the voice behind the badge.  Join your host Rich Schumaker and his friends for a weekly podcast for cops - by cops.  Each week we get together to discuss cop and tech news.</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:keywords>cops, law enforcement, police, jailors</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://copcast.net/images/copcast3.png"/>
    <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
    <itunes:category text="Education">
      <itunes:category text="Training"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:category text="Technology">
      <itunes:category text="Tech News"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/>
    <item>
      <title>CopCAST - Episode 164 - Cage Match</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the late edition of CopCAST.  Actually it is the only edition but it is late.</p>

<p>Again this week, I was able to get together with our very own Two Girls From Utah to get their perspective on last week's show. And, as usual, we just never know what they have on their minds so lets have a listen.</p>

<p>Is the Internet a fundamental right?  For our keynote story some guys you would just like to have for 15 minutes alone in a cage with no rules.  They didn't have female cops like that when I was on the street.  Hired, fired and arrested by the police all in the same afternoon.  Two dudes skinny dipping at 0200 hours - really?  Suspicious noises in the bedroom.  A Highlander for a mom.  "A really clumsy attempt at an adoption proceeding."  P*ss on it - he's dead.  Small businesses get hosed by computer scams.</p>

<p>This week we have another installment of the Tales From George's Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  Last week George was part of an armed stop on a suspect, this week the tables have turned and he finds himself on the receiving end.</p>

<p>2010 National Summit on Gang Violence contact information:</p>

<p>Melvin Hall
<br />Associate Director
<br />202-739-9630
<br />
<a href="mailto:hall@theinstituteweb.org">hall@theinstituteweb.org</a>
<br />
<a href="http://www.performanceweb.org/2010/01/20/l281/" target="_blank">http://www.performanceweb.org/2010/01/20/l281/
<br />
</a></p>

<p>I am beginning to see the light at the end of the tunnel - spring is springing in Virginia.  So download the show, fire up the iPod, grab a lawn chair, set it out in the sun and give us a listen.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 22:19:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://copcast.net/podcast/cc030710.mp3" length="41871679" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">copcast-episode-164-cage-match</guid>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 164 - Cage Match.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Welcome to the late edition of CopCAST.  Actually it is the only edition but it is late.

Again this week, I was able to get together with our very own Two Girls From Utah to get their perspective on last week&apos;s show. And, as usual, we just never know what they have on their minds so lets have a listen.

Is the Internet a fundamental right?  For our keynote story some guys you would just like to have for 15 minutes alone in a cage with no rules.  They didn&apos;t have female cops like that when I was on the street.  Hired, fired and arrested by the police all in the same afternoon.  Two dudes skinny dipping at 0200 hours - really?  Suspicious noises in the bedroom.  A Highlander for a mom.  &quot;A really clumsy attempt at an adoption proceeding.&quot;  P*ss on it - he&apos;s dead.  Small businesses get hosed by computer scams.

This week we have another installment of the Tales From George&apos;s Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  Last week George was part of an armed stop on a suspect, this week the tables have turned and he finds himself on the receiving end.

2010 National Summit on Gang Violence contact information:

Melvin Hall
Associate Director
202-739-9630
hall@theinstituteweb.org
http://www.performanceweb.org/2010/01/20/l281/

I am beginning to see the light at the end of the tunnel - spring is springing in Virginia.  So download the show, fire up the iPod, grab a lawn chair, set it out in the sun and give us a listen.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>43:36</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CopCAST - Episode 163 - Goin&apos; Fishin</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>This has been a really tough week.  I am traveling on business, Shell had a death in the family and Suz is still recovering from surgery.  So now you know why we are late and a little light on content.</p>
<p>Needless to say, the Two Girls From Utah were not available this week but I hope to catch up with them next week.</p>
<p>An Atlantic City police officer died of an accidental gunshot wound.  Angry parents catch speeding robbery suspect.  Who would paint Andy and Opie?  Why some folks really need to reconsider a life outside of the criminal ranks.  New Zealand isn't the only place with unfit cops.</p>
<p>In this week's Tales From George's Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain, George has a bad night.  In the UK the New Year is the busiest time for anyone involved with any of the emergency services, all hell is sure to break loose and all of your worst experiences can be packed into a single night.</p>
<p>We continue our review of Dr. Michael Asken's article entitled 10 psychological keys to keeping your exercise commitment...or building any other new habits.</p>
<p>Again, I am sorry for my tardiness and we will try to do better next week.  Since the show is shorter you will have more time to work on your taxes.  You have started your taxes haven't you?  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 05:55:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://copcast.net/podcast/cc022810.mp3" length="18004660" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">copcast-episode-163-goin-fishin</guid>
      <itunes:author>Rich Schumaker</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 163 - Goin&apos; Fishin.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>This has been a really tough week.  I am traveling on business, Shell had a death in the family and Suz is still recovering from surgery.  So now you know why we are late and a little light on content.

Needless to say, the Two Girls From Utah were not available this week but I hope to catch up with them next week.

An Atlantic City police officer died of an accidental gunshot wound.  Angry parents catch speeding robbery suspect.  Who would paint Andy and Opie?  Why some folks really need to reconsider a life outside of the criminal ranks.  New Zealand isn&apos;t the only place with unfit cops.

In this week&apos;s Tales From George&apos;s Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain, George has a bad night.  In the UK the New Year is the busiest time for anyone involved with any of the emergency services, all hell is sure to break loose and all of your worst experiences can be packed into a single night.

We continue our review of Dr. Michael Asken&apos;s article entitled 10 psychological keys to keeping your exercise commitment...or building any other new habits.

Again, I am sorry for my tardiness and we will try to do better next week.  Since the show is shorter you will have more time to work on your taxes.  You have started your taxes haven&apos;t you?  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>18:45</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CopCAST - Episode 162 - Dog Bites Cop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Two in a row!  That's right Michael is back for a second week in row and this is another great show.</p>

<p>This week, Suz is recovering from her operation so we couldn't connect up with her but I did get hold of Shell.  She said she has been carrying Suz's water for years so it wasn't a problem to do this week's show by herself. And, as usual, even with only half of the dynamic duo, we just never know what the Two Girls From Utah have on their minds.</p>

<p>Felony snowball charges in Virginia.  Our keynote story involves cops, dogs, doctors, nurses, fist fights, a criminal and a bad day at the office.  The driveway pavers, Willie and the cops.  It couldn't? have waited until they got off the interstate?  An expensive spare tire.  Russian takes gardening seriously.  UK cops ground remote control drone.  And you thought your vest was important - wear your vest.  A little highway entertainment in Chechnya.  Finding Facebook through Google may be a problem for one Website.</p>

<p>This week we have another installment of the Tales From George's Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  You know, in the UK, contrary to what you might read in certain sensationalist newspapers, possession of firearms is still rare and offenses involving firearms even rarer. The police in the UK are unarmed so when there's an incident involving firearms, they take things very seriously.</p>

<p>Don't miss our continuing review  from the <a href="http://www.forcesciencenews.com/home/index.html" target="_blank">Force Science News - Transmission 141</a>.  Maybe we can help you get back into the gym.</p>

<p>The weather is heating up and this week's show is hot!  So download the show, load up the iPod, put on the headphones and think summer!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 05:55:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://copcast.net/podcast/cc022110.mp3" length="47389699" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">copcast-episode-162-dog-bites-cop</guid>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 162 - Dog Bites Cop.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a good week!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Two in a row!  That&apos;s right Michael is back for a second week in row and this is another great show.

This week, Suz is recovering from her operation so we couldn&apos;t connect up with her but I did get hold of Shell.  She said she has been carrying Suz&apos;s water for years so it wasn&apos;t a problem to do this week&apos;s show by herself. And, as usual, even with only half of the dynamic duo, we just never know what the Two Girls From Utah have on their minds.

Felony snowball charges in Virginia.  Our keynote story involves cops, dogs, doctors, nurses, fist fights, a criminal and a bad day at the office.  The driveway pavers, Willie and the cops.  It couldn&apos;t? have waited until they got off the interstate?  An expensive spare tire.  Russian takes gardening seriously.  UK cops ground remote control drone.  And you thought your vest was important - wear your vest.  A little highway entertainment in Chechnya.  Finding Facebook through Google may be a problem for one Website.

This week we have another installment of the Tales From George&apos;s Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  You know, in the UK, contrary to what you might read in certain sensationalist newspapers, possession of firearms is still rare and offenses involving firearms even rarer. The police in the UK are unarmed so when there&apos;s an incident involving firearms, they take things very seriously.

Don&apos;t miss our continuing review  from the Force Science News - Transmission 141.  Maybe we can help you get back into the gym.

The weather is heating up and this week&apos;s show is hot!  So download the show, load up the iPod, put on the headphones and think summer!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>49:21</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CopCAST - Episode 161 - Stolen Doggie Coat (Rev)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>This week Michael is co-hosting and the production process went a little more smoothly.  I got the entire show up and running without incident - including the Two Girls From Utah segment.</p>

<p>I am sending out an electronic 911 request.  I need a copy of Episode 158 since I accidentally deleted it.  If anyone has a copy, please send me an email at talkback@copcast.net.</p>

<p>Again this week, I was able to tap into the vast redneck wisdom of our very own Two Girls From Utah to get their perspective on last week's show.  This week Shell get all excited about the Guns and Hoses story from last week until explained what is was.  And Suz wanted to talk about the infamous Utah runner.</p>

<p>The federal court system found out about this internet thing and they don't like it.  A vindictive ex-boyfriend will hopefully go to jail for many years.  Our keynote story is really low - stealing Lexie's coat.  A food fight ends up being a real fight.  How to plan the perfect romantic interlude for Valentines Day.  A cop killer cold case is solved in Great Britain.  A metropolitan police commander is on the wrong side of the law in Great Britain.  So sorry - I bet that Taser is going to leave a mark.  A Taser and a sledgehammer - sounds like fun.  Door to door pee collection? Really?</p>

<p>Next is the latest installment of the Tales From George's Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  Any old copper will tell you experience is priceless but sadly it has a cost, you have to make mistakes to gain it. Those of us that have made our fair share of mistakes can still learn though and no amount of experience will prevent those around us making mistakes either.</p>

<p>Don't miss the Women in Policing Career Expo which will be on Saturday April 10th from noon - 4:00 pm at Center Court inside Irving Mall, in Irving, TX. Kalena Barber is the contact person so visit their website at <a href="http://policetexas.org" target="_blank">http://policetexas.org</a>.  While you are talking to her ask her about the applicant testing they will be conducting on June 12, 2010.  They are expecting 4 - 6 vacancies.</p>

<p>So if you are among the 70% of the U.S. that currently has snow on the ground, you probably need some entertainment.  Why not download CopCAST Episode 161 and give it a listen while enjoy your Sunday off.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 17:55:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://copcast.net/podcast/cc021410.mp3" length="53695038" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">copcast-episode-161-stolen-doggie-coat</guid>
      <itunes:author>Rich Schumaker</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 161 - Stolen Doggie Coat.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>This week Michael is co-hosting and the production process went a little more smoothly.  I got the entire show up and running without incident - including the Two Girls From Utah segment.

I am sending out an electronic 911 request.  I need a copy of Episode 158 since I accidentally deleted it.  If anyone has a copy, please send me an email at talkback@copcast.net.

Again this week, I was able to tap into the vast redneck wisdom of our very own Two Girls From Utah to get their perspective on last week&apos;s show.  This week Shell get all excited about the Guns and Hoses story from last week until explained what is was.  And Suz wanted to talk about the infamous Utah runner.

The federal court system found out about this internet thing and they don&apos;t like it.  A vindictive ex-boyfriend will hopefully go to jail for many years.  Our keynote story is really low - stealing Lexie&apos;s coat.  A food fight ends up being a real fight.  How to plan the perfect romantic interlude for Valentines Day.  A cop killer cold case is solved in Great Britain.  A metropolitan police commander is on the wrong side of the law in Great Britain.  So sorry - I bet that Taser is going to leave a mark.  A Taser and a sledgehammer - sounds like fun.  Door to door pee collection? Really?

Next is the latest installment of the Tales From George&apos;s Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  Any old copper will tell you experience is priceless but sadly it has a cost, you have to make mistakes to gain it. Those of us that have made our fair share of mistakes can still learn though and no amount of experience will prevent those around us making mistakes either.

Don&apos;t miss the Women in Policing Career Expo which will be on Saturday April 10th from noon - 4:00 pm at Center Court inside Irving Mall, in Irving, TX. Kalena Barber is the contact person so visit their website at http://policetexas.org.  While you are talking to her ask her about the applicant testing they will be conducting on June 12, 2010.  They are expecting 4 - 6 vacancies.

So if you are among the 70% of the U.S. that currently has snow on the ground, you probably need some entertainment.  Why not download CopCAST Episode 161 and give it a listen while enjoy your Sunday off.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>55:55</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CopCAST - Episode 160 - Idol Fanatic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Well it has been another snowy week in Virginia but I finally got the show up and running.</p>

<p>Cops Online at copsonline.com surpassed 7000 member this week which is just incredible.  If you haven't joined yet surf on over to copsonline.com and join - it FREE!  There is a chat room, specialty groups and a ton of info on the site.  The whole CopCAST crew are members and I am an admin.</p>

<p><p>Check out the GovSec/U.S. Law 2010 Conference & Expo.  GovSec/U.S. Law is the only event that offers a comprehensive perspective on homeland security and has the convergence of IT and physical security at its core.   The Conference is offering a 20-session program, including the Law Enforcement Theater.  The show takes place on March 23 & 24 in Washington, DC.  For more information contact Kalin Tyler at ktyler@1105media.com or check out the following contact sites:</p>

Twitter: <a href="http://twitter.com/GovSecUSLaw" target="_blank">http://twitter.com/GovSecUSLaw</a>
<br />Facebook: <a href="http://cli.gs/VHZ7PA" target="_blank">http://cli.gs/VHZ7PA</a>
<br />LinkedIn: <a href="http://cli.gs/bJeLMp" target="_blank">http://cli.gs/bJeLMp</a>
<br />GovLoop: <a href="http://www.govloop.com/events/govsecus-law-2010" target="_blank">http://www.govloop.com/events/govsecus-law-2010</a></p>

<p>Again this week, I was able to get together with our very own Two Girls From Utah to get their perspective on last week's show. This week Shell picked our story on a unique noise violation and Suz picked the story about the attack kids.</p>

<p>That kid is possessed!  She puts the fanatic back in being a fan.  The Mounties get their man.  Can you fix a flat officer?  Boobs are a blast.  Run Elmondo Run!  Polizei - NOT! Guns and Hoses cops tackle bad guys.  Was he just tossing her a beer?  He was ripped off by a hooker.</p>

<p>Street Survival Seminar in Durham, NC being instructed by Ray DeCunto and Chief Tim Goergen on February 23-24.  Contact Info: 1-800-323-0037 ext 4150 or 469-671-4766. Ask for Candis Smith.</p>

<p>Hey football season is over so you might as well download the show, grab a left over hot wing and enjoy.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest, and have a great week!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 19:28:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://copcast.net/podcast/cc020710.mp3" length="37053986" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">copcast-episode-160-idol-fanatic</guid>
      <itunes:author>Rich Schumaker</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 160 - idol Fanatic.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest, and have a great week!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>38:35</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CopCAST - Episode 159 - Bite The Cop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>For the second time this year, the digital command center got hammered with a foot of snow.  Somehow we got the show out despite having to shovel tons of snow.</p>

<p>Again this week, I was able to get together with our very own Two Girls From Utah to get their perspective on last week's show. This week Shell wanted to talk about our Mommy Dearest story - you know the one where the mom made her kid kill his pet hamster because he made bad grades.  And naturally Suz could not pass up the nipple biting bad guy.</p>

<p>It is Miller time in New Zealand.  Time for the Crocodile Dundee technique.  Complaints from neighbours, a postman and a woman taking her child to school. The SC doper gets smoked.  NOTE:  The last 4 idiots who broke in here and stole from us are at the martin county correctional facility getting acquainted with Bubba.  Our keynote story tell us to encourage your kids to "bite the officers' faces off?"  Paying for love from all the wrong places.  Looks like this guy nailed it.  Another fatality chalked up to porn.  Drunk says, "take me to Orient."</p>

<p>This week we have another installment of the Tales From George's Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  Are there times when you feel like work is just something you do? Sometimes it helps just to see the same things that you do but from a fresh perspective to remind you just how much you really enjoy your job.</p>

<p>Sign up for the Force Science Certification Course scheduled for April 26-30, 2010 in Wisconsin. For the informational brochure, visit: <a href="http://www.forcescience.org/milwaukeecertification.pdf" target="_blank">http://www.forcescience.org/milwaukeecertification.pdf</a>.  To register, e-mail your name, rank and all contact information to: <a href="mailto:training@forcescience.org">training@forcescience.org</a>.</p>

<p>For information about the Transportation Safety Administration's Air Marshall vacancies visit <a href="http://www.policeone.com/careers/1785658-Transportation-Security-Officer-Transportation-Security-Administration-Various-Cities-across-the-U-S/" target="_blank">http://www.policeone.com/careers/1785658-Transportation-Security-Officer-Transportation-Security-Administration-Various-Cities-across-the-U-S/</a>.</p>

<p>If you are like 70% of the United States you have snow on the ground.  So heat up a cup of tea, download the show and fire up the iPod or iPad.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 06:39:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://copcast.net/podcast/cc013110.mp3" length="35292706" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">copcast-episode-159-bite-the-cop</guid>
      <itunes:author>Rich Schumaker</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 159 - Bite The Cop.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>For the second time this year, the digital command center got hammered with a foot of snow.  Somehow we got the show out despite having to shovel tons of snow.

Again this week, I was able to get together with our very own Two Girls From Utah to get their perspective on last week&apos;s show. This week Shell wanted to talk about our Mommy Dearest story - you know the one where the mom made her kid kill his pet hamster because he made bad grades.  And naturally Suz could not pass up the nipple biting bad guy.

It is Miller time in New Zealand.  Time for the Crocodile Dundee technique.  Complaints from neighbours, a postman and a woman taking her child to school. The SC doper gets smoked.  NOTE:  The last 4 idiots who broke in here and stole from us are at the martin county correctional facility getting acquainted with Bubba.  Our keynote story tell us to encourage your kids to &quot;bite the officers&apos; faces off?&quot;  Paying for love from all the wrong places.  Looks like this guy nailed it.  Another fatality chalked up to porn.  Drunk says, &quot;take me to Orient.&quot;

This week we have another installment of the Tales From George&apos;s Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  Are there times when you feel like work is just something you do? Sometimes it helps just to see the same things that you do but from a fresh perspective to remind you just how much you really enjoy your job.

Sign up for the Force Science Certification Course scheduled for April 26-30, 2010 in Wisconsin. For the informational brochure, visit: http://www.forcescience.org/milwaukeecertification.pdf.  To register, e-mail your name, rank and all contact information to: training@forcescience.org.

For information about the Transportation Safety Administration&apos;s Air Marshall vacancies visit http://www.policeone.com/careers/1785658-Transportation-Security-Officer-Transportation-Security-Administration-Various-Cities-across-the-U-S/.

If you are like 70% of the United States you have snow on the ground.  So heat up a cup of tea, download the show and fire up the iPod or iPad.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>36:45</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CopCAST - Episode 158 - Lead Foot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Well it was a rainy weekend but that didn't dampen our spirits for this week's show.  It will be the the Colts and the Saints in the Super Bowl.  We had a ton of email this week.  Remember, 20 days until Valentines Day on February 14th - don't mess it up this year.</p>

<p>I was able to tap into the vast redneck wisdom of our very own Two Girls From Utah to get their perspective on last week's show. This week Shell had a little problem making up her mind on her favorite article so we had to let her comment on three while Suz talks about round holes and diesel fuel.</p>

<p>Our keynote story involves a heavy fine for a heavy foot.  It is easy to miss things lying around a crash site.  If at first you don't succeed - just quit.  Bad grades?  Kill the pet.  Love can be a heavy burden.  Looking for love in all the wrong places.  These guys made a big withdraw from the bank.  Our record setter pleaded guilty.  Guns save lives - or at least one life.  You know that is going to leave a mark.</p>

<p>In this week's installment of the Tales From George's Pocketbook, we need to be kind to the British, they're not used to getting snow and apparently four inches of the stuff is enough to pretty much stop the UK dead in its tracks. Some people still have to carry on as normal though, even if in some cases this means acting like a bunch of kids themselves.</p>

<p>For information on the Monannock Expandable Straight Baton Basic Instructor/Re-cert Course and the OCAT Instructor/Re-cert Course send an email to <a href="mailto:TMOY302@aol.com">TMOY302@aol.com</a>.</p>

<p>If you are in Virginia, dock your boat, wait for the flood waters to recede while you listen to this week's show.  The rest of you should just download the show, load up the iPod and listen to it while you sweat your way toward accomplishing that New Year's resolution.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 05:55:30 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://copcast.net/podcast/cc012410.mp3" length="37611541" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">copcast-episode-158-lead-foot</guid>
      <itunes:author>Rich Schumaker</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 158 - Lead Foot.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week! </itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Well it was a rainy weekend but that didn&apos;t dampen our spirits for this week&apos;s show.  It will be the the Colts and the Saints in the Super Bowl.  We had a ton of email this week.  Remember, 20 days until Valentines Day on February 14th - don&apos;t mess it up this year.

I was able to tap into the vast redneck wisdom of our very own Two Girls From Utah to get their perspective on last week&apos;s show. This week Shell had a little problem making up her mind on her favorite article so we had to let her comment on three while Suz talks about round holes and diesel fuel.

Our keynote story involves a heavy fine for a heavy foot.  It is easy to miss things lying around a crash site.  If a first you don&apos;t succeed - just quit.  Bad grades?  Kill the pet.  Love can be a heavy burden.  Looking for love in all the wrong places.  These guys made a big withdraw from the bank.  Our record setter pleaded guilty.  Guns save lives - or at least one life.  You know that is going to leave a mark.

In this week&apos;s installment of the Tales From George&apos;s Pocketbook, we need to be kind to the British, they&apos;re not used to getting snow and apparently four inches of the stuff is enough to pretty much stop the UK dead in its tracks. Some people still have to carry on as normal though, even if in some cases this means acting like a bunch of kids themselves.

For information on the Monannock Expandable Straight Baton Basic Instructor/Re-cert Course and the OCAT Instructor/Re-cert Course send an email to TMOY302@aol.com.

If you are in Virginia, dock your boat, wait for the flood waters to recede while you listen to this week&apos;s show.  The rest of you should just download the show, load up the iPod and listen to it while you sweat your way toward accomplishing that New Year&apos;s resolution.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>39:10</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CopCAST - Episode 157 - 0.708 BAC</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Well this has been a lazy weekend since the football playoffs are in full swing.  That is the National Football League for our listeners from around the world.  You know, big guys with lots of pads, crashing into each other on purpose.  I did get the oil changed in the Honda, both cars washed and this episode of CopCAST out so I did accomplished something.</p>

<p>I was also able to get together with our very own Two Girls From Utah to get their perspective on last week's show. Although, the audio quality was a little worse than normal.  They were sort of  impressed with the escapee who went to court with his girlfriend and the race horse threat.</p>

<p>This week we have the great Walmart scooter escape.  A shocking Christmas hug.  A new Miranda iPhone/iPod Touch application (visit <a href="http://www.methowwebdesign.com target="_blank">http://www.methowwebdesign.com</a> for more info).  Guts and balls defined.  Our keynote story is about a near record setting BAC.  A guy is punched out after "weird sex".  Diesels don't run well on unleaded.  A German guys grabs a handful and rips.  A loose nut takes out a Harley rider.  Some Danish gamblers are in the red.</p>

<p>This week we have another installment of the Tales From George's Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  You know the justice system relies on a balance between effective investigation and evidence gathering on one side and independent legal representation and advice on the other. While police officers work hard to ensure their cases are dealt with fairly, that legal help is a right and not a requirement, a thing that some people may forget from time to time.</p>

<p>Check out the Advanced Narcotics Training, a working seminar with canine. It will be hosted by East Coast Canine on February 24 - 26 in Tarboro, NC.  For more informations contact Tim Braddy, tim@eastcoastcanine.com, (252) 813-2543 or visit <a href="http://www.eastcoastcanine.com" target="_blank">http://www.eastcoastcanine.com</a>.</p>

<p>Well the playoffs are over until next week and Dallas has been eliminated so the world is right.  Download CopCAST, fire up the iPod, kick back and enjoy.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 00:45:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://copcast.net/podcast/cc011710.mp3" length="31972435" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">copcast-episode-157-0708-bac</guid>
      <itunes:author>Rich Schumaker</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 157 - 0.708 BAC.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Well this has been a lazy weekend since the football playoffs are in full swing.  That is the National Football League for our listeners from around the world.  You know, big guys with lots of pads, crashing into each other on purpose.  I did get the oil changed in the Honda, both cars washed and this episode of CopCAST out so I did accomplished something.

I was also able to get together with our very own Two Girls From Utah to get their perspective on last week&apos;s show. Although, the audio quality was a little worse than normal.  They were sort of  impressed with the escapee who went to court with his girlfriend and the race horse threat.

This week we have the great Walmart scooter escape.  A shocking Christmas hug.  A new Miranda iPhone/iPod Touch application (visit http://www.methowwebdesign.com for more info).  Guts and balls defined.  Our keynote story is about a near record setting BAC.  A guy is punched out after &quot;weird sex&quot;.  Diesels don&apos;t run well on unleaded.  A German guys grabs a handful and rips.  A loose nut takes out a Harley rider.  Some Danish gamblers are in the red.

This week we have another installment of the Tales From George&apos;s Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  You know the justice system relies on a balance between effective investigation and evidence gathering on one side and independent legal representation and advice on the other. While police officers work hard to ensure their cases are dealt with fairly, that legal help is a right and not a requirement, a thing that some people may forget from time to time.

Check out the Advanced Narcotics Training, a working seminar with canine. It will be hosted by East Coast Canine on February 24 - 26 in Tarboro, NC.  For more informations contact Tim Braddy, tim@eastcoastcanine.com, (252) 813-2543 or visit http://www.eastcoastcanine.com.

Well the playoffs are over until next week and Dallas has been eliminated so the world is right.  Download CopCAST, fire up the iPod, kick back and enjoy.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>33:18</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CopCAST - Episode 156 - Cigarettes and Gasoline</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Winter is upon us!  If you are unfortunate enough to live in Kentucky, West Virginia, Pennsylvania or a host of other northern states you probably spent you week snow bound.  We have the solution to your cabin fever - this week's episode of CopCAST.</p>

<p>This week, I was only able to get up with half of our dynamic duo from Utah but Shell was able to carry the water.  Listen to what she had to say about last week's show.</p>

<p>This week our keynote story is explosive.  A chaplain is charged with disorderly conduct for "just talking."  A worthless Indian son.  How to stay awake in church.  Don't page me.  Fruit of the Looms and dye packs.  That's not what I said!  A thumb and finger gun.  I am going to kill your horse.  Food fight!  Funny911calls Twitter account.  I have a bunch of left feet.  Low speed pursuit.</p>

<p>We have another installment of the Tales From George's Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  Ever since there have been Control Rooms and radios for them to use to direct officers on calls, those officers on the calls have complained that it's all very well giving orders from miles away but you can't see what's actually happening on scene. Unfortunately every once in a while, those complaints come true and someone ends up on the sharp end of something ... literally. </p>

<p>Don't forget to check out the Street Crimes course at <A <a href="http://www.policeone.com/training/events/1966849-Street-Crimes-Seminar/" target="_blank">http://www.policeone.com/training/events/1966849-Street-Crimes-Seminar/</a>.</p>

<p>It is too cold to go anywhere so download the show, fire up the iPod, grab a spiked hot cider and enjoy.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 05:31:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://copcast.net/podcast/cc011010.mp3" length="44190233" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">copcast-episode-156-cigarettes-and-gasoline</guid>
      <itunes:author>Rich Schumaker</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 156 - Cigarettes and Gasoline.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Winter is upon us!  If you are unfortunate enough to live in Kentucky, West Virginia, Pennsylvania or a host of other northern states you probably spent you week snow bound.  We have the solution to your cabin fever - this week&apos;s episode of CopCAST.

This week, I was only able to get up with half of our dynamic duo from Utah but Shell was able to carry the water.  Listen to what she had to say about last week&apos;s show.

This week our keynote story is explosive.  A chaplain is charged with disorderly conduct for &quot;just talking.&quot;  A worthless Indian son.  How to stay awake in church.  Don&apos;t page me.  Fruit of the Looms and dye packs.  That&apos;s not what I said!  A thumb and finger gun.  I am going to kill your horse.  Food fight!  Funny911calls Twitter account.  I have a bunch of left feet.  Low speed pursuit.

We have another installment of the Tales From George&apos;s Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  Ever since there have been Control Rooms and radios for them to use to direct officers on calls, those officers on the calls have complained that it&apos;s all very well giving orders from miles away but you can&apos;t see what&apos;s actually happening on scene. Unfortunately every once in a while, those complaints come true and someone ends up on the sharp end of something ... literally. 

Don&apos;t forget to check out the Street Crimes course at http://www.policeone.com/training/events/1966849-Street-Crimes-Seminar/.

It is too cold to go anywhere so download the show, fire up the iPod, grab a spiked hot cider and enjoy.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>46:01</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CopCAST - Episode 155 - Ransom Weed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>"I'm late! I'm late! For a very important date I'm late. I'm late."  That is me this week.  The start of the new year brings lots of pressing business issues but I was finally able to get out this episode.  Sorry for the delay.</p>

<p>The Two Girls From Utah give us their perspective on last week's show. With stories like butt sniffers and the dynamite elf there is no telling what they will say.</p>

<p>Our keynote story about a ransom note and pot plants shows there is truly no limits to stupidity.  She wants her chicken nuggets - NOW!  A student passed gas not the class.  Potato chips are a gateway snack.  That is Mr. Prisoner to you.  At least cover you head when cycling in New Zealand.  Call the cops for Grand Theft Auto - the game?   Teddy is a stoner.  Facebook fun for an escapee.</p>

<p>This week we have another installment of the Tales From George's Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  No matter how good you are, it's always good to remember not to get too cocky.  The higher you build yourself up, the further it leaves for you to fall when someone else comes along and makes you look stupid.</p>

<p>Check out the variety of Calibre Press "Street Survival" seminars at <a href="http://www.policeone.com/training/" target="_blank">http://www.policeone.com/training</a>.</p>

<p>Christmas is over and the new year has dawned.  You have done well my friend.  So download this episode of CopCAST, fire up the iPod and relax.  Tax time is just around the corner.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 22:33:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://copcast.net/podcast/cc010310.mp3" length="30932973" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">copcast-episode-155-ransom-weed</guid>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 155 - Ransom Weed.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>&quot;I&apos;m late! I&apos;m late! For a very important date I&apos;m late. I&apos;m late.&quot;  That is me this week.  The start of the new year brings lots of pressing business issues but I was finally able to get out this episode.  Sorry for the delay.

The Two Girls From Utah give us their perspective on last week&apos;s show. With stories like butt sniffers and the dynamite elf there is no telling what they will say.

Our keynote story about a ransom note and pot plants shows there is truly no limits to stupidity.  She wants her chicken nuggets - NOW!  A student passed gas not the class.  Potato chips are a gateway snack.  That is Mr. Prisoner to you.  At least cover you head when cycling in New Zealand.  Call the cops for Grand Theft Auto - the game?   Teddy is a stoner.  Facebook fun for an escapee.

This week we have another installment of the Tales From George&apos;s Pocketbook, our audio segment from our brother officers Great Britain.  No matter how good you are, it&apos;s always good to remember not to get too cocky.  The higher you build yourself up, the further it leaves for you to fall when someone else comes along and makes you look stupid.

Check out the variety of Calibre Press &quot;Street Survival&quot; seminars at http://www.policeone.com/training.

Christmas is over and the new year has dawned.  You have done well my friend.  So download this episode of CopCAST, fire up the iPod and relax.  Tax time is just around the corner.  Remember to stay safe, always wear your vest and have a great week!</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:duration>32:13</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>