<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">


<channel>
<title>Open Your Eyes to Australia with Jim Low</title>
<link>http://jimlow.net</link>
<itunes:new-feed-url>http://www.jimlow.net/podcast/australia.xml</itunes:new-feed-url>
<language>en-us</language>

<copyright>&#x2117; &amp; &#xA9; 2006 Jim Low</copyright>

<itunes:subtitle>Open Your Eyes to Australia is a series presented by Jim Low  focusing on Australian themes which highlight history, people and places through the use of original songs.
</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:author>Jim Low</itunes:author>

<itunes:summary>Open Your Eyes to Australia is a series presented by Jim Low  focusing on Australian themes which highlight history, people and places through the use of original songs.Jim Low is an Australian country folk singer / songwriter who plays guitar and harmonica. His songs and writing reflect a love of  Australia - the history, the people and the  Australian environment. Each year he travels to Australian places - listening to, and documenting, the stories of the people who live there.</itunes:summary>

<description>Open Your Eyes to Australia is a series presented by Jim Low  focusing on Australian themes which highlight history, people and places through the use of original songs.Jim Low is an Australian country folk singer / songwriter who plays guitar and harmonica. His songs and writing reflect a love of  Australia - the history, the people and the  Australian environment. Each year he travels to Australian places - listening to, and documenting, the stories of the people who live there.</description>

<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Jim Low</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>jim@jimlow.net</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>

<itunes:image href="http://jimlow.net/images/eyes-button.jpg" />


<itunes:category text="Music" />
<itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
<itunes:category text="History" />
	</itunes:category> 

<item>
<title>In Mulga Loand with King Tommy and Polly Flood</title>
<itunes:author>Jim Low</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle> Two lives from the writings of Jim Harper</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary> This episode looks at the lives of two Aboriginal people, King Tommy and Polly Flood. They lived in the northern New South Wales town of Angledool . Their lives were uniquely documented by local poet and writer Jim Harper. Harper, a friend of both, knew only too well how the spread of European settlement impacted on their lives.
More information about Jim and the podcast can be found at his website at http://jimlow.net</itunes:summary>
<link>http://jimlow.net/podcast-6.htm</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.users.on.net/~tracks/podcasts/Jim-Low_podcast6.mp3" length="37207798" type="audio/mp3" />
<guid>http://www.users.on.net/~tracks/podcasts/Jim-Low_podcast6.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 11:09:00 UT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>25:50</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Jim Low, New South Wales, NSW, Aboriginal, aborigine, Angledool, Jim Harper, frontier settlement, bush poetry, Narran, Walgett, breastplate, Thomas McCarthy, songwriter, Australian history, Australia, history, heritage, music,</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Two Women Travellers</title>
<itunes:author>Jim Low</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle> Two Women who experienced the life of the swaggie</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary> The image of the swaggie, that itinerant soul who walked the roads and tracks of the land in search of work, features prominently in Australia’s stories, songs and poetry. But the swaggies we mainly read and sing about are men. In this episode I introduce you to Charcoal Annie and Syrian Mary, two women who experienced the life of the swaggie. Although very little is known about them, I share the information I have gathered over the years. Included are songs I've written about each of these extraordinary ladies.
More information about Jim and the podcast can be found at his website at http://jimlow.net</itunes:summary>
<link>http://jimlow.net/podcast-5.htm</link>
<enclosure url="http://www.users.on.net/~tracks/podcasts/Jim-Low_podcast5.mp3" length="22809628" type="audio/mp3" />
<guid>http://www.users.on.net/~tracks/podcasts/Jim-Low_podcast5.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2008 11:09:00 UT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>16:42</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Jim Low, New South Wales, NSW, Charcoal Annie, Syrian Mary, swaggy, swagman,swaggies, travelling, swagmen, swagwomen, charcoal, charcoal burning, songwriter, Australian history, Australia, history, heritage, music,</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Boyd's Tower at Twofold Bay</title>
<itunes:author>Jim Low</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Whaling at Twofold Bay</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Boyd's Tower  at Twofold Bay
Jim looks at the tower through the lives of two people associated with it - Ben Boyd, its builder, and Peter Lia, a young whaler who lost his life chasing a whale. The featured song is  Boyd's Tower. 
More information about Jim and the podcast can be found at his website at http://jimlow.net</itunes:summary>
<link>http://jimlow.net/podcast-1.htm</link>
<enclosure url="http://mountaintracks.com.au/podcast/australia_1.mp3" length="6079950" type="audio/mp3" />
<guid>http://mountaintracks.com.au/podcast/australia_1.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2006 11:09:00 UT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>12:39</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Jim Low, song, history, guitar, singer, songwriter, Australian history, country music, Australian country music, Australia, history, heritage, music, folksong, folksinger, Australian</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Sir Charles Kingsford-Smith and the Southern Cross Trans-Pacific Flight</title>
<itunes:author>Jim Low</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle> Four men and their  record breaking 1928 flight into history</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Jim looks at the 1928 Pacific Ocean Crossing led by Charles Kingsford-Smith in the Southern Cross aeroplane. He looks at some of the difficulties faced, some personal memories of his late father and sings a song, From Oakland to Brisbane, which tells of the successful trans-Pacific flight.
More information about Jim and the podcast can be found at his website at http://jimlow.net</itunes:summary>
<link>http://jimlow.net/podcast-2.htm</link>
<enclosure url="http://mountaintracks.com.au/podcast/australia_2.mp3" length="17793072" type="audio/mp3" />
<guid>http://mountaintracks.com.au/podcast/australia_2.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 11:09:00 UT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>14:49</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Jim Low, Kingsford Smith, Smithy, Sir Charles Kingsford Smith, Charled Ulm, Southern Cross, California, trans-pacific, flight, song, history, guitar, singer, songwriter, Australian history, country music, Australian country music, Australia.</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>In Search of Mr Murphy</title>
<itunes:author>Jim Low</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle> a fascinating Blue Mountains character</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Jim pieces together some of the life of William Murphy who, early last century, lived in an isolated part of the Blue Mountains of Australia. Information is gathered from a variety of sources including an oral history recording, a newspaper cutting, photographs and a death certificate. The podcast also features an original song about this fascinating man. 
More information about Jim and the podcast can be found at his website at http://jimlow.net</itunes:summary>
<link>http://jimlow.net/podcast-3.htm</link>
<enclosure url="http://mountaintracks.com.au/podcast/open_your_eyes_to_australia_3_jim_low.mp3" length="17793072" type="audio/mp3" />
<guid>http://mountaintracks.com.au/podcast/open_your_eyes_to_australia_3_jim_low.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2006 11:09:00 UT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>15:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Jim Low, William Murphy, Blue Mountains, the Blue Mountains, Blackheath, birds, anumals, environment, oral history, song, history, guitar, singer, songwriter, Australian history, country music, Australian country music, Australia.</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Sydney Harbour Bridge - Happy Birthday</title>
<itunes:author>Jim Low</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle> celebrating the 75th anniversary of the bridge opening</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary> In this episode Jim remembers some 50th anniversary celebrations and discusses Dr Frank Cash, who took thousands of photographs during the Bridge construction. He considers the changes to North Sydney resulting from the building of the Bridge and later the Warringah Expressway. North Sydney was the suburb where Jim lived as a child. Two songs, one a birthday song, are included in this episode. 
More information about Jim and the podcast can be found at his website at http://jimlow.net</itunes:summary>
<link>http://jimlow.net/podcast-4.htm</link>
<enclosure url="http://mountaintracks.com.au/podcast/podcast_4_JimLow-SydneyHarbourBridge.mp3" length="22809628" type="audio/mp3" />
<guid>http://mountaintracks.com.au/podcast/podcast_4_JimLow-SydneyHarbourBridge.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2007 10:09:00 UT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>19:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Jim Low, Sydney, Sydney Harbour Bridge, harbour bridge, bridge, Rev Frank Cash, Dr Cash, Frank Cash, Lapstone Public School,Reverend Cash, North Sydney, Australia, history, heritage, music, Warringah Expressway</itunes:keywords>
</item>


</channel>
</rss>