<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
<atom:link href="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/RSSfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<title>Collective Voice</title>
		<link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/</link>
		<description>Collective Voice is a syndicated program featuring a wide variety of eclectic and experimental music, hosted by Rory Hinchey. Particular editions can include news related to artists whose work is featured on the broadcast, interviews, label spotlights, contests, and much else. The program airs weekly on 8 radio stations in North America. Audio submissions are very much welcome, however digital submissions are not accepted.
</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>2008</copyright>
		<pubDate>Thu, 1 May 2008 01:00:00 EST</pubDate>
<webMaster>r_hinchey@collectivevoice.net (Rory Hinchey)</webMaster>
		<ttl>1</ttl>

<item><title>Collective Voice - May 01, 2008</title>
<description>The final edition of Collective Voice, with music from Excepter, Son of Earth, Wolfcow, Storm Bugs, The Goslings, Jessica Bailiff and Annelies Monsere, Sun City Girls, Smegma, Hilt, Helen Carlson, Gang Wizard, Current 93, Lake Of Dracula, Old Hack and Friends, Caroliner, The Poppy Family, Raymond Scott Quintette, Dorothy, Throbbing Gristle, and others.
Thank you for your interest and support. 

</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may0108.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may0108.mp3" length="265821404" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may0108.mp3</guid>
			</item>


<item><title>Collective Voice - April 24, 2008</title>
<description>This installment in April's best of spotlights 2007 series includes features on Aufgehoben and Grouper.

</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2408.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2408.mp3" length="257668637" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2408.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - April 17, 2008</title>
<description>This installment in April's best of spotlights 2007 series will feature a showcase of the Snatch Tapes label followed by a spotlight on Colleen.

</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr1708.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr1708.mp3" length="264165122" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr1708.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - April 10, 2008</title>
<description>After a six-year run, I've decided that the last edition of Collective Voice will air on May 01, 2008. I'd like to take this opportunity to thank everyone who made the show what it was - listeners, musicians, and friends. The Collective Voice podcast archive will remain online for the foreseeable future, albeit in a slightly modified form.
As the first installment in April's best of 2007 series is a three-hour feature on the work of Scott Foust and Idea Fire Company. The program includes a wide variety of selections from IFCO, Tart, The Pickle Factory and other related projects, interview segments from a discussion with Scott Foust, and selections from the now recently issued Idea Fire Company album "The Island of Taste". 

</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec0607.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec0607.mp3" length="251959167" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/</guid>
			</item>

<item>
<title>Collective Voice - March 27, 2008</title>
<description>Expect music from Hilt, Mouthus, Sun City Girls, Excepter, Herschell Gordon Lewis, Omit, Jessica Bailiff, Lamborghini Crystal, The Goslings, Sol Invictus, Teddy Lasry, Francoise Hardy, Axolotl, Throbbing Gristle, Delia Derbyshire, The Legendary Pink Dots, The Pickle Factory, Black Dice, and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2708.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2708.mp3" length="251466395" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2708.mp3</guid>
</item>



<item>
<title>Collective Voice - March 20, 2008</title>
<description>Expect music from Hilt, Mouthus, Sun City Girls, Excepter, Herschell Gordon Lewis, Omit, Jessica Bailiff, Lamborghini Crystal, The Goslings, Sol Invictus, Teddy Lasry, Francoise Hardy, Axolotl, Throbbing Gristle, Delia Derbyshire, The Legendary Pink Dots, The Pickle Factory, Black Dice, and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2008.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2008.mp3" length="255610461" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2008.mp3</guid>
</item>



<item>
<title>Collective Voice - March 13, 2008</title>
<description>Music to come this week from Mouthus, Giancarlo Barigozzi and Fabia Fabor, Fursaxa, Teotihuacan, Sun City Girls, Doc Wor Mirran, BunnyBrains 88, N., Lamborghini Crystal, Leslie Keffer, Ed Yazijian, Axolotl, At Jennie Richie, Dr. Id, Raccoo-oo-oon, Shit and Shine, Michael Flower, Skeleton Warrior and The Psychic Ether Flower Machine, Russian Tsarcasm, Omit, Lalo Schifrin, Justice Yeldham and The Dynamic Ribbon Device, and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar1308.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar1308.mp3" length="253645635" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar1308.mp3</guid>
</item>



<item>
<title>Collective Voice - March 06, 2008</title>
<description>From the Collective Voice archives, an edited edition which originally aired in April of 2005 featuring guest co-host Rick Kinney of EmptyFree.com. Expect music by Death In June, Hexentanz, This Heat, Flock of Seagulls, The Legendary Pink Dots, Ennio Morricone, Labradford, Rita Chao and the Quests, The Cougars, Heinz Kiessling, Badawi, Kaleidoscope, Spacemen 3, Simon Finn, France Gall, Manon, and Test Dept. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0608.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0608.mp3" length="252087692" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0608.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Collective Voice - February 28, 2008</title>
<description>Some of host Rory Hinchey's current favorite artists and music, with selections from Giancarlo Barigozzi Group, Caroliner, Syd Barrett, Marion Marz, Black Dice, Nick Cave And The Bad Seeds, Serge Gainsbourg, The Frogs, Gang wizard, Crank Sturgeon, Sun City Girls, Sightings, Chromatics, Dorothy, Screaming Lord Sutch and The Savages, No Doctors, Lou Reed, Ohgr, Gang of Four, Excepter, Edd Kalehoff, The Poppy Family, and Zack Kouns.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2808.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2808.mp3" length="258566477" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2808.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Collective Voice - February 21, 2008</title>
<description>The first half of this edition will include music by Moondog, Caroliner Rainbow Scrambled Egg Taken For a Wife, Bourbonese Qualk, Adam Frank + Sam Shalabi, Jeremy From Boise, Justice Yeldham and The Dynamic Ribbon Device, Death In June, Ju Suk Reet Meate, Herschell Gordon Lewis, Excepter, Cabaret Voltaire, HNAS, and Dadamah. The second half is a feature on the Abandon Ship Records label. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2108.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2108.mp3" length="254914559" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2108.mp3</guid>
</item>


<item>
<title>Collective Voice - February 14, 2008</title>
<description>Music this week from Caroliner, Joe Meek and The Blue Men, Collection of the Late Howell Bend, Zack Kouns, Boyd Rice and Frank Tovey, Argumentix, Stars Of The Lid, Idea Fire Company, Excepter, Crawling Chaos, HNAS, Carter Tutti, Hair Police, Teen Community, Blumen Des Exotischen Eises, Jessica Bailiff, Roxanne Jean Polise + The Goslings, Weasel Walter, German Shepherds, Sun City Girls, Sightings, The Elektrosoniks, Los Iniciados, and Volcano The Bear. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb1408.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb1408.mp3" length="261518732" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb1408.mp3</guid>
</item>


<item>
<title>Collective Voice - February 07, 2008</title>
<description>The first hour of this week's program will include music by The Crawling Chaos, Inca Ore, Justice Yeldham, Russian Tsarcasm, Pink Floyd, Richard H. Kirk, Son of Earth, Volcano The Bear, Chthonic Force, and The Goslings. The second and third hours are a feature on the work of Irene Moon, complete with interview. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0708.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0708.mp3" length="260107492" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0708.mp3</guid>
</item>


<item>
<title>Collective Voice - January 31, 2008</title>
<description>Music this week by The Thunderbolts, Hetero Skeleton, Russian Tsarcasm, Zack Kouns, Iovae, Blues Control, Excepter, Islaja, The Wooden Cupboard, Sir Richard Bishop, The Rubber-0-Cement Speculum Fight, Collection of the Late Howell Bend, HNAS, Griefer, Alfredo Costa Monteiro, Justice Yeldham + The Dynamic Ribbon Device, Schwump, Gas Shepherds, Crawling Chaos, Doo-dooettes, and Faust. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan3108.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan3108.mp3" length="260351999" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan3108.mp3</guid>
</item>


<item>
<title>Collective Voice - January 24, 2008</title>
<description>This week's program will feature music by Bunnybrains 88, Alvars Orkester, People Like Us + Ergo Phizmiz, Dead Girl's Party, Factrix, Gang Wizard, Griefer, Kemialliset Ystavat, Chthonic Force, and Ohgr during the first hour. The second and third hours are a spotlight on the duo of Russ Waterhouse and Lea Cho who create music as Blues Control and Watersports.  
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan2408.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan2408.mp3" length="256142105" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan2408.mp3</guid>
</item>



<item>
<title>Collective Voice - January 10, 2008</title>
<description>This week's edition features lengthy works by Current 93, To Live And Shave In L.A., Robert Rental and The Normal, The No-Neck Blues Band, and Throbbing Gristle. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1008.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1008.mp3" length="254674441" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1008.mp3</guid>
</item>



<item>
<title>Collective Voice - January 03, 2008</title>
<description>The second half of this week's edition is a spotlight on Michael Gira and The Angels of Light, which includes a recent telephone interview. Music in the first half from Islaja, Butthole Surfers, Shit And Shine, This Heat, Rubber O Cement and James Twig Harper, You've Got Foetus On Your Breath, Sun City Girls, Nervous Gender, Armpit, and Mouthus + Axolotl. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan0308.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan0308.mp3" length="250334145" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan0308.mp3</guid>
</item>


<item>
<title>Collective Voice - December 27, 2007</title>
<description>2007 in review, with music from Hilt, Excepter, Eric Copeland, Blues Control, Sightings, Cabinet of Natural Curiosities, Throbbing Gristle, Gang Wizard, Volcano The Bear, Ralph Gean, Religious Knives, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Jessica Bailiff, Zack Kouns, No Doctors, Angels of Light, Colleen, Smegma and Jazkamer, Grouper, Goslings, Auk Theatre, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2707.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2707.mp3" length="259614092" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2707.mp3</guid>
</item>


<item>
<title>Collective Voice - December 20, 2007</title>
<description>The first hour of this edition will include music by Jessica Bailiff, Pukers, Auk Theatre, Throbbing Gristle, Blues Control, Shock Headed Peters, MWMV, Rubber-0-Cement, David Bowie, and Demons, while the second and third hours are a showcase of the Not Not Fun label with music from Changeling, Barn Owl, Barrabarracuda, Black Monk, Drumlins, Robedoor, Raccoo-oo-oon, Goliath Bird Eater, Pocahaunted, and exclusive interview segments.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2007.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2007.mp3" length="246201364" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2007.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Collective Voice - December 13, 2007</title>
<description>Music this week from Auk Theatre, SPK, Excepter, Temple Of Bon Matin, Panicsville, Idea Fire Company, Caroliner, Gang Wizard, Clear Horizon, Orphan Fairytale, Ginger Leigh, Volcano The Bear, Angels of Light, Loosers, Ju Suk Reet Meate, Teen Community, Rubber-O-Cement and James Twig Harper, Pan Sonic, Scissor Shock, Minimal Man, and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec1307.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec1307.mp3" length="256281909" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec1307.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - December 06, 2007</title>
<description>This week's edition is a three-hour feature on the work of Scott Foust and Idea Fire Company. The program includes a wide variety of selections from IFCO, Tart, The Pickle Factory and other related projects, interview segments from a discussion with Scott Foust, and selections from the forthcoming Idea Fire Company album "The Island of Taste".

</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec0607.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec0607.mp3" length="251959167" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec0607.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item>
<title>Collective Voice - November 29, 2007</title>
<description>The first two hours of this edition will feature music by Zack Kouns, Fricara Pacchu, To Live And Shave In L.A.2, Idea Fire Company, Flies Inside The Sun, Altar of Flies, Auk Theatre, Sleeping Babies, The MSR Singers, Excepter, Dinosaurs With Horns, Smegma , and others. The third and final hour is a special presentation of Throbbing Gristle's March 16, 1980 Oundle School Performance in honour of the soon-to-be-released TGV box set. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov2907.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov2907.mp3" length="252684535" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov2907.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - November 22, 2007</title>
<description>Music this week from Throbbing Gristle, The Skaters, Fricara Pacchu, Orphan Fairytale, Temple of Bon Matin, Sleeping Babies, Blues Control, To Live And Shave In L.A. 2, Tom Recchion, Cahier, Crank Sturgeon, Chrome, Rubber 0 Cement, Soil Sing Through Me, Black Vatican, Filthy Turd, Sunburned Circle, Wolf Eyes, Hilt, Das Synthetische Mischgewebe, Zack Kouns, and Robedoor.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov2207.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov2207.mp3" length="256067497" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov2207.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - November 15, 2007</title>
<description>A spotlight on Temple of Bon Matin will be featured during the second half of this week's edition, while the first hour and a half will include music by Eric Copeland, Millions Like Us, Rubber O Cement and Truck Van Rental, Tom Recchion, Filthy Turd, Excepter, The Haters, Gang Wizard, Renaldo and The Loaf, Sun City Girls, Fantastic Magic, Vaginals, Talibam!, and Rise Of The City Cat Cult.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov1507.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov1507.mp3" length="258500646" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov1507.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - November 08, 2007</title>
<description>This week's edition features music by Angels of Light, Renaldo and The Loaf, Disjunct, Temple of Bon Matin, Excepter, Vaginals, Rise Of The City Cat Cult, Loopool, Can, With Throats As Fine As Needles, Minimal Man, Death In June, Nautical Almanac, Islaja, Blues Control, Sword Heaven, Fantastic Magic, Sprung Aus Den Wolken, Crappy Nightmareville, Lezet, VxPxC, and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0807.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0807.mp3" length="261982664" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0807.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - November 01, 2007</title>
<description>A spotlight on Nautical Almanac will be featured during the second and third hours of this week's edition, while the first hour will include music by Syd Barrett, Panicsville, Fantastic Magic, Sightings, Charalambides, The Residents, Reformed Faction, No Neck Blues Band, Sunburned Hand Of the Man, and Fred Lane. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0107.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0107.mp3" length="256549612" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0107.mp3</guid>
			</item>


<item><title>Collective Voice - October 25, 2007</title>
<description>This week's edition features music by Fred Lane + Ron Pate's Debonairs, Wolf Eyes, Scissor Shock, Psychic TV, Guilty Connector, No Doctors, Caroliner, Tom Carter + Robert Horton, Sightings, Crappy Nightmareville, Jessica Bailiff, Sun City Girls, Argumentix, Cabinet of Natural Curiosities, Eeyow Karoom, Carter Tutti, Goslings, Gelding Express, Charles Balls, Bound, and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct2507.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct2507.mp3" length="252866347" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct2507.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - October 18, 2007</title>
<description>A spotlight on Grouper will be heard during the second half of this week's edition, while the first hour-and-a-half will include music by Psychic TV, Caroliner, Sightings, Fred Lane + Ron Pate's Debonairs, Panicsville, Temple of Bon Matin, No Neck Blues Band, Gastric Female Reflex, Parade Ground, Justice Yeldham + the Drummer Who Wishes to Remain Nameless, Mouthus, Neil Campbell, Sun City Girls, and Sword Heaven.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1807.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1807.mp3" length="256555255" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1807.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - October 11, 2007</title>
<description>Music this week from Excepter, Mouthus, Panicsville, Boyd Rice, Anla Courtis + Ralf Wehowsky, Sun City Girls, Kites, Angels of Light, Envenomist, Islaja, Nihilist Spasm Band + Joe McPhee, Colleen, Pyrolator, Skullflower, Blues Control, Grouper, Talibam, Charalambides, Gary Smith, Vetza and Airway, Jessica Bailiff, and many others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1107.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1107.mp3" length="257641112" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1107.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - October 04, 2007</title>
<description>A spotlight on Xenis Emputae Travelling Band will be heard during the second half of this week's edition, while the first hour-and-a-half will include music from Ashtray Navigations, Armpit, Eric Copeland, Kites, .45 Grave, Nautical Almanac, Jesus Drill, Throbbing Gristle, Algebrassiere, Crappy Nightmareville, Tom Carter + Robert Horton, Lezet, Sun City Girls, Moongang, and This Heat.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct0407.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct0407.mp3" length="255029912" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct0407.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - September 27, 2007</title>
<description>Music this week from Islaja, Black Dice, Harry Pussy, Xenis Emputae Travelling Band, Giggle The Ozone, Religious Knives, Storm Bugs, Robedoor, Dreams, Cabinet of Natural Curiosities, Ignatz, Ellen Fullman, Angels Of Light, GHQ, Simio Superior, Mudboy, Hilt, The Goslings, Psychic TV, Sir Richard Bishop, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2707.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2707.mp3" length="259952773" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2707.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - September 20, 2007</title>
<description>The second half of this week's edition is a spotlight on Religious Knives, complete with interview segments from a recent conversation with Religious Knives member Mike Bernstein. Music in the first half from The Residents, Non, Bythesea, Xenis Emputae Travelling Band, Cabaret Voltaire, Dapper, Black To Comm, Gang Wizard, Grouper, Eric Copeland, Acid Eagle, Silvester Anfang, and Excepter. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2007.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2007.mp3" length="253675098" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2007.mp3</guid>
			</item>

		<item><title>Collective Voice - September 13, 2007</title>
<description>Expect music this week from Colleen, Shadow Ring, Islaja, Black Dice, Xiu Xiu + Grouper, Xenis Emputae Travelling Band, Mudboy + Orphan Fairytale, Religious Knives, Brothers of the Occult Sisterhood, Excepter, Moongang, Loopool, Jessica Bailiff, The Goslings, Psychic TV and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep1307.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep1307.mp3" length="256572183" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep1307.mp3</guid>
			</item>
		<item><title>Collective Voice - September 06, 2007</title>
<description>The second and third hours of this edition is a spotlight on Graham Lambkin, while the first hour will include music by Idea Fire Company, Hilt, Terrestrial Tones, Blowhole, Crappy Nightmareville, Telepathe, Rodd Keith, Caroliner Rainbow Open Wound Chorale, Blumen Des Exotischen Eises, and Jessica Bailiff.    
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep0607.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep0607.mp3" length="258561458" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep0607.mp3</guid>
			</item>

		<item><title>Collective Voice - August 30, 2007</title>
<description>A new edition featuring music by Caroliner, The Shadow Ring, Grouper, Foot Village, Jessica Bailiff, Blumen Des Exotischen Eises, Hunting Lodge, Brothers Of The Occult Sisterhood, Full Scales, Panicsville, Michael Weaver + Occasionally A Williams, Needlegun, Kukkiva Poliisi, William Henshall, Sleeping Police, No Doctors, Gary Smith + Steve Roden, Los Iniciados, and Idea Fire Company.  
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug3007.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug3007.mp3" length="252557893" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug3007.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - August 23, 2007</title>
<description>The fourth edition of the 2006-7 spotlights revisited series includes a showcase of this year's No Fun Fest which originally aired on January 25, 2007, and a spotlight on Crawling Chaos from March 22, 2007.   
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug2307.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug2307.mp3" length="253446954" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug2307.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - August 16, 2007</title>
<description>The third edition of the 2006-7 spotlights revisited series includes a spotlight on Stars of the Lid which originally aired on November 30, 2006, and a spotlight on Jessica Rylan/Can't from February 22, 2007.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug1607.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug1607.mp3" length="258345165" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug1607.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - August 9, 2007</title>
<description>The second edition of the 2006-7 spotlights revisited series includes a spotlight on Charalambides + Tom Carter which originally aired on August 10, 2006, and a spotlight on Axolotl from December 28, 2006.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug0907.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug0907.mp3" length="258694997" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug0907.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - August 2, 2007</title>
<description>The first edition of the 2006-7 spotlights revisited series includes a showcase of Deathbomb Arc which originally aired on July 26, 2006, and a spotlight on Jessica Bailiff from September 14, 2006.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug0207.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug0207.mp3" length="257311342" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug0207.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - July 26, 2007</title>
<description>The second half of this week's edition is a spotlight on Colleen, complete with segments from an interview with Cecile Schott. The first half will feature music by Crawling Chaos, Zack Kouns, Mukai Chie and Gary Smith, Smegma and Jazkamer, Hilt, Grease Whore, Click Click, Foot Village, William C. Harrington, Graham Lambkin, Cabinet of Natural Curiosities, and Jessica Bailiff.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul2607.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul2607.mp3" length="260422212" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul2607.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - July 19, 2007</title>
<description>Music this week from No Doctors, Cock E.S.P., Colleen, Newage Panther Mistique, Lee Rockey, Anaksimandros, The Goslings, Outermost, Big City Orchestra, Shadow Ring, Needle gun, Audrey Arno, Death In June, Vox Populi!, Caroliner Rainbow Stewed Angel, Smegma and Jazkamer, Charalambides, Curse of the Birthmark, and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul1907.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul1907.mp3" length="256711363" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul1907.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - July 12, 2007</title>
<description>This edition is co-hosted by musician, author, artist, and film-maker Boyd Rice as we showcase some of his obscure girl group favorites. Expect music by Little Peggy March, Glenda Collins, France Gall, Diane Renay, April March, Lesley Gore, Dusty Springfield, and many others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul1207.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul1207.mp3" length="256758383" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul1207.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - July 5, 2007</title>
<description>Music this week from The Moontrekkers, Burning Star Core, Davenport Family, Caroliner, Gary Smith, Moongang, Brothers of the Occult Sisterhood, Teatro Satanico, Excepter, Bitrate, NON, Panther Skull, Haunted Castle, Anaksimandros, Smegma, Savage Republic, The Goslings, Sun City Girls, Family Underground, Hototogisu, Needlegun, Cabinet of Natural Curiosities, and many others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul0507.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul0507.mp3" length="264163157" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul0507.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - June 29, 2007</title>
<description>Expect a spotlight on Caroliner this week during the second half of the program, with music from Hilt, Child Pornography, Davenport Family, Jessica Bailiff, Throbbing Gristle, Anaksimandros, Bodyvehicle, Gang Wizard, Fursaxa, Bad Sector + Sshe Retina Stimulants, The Residents, Panther Skull and The Shadow Ring during the first half. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2807.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2807.mp3" length="262899248" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2807.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - June 21, 2007</title>
<description>This week, expect a rebroadcast of the February 08, 2007 spotlight on Volcano the Bear. This three-hour feature includes a wide variety of selections from the VTB repertoire, interview segments from a discussion with Aaron Moore, and an exclusive soundboard recording of a Volcano the Bear performance carried out in November of 2006.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2107.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2107.mp3" length="216139317" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2107.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - June 14, 2007</title>
<description>A spotlight on the Lal Lal Lal label and Avarus is to be heard during the second half of this week's edition, with selections from Islaja, Mel, Leather Nun, Raking Bombs, Serge Gainsbourg + Brigitte Bardot, Roxanne Jean Polise, Kukkiva Poliisi, Gang Wizard, NON, Xome, Doubled Yellow Swans, Shadow Ring, and Caroliner during the first. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun1407.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun1407.mp3" length="254666289" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun1407.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - June 7, 2007</title>
<description>An assortment of selections this week from artists such as Bryan Saunders, Cabinet of Natural Curiosities, Barrabarracuda, Fonik, Charles Cohen/Ed Wilcox, Mel, One, Jessica Bailiff, Embryo, Axolotl, Gang Wizard, Floating Mind, Anaksimandros, Blodyminded, O'Rourke/Merzbow/Giffoni, Ralph Gean, Lezet + Throuroof, If Thousands, and Volcano The Bear. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun0707.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun0707.mp3" length="258634810" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun0707.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - May 31, 2007</title>
<description>The second half of this week's program is a spotlight on Ralph Gean, while the first hour and a half of the show features music by Avarus, Charles C. Oldman, Jessica Bailiff, Herb Diamante, William Henshall, The Shadow Ring, Throbbing Gristle, Vodka Soap, No-Neck Blues Band, Grease Whore, The Residents, and Lambsbread. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may3107.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may3107.mp3" length="258209747" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may3107.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - May 24, 2007</title>
<description>Expect music this week from Ilitch, Smegma, P16.D4, Crawling Chaos, GHQ, New 7th Music, Non, Hair Police, Can't, Colleen, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Aufgehoben, Ellen Fullman, Merzbow/Giffoni/O'Rourke, Zack Kouns, Egypt is the Magick #, Lefthandeddecision, Dave Pike, Panicsville, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may2407.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may2407.mp3" length="252031891" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may2407.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - May 17, 2007</title>
<description>The second and third hours of this week's program are a spotlight on Aufgehoben, which includes exclusive segments from interviews with members Stephen Robinson and Gary Smith, and a selection from Aufgehoben's forthcoming 5th album. The first hour of this week's edition will include music by Herb Diamante, Family Underground, Ilitch, Ralph Gean, Curtains, The Franciscan Hobbies, The Bummer Road, Drunjus, The Poppy Family, and Smegma. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may1707.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may1707.mp3" length="256419836" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may1707.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - May 10, 2007</title>
<description>Music this week from Islaja, The Ghost Orchid, Brothers Of The Occult Sisterhood, Panicsville, Aufgehoben No Process vs. Gary Smith, Little Howlin' Wolf, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Envenomist, Smegma, Hair Police, Ilitch, David Jackman, Caroliner, Laughing Hands, Robedoor, Loopool, The Franciscan Hobbies, The Inside Of The Outside or the Outside of the Inside, Sunburned Hand Of The Man, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may1007.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may1007.mp3" length="254664408" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may1007.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - May 3, 2007</title>
<description>The second and third hours of this week's edition will feature a showcase on the Snatch Tapes label, while the first hour will include music from True Primes, Hair Police, Brothers Of The Occult Sisterhood, Dada X, Throbbing Gristle, Yuma Nora, Hematic Sunsets, Flower-Corsano Duo, Robedoor, and Ralph Gean. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may0307.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may0307.mp3" length="258145172" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may0307.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - April 26, 2007</title>
<description>The post wisdom teeth removal edition! Featuring selections by This Heat, Smegma, Jessica Bailiff, Throbbing Gristle, Debt Of Nature, Death In June, Clock DVA, Blowhole, The Inside Of The Outside, Stars Of The Lid, Sun City Girls, Zoviet France, Aufgehoben, Caroliner, Gang Wizard, Non, Sunburned Hand of the Man, Synth Jerkshop, Solid Eye, Panicsville and Vertonen, Varunna, and many, many others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2607.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2607.mp3" length="250784283" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2607.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - April 19, 2007</title>
<description>The first hour of the program will feature work by Caroliner, Non, Shadow Ring, The Nihilist Spasm Band, Throbbing Gristle, Ike Yard, Robedoor, Fursaxa, Aufgehoben, and Christina Kubisch. A two hour spotlight on the work of Smegma is to follow.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr1907.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr1907.mp3" length="251679552" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr1907.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - April 12, 2007</title>
<description>This week's edition presents work by artists such as Renaldo and the Loaf, Lefthandeddecision, Bunsenlamppu, Max Cloud, Sightings, Stars Of The Lid, NON, Smegma, Zack Kouns, Vibracathedral Orchestra, The Skaters, Terrestrial Tones, Maniacs Dream, Lezet, Aufgehoben, Can't, The Sailors, Nonhorse, Menstruation Sisters, Storm Bugs, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr1207.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr1207.mp3" length="258532619" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr1207.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - April 5, 2007</title>
<description>This week's edition presents selctions by Throbbing Gristle, Smegma, Stuart Powers, Temple of Bon Matin, Gang Wizard, Dylan Nyoukis, Hertta Lussu Assa, Charles C. Oldman, Sightings, Bloodyminded, Idea Fire Company, The Shadow Ring, Crawling Chaos, and Ashtray Navigations in the first half of the program and a spotlight on Zack Kouns during the second.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr0507.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr0507.mp3" length="254589802" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr0507.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - March 29, 2007</title>
<description>During this edtion, expect selections from Shadow Ring, Menstruation Sisters, Hair Police, Clear Horizon, Non, Sunburned Hand Of The Man, Nonhorse, Volcano the Bear, Excepter, The Brain Band, Christmas Decorations, Ryoji Ikeda + Carsten Nicolai, Jessica Rylan, Bloodyminded, Ralph Gean, Charalambides, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Max Cloud, Maniacs Dream, Caroliner, Religious Knives, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2907.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2907.mp3" length="212748405" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2907.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - March 22, 2007</title>
<description>A spotlight on the work of Crawling Chaos is to come during the second half of this week's edition, with music from SPK, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Aranos, John Rehberger, Non Toxique Lost, Quintron and Miss Pussycat, Fonik, Burning Star Core, Excepter, Frank Tovey and Boyd Rice, Charles Cohen and Ed Wilcox, Mouthus, and Solid Eye during the first. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2207.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2207.mp3" length="212458173" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2207.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - March 15, 2007</title>
<description>Selections this week from Crawling Chaos, Maniacs Dream, Ankh, Gang Wizard, Religious Knives, Lezet, Plastic Crimewave, Fursaxa, Charles Cohen and Ed Wilcox, Peter Thomas Sound Orchestra, Mika Vainio + Carsten Nicolai, Sun City Girls, Burning Star Core, Sword Heaven, The Frogs, Ghedalia Tazartes, Sunburned Hand of the Man, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Silvester Anfang, and many others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar1507.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar1507.mp3" length="218457937" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar1507.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - March 8, 2007</title>
<description>The FUN edition! Featuring gr00vy tracks from the likes of Francoise Hardy, Samabalanco Trio, Quintron and Miss Pussycat, Rod McKuen, Peter Wyngarde, DAF, The Frogs, Pete Rugulo + His Orchestra, Rodd Keith, Crawling Chaos, Bill Joy, Martin Denny, Volcano The Bear, Sheldon Allman, Neal Hefti, Joi Lansing, Dorothy, MSR Singers, Faust, Sri Darwin Gross, Dean Elliot, Sunburned Hand of the Man, Walter Wanderley, Esquivel, The Three Suns, The Residents, Coyle + Sharpe, Boyd Rice, Adele, and many others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0807.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0807.mp3" length="211063285" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0807.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - March 1, 2007</title>
<description>Music this week from Sun City Girls, Robotnics Crossing, Ptose, The Lost Domain, Throbbing Gristle, The Frogs, Death In June, Kaiser Nietzsche, Hair Police, Silvester Anfang, Smegma, Prick Decay, Gang Wizard, Toho Sara, Braspyreet, Sic Alps, Runzelstirn + Gurgelstock, Ames Sanglantes, Rodd Keith, and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0107.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0107.mp3" length="213133870" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0107.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - February 22, 2007</title>
<description>A spotlight on Jessica Rylan/Can't is to come during the second half of this week's edition, with music from Mr. Brinkman, Sculptress, Axolotl, Dadamah, Robert Rental, Volcano the Bear, George Liberace, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Lambsbread, Storm Bugs, Kemialliset Ystavat, Son of Earth, and Decaer Pinga during the first. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2207.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2207.mp3" length="209813199" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2207.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - February 15, 2007</title>
<description>Selections this week from Mark Tucker, Bomis Prendin, Volcano the Bear, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Mammal, And The Native Hipsters, Jessica Rylan, Blues Control, Axolotl, Vehikel + Gefaess, Jessica Bailiff, Lezet, Smashed Femur Dance Party, Spectre Folk, Evil Moisture + Macronympha, Kaiser Nietzsche, Silvester Anfang, Aarktica, Zack Kouns, Storm Bugs, and others. Listen for a chance to win a copy of the latest issue of Modern Drunkard Magazine! 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb1507.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb1507.mp3" length="212927973" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb1507.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - February 08, 2007</title>
<description>Expect a three hour spotlight on the work of Volcano the Bear this week, set to include a wide variety of selections from the VTB repertoire, interview segments from a discussion with Aaron Moore, and an exclusive soundboard recording of a Volcano the Bear performance carried out in November of 2006.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0807.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0807.mp3" length="216139317" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0807.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - February 01, 2007</title>
<description>Selections this week from The Shadow Ring, Telepathe, Axolotl, Snowsuit, Tar Pet, Panicsville, Rotten Piece, Metabolist, Grouper, Grease Whore, AEMAE, Air Conditioning, Nihilist Spasm Band, Gastric Female Reflex, Raccoo-oo-oon, Uncle Wiggly, Bryan Saunders, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0107.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0107.mp3" length="210641509" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0107.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - January 25, 2007</title>
<description>To come this week, a general assortment of selections for the first hour, with the second and third hours featuring music from folks scheduled to appear at this year's No Fun Fest, and interview segments with the man behind the festival, Carlos Giffoni. Expect tracks from Hilt, Tomu Tonttu, NON, Tommi Parko, Sunburned Hand of the Man, Excepter, Dave Phillips, Zach Kouns, Enema Syringe, Hair Police, Pedestrian Deposit, Nautical Almanac, Air Conditioning, Grunt/Sickness, Sissy Spacek, Gastric Female Reflex, The Rita, Evil Moisture, Mouthus/Axolotl, and many others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan2507.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan2507.mp3" length="212629389" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan2507.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - January 18, 2007</title>
<description>Music from Robert Rental, Pink Elephants, Can't, Zach Kouns, Volcano The Bear, Mouthus, Death In June, Clothilde, Alien Brains, AEMAE, The Futurians, Mammal, Factrix, Bryan Saunders, Kulkija, Gang Wizard, Smack Music 7, Excepter, and others in this week's edition. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1807.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1807.mp3" length="212984981" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1807.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - January 11, 2007</title>
<description>Expect a spotlight on the work of Bloodyminded to be heard during the second half of this week's program, with music from Volcano the Bear, To Live and Shave in L.A. 2, Blood Stereo, Brezel Goring, PGR, Karl's Empty Body, Sleep, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Colleen, Futurians, Gang Wizard, Pseudo Code, NON, Aufgehoben, and The Residents to come in the first. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1107.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1107.mp3" length="212044227" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1107.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - January 4, 2007</title>
<description>Memorable selections from 2006, with music from Excepter, Bloodyminded, Jessica Bailiff, Black Dice, Matmos, No-Neck Blues Band and Embryo, Charalambides, Gang Wizard, Volcano The Bear, Pan American, Axolotl, Sun City Girls, Zodiac Mountain, Loscil, Lambsbread, Black Happy Day, Aaron Dilloway, Dialing In, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan0407.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan0407.mp3" length="210483447" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan0407.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - December 28, 2006</title>
<description>This week will feature a spotlight on Axolotl with interview during the second half of the program. The first half will see music from And The Native Hipsters, Skaters, Lezet, The Vitamin B12, Zach Kouns, Blood Stereo, System Planning Korporation, The Guitars Unlimited Plus 7, Leslie Keffer, Forseti, Rubbish, Mouthus, Northern Song Dynasty, and Flies Inside The Sun.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2806.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2806.mp3" length="214912095" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2806.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - December 21, 2006</title>
<description>This week's program focuses on memorable selections released prior to 2006 which were heard on Collective Voice in the past 12 months. Anticipate work from Excepter, Minimal Man, The Elektrosoniks, Can't, The Sunburned Hand of the Man, To Live and Shave In LA, Un, The Early Worm, Gang Wizard, Volcano the Bear, Panicsville, Schwump, Crawling Chaos, Zoviet France, Quintron, Mr. Brinkman, Sun City Girls, Dennis Duck, Scorpion Wind, Jessica Bailiff, and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2106.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2106.mp3" length="211472011" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec2106.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - December 14, 2006</title>
<description>A spotlight on the work of Lily Frost will be featured during the second half of this week's program, with music from Aemae, Inquiet, Raionbashi, Richard Amp, Grouper, Svarte Greiner, Barrabarracuda, Coyle + Sharpe, Boyd Rice, Ville Moskiitto, Throbbing Gristle, Gang Wizard, and Vluba to be heard in the first hour and a half. Listen for a chance to win two discs from Brother Sister Records.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec1406.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec1406.mp3" length="212353103" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec1406.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - December 7, 2006</title>
<description>Selections this week from Gang Wizard, Witcyst, Raccoo-oo-oon, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Terrestrial Tones, Glenn Branca Ensemble, Hertta Lussu Assa, Y Pants, Steven R. Smith, Idea Fire Company, Terracid, With Throats as Fine as Needles, Xenis Emputae Travelling Band, Bill Joy, Michel Waisvisz, Ashtray Navigations, Tirath Singh Nirmala, Spine Scavenger, and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec0706.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec0706.mp3" length="211604181" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-dec0706.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - November 30, 2006</title>
<description>This week during the second half of the program, a spotlight on Stars of the Lid + Adam Wiltzie is set to air. The first portion will feature music from Jessica Bailiff, Michel Waisvisz, Xenis Emputae Travelling Band, Las Malas Amistades, Lambsbread, Cromagnon, Herbert Chappell, Woods, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Throbbing Gristle, Shit and Shine, Hertta Lussu Assa, The Shadow Ring, and Aemae. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov3006.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov3006.mp3" length="211604181" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov3006.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - November 23, 2006</title>
<description>Expect music this week from And The Native Hipsters, Lord Sun Son, Henrik Rylander, Jane, Shit and Shine, Sightings, Lily Frost, Cabinet of Natural Curiosities, Pan American, Dylan Nyoukis, Joanna, Hans Grusel's Krankenkabinet, Hototogisu, Polly Shang Kuan Band, Vibracathedral Orchestra, Elio Martusciello, Dialing In, and The Abrasion Ensemble. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov2306.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov2306.mp3" length="171931272" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov2306.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - November 16, 2006</title>
<description>A spotlight on Mark Nelson/Pan American is set to come during the second half of this edition, while the first half will feature music by Bloodyminded, Lemon Kittens, Munch, The Gerogerigegege, April March, Acid Mothers Afrirampo, Bitrate, Cabinet of Natural Curiosities, Throbbing Gristle, Burning Star Core, The Skaters, Mouthus, and Music Magicians. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov1606.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov1606.mp3" length="169343682" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov1606.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - November 9, 2006</title>
<description>Music this week from Monitor, Contrastate, Jasmine Dreame Wagner, Alvarius B, Gang Wizard, Excepter, Terracid, Lily Frost, Axolotl, No Doctors, No-Neck Blues Band, Dr. Gretchen's Musical Weightlifting Program, Hugh Le Caine, Quintron + Miss Pussycat, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0906.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0906.mp3" length="168072250" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0906.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - November 2, 2006</title>
<description>Look forward to selections from Dick Kent, Jessica Bailiff, Inquiet, Bitrate, Loscil, Throbbing Gristle, Pumice, Wolf Eyes, Gang Gang Dance, Bloodyminded, Axolotl, Omit, Wm. H. Arpaia + The Jerrymanders, Big City Orchestra, Crank Sturgeon, Sunburned Hand of the Man, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0206.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0206.mp3" length="166514934" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-nov0206.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - October 26, 2006</title>
<description>Expect a spotlight on Loscil to come during the second half of this week's program, with music during the first portion from The Avant Garde, Scott Jenerik + R. H.Y. Yau, Thomas Leer, Null, Gang wizard, Test Dept., Queen Meanie Puss, Crash Worship, Religious Knives, Jessica Bailiff, Gene Marshall, Windy and Carl, No-Neck Blues Band, and Labradford. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct2606.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct2606.mp3" length="172552359" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct2606.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - October 19, 2006</title>
<description>Music this week from Non, The Decades, Ryoji ikeda + Carsten Nicolai, Andy Ortmann, No-Neck Blues Band, Decayes, Burns, Norm + Singers, Christina Carter, Bomis Prendin, Excepter, Bloodyminded, COUM Transmissions, Loscil, Crawling Chaos, Keiji Haino + Tatsuya Yoshida, Wolf Eyes, Axolotl, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1906.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1906.mp3" length="169713158" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1906.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - October 12, 2006</title>
<description>The second and third hours of this week's edition will feature a spotlight on The No-Neck Blues Band, which will include an exclusive interview with member Dave Nuss. During the first hour, expect music from Schwump, Ashtray Navigations, Wolf Eyes, Lovely Midget, Inca Ore with Lemon Bear Orchestra, Faust, Birchville Cat Motel, Willie Klein, Matmos, and Bitrate. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1206.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1206.mp3" length="169801766" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct1206.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - October 5, 2006</title>
<description>Music this week from No-Neck Blues Band + Embryo, Oubliette, Boyd Rice, Bertin, Religious Knives, Bourbonese Qualk, Acoustic Guitar Trio, Panicsville, Loscil, Quintron + Miss Pussycat, Clear Spots, Wolf Eyes + John Wiese, Jessica Bailiff, Black Happy Day, Kjetil D Brandsdal + Jan Christian Kyvik, A Hawk and a Hacksaw, Inquiets, Alvarius B + Dylan Nyoukis, and others. </description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct0506.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct0506.mp3" length="181864313" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-oct0506.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - September 28, 2006</title>
<description>Tonight, a special showcase on the label Silber during the second and third hours of the program. The feature will include music by Vlor, Rollerball, Alan Sparhawk, Kobi, Remora/Clang Quartet, Goddakk, Peter Aldrich (featuring David Williams), Jamie Barnes, Black Happy Day, If Thousands, Plumerai, Aarktica, and Rivulets, along with interviews from Silber artists and friends of the label. During the first hour of this week's edition, expect selections from Death in June, Dylan Nyoukis, Picks and Lighters, Kjetil D Brandsdal, The Blue Humans, Lily Frost, Wooden Wand + the Vanishing Voice, Syd Barrett, COH, DAF, and Bloodyminded. </description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2806.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2806.mp3" length="175322171" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2806.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - September 21, 2006</title>
<description>Music this week derived from exclusively from various artist compilations, with selections from Christine Shields, Vagta Zo Hallot Kemek, Jason Bill and Jack Rose, John Duncan, Brume, The Whitefronts, Keiji Haino, Landed, Drekka, Kerosene, Flossie and the Unicorns, The One Ensemble of Daniel Padden, Spam All Stars, Daniel Johnston, Two Daughters, Crash Worship, Boyd Rice + Tiffany Anders, Vert, and others.  </description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2106.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2106.mp3" length="169803019" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep2106.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - September 14, 2006</title>
<description>Expect a spotlight on Jessica Bailiff during the second half of this week's edition, which will include segments from an exclusive interview. Music to come in the first hour and a half from Religious Knives, Swell Maps, Bloodyminded, Aline, COH, Dialing In, Possession, Volcano The Bear, and others. </description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep1406.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep1406.mp3" length="172495931" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep1406.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - September 7, 2006</title>
<description>A new edition with music from artists such as Black Happy Day, Non, Grease Whore, Sri Mersing, Excepter, Bertin, Bitrate, Charalambides, Michael Nace and the Nace Family, Arm, Matmos, Yuma Nora, Zoffy, Big City Orchestra + Deathranch, Sunburned Hand of the Man, Minimal Mecca, Black Dice + Wolf Eyes, Dialing In, Gina Dobra, and Repetition/Distract.  </description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep0706.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep0706.mp3" length="171875679" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-sep0706.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - August 31, 2006</title>
<description>This week's edition, the third and final installment of August's best of series, is a spotlight on Throbbing Gristle's Industrial Records label. </description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug3106.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug3106.mp3" length="127091775" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug3106.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - August 24, 2006</title>
<description>August's "best of" series continues, with previously featured spotlights on the works of No Doctors and Sightings this week.  </description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug2406.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug2406.mp3" length="167882915" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug2406.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - August 17, 2006</title>
<description>As the first part of this year's "best of" series, previously featured spotlights on the works of Panicsville and Black Dice are to come this week. </description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug1706.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug1706.mp3" length="174078324" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug1706.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - August 10, 2006</title>
<description>The second half of this week's edition is a spotlight on Charalambides, featuring musical selections from the Wholly Other family, and exclusive interview segments from a discussion with Tom Carter. Music during the first half of the broadcast from people such as Quintron and Miss Pussycat, Arthur Berkhoff, Phonophani, Ashtray Navigations, Coil, The Beast People, Lithops, and Burning Star Core, just to name a few. </description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug1006.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug1006.mp3" length="168773585" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug1006.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - August 3, 2006</title>
<description>Music this week from Mecanique Vegetale, Hugh Le Caine, Quintron, Zero Kama, Beehive and The Barracudas, Excepter, Steve Mackay and The Radon Ensemble, Spires That in the Sunset Rise, Alarmist, Vlor, Vrischika, Laurie Johnson, and Frango, amongst others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug0306.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug0306.mp3" length="167760034" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-aug0306.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - July 27, 2006</title>
<description>Look forward to a Deathbomb Arc showcase to come during the second portion of this week's edition. Music featured by Tender Buttons, Yuma Nora, Rose for Bodan, Friends Forever, Micose and the Mau Maus, Draught Yellow Swans, Gang Wizard, and Captain Ahab and others along with exclusive interview segments. Selections during the first half of the broadcast from folks such as Arthur Lyman, Excepter, Out Level, Meg the Sue, The Reformed Faction of Soviet France, Jessica Bailiff, Big City Orchestra, Bliss Blood, and No Doctors, amongst others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul2706.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul2706.mp3" length="171669207" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul2706.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - July 20, 2006</title>
<description>Music to come during this week's edition from Fad Gadget, Panicsville, Sir Julian, Giorgio Marauder and Luz Alibi, Dinosaurs With Horns, Psychic TV, Matmos, Dosdedos, Excepter, Friends Forever, The Threshold Houseboys Choir Under the Direction of Peter Christorpherson, Dopo, Peter Wright, To Live and Shave in L.A., Voice Crack, Don Kirsten, Alan Sparhawk, Sunburned Hand of the Man , and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul2006.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul2006.mp3" length="170526507" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul2006.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - July 13, 2006</title>
<description>This week, a special two-hour spotlight on Matmos with exclusive interview segments. Also, expect music from Richard H. Kirk, Danyyys, Jessica Bailiff, Le Forte Four, Vlor, Strap the Button, Lezet, and others during the first hour of the program. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul1306.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul1306.mp3" length="171613201" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul1306.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - July 6, 2006</title>
<description>Music featured during this week's edition from Throbbing Gristle, Human Head, Matmos, Brothers of the Occult Sisterhood, Birchville Cat Motel, Solid Eye, Mr Brinkman, Kevin Shields, Idea Fire Company, Sunburned Hand of the Man, Richard H. Kirk, Norbert Moslang, Total, KUT, and others.  
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul0606.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul0606.mp3" length="173539575" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jul0606.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - June 29, 2006</title>
<description>Expect music during the first half of this week's edition from artists such as This Heat, Replikants, Wolf Eyes, The Ursula Tree, Stella, Sunroof!, Deutsche Schaferhunde, and Friends of Leslie. The second half will be a feature on new music from Portugal, brought to you by Searching Records, with selections from Barcos, Fish + Sheep, PCF Moya, Dopo, Loosers, Ivone, and Frango, amongst others.   
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2906.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2906.mp3" length="167380110" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2906.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - June 22, 2006</title>
<description>This week, a rebroadcast of previously featured spotlights on the works of Excepter and Quintron and Miss Pussycat. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2206.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2206.mp3" length="174538318" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun2206.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - June 15, 2006</title>
<description>This week brings forth a spotlight on the works of J.G. Thirlwell, which will include musical selections of his composition, and exclusive interview segments. Also music to come from The Incredible String Band, Mr. Brinkman, The Legendary Pink Dots, Can't, Taiwan Death, Cousins Of Reggae, Matmos, Solid Eye, Doo-dooettes, and others in the first half of this week's edition. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun1506.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun1506.mp3" length="171748202" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun1506.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - June 8, 2006</title>
<description>Music this week from acts such as Death in June, The Legendary Stardust Cowboy, Forcefield, Matmos, Ovum, To Live and Shave in L.A., Can't, 45 Grave, Burning Star Core, Ceramic Hello, Charalambides, The Elektrosoniks, Cousins of Reggae, Windy and Carl, Vox Populi, In Gowan Ring, Sightings, and Kieran Hebden And Steve Reid, just to name a few. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun0806.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun0806.mp3" length="169939693" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun0806.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - June 1, 2006</title>
<description>This week's edition includes a spotlight on the work of Aaron Dilloway, with interview segments and audio works of his creation. Also, music to come from Graveyards, Volcano the Bear, Hartmut Geerken, Matmos, Masaki, Kreamy Lectric Santa, Guerra Pagan, Faust, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun0106.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun0106.mp3" length="173519512" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jun0106.mp3</guid>
			</item>


<item><title>Collective Voice - May 25, 2006</title>
<description>A standard edition this week with music from Kevin Harrison, Ash Castles On The Ghost Coast, Charalambides, Matmos, Aaron Dilloway, You've Got Foetus on Your Breath, Lithops, Trafficante, Hive Mind and Dead Brain, Kevin Coyne, Excepter, Pumice, Randy Thornton, Sunburned Hand of the Man, Simio Superior, If Thousands, Dennis Duck, Cara Stewart, and others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may2506.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may2506.mp3" length="173519512" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may2506.mp3</guid>
			</item>


<item><title>Collective Voice - May 18, 2006</title>
<description>This week, a spotlight on the work of Gang Wizard makes up the second half of the program, which will include exclusive musical selections from the band and a very special interview with Mike of Gang Wizard. Music to come in the first half from many others including Barcos, To Live and Shave In L.A., Pumice, Excepter, Masanka Sankayi, Un, The Beast People, and Tuxedomoon.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may1806.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may1806.mp3" length="173519512" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may18106.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - May 11, 2006</title>
<description>This week, a spotlight on the work of Gang Wizard makes up the second half of the program, which will include exclusive musical selections from the band and a very special interview with Mike of Gang Wizard. Music to come in the first half from many others including Barcos, To Live and Shave In L.A., Pumice, Excepter, Masanka Sankayi, Un, The Beast People, and Tuxedomoon. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may1106.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may1106.mp3" length="171615708" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may1106.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - May 4, 2006</title>
<description>During the later half of this edition, a spotlight on Sightings will feature not only many musical selections from the project, but exclusive interview segments with bassist Richard Hoffman as well. Aside from the aforementioned, music also to come from To Live and Shave in L.A., Fursaxa, No Doctors, Ralph Gean, Shadow Ring, Ryoji Ikeda, and Drift Yellow Swans, along with others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may0406.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may0406.mp3" length="172832806" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-may0406.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - April 27, 2006</title>
<description>Music this week from Excepter, Axolotl, Throbbing Gristle, Fat Worm Of Error, Noun Cocoon, Burning Star Core, Charalambides, Deficit des Annees Anterieures, The Cherry Point, Dagda Mor, Sick Llama, Spine Scavenger, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2706.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2706.mp3" length="167939757" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2706.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - April 20, 2006</title>
<description>A standard edition with selections to be heard by The Future, John Wiese, To Live and Shave in L.A., Sightings, Peter Ivers, Early Worm, Panicsville, Burning Star Core, Robert Babicz, Axolotl and The Skaters, Rubber O Cement and James Twig Harper, Flanged Confection, Factrix, Idiosycrasia, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2006.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2006.mp3" length="171469005" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr2006.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - April 6, 2006</title>
<description>During the later half of this week's edition, expect a feature on the work of Black Dice which includes music and an exclusive interview with Eric Copeland. Other selections as well from folks such as Piglatin, Factrix, To Live and Shave In L.A., Richard H. Kirk, The Shadow Ring, Solmania, and John Contreras + Nurse With Wound, are to come earlier in the program. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr0606.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr0606.mp3" length="170834543" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-apr0606.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - March 30, 2006</title>
<description>Expect tracks from Black Dice, Sprung aus den Wolken, National Disgrace, Jocy, Excepter, Sunburned Hand of the Man, No Doctors, Draught Yellow Swans, The Box, Skaters, Four Tet, Quartette Tres Bien, Charalambides, Fat Worm of Error, Fad Gadget, and Whitehouse in this edition. A feature (with music and interview) on the work of Black Dice is to come next week. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar3006.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar3006.mp3" length="167319923" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar3006.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - March 23, 2006</title>
<description>During the later half of this edition, a spotlight on Panicsville will feature not only many musical selections from the work of Andy Ortmann and company, but exclusive interview segments as well. Aside from the aforementioned, music also to come from Dearraindrop, LSD-march, Fat Worm of Error, Sick Llama, Edward Ka-Spel, Borbetomagus, Quintron, Zeena Parkins, Die Verspannten, and others. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2306.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2306.mp3" length="171896163" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar2306.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - March 16, 2006</title>
<description>Music in this week's edition by Matmos, Suckdog, Culturcide, Crank Sturgeon, Burning Star Core, Sunburned Hand of the Man, Spell, Michael Yonkers and the Mumbles, and as the last hour of this show is dedicated to artists appearing at this year's No fun Fest, Zeena Parkins + Ikue Mori, Lee Ranaldo, Sick Llama, Carlos Giffoni, and Daniel Menche, along with other artists and tracks. Tune in next week for a spotlight (with interview and music) on the work of Panicsville. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar1606.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar1606.mp3" length="170868815" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar1606.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - March 9, 2006</title>
<description>This week's Collective Voice includes a spotlight on the work Excepter, consisting of an interview and exclusive/rare tracks. Music also from folks such as Quintron and Miss Pussycat, Shadow Ring, Liz Allbee, John Wiese, Lily Frost, Aaron Dilloway + Prurient, The Tower Recordings, and Charalambides, along with much else. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0906.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0906.mp3" length="167930984" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0906.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - March 2, 2006</title>
<description>This time around, music from the likes of Smegma, M.V. Carbon, Panicsville, Liz Allbee, Metabolist, John Wiese, Volcano The Bear, Eyes and Arms of Smoke, The Screamers, and Mouthus and Valerie Allen, just to name a few. Next week's edition of Collective Voice will include a spotlight on the work of Excepter, containing an interview with John Fell Ryan, and plenty of previously unreleased Excepter tracks.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0206.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0206.mp3" length="168944949" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-mar0206.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - February 23, 2006</title>
<description>In the form of an artist spotlight, Collective Voice takes a look at the work Fursaxa during the second half of this week's edition, which includes many selections by Fursaxa and an interview with Tara Burke. The first half of the program will feature music from Little Fyodor, Monopoly Queen, The Tape-beatles, Gang Gang Dance, Skinny Puppy, Wolf Eyes, Ryoji Ikeda, Cristian Vogel, Dove Yellow Swans, Hair Police, This Heat, Volcano The Bear, and Current 93. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2306.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2306.mp3" length="171327735" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb2306.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - February 16, 2006</title>
<description>This week's program presents music by Monopoly Queen, Ritualistic School of Errors, Shockheaded Peters, Caroliner Rainbow Hernia Milk Queen, Taurpis Tula, SPK, Body Lovers, Crash Course in Science, and many others. Look forward to a spotlight feature during the second half of next week's broadcast.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb1606.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb1606.mp3" length="127496149" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb1606.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - February 9, 2006</title>
<description>This week brings an artist spotlight on Graham Bowers, which will include an interview conducted with Graham during this past January. Aside from many musical selections from Graham Bowers, also look forward to work by individuals and groups such as Excepter, Richard H. Kirk, Crash Course in Science, Konono nr.1, The Dead C, Renaldo + the Loaf, SPK, and Pan Sonic. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0906.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0906.mp3" length="127813066" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0906.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - February 2, 2006</title>
<description>Look forward to a standard edition this week, with music from Eau Claire, Tom Recchion, Richard H. Kirk, Excepter, Liz Brady, Pigbag, Gang wizard, Panicsville, Prurient, Gang Gang Dance, The Fridges, Dome, and Sunburned Hand of the Man, amongst many others. Next week's program will feature an artist spotlight on Graham Bowers. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0206.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0206.mp3" length="130300760" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-feb0206.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - January 26, 2006</title>
<description>The initial portion of this week's program will feature music from the likes of the No Neck Blues Band, Pope Paul Pot, Sun City Girls, Zoviet France, Eugenics Council, Taurpis Tula, Big Hair, Metalux, and Vibracathedral Orchestra. The second half is an artist spotlight on Sunburned Hand of the Man, which will include music from the band, along with an exclusive interview conducted earlier this month with Marc Orleans of Sunburned.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan2606.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan2606.mp3" length="130300760" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan2606.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - January 19, 2006</title>
<description>Tonight's broadcast is typical in nature, with much in the way of new music. Look forward to work by Sunburned Hand of the Man, Mammal, Kites, Crank Sturgeon, D Yellow Swans, The Legendary Pink Dots, Pre Fix, The Naffis, Graham Bowers, The Wardrobe, Ryoji Ikeda, Prurient, and Nurse With Wound.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1906.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1906.mp3" length="218136198" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1906.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - January 12, 2006</title>
<description>The first half of tonight's program will feature music from Harry Merry, Minimal Man, Cindytalk, Eau Claire, Cardiac Arrest, The Wardrobe, Edward Ka-Spel, My Fun, Graham Bowers, and others, while the second portion focuses on the work of Quintron and Miss Pussycat, and will include an interview conducted with the duo earlier this week. 
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1206.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1206.mp3" length="131200730" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan1206.mp3</guid>
			</item>

<item><title>Collective Voice - January 5, 2006</title>
<description>Tonight's program is an all-instrumental edition of Collective Voice, with music to come from Legendary Pink Dots, The Tower Recordings, Bomb 20, Human Hands, Jelly Roll Morton, Blowhole, Sunroof!, Chris Carter, Matmos, Volcano the Bear, Merzbow + Christoph Heemann, Bernard Permegiani, and Vox Populi, along with many others.
</description>       <link>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan0506.mp3</link>
			<enclosure url="http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan0506.mp3" length="127711190" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://www.collectivevoice.net/podcast/collectivevoicepodcast-jan0506.mp3</guid>
			</item>


		</channel>
	</rss>