<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/Version3/Audio/Readings.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>Janny Wurts, SF/Fantasy Excerpts</title>
    <description>Readings from the works of Janny Wurts, a published SF/Fantasy author.</description>
    <link>http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/Version3/Audio/Readings.rss</link>
    <category domain="">Science Fiction and Fantasy</category>
    <copyright>(c) Janny Wurts</copyright>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 6 Oct 2010 15:24:10 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 6 Oct 2010 15:23:22 -0400</pubDate>
    <webMaster>webmaster@paravia.com (Jeff Watson)</webMaster>
    <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.3.1) unlicensed version http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Stormwarden: Chapter 1</title>
      <description>For the first time in audio, the Cycle of Fire Trilogy, a stout and epic tale mixing sci-fi and fantasy by acclaimed author Janny Wurts. This classic fantasy trilogy follows three young people struggling to free the Stormwarden, the last of the elemental power-wielding Vaere sorcerers, so that he can battle the humanity-threatening demonkind. 
        
        Far in the future, a human-crewed starship crashes on a distant planet, carrying alien POWs taken to help discover the secrets of a deadly foe, the group mind known as the Gierj. In time, the humans revert to a feudal society, the aliens are seen as &quot;demons&quot;, and the starship&apos;s computer survives as a &quot;magical&quot; entity known as the Vaere. 
        
        In Book 1, Stormwarden, Anskiere, wizard of wind and water, binds the Mharg-demons with the aid of Ivan, master of fire and earth. But at the moment of his greatest peril, Ivan is betrayed and he swears a terrible oath against his betrayer - an oath so powerful that it begins a relentless &quot;cycle of fire&quot;.</description>
      <link>http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/AudibleBooks/Stormwarden.html</link>
      <category domain="">Cycle of Fire</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/Version3/Audio/StormwardenCh1.mp3" length="65857936" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16DDB984-94B2-440E-B059-23C9807B6F3E</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 6 Oct 2010 14:48:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <source url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/AudibleBooks/Stormwarden.html">http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/AudibleBooks/Stormwarden.html</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormed Fortress: Chapter 6</title>
      <description>Author Janny Wurts reads from her fantasy novel, Stormed Fortress, the closing book of Arc III, Alliance of Light. Though Athera may be free, the fight is far from over...
        The heartstopping conclusion to the Alliance of Light series brings Lysaer&apos;s army of Light to besiege the great citadel at Alestron.
        
        Master of Shadow, Arithon, with barely a moment&apos;s recuperation from his victory over the necromancers, has discovered that young Jeynsa s&apos;Valerient, whom he has sworn to protect, has joined the ranks of his disowned allies within the threatened citadel. Worse, following a failed rescue attempt, his beloved Elaira, his double Fionn Areth, and the spellbinder Dakar are also trapped within Alestron&apos;s walls.
        
        Arithon stands alone at the hour of reckoning as the true purpose of the Koriani enchantresses becomes, at long last, fully unveiled - with the covetous Prime Matriarch poised to snatch a prize, a prize beyond that of merely integrity and life...</description>
      <link>http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/StormedFortress.html</link>
      <category domain="">Cycle of Fire</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/Version3/Audio/StormedFortressCh6.mp3" length="25562771" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">B8F7131E-31F7-4772-8401-C4678C3B584F</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2008 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <source url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/StormedFortress.html">http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/StormedFortress.html</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormed Fortress: Chapter 6a</title>
      <description>Author Janny Wurts reads from her fantasy novel, Stormed Fortress, the closing book of Arc III, Alliance of Light. Though Athera may be free, the fight is far from over...
        The heartstopping conclusion to the Alliance of Light series brings Lysaer&apos;s army of Light to besiege the great citadel at Alestron.
        
        Master of Shadow, Arithon, with barely a moment&apos;s recuperation from his victory over the necromancers, has discovered that young Jeynsa s&apos;Valerient, whom he has sworn to protect, has joined the ranks of his disowned allies within the threatened citadel. Worse, following a failed rescue attempt, his beloved Elaira, his double Fionn Areth, and the spellbinder Dakar are also trapped within Alestron&apos;s walls.
        
        Arithon stands alone at the hour of reckoning as the true purpose of the Koriani enchantresses becomes, at long last, fully unveiled - with the covetous Prime Matriarch poised to snatch a prize, a prize beyond that of merely integrity and life...</description>
      <link>http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/StormedFortress.html</link>
      <category domain="">Cycle of Fire</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/Version3/Audio/StormedFortressCh6a.mp3" length="23462792" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">386C0811-D439-423C-B476-F562D1AE58A2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 6 Oct 2010 15:23:22 -0400</pubDate>
      <source url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/StormedFortress.html">http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/StormedFortress.html</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Ride Hell&apos;s Chasm: Chapter 1</title>
      <description>Author Janny Wurts reads chapter 1 from her fantasy novel, To Ride Hell&apos;s Chasm, a stand alone fantasy novel. The seed concept for To Ride Hell&apos;s Chasm is a thread played through a tapestry of intrigue and mystery: where does the right and true course of the warrior lie when the man bearing the sword and responsible knowledge must tread a collision course between the ethics of human justice and law – when not all things are as they appear, and the disappearance of a young princess catapults a small kingdom into a crisis beyond precident? Each individual character has their own insight and vision. Limited or experienced, their passionate views and their choices will either contribute or detract, with high stakes action and more than survival set on the outcome.</description>
      <link>http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/ToRideHellsChasm/ToRideHellsChasm.html</link>
      <category domain="">Wars of Light and Shadow</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/Version3/Audio/HellsChasmCh1.mp3" length="23584742" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">043D3C96-F67F-4B48-AA63-2E7CE4207B0B</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <source url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/ToRideHellsChasm/ToRideHellsChasm.html">http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/ToRideHellsChasm/ToRideHellsChasm.html</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Ride Hell&apos;s Chasm: Chapter 2</title>
      <description>Author Janny Wurts reads chapter 2 from her fantasy novel, To Ride Hell&apos;s Chasm, a stand alone fantasy novel. The seed concept for To Ride Hell&apos;s Chasm is a thread played through a tapestry of intrigue and mystery: where does the right and true course of the warrior lie when the man bearing the sword and responsible knowledge must tread a collision course between the ethics of human justice and law – when not all things are as they appear, and the disappearance of a young princess catapults a small kingdom into a crisis beyond precedent? Each individual character has their own insight and vision. Limited or experienced, their passionate views and their choices will either contribute or detract, with high stakes action and more than survival set on the outcome.</description>
      <link>http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/ToRideHellsChasm/ToRideHellsChasm.html</link>
      <category domain="">Wars of Light and Shadow</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/Version3/Audio/HellsChasmCh2.mp3" length="17175528" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36812CEE-9728-45C4-BCFA-3977FA45ED61</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <source url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/ToRideHellsChasm/ToRideHellsChasm.html">http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/ToRideHellsChasm/ToRideHellsChasm.html</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Ride Hell&apos;s Chasm: Chapter 3</title>
      <description>Author Janny Wurts reads chapter 3 from her fantasy novel, To Ride Hell&apos;s Chasm, a stand alone fantasy novel. The seed concept for To Ride Hell&apos;s Chasm is a thread played through a tapestry of intrigue and mystery: where does the right and true course of the warrior lie when the man bearing the sword and responsible knowledge must tread a collision course between the ethics of human justice and law – when not all things are as they appear, and the disappearance of a young princess catapults a small kingdom into a crisis beyond precedent? Each individual character has their own insight and vision. Limited or experienced, their passionate views and their choices will either contribute or detract, with high stakes action and more than survival set on the outcome.</description>
      <link>http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/ToRideHellsChasm/ToRideHellsChasm.html</link>
      <category domain="">Wars of Light and Shadow</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/Version3/Audio/HellsChasmCh3.mp3" length="18724503" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">F6B2E721-60BE-406C-83EA-747630BA9FEE</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <source url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/ToRideHellsChasm/ToRideHellsChasm.html">http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/ToRideHellsChasm/ToRideHellsChasm.html</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curse of the Mistwraith: Chapter 6</title>
      <description>Author Janny Wurts reads chapter 6 from her fantasy novel, Curse of the Mistwraith, the story which opens the first arc of her Wars of Light and Shadow series. A ruinous curse of war divides the loyalties of two half-brothers, one of whom commands the power of light, and the other, a musician and mage, who is gifted with mastery of shadow.</description>
      <link>http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/CurseOfTheMistwraith.html</link>
      <category domain="">Wars of Light and Shadow</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/Version3/Audio/CurseOfTheMistwraithCh6.mp3" length="32164294" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">A2D5FB75-B6B4-41D5-87A3-3C4E6D6895E2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <source url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/CurseOfTheMistwraith.html">http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/CurseOfTheMistwraith.html</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curse of the Mistwraith: Chapter 11</title>
      <description>Author Janny Wurts reads chapter 11 from her fantasy novel, Curse of the Mistwraith, the story which opens the first arc of her Wars of Light and Shadow series. A ruinous curse of war divides the loyalties of two half-brothers, one of whom commands the power of light, and the other, a musician and mage, who is gifted with mastery of shadow.</description>
      <link>http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/CurseOfTheMistwraith.html</link>
      <category domain="">Wars of Light and Shadow</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/Version3/Audio/CurseOfTheMistwraithCh11.mp3" length="38704312" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79096AE6-28ED-479D-AD85-9E24D31D64B6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <source url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/CurseOfTheMistwraith.html">http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/CurseOfTheMistwraith.html</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive Prince: Chapter 11</title>
      <description>Author Janny Wurts reads the chapter 11 from her fantasy novel, Fugitive Prince, the story which opens the Alliance of Light arc of her Wars of Light and Shadow series. A ruinous curse of war divides the loyalties of two half-brothers, one of whom commands the power of light, and the other, a musician and mage, who is gifted with mastery of shadow.</description>
      <link>http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/FugitivePrince.html</link>
      <category domain="">Wars of Light and Shadow</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/Version3/Audio/FugitivePrince.mp3" length="8301472" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">B3F58203-66C6-4EAE-A471-A1269A8E5539</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 1 Nov 2007 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <source url="http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/FugitivePrince.html">http://www.paravia.com/JannyWurts/website/Books/WoLaS/FugitivePrince.html</source>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
