<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><ttl>1440</ttl><title>ELT Podcast - Basic Conversations for EFL and ESL</title><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc</link><language>en-us</language><itunes:subtitle>Theme-based conversations and language practice for students of English, such as EFL, ESL and ESOL. The dialogs have two or more speakers. Read transcripts and listen to mp3 files.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:author>Robert Chartrand and Bill Pellowe</itunes:author><itunes:summary>Theme-based conversations and language practice for students of English, such as EFL, ESL and ESOL, at a beginner level. The dialogs have two or more speakers. Read transcripts and listen to mp3 files.</itunes:summary><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><description>Theme-based conversations and language practice for students of English, such as EFL, ESL and ESOL, at a beginner level. The dialogs have two or more speakers. Read transcripts and listen to mp3 files.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2007 05:28:34 GMT</pubDate><copyright>&#x2117; &amp; &#xA9; ELTpodcast.com</copyright><itunes:owner><itunes:name>Robert Chartrand and Bill Pellowe</itunes:name><itunes:email>podcast@eltpodcast.com</itunes:email></itunes:owner><itunes:image href="http://www.eltpodcast.com/images/cooleltpodcast300.jpg" /><image><url>http://www.eltpodcast.com/images/eltpodcastlogo_sm.gif</url><title>ELT Podcast</title><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc</link><width>144</width><height>40</height></image><itunes:category text="Education"><itunes:category text="Language Courses" /></itunes:category><item><title>Basic Conversations - Introductions</title><itunes:author>Robert Chartrand and Bill Pellowe</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Nice to meet you! An EFL lesson about introducing yourself.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>This is a basic introduction between two people. You will hear it three times: first at a regular speed, then at a slower speed, then at the regular speed again.

Robert: Hi, I&apos;m Robert Chartrand. 
Bill: Hi. I&apos;m Bill Pellowe. Nice to meet you. 
Robert: Nice to meet you, too. What do you do? 
Bill: I&apos;m a university teacher. How about you? 
Robert: Me too! What university do you teach at? 
Bill: I teach at Kinki University. And you? 
Robert: Oh, I teach at Kurume University. </itunes:summary><enclosure url="http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc1.mp3"  length="1036298"  type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc1.mp3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2007 10:35:39 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2:03</itunes:duration><itunes:keywords>ELT, EFL, ESL, learning English, English as a second language, English as a foreign language, ELT podcast</itunes:keywords><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc/introductions.html</link><description><![CDATA[This is a basic introduction between two people. You will hear it three times: first at a regular speed, then at a slower speed, then at the regular speed again.  Robert: Hi, I&apos;m Robert Chartrand.  Bill: Hi. I&apos;m Bill Pellowe. Nice to meet you.  Robert: Nice to meet you, too. What do you do?  Bill: I&apos;m a university teacher. How about you?  Robert: Me too! What university do you teach at?  Bill: I teach at Kinki University. And you?  Robert: Oh, I teach at Kurume University.]]></description></item><item><title>Basic Conversations - How long are you staying?</title><itunes:author>Robert Chartrand and Bill Pellowe</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>When are you leaving?</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Bill: Hi Robert! What&apos;s up?
Robert: I&apos;m going to the U.S. next week.
Bill: Oh, really? I didn&apos;t know that. Where are you going?
Robert: I&apos;m going to Tampa.
Bill: Where&apos;s that?
Robert: In Florida.
Bill: What are you going to do there?
Robert: I&apos;m going to visit my family. My grandmother lives there.
Bill: That sounds nice. When are you leaving?
Robert: On Saturday March 11th. 
Bill: How long are you staying?
Robert: A couple of weeks.

Let&apos;s practice.

Where are you going?
To Rock Island.
Where&apos;s that?
In Illinois.
When are you leaving?
On Monday February 2nd.
How long are you staying?
For a month.

Where are you going?
To Abbotsford.
Where&apos;s that?
In British Columbia, Canada.
When are you leaving?
On Thursday November 1st.
How long are you staying?
For four years.

Your turn... You answer... 
Where are you going?
Where&apos;s that?
When are you leaving?
How long are you staying there?</itunes:summary><enclosure url="http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc8.mp3"  length="2317248"  type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc8.mp3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2006 04:11:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>4:49</itunes:duration><itunes:keywords>ELT, EFL, ESL, English conversations, eikaiwa</itunes:keywords><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc/howlong.html</link><description><![CDATA[Bill: Hi Robert! What&apos;s up? Robert: I&apos;m going to the U.S. next week. Bill: Oh, really? I didn&apos;t know that. Where are you going? Robert: I&apos;m going to Tampa. Bill: Where&apos;s that? Robert: In Florida. Bill: What are you going to do there? Robert: I&apos;m going to visit my family. My grandmother lives there. Bill: That sounds nice. When are you leaving? Robert: On Saturday March 11th.  Bill: How long are you staying? Robert: A couple of weeks.  Let&apos;s practice.  Where are you going? To Rock Island. Where&apos;s that? In Illinois. When are you leaving? On Monday February 2nd. How long are you staying? For a month.  Where are you going? To Abbotsford. Where&apos;s that? In British Columbia, Canada. When are you leaving? On Thursday November 1st. How long are you staying? For four years.  Your turn... You answer...  Where are you going? Where&apos;s that? When are you leaving? How long are you staying there?]]></description></item><item><title>Basic Conversations - What kind of sports do you like?</title><itunes:author>Bill Pellowe and Robert Chartrand</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>I like soccer. A basic conversation for English students.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Bill: Robert, I have some tickets to the Hawks game. Do you want to go?
Robert: Not really, Bill. I don&apos;t like baseball.
Bill: Oh, do you like sports?
Robert: Yes, of course.
Bill: What kind of sports do you like?
Robert: I like soccer.
Bill: Well, that&apos;s the world&apos;s most popular sport.

Let&apos;s practice.
A: What kind of sports do you like?
B: I like soccer.

A: What kind of Japanese food do you like?
B: I like sushi.

A: What kind of books do you like?
B: I like Harry Potter.

A: What kind of movies do you like?
B: I like action movies.

A: What kind of cars do you like?
B: I like sports cars.

A: What kind of computers do you like?
B: I like Apple computers.

www.eltpodcast.com
</itunes:summary><enclosure url="http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc6.mp3"  length="1362239"  type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc6.mp3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2006 02:52:19 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2:44</itunes:duration><itunes:keywords>ELT, EFL, ESL, English conversations, eikaiwa</itunes:keywords><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc/whatkindof.html</link><description><![CDATA[Bill: Robert, I have some tickets to the Hawks game. Do you want to go? Robert: Not really, Bill. I don&apos;t like baseball. Bill: Oh, do you like sports? Robert: Yes, of course. Bill: What kind of sports do you like? Robert: I like soccer. Bill: Well, that&apos;s the world&apos;s most popular sport.  Let&apos;s practice. A: What kind of sports do you like? B: I like soccer.  A: What kind of Japanese food do you like? B: I like sushi.  A: What kind of books do you like? B: I like Harry Potter.  A: What kind of movies do you like? B: I like action movies.  A: What kind of cars do you like? B: I like sports cars.  A: What kind of computers do you like? B: I like Apple computers.  www.eltpodcast.com]]></description></item><item><title>Basic Conversations - The Weekend</title><itunes:author>Robert Chartrand and Bill Pellowe</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Did you have a nice weekend?</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>This is a basic conversation about the weekend. First, you&apos;ll hear it at a normal speed, then at a slower speed. Next, you&apos;ll hear some practice drills. Finally, you&apos;ll hear the conversation again at a normal speed. 

Robert: Good morning, Bill. How are you today?
Bill: Good morning, Robert. I&apos;m all right. How are you?
Robert: Pretty good. Did you have a nice weekend?
Bill: Not bad. I went to the movies on Saturday night.
Robert: Oh yeah? What did you see?
Bill: I saw the new Harry Potter movie.
Robert: Did you like it?
Bill: Yes, it was excellent!

Practice
A: I went to the movies.
B: Oh yeah? What did you see?

A: I went to a new restaurant.
B: Oh yeah? What did you eat?

A: I went shopping.
B: Oh yeah? What did you buy?

A: I went for a drive.
B: Oh yeah? Where did you go?</itunes:summary><enclosure url="http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc2.mp3"  length="1245194"  type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc2.mp3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2006 00:05:25 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2:30</itunes:duration><itunes:keywords>ELT, EFL, ESL, learn English, learning English, English as a second language, English as a foreign language, ELT podcast, dialog, transcript</itunes:keywords><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc/pastweekend.html</link><description><![CDATA[This is a basic conversation about the weekend. First, you&apos;ll hear it at a normal speed, then at a slower speed. Next, you&apos;ll hear some practice drills. Finally, you&apos;ll hear the conversation again at a normal speed.   Robert: Good morning, Bill. How are you today? Bill: Good morning, Robert. I&apos;m all right. How are you? Robert: Pretty good. Did you have a nice weekend? Bill: Not bad. I went to the movies on Saturday night. Robert: Oh yeah? What did you see? Bill: I saw the new Harry Potter movie. Robert: Did you like it? Bill: Yes, it was excellent!  Practice A: I went to the movies. B: Oh yeah? What did you see?  A: I went to a new restaurant. B: Oh yeah? What did you eat?  A: I went shopping. B: Oh yeah? What did you buy?  A: I went for a drive. B: Oh yeah? Where did you go?]]></description></item><item><title>Basic Conversations - Who did you talk to?</title><itunes:author>Robert Chartrand and Bill Pellowe</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>I talked to someone interesting yesterday.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Who did you talk to?

Robert: I talked to someone interesting yesterday.
Bill: Who did you talk to?
Robert: I can&apos;t remember his name, but I was sitting on the train...
Bill: Yeah...
Robert: ...and this young man started talking to me.
Bill: What did he say?
Robert: He said that he was from Thailand and he was studying here in Japan.
Bill: You mean he was a university student.
Robert: No, he was a high school student. He had a uniform on.
Bill: I see, so what did you talk about?
Robert: Well, he said that he enjoyed living in Japan, but he did not have much chance to speak in English.
Bill: How was his English?
Robert: Pretty good. So, he asked me if we could chat while sitting on the train.
Bill: That&apos;s interesting. It&apos;s not everyday that you meet a Thai student in Japan.
Robert: That&apos;s right.

Let&apos;s practice...

I saw someone interesting last week.
Who did you see?

I went somewhere fun last month.
Where did you go?

I ate something strange. I don&apos;t feel so good.
When did you eat it?

I read an interesting book.
What did you read?

I have to go to England next week.
Why do you have to go there?

www.eltpodcast.com</itunes:summary><enclosure url="http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc10.mp3"  length="2580096"  type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc10.mp3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2006 05:51:50 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>5:23</itunes:duration><itunes:keywords>ELT, EFL, ESL, English conversations, eikaiwa, reported speech</itunes:keywords><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc/whodidyou.html</link><description><![CDATA[Who did you talk to?  Robert: I talked to someone interesting yesterday. Bill: Who did you talk to? Robert: I can&apos;t remember his name, but I was sitting on the train... Bill: Yeah... Robert: ...and this young man started talking to me. Bill: What did he say? Robert: He said that he was from Thailand and he was studying here in Japan. Bill: You mean he was a university student. Robert: No, he was a high school student. He had a uniform on. Bill: I see, so what did you talk about? Robert: Well, he said that he enjoyed living in Japan, but he did not have much chance to speak in English. Bill: How was his English? Robert: Pretty good. So, he asked me if we could chat while sitting on the train. Bill: That&apos;s interesting. It&apos;s not everyday that you meet a Thai student in Japan. Robert: That&apos;s right.  Let&apos;s practice...  I saw someone interesting last week. Who did you see?  I went somewhere fun last month. Where did you go?  I ate something strange. I don&apos;t feel so good. When did you eat it?  I read an interesting book. What did you read?  I have to go to England next week. Why do you have to go there?  www.eltpodcast.com]]></description></item><item><title>Basic Conversations - Weekend plans</title><itunes:author>Robert Chartrand and Bill Pellowe</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Do you have any plans for this weekend?</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Weekend plans

Robert: Do you have any plans for this weekend?
Bill: I don&apos;t know. I might watch a video at home. And you?
Robert: I&apos;m going to meet some friends.
Bill: What are you going to do?
Robert: We might go sailing if the weather is nice.
Bill: Sailing, wow! Do you have a sailboat?
Robert: No, my friend has one. She goes sailing every weekend.

Let&apos;s practice.

A: We might go for a drive.
B: A drive, wow! Do you have a car?

A: We might go hunting.
B: Hunting, wow! Do you have a gun?

A: We might go surfing.
B: Surfing, wow! Do you have a surfboard?

A: We might buy a house.
B: A house, wow! Do you have enough money?

A: We might play some music.
B: Play music, wow! Do you have a band?

Your turn... You answer... 

What are going to wear tomorrow?
What are you are going eat for dinner?
Who are you going to meet later?
When are you going to go home?
Where are you going to go for your next vacation?
How are you going to go home?

www.eltpodcast.com</itunes:summary><enclosure url="http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc9.mp3"  length="2426880"  type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc9.mp3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2006 08:21:34 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>5:03</itunes:duration><itunes:keywords>ELT, EFL, ESL, English conversations, eikaiwa, weekend plans</itunes:keywords><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc/weekendplans.html</link><description><![CDATA[Weekend plans  Robert: Do you have any plans for this weekend? Bill: I don&apos;t know. I might watch a video at home. And you? Robert: I&apos;m going to meet some friends. Bill: What are you going to do? Robert: We might go sailing if the weather is nice. Bill: Sailing, wow! Do you have a sailboat? Robert: No, my friend has one. She goes sailing every weekend.  Let&apos;s practice.  A: We might go for a drive. B: A drive, wow! Do you have a car?  A: We might go hunting. B: Hunting, wow! Do you have a gun?  A: We might go surfing. B: Surfing, wow! Do you have a surfboard?  A: We might buy a house. B: A house, wow! Do you have enough money?  A: We might play some music. B: Play music, wow! Do you have a band?  Your turn... You answer...   What are going to wear tomorrow? What are you are going eat for dinner? Who are you going to meet later? When are you going to go home? Where are you going to go for your next vacation? How are you going to go home?  www.eltpodcast.com]]></description></item><item><title>Basic Conversations - How often do you go skiing?</title><itunes:author>Bill Pellowe and Robert Chartrand</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>About once a month</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>Bill: How was your weekend?
Robert: It was great. I went skiing.
Bill: How was it?
Robert: It was fun. Do you ski?
Bill: Yes.
Robert: You should come next time.
Bill: That sounds good. How often do you go skiing?
Robert: About once a month.

Let&apos;s Practice

A: I went to the movies.
B: How often do you go to the movies?
A: About twice a month.

A: I baked a cake.
B: How often do you bake cakes?
A: About once every two months.

A: I went running.
B: How often do you go running? 
A: About three times a week.

A: I had to work.
B: How often do you work? 
A: Five days a week.

A: I visited my parents.
B: How often do you visit your parents?
A: Once a year.

Find more at www.eltpodcast.com</itunes:summary><enclosure url="http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc7.mp3"  length="1369433"  type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc7.mp3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 00:46:04 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2:49</itunes:duration><itunes:keywords>ELT, EFL, ESL, English conversations, eikaiwa</itunes:keywords><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc/howoften.html</link><description><![CDATA[Bill: How was your weekend? Robert: It was great. I went skiing. Bill: How was it? Robert: It was fun. Do you ski? Bill: Yes. Robert: You should come next time. Bill: That sounds good. How often do you go skiing? Robert: About once a month.  Let&apos;s Practice  A: I went to the movies. B: How often do you go to the movies? A: About twice a month.  A: I baked a cake. B: How often do you bake cakes? A: About once every two months.  A: I went running. B: How often do you go running?  A: About three times a week.  A: I had to work. B: How often do you work?  A: Five days a week.  A: I visited my parents. B: How often do you visit your parents? A: Once a year.  Find more at www.eltpodcast.com]]></description></item><item><title>Basic Conversations - I do not know how</title><itunes:author>Robert Chartrand and Bill Pellowe</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>I want to go to the art museum. A basic conversation for English students.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>First, you&apos;ll hear this a basic conversation at a normal speed, then at a slower speed. Next, you&apos;ll hear some practice drills. Finally, you&apos;ll hear the conversation again at a normal speed. 

Robert: Hi Bill.  What&apos;s happening?
Bill:  Not much. How about you, Robert?
Robert: Well, actually, I want to go to the art museum this afternoon, but I don&apos;t know where it is.  Do you know where it is?
Bill: Which one? There are a few art museums in Fukuoka.
Robert: I want to see the Napoleon exhibit. Have you heard about it?
Bill:  Ah, sure. That&apos;s the Fukuoka Municipal Art Museum. It&apos;s in Ohori Park.
Robert: So, how do I get there?
Bill:  That&apos;s easy. Just take the subway to the Ohori Park station. Walk through the park, and it&apos;s there. You can&apos;t miss it!
Robert: Do you mean that I have to walk to the other side of the park to get to the musem?
Bill: Yes, that&apos;s right. It doesn&apos;t take long. About ten minutes or so.
Robert:  OK, I think I understand. Thanks.
Bill:  You&apos;re welcome.

Let&apos;s Practice:

A: I want to buy a suit, but I don&apos;t know where to shop. Do you know a good shop?
B: Yes, I like to buy suits at Fukuyama. You should go there.

A: I want to bake a cake, but I don&apos;t know how. Can you help me?
B: Sorry, I don&apos;t know how. You should buy a cook book.

A: I want to see a dentist, but I don&apos;t know who to see. Do you know a good dentist?
B: Yes, my dentist is good. I&apos;ll give you his number.

Find more at www.eltpodcast.com</itunes:summary><enclosure url="http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc5.m4a"  length="2553431"  type="audio/x-m4a" /><guid>http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc5.m4a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2006 07:27:44 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>5:05</itunes:duration><itunes:keywords>ELT, EFL, ESL, English conversations, eikaiwa</itunes:keywords><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc/knowhow.html</link><description><![CDATA[First, you&apos;ll hear this a basic conversation at a normal speed, then at a slower speed. Next, you&apos;ll hear some practice drills. Finally, you&apos;ll hear the conversation again at a normal speed.   Robert: Hi Bill. What&apos;s happening? Bill: Not much. How about you, Robert? Robert: Well, actually, I want to go to the art museum this afternoon, but I don&apos;t know where it is. Do you know where it is? Bill: Which one? There are a few art museums in Fukuoka. Robert: I want to see the Napoleon exhibit. Have you heard about it? Bill: Ah, sure. That&apos;s the Fukuoka Municipal Art Museum. It&apos;s in Ohori Park. Robert: So, how do I get there? Bill: That&apos;s easy. Just take the subway to the Ohori Park station. Walk through the park, and it&apos;s there. You can&apos;t miss it! Robert: Do you mean that I have to walk to the other side of the park to get to the musem? Bill: Yes, that&apos;s right. It doesn&apos;t take long. About ten minutes or so. Robert: OK, I think I understand. Thanks. Bill: You&apos;re welcome.  Let&apos;s Practice:  A: I want to buy a suit, but I don&apos;t know where to shop. Do you know a good shop? B: Yes, I like to buy suits at Fukuyama. You should go there.  A: I want to bake a cake, but I don&apos;t know how. Can you help me? B: Sorry, I don&apos;t know how. You should buy a cook book.  A: I want to see a dentist, but I don&apos;t know who to see. Do you know a good dentist? B: Yes, my dentist is good. I&apos;ll give you his number.  Find more at www.eltpodcast.com]]></description></item><item><title>Basic Conversations - Where do you usually go?</title><itunes:author>Robert Chartrand and Bill Pellowe</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Don&apos;t you want to spend Christmas in Canada? A basic conversation for English students.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>First, you&apos;ll hear a basic conversation at a normal speed, then at a slower speed. Next, you&apos;ll hear some practice drills. Finally, you&apos;ll hear the conversation again at a normal speed. 

Bill: Where do you usually go on your vacation, Robert?
Robert: I usually go to Canada in the summer.
Bill: What about the winter vacation?
Robert: I like to stay here in Japan in the winter. 
Bill: Don&apos;t you want to spend Christmas in Canada?
Robert: I do, but it&apos;s just too cold.
Bill: I know what you mean.

Practice

A: Where do you usually buy clothes?
B: I usually shop on the Internet.
A: Don&apos;t you want to try on the clothes first?

A: Where do you usually study?
B: I usually don&apos;t study much.
A: Don&apos;t you want to pass your tests?

A: Where do you usually go on the weekends?
B: I usually stay home.
A: Don&apos;t you want to go out?

A: Where do you usually eat lunch?
B: I usually eat lunch at a restaurant.
A: Don&apos;t you like the cafeteria?</itunes:summary><enclosure url="http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc4.m4a"  length="1464381"  type="audio/x-m4a" /><guid>http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc4.m4a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2006 07:16:07 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2:53</itunes:duration><itunes:keywords>ELT, EFL, ESL, English conversations, eikaiwa, winter vacation, summer vacation, usually</itunes:keywords><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc/onyourvacation.html</link><description><![CDATA[First, you&apos;ll hear a basic conversation at a normal speed, then at a slower speed. Next, you&apos;ll hear some practice drills. Finally, you&apos;ll hear the conversation again at a normal speed.   Bill: Where do you usually go on your vacation, Robert? Robert: I usually go to Canada in the summer. Bill: What about the winter vacation? Robert: I like to stay here in Japan in the winter.  Bill: Don&apos;t you want to spend Christmas in Canada? Robert: I do, but it&apos;s just too cold. Bill: I know what you mean.  Practice  A: Where do you usually buy clothes? B: I usually shop on the Internet. A: Don&apos;t you want to try on the clothes first?  A: Where do you usually study? B: I usually don&apos;t study much. A: Don&apos;t you want to pass your tests?  A: Where do you usually go on the weekends? B: I usually stay home. A: Don&apos;t you want to go out?  A: Where do you usually eat lunch? B: I usually eat lunch at a restaurant. A: Don&apos;t you like the cafeteria?]]></description></item><item><title>Basic Conversations - What are you reading?</title><itunes:author>Bill Pellowe and Robert Chartrand</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>How is it? A basic conversation for English students.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:summary>First, you&apos;ll hear this a basic conversation at a normal speed, then at a slower speed. Next, you&apos;ll hear some practice drills. Finally, you&apos;ll hear the conversation again at a normal speed. 

Bill: What are you reading?
Robert: A spy novel.
Bill: How is it?
Robert: It&apos;s good. Do you want to borrow it when I&apos;m finished?
Bill: Sure. Thanks.

Practice:
A: What are you eating?
B: A tuna sandwitch.
A: How is it?
B: It&apos;s delicious.

A: What are you listening to?
B: A podcast.
A: How is it?
B: It&apos;s great!

A: What are you watching?
B: A movie.
A: What movie?
B: I don&apos;t know.
A: How is it?
B: It&apos;s boring.

Find more at www.eltpodcast.com</itunes:summary><enclosure url="http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc3.m4a"  length="938913"  type="audio/x-m4a" /><guid>http://www.eltpodcast.com/audio/bc/eltbc3.m4a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2006 06:36:27 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>1:53</itunes:duration><itunes:keywords>ELT, EFL, ESL, English conversations, eikaiwa</itunes:keywords><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit><link>http://www.eltpodcast.com/archive/bc/whatareyou.html</link><description><![CDATA[First, you&apos;ll hear this a basic conversation at a normal speed, then at a slower speed. Next, you&apos;ll hear some practice drills. Finally, you&apos;ll hear the conversation again at a normal speed.   Bill: What are you reading? Robert: A spy novel. Bill: How is it? Robert: It&apos;s good. Do you want to borrow it when I&apos;m finished? Bill: Sure. Thanks.  Practice: A: What are you eating? B: A tuna sandwitch. A: How is it? B: It&apos;s delicious.  A: What are you listening to? B: A podcast. A: How is it? B: It&apos;s great!  A: What are you watching? B: A movie. A: What movie? B: I don&apos;t know. A: How is it? B: It&apos;s boring.  Find more at www.eltpodcast.com]]></description></item></channel></rss>