<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <copyright>LifePoint Church</copyright>
    <description>Discover helpful truths for life's issues through the free weekly audio teaching of LifePoint Church in Greenville SC. Enjoy Bible teaching that will encourage you and challenge you to grow deeper in your walk with God. Listen to these messages directly from your PC, or put them on your MP3 player and listen while you're on the go. See all our teaching at www.lifepointsc.org. (To subscribe to our Podcast, simply add http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/lifepoint_sermons.xml to your Podcast software. Or go to the iTunes Store and search for LifePoint Church Greenville SC.) If you're in the Greenville SC area, please stop by and visit with us!</description>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>Over the centuries, false doctrine has made its way into the church in many forms, and today there are millions of people being taught things that are absolutely untrue. Many people are told to pray to Mary, that she was sinless, that she is a co-savior with Christ, and even that she rose from the dead and ascended to heaven! How is it possible that churches can teach such things when there is not one verse in the entire Bible to verify these false claims? How did such lies make their way into the church, and what should our response be?</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/The_Corruption_of_the_Church_-_Part_2.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/The_Corruption_of_the_Church_-_Part_2.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-05-27T04:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>The Corruption of the Church - Part 2</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>When Jesus died on the cross, He opened the way for every believer to have direct access to God through Him. This new relationship was one of the foundational doctrines of the early church, but in 312 A.D. Emperor Constantine of Rome forced a system of lies into the church that completely distorted this biblical truth. Pastors were no longer seen as "Shepherds," but were renamed Priests and wore visually intimidating robes to elevate themselves above the common man. Church members were falsely told that they now had to go through a Priest in order to reach God, and this began the corruption of the church which continues to this very day!</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/The_Corruption_of_the_Church_-_Part_1.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/The_Corruption_of_the_Church_-_Part_1.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-05-20T04:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>The Corruption of the Church - Part 1</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>Church. We say that word all the time, but do we really know what it means? Is the church the building down on the corner? Is it really the "house of God?" Are there traditions that have been added to the church that are actually hindering its mission? Which issues are worth defending in the church and which ones are a waste of time? Join us as we peel back these layers, and many more, to discover some eye-opening truths and make sure we're being the kind of church Jesus intended from the start.</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Church_Its_Not_About_Buildings_and_Steeples.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Church_Its_Not_About_Buildings_and_Steeples.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-05-13T04:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Church: It's Not About Buildings and Steeples</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>Most of us who were raised in Christian circles will spend our entire life involved in the church to one degree or another. But what do we really know about the history of the church? Who started it, and why do we even bother being part of a 2,000-year-old organization, anyway? How has the church survived that long when most other organizations, and even entire nations, have long since failed and vanished from the face of the earth? Why are people willing to give their lives for the church, and exactly how big of a commitment should I be willing to make?</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Church_Whose_Idea_Was_This.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Church_Whose_Idea_Was_This.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-05-06T04:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Church: Whose Idea Was This?</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Reggie McNeal</author>
      <description>For far too long Christians have believed that if we could just get the people "out there" to come to our church, then we have accomplished the mission of the church. The more people who show up on Sunday, the more we think we're winning. Nothing could be further from the truth! In this powerful message, Reggie McNeal shows us that we're using the wrong scorecard, and reminds us that the church is not the destination, but rather the "connector" to get people where God really wants them to go.</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/The_Church_Is_Not_The_Destination.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/The_Church_Is_Not_The_Destination.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-04-29T04:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>The Church Is Not The Destination</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Various</author>
      <description>Starvation. Extreme poverty. Child slavery. Child prostitution. These are words that should not exist in any language. Yet they do exist, and for millions of people, these words are a daily reality. As the church, we have been called to not only help these people physically, but most importantly, to take the hope of Jesus Christ to them. LifePoint is committed to doing this locally as well as globally, and today we hear from two of our members who recently returned from touching the "untouchables" in India.</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/India_Mission_2012.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/India_Mission_2012.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-04-22T04:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>India Mission 2012</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>During World War II, men in a prisoner of war camp were radically changed when they saw an innocent soldier lay down his life to save theirs. Decades after that event, they still remembered that soldier and paid tribute to his selfless sacrifice. Join us for today's message as we pause to remember the ultimate sacrifice that was made for us when Jesus willingly laid down His life to save us. How has this great sacrifice affected you?</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Communion_04152012.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Communion_04152012.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-04-15T04:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Communion Service and Testimony</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>We have all done things in our lifetime that we know are wrong. Sadly, many people go through their entire life carrying the guilt and shame of things from their past, never feeling worthy, loved or accepted by God. But because Jesus died on the cross and rose again, we can break free from a life of guilt by receiving the forgiveness and grace He offers to us. Regardless of who you are or what you've done, God's grace is greater than all our sin, and you can receive that grace today!</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Grace_that_is_Greater_than_All_Our_Sin.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Grace_that_is_Greater_than_All_Our_Sin.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-04-08T04:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Grace that is Greater than All Our Sin</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>Someone once said, "I climbed the ladder of success, only to find when I reached the top that it was leaning against the wrong wall." How sad it would be to live your entire life chasing things that didn't matter in the end. The truth is, we're all pursuing something. How can we be sure the things we're pursuing will matter in eternity, or whether they will slip through our fingers like sand when life is over? Join us as we study the Book of Ecclesiastes to make sure we're living the life God intended!</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/How_to_Conclude_Your_Life_Well.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/How_to_Conclude_Your_Life_Well.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-04-01T04:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>How to Conclude Your Life Well</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>Someone once said, "I climbed the ladder of success, only to find when I reached the top that it was leaning against the wrong wall." How sad it would be to live your entire life chasing things that didn't matter in the end. The truth is, we're all pursuing something. How can we be sure the things we're pursuing will matter in eternity, or whether they will slip through our fingers like sand when life is over? Join us as we study the Book of Ecclesiastes to make sure we're living the life God intended!</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Remember_Your_Creator_While_There_is_Still_Time.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Remember_Your_Creator_While_There_is_Still_Time.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-03-25T04:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Remember Your Creator While There is Still Time</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>It's one thing to read books about faith and hear stories about other people's faith, but it's another thing entirely when God calls us to step out on faith! The fact is, we can't live on someone else's faith. There comes a time in each of our lives when we must decide to either step out into an impossible situation and trust God completely, or turn and go the other way. Are you content to live your entire life just hearing stories about great faith, or are you determined to step out for God and have stories of your own to share with your grandchildren? God is looking for people to step out and trust Him wherever He leads. Will you be one of those people?</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Crossing_Our_Jordan_Rivers_-_Part_2.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Crossing_Our_Jordan_Rivers_-_Part_2.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-03-18T04:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Crossing Our Jordan Rivers - Part 2</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>God's paths seldom make sense. Often in life God leads us straight into what looks like an impossible situation where even our best resources are not enough to get us through. This is how the Israelites felt when God led them to the banks of the Jordan River at flood stage and commanded them to step out into the water and go across! These moments are not obstacles, but opportunities to see God's power displayed! Are we willing to trust God to make a way where there is no way?</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Crossing_Our_Jordan_Rivers_-_Part_1.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Crossing_Our_Jordan_Rivers_-_Part_1.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-03-11T05:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Crossing Our Jordan Rivers - Part 1</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>Living a righteous life does not exempt us from suffering. In fact, the Bible says we often see the wicked getting what the righteous deserve, and the righteous getting what the wicked deserve. While this may leave us confused and unsettled, there is one thing we can know for sure -- that we are all in God's hands. Both the good times and the bad times of life are in God's hands and under His watchful care. Even though you may not be able to make sense of the circumstances in your life right now, you can take great comfort in knowing that God is holding you safely in His hands!</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Safe_in_the_Hands_of_God.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Safe_in_the_Hands_of_God.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-02-26T05:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Safe in the Hands of God</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>Whether we realize it or not, we will all leave some kind of monument after we die that others will remember us by. The Bible warns us how important it is for us to live in such a way that we will not only have a good name while we're alive, but that even after we're gone, our good name will linger on as a sweet fragrance to bless the lives of those who follow. Each day we live we're adding a new page to the memoir of our life. What are you writing on your page today, and what will be written on your tombstone when your life is over?</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/What_Will_Be_Written_on_Your_Tombstone.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/What_Will_Be_Written_on_Your_Tombstone.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-02-19T05:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>What Will Be Written on Your Tombstone?</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>Have you ever noticed how Sunday mornings can be the most frantic time of the week? After rushing to get the kids ready, cleaning up the spilled orange juice, leaving the house late (again) and racing across town just in time for the service to start... the first few songs go by and you realize you haven't given any thought to God at all. In this fast-paced world it's easy to allow our worship to become just another event, but God warns us that He despises heartless worship! Today's message is a reminder of the awesome God we serve, and that we must never allow our worship of Him to be treated casually.</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Stand_in_Awe_of_God.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Stand_in_Awe_of_God.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-02-12T05:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Stand in Awe of God</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>In a world filled with non-stop advertising telling us how to improve OUR finances, OUR career, OUR possessions, OUR lifestyle, etc., it requires constant diligence to remind ourselves that as followers of Christ, this life is NOT about us! The truth is, the more we gather for ourselves, the more enslaved we become. Real life and freedom can only be found when we give our lives away. So how do we rise above this temptation to live for ourselves and answer the call of Christ to live for the sake of others?</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Living_Life_for_the_Sake_of_Others.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Living_Life_for_the_Sake_of_Others.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-02-05T05:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Living Life for the Sake of Others</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>We all go through many different seasons in life. Some seasons bring laughter and comfort, while other seasons bring sorrow and pain. It is natural for us to pray and ask God to get us out of the difficult seasons as quickly as possible... but when we do, we fail to realize this vital principle: Whenever we choose to change God's timing, we're choosing to depart from God's plan. Does God have you in a season of life right now that you wish He would hurry up and get you out of? If so, we pray that this message will be a great encouragement to you!</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Trusting_God_in_the_Hard_Seasons_of_Life.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Trusting_God_in_the_Hard_Seasons_of_Life.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-01-29T05:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Trusting God in the Hard Seasons of Life</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>What do you think the richest, most popular, most successful man in history might say about life when he reached the end? The fact is, we don't have to wonder... we can know exactly what he said by reading the book of Ecclesiastes. Solomon had it all. He spared himself no pleasure and denied himself nothing his eyes saw. Yet he reached the end and summed it up by saying that he hated life, and all his pursuits were meaningless. Are the things you're chasing after going to matter in eternity, or will they run through your fingers like sand?</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Choose_Carefully_What_You_Chase_After_in_Life.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Choose_Carefully_What_You_Chase_After_in_Life.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-01-22T05:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Choose Carefully What You Chase After in Life</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>Phil Pike</author>
      <description>Someone once said, "I climbed the ladder of success, only to find when I reached the top that it was leaning against the wrong wall." How sad it would be to live your entire life chasing things that didn't matter in the end. The truth is, we're all pursuing something. How can we be sure the things we're pursuing will matter in eternity, or whether they will slip through our fingers like sand when life is over? Join us as we explore these questions, and many more, to make sure we're living the life God intended!</description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Does_Life_Feel_Like_an_Endless_Cycle.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/Does_Life_Feel_Like_an_Endless_Cycle.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-01-15T05:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>Does Life Feel Like an Endless Cycle?</title>
    </item>
    <item>
      <author>David Cline</author>
      <description>God is the Potter...you are the clay. He is the Artist...you are His workmanship. As His masterpiece in the making, God has re-created you with a divine design to help you find and fulfill your unique purpose for life. Join us today as we take a 'behind the scenes' look at this transformational process and discover how what He’s done and who you are will determine what you will do. </description>
      <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/In_the_Hands_of_the_Potter.mp3" />
      <link>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/In_the_Hands_of_the_Potter.mp3</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <pubDateParsed>2012-01-08T05:00:00</pubDateParsed>
      <title>In the Hands of the Potter</title>
    </item>
    <link>http://www.lifepointsc.org</link>
    <managingEditor>info@lifepointsc.org</managingEditor>
    <title>LifePoint Church Podcast</title>
    <webMaster>info@lifepointsc.org</webMaster>
    <image>
      <description>LifePoint Church Podcast</description>
      <height>144</height>
      <link>http://www.lifepointsc.org</link>
      <title>LifePoint Church, Greenville SC</title>
      <url>http://www.lifepointaudio.org/sermons/RSSLogo150.jpg</url>
      <width>144</width>
    </image>
    <language>en-us</language>
  </channel>
</rss>