<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
 
<channel>
<title>City Boy Records</title>
<link>http://www.myspace.com/cityboyrecordsUSA</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>&#x2117; &amp; &#xA9; 2009 Bruce Pegg</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle>A podcast featuring in-depth interviews and conversations with music professionals and news about City Boy Records</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>City Boy Records</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>The City Boy Records podcast features lively interviews and conversations about music and the music business with music professionals from around the world. It's also a great way to receive up-to-the-minute news about City Boy Records.</itunes:summary>
<description>The City Boy Records podcast features lively interviews and conversations about music and the music business with music professionals from around the world. It's also a great way to receive up-to-the-minute news about City Boy Records.</description>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>City Boy Records</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>cityboyrecords@ymail.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://www.cityboyrecords.biz/Site/Images/podcast.jpg"/>
<itunes:category text="Music"/>
 
<item>
<title>Episode 1: A Conversation with Glenn Williams</title>
<itunes:author>City Boy Records</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Bruce and Glenn discuss TKO Records, Japan</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In this, the first podcast from City Boy Records, Bruce Pegg, City Boy's founder and owner, talks to Glenn Williams, CEO of TKO Records, Japan. Along the way, the two discuss their lives in music, the current state of the music business, and TKO releases by Blah Blah, Ministry, Lisa Bouchelle and Obituary. The two also preview the forthcoming release of Tied to the Machine, the debut album on City Boy and TKO by Welsh alternative power rockers Circle of One.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.cityboyrecords.biz/Audio/CityBoyPodcast1.mp3"
length="58884934" type="audio/mpeh" />
<guid>http://www.cityboyrecords.biz/Audio/CityBoyPodcast1.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:01:20</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>music, indie, power rock, Circle of One, alternative, modern rock, K rock</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 2: Bruce interviews Julian and Rich Gardner from Circle of One</title>
<itunes:author>City Boy Records</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Julian and Rich Gardner of Circle of One preview their forthcoming album Tied to the Machine</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Bruce Pegg of City Boy interviews Julian and Rich Gardner of Circle of One about Tied to the Machine, their debut album on City Boy Records. The three discuss the band's influences, their creative process and the band's political philosophy. Additionally, they preview a number of tracks from the album and one brand new acoustic tune that can only be heard right here on the podcast</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.cityboyrecords.biz/Audio/CityBoyPodcast2.mp3"
length="61398957" type="audio/mpeh" />
<guid>http://www.cityboyrecords.biz/Audio/CityBoyPodcast2.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>42:34</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>music, indie, power rock, Circle of One, alternative, modern rock, K rock, Foo Fighters, Papa Roach, Styx</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 3: Bruce interviews Mike Harper and Chris "Suv" Lewis from Circle of One</title>
<itunes:author>City Boy Records</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Mike Harper and Chris "Suv" Lewis, the rhythm section of Circle of One discuss their new album, Tied to the Machine</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>In this, the second part of a two-part podcast, Bruce Pegg of City Boy interviews Mike Harper and Chris "Suv" Lewis, the rhythm section of Circle of One. Mike and Chris talk about how their musical careers began, how they joined Circle of One and how they contribute to the band's music and sound. The three also discuss the current music scene in South Wales and the UK, and how Circle of One are beginning to get noticed in the UK and beyond.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.cityboyrecords.biz/Audio/CityBoyPodcast3.mp3"
length="43417518" type="audio/mpeh" />
<guid>http://www.cityboyrecords.biz/Audio/CityBoyPodcast3.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2009 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>45:13</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>music, indie, power rock, Circle of One, alternative, modern rock, K rock, Foo Fighters, Papa Roach, Styx</itunes:keywords>
</item>
 
</channel>
</rss>
