<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!-- generator="wordpress/2.0.11" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
	xmlns:dtvmedia="http://participatoryculture.org/RSSModules/dtv/1.0"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

<channel>
	<title>Learn German | GermanPod101.com</title>
	<link>http://www.germanpod101.com</link>
	<description>Learn German with Free Podcasts Whether you are student or a seasoned speaker, our lessons offer something for everyone. We incorporate culture and current issues into each episode to give the most informative, both linguistically and culturally, podcasts possible.  For those of you with just the plane ride to prepare, check our survival phrase series at GermanPod101.com. One of these phrases just might turn your trip into the best one ever!</description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 08:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=2.0.11</generator>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<!-- podcast_generator="podPress/4.8" -->
		<copyright>&#xA9;GermanPod101.com 2003-2012</copyright>
		<managingEditor>contactus@germanpod101.com (GermanPod101.com)</managingEditor>
		<webMaster>contactus@germanpod101.com</webMaster>
		<category>Education: German</category>
		<ttl>1</ttl>
		<itunes:keywords>learn, german, language, culture, travel, germanpod101</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:subtitle>Learn German with free daily podcasts.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>GermanPod101.com is an innovative and fun way of learning the German language and culture at your own convenience and pace. Our language training system consists of free daily podcast audio lessons, video lessons, German Word of the Day, a premium learning center, and a vibrant user community. Stop by GermanPod101.com today for a Premium 7-Day Free Trial and Lifetime Account!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:category text="Education">
  <itunes:category text="Language Courses"/>
</itunes:category>
<itunes:category text="Education">
  <itunes:category text="Higher Education"/>
</itunes:category>
<itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
  <itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel"/>
</itunes:category>
		<itunes:owner>
			<itunes:name>GermanPod101.com</itunes:name>
			<itunes:email>contactus@germanpod101.com</itunes:email>
		</itunes:owner>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:image href="http://www.germanpod101.com/images/itunes_logo.jpg" />
		<image>
			<url>http://www.germanpod101.com/static/images/germanpod101/itunes_logo.jpg</url>
			<title>GermanPod101.com</title>
			<link>http://www.germanpod101.com</link>
			<width>144</width>
			<height>144</height>
		</image>
	<item>
		<title>News #80 - Win a 1-Year Premium Account when we hit 200 Million!</title>
		<description>We have big news for you, listener. If you were around in April of 2010, you&#8217;ll remember that we hit 100 million downloads. Well, guess what? That number is about to double very, very soon. We&#8217;re on track to deliver over 200 million lessons, which means only ONE thing&#8230;you&#8217;ve downloaded A LOT of lessons! As [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/06/03/news-80-win-a-1year-premium-account-when-we-hit-200-million/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/N_L80_060312_gpod101.mp3" length="4679403" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>We have big news for you, listener. If you were around in April of 2010, you&amp;rsquo;ll remember that we hit 100 million downloads. Well, guess ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>News</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>5:09</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/06/03/news-80-win-a-1year-premium-account-when-we-hit-200-million/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>News</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/06/03/news-80-win-a-1year-premium-account-when-we-hit-200-million/</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Upper Beginner #14 - There Are No Headaches With German Prefixes!</title>
		<description>Oh no! You woke up this morning and your head feels like a drummer has been using it for practice. It&#8217;s not a hangover, maybe a cold going around in Germany. You have to find relief, and quickly. A look in the medicine cabinet reveals that you have no more headache medicine left. You will [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/31/upper-beginner-14-there-are-no-headaches-with-german-prefixes/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/UB_S1L14_100610_gpod101.mp3" length="19515801" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Oh no! You woke up this morning and your head feels like a drummer has been using it for practice. It's not a hangover, maybe ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Joe: Hallo.
Apothekerin: Ja, bitte sehr?
Joe: Hmm, also ich habe Kopfschmerzen. Haben Sie etwas damit die Schmerzen weggehen?
Apo: Aber natürlich. Ich gebe Ihnen Tabletten. Die wirken sehr schnell gegen Kopfschmerzen.
Joe: Wie muss ich die Tabletten einnehmen?
Apo: Sie müssen die Tabletten in Wasser auflösen…
Joe: Hmm…aber ich möchte sie jetzt einnehmen…
Apo: Ach ja, natürlich. Dann gebe ich Ihnen andere Tabletten. Die können Sie mit etwas Wasser einnehmen.
Joe: Ah, super. Wie viel kosten die Tabletten?
Apo: Sie kosten 3,50 Euro.
Joe: Okay. Ich nehme sie.
Apo: Darf es noch etwas sein?
Joe: Wie bitte?
Apo: Möchten Sie sonst noch etwas?
Joe: Ja. Ich glaube, ich brauche ein paar Taschentücher.
Apo: Ja, gerne. War's das?
Joe: Wie bitte?
Apo: Ich meine, ist das alles?
Joe: Ja.
Apo: Gut, dann bekomme ich 3,50 Euro von Ihnen.
Joe: Äh... für alles zusammen?
Apo: Äh, ja…warum?
Joe: Aber… was ist mit den Taschentüchern?
Apo: Die Taschentücher bekommen Sie kostenlos mit dazu.
Joe: Oh, danke. … Hier bitte…
Apo: 4 Euro, danke…und 50 Cent zurück….Schönen Tag noch!
Joe: Danke schön!

----Formal English----

Joe: Hello
Pharmacist: Yes, can I help you?
Joe: Hmm, well I have a headache.  Do you have something that will make it go away?
Pharmacist: Of course.  I'll give you some tablets.  They take effect very quickly against headaches.
Joe: How do I take the tablets?
Pharmacist: You have to dissolve the tablets in water.
Joe: Hmm...but I would like to take them now.
Pharmacist: Oh, of course.  Then I'll give you other tablets.  These ones you can take with water.
Joe: Ah, super.  How much do the tablets cost?
Pharmacist: They cost 3 euros and 50 cents.
Joe: Okay, I'll take them.
Pharmacist: Is there anything else?
Joe: Sorry?
Pharmacist: Would you like something else?
Joe: Yes, I think I need a few tissues
Pharmacist: Great.  That's it?
Joe: Sorry?
Pharmacist: I mean is that all?
Joe: Yes.
Pharmacist: Good, then I'll get 3.50 from you.
Joe: Uh...for everything altogether?
Pharmacist: Uh, yes...why?
Joe: But...what about the tissues?
Pharmacist: You get the tissues included for free.
Joe: Oh, thanks.  Here you go.
Pharmacist: 4 euros, thanks...and 50 cents back.  Have a good day!
Joe: Thanks!

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Throwback Thursday</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>16:19</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/31/upper-beginner-14-there-are-no-headaches-with-german-prefixes/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Throwback Thursday</dc:subject><dc:subject>at the pharmacy</dc:subject><dc:subject>being sick</dc:subject><dc:subject>buying something</dc:subject><dc:subject>headache</dc:subject><dc:subject>medicine</dc:subject><dc:subject>pharmacies</dc:subject><dc:subject>verb prefixes</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Intermediate S4 #22 - A Visit to the German Police</title>
		<description>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! You&#8217;ve never been in the German police station before because you&#8217;ve never had a reason to. Crime is not that high so you were surprised when your phone was taken. Hopefully this is the first&#8230;and last visit to the police station!&#160;
In this German Intermediate lesson you will learn about the crimes [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/29/intermediate-s4-22-a-visit-to-the-german-police/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/I_S4L22_052912_gpod101.mp3" length="19375974" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! You've never been in the German police station before because you've never had a reason to. Crime is not that high ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Polizistin: Guten Tag, kann ich Ihnen helfen?
Joe: Ja, ich hoffe schon. Ich möchte einen Diebstahl melden.
Polizistin: Was wurde gestohlen?
Joe: Mein iPhone.
Polizistin: Und wissen Sie wo und wann?
Joe: Ja, das kann ich sogar sehr genau sagen. Es war gestern auf der Übersetzerkonferenz, während der Eröffnungsrede.
Polizistin: Gut. Ich werde jetzt einen Bericht verfassen. Können Sie bitte beschreiben, wie der Diebstahl ablief? Seien Sie so genau wie möglich.
Joe: Also, ich ging gestern auf die Übersetzerkonferenz. Zunächst meldete ich mich an. Dabei hatte ich das iPhone noch.
Polizistin: Woher wissen Sie, dass Sie das iPhone bei der Anmeldung noch hatten?
Joe: Es gab eine lange Schlange bei der Anmeldung, also vertrieb ich mir die Zeit mit Spielchen auf dem iPhone. Als ich an der Reihe war, steckte ich das iPhone in meine Jackentasche. 
Polizistin: Also ist es möglich, dass jemand das iPhone schon gestohlen hat, während Sie sich anmeldeten?
Joe: Ja. Dann nach der Anmeldung sagte man mir, dass ich einen Teil der Eröffnungsrede noch mitkriegen könnte, also lief ich ohne Umwege zum großen Saal, vielleicht 300 Meter. 
Polizistin: Trugen Sie dabei Ihre Jacke?
Joe: Ich hatte die Jacke nicht an, aber ich trug sie über den Arm.
Polizistin: Okay, fahren Sie fort. Wann haben Sie den Diebstahl bemerkt?
Joe: Also, ich stand vor den Türen des großen Saals und da hat mich eine Übersetzerin angesprochen. Wir unterhielten uns ein bißchen. Später wollten wir E-Mail Adressen austauschen. Dazu wollte ich mein iPhone aus der Jackentasche holen, und es war nicht mehr da.

----Formal English----

Police: Hello, can I help you?
Joe: Yes, I hope so. I'd like to report a theft.
Police: What was stolen?
Joe: My iPhone.
Police: Do you know where and when?
Joe: Yes, I can even say quite exactly. It was yesterday at the translator conference, during the opening speech.
Police: Good. I'll write a report now. Could you please describe how the theft happened? Be as exact as possible.
Joe: So, I went to the translator conference yesterday. First I registered myself. At that point I still had the iPhone. 
Police: How do you know that you still had it at the registration?
Joe: There was a long line up at registration, so I passed the time with games on the iPhone. As I came to the front, I put the iPhone in my jacket pocket.
Police: So it's possible that someone stole the iPhone while you registered?
Joe: Yes. Then after the registration, someone said that I could still catch part of the opening speech, so I walked directly to the large hall, perhaps 300 meters.
Police: Were you wearing your jacket during that time?
Joe: I didn't have the jacket on, but I carried it over my arm.
Police: Okay, continue. When did you notice the theft?
Joe: Well, I stood in front of the doors to the large hall, and a translator spoke to me. We talked with each other a bit. Later we wanted to exchange emails. For that, I wanted to take my iPhone out of the jacket pocket, and it wasn't there any more.

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Intermediate Season 4</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>15:24</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/29/intermediate-s4-22-a-visit-to-the-german-police/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Intermediate Season 4</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/29/intermediate-s4-22-a-visit-to-the-german-police/</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Survival Phrases #42 - Buying Phone Cards in Germany</title>
		<description>Learn German travel phrases with GermanPod101.com! A little German can go such a long way! Whether you&#8217;re traveling, visiting, or sightseeing, GermanPod101.com has all the essential travel phrases just for you! Today is no exception, as we&#8217;re going to uncover the mysteries of buying phone cards in Germany. Don&#8217;t you worry; it&#8217;s quite a simple [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/28/survival-phrases-42-buying-phone-cards-in-germany/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/S_S1L42_052812_gpod101.mp3" length="14334652" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Learn German travel phrases with GermanPod101.com! A little German can go such a long way! Whether you&amp;rsquo;re traveling, visiting, or sightseeing, GermanPod101.com has all the ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Haben Sie Telefonkarten?
Eine Telefonkarte für fünf Euro Euro bitte.
Eine Telefonkarte für zehn Euro bitte.
Gibt es eine Telefonzelle in der Nähe?

----Formal English----

Do you have telephone cards?
A 5 Euro telephone card please.
A 10 Euro telephone card please.
Is there a pay phone near here?

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Survival Phrases</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>8:02</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/28/survival-phrases-42-buying-phone-cards-in-germany/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Survival Phrases</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/28/survival-phrases-42-buying-phone-cards-in-germany/</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>News #79 - Countdown to 200 million and 6 new languages!</title>
		<description>The next two months will be pretty big. How big, you ask? Bigger than the Pretty Big Deal Sale. We’re talking 200 million big! Thanks to you listeners, over 170 million lessons have been downloaded to date. Can we hit 200 million by July? We need your help and once we hit the goal, there’s [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/27/news-79-countdown-to-200-million-and-6-new-languages/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/N_L79_052712_gpod101.mp3" length="3681483" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>The next two months will be pretty big. How big, you ask? Bigger than the Pretty Big Deal Sale. We’re talking 200 million big! Thanks ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>News</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>4:03</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/27/news-79-countdown-to-200-million-and-6-new-languages/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>News</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/27/news-79-countdown-to-200-million-and-6-new-languages/</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Upper Intermediate #16 - Is Your German Kaputt?</title>
		<description>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! Back at the office, you tell your German co-worker all about the experience. How you stood in line for so long, how you couldn&#8217;t get the automatic transfer to work, how you had to resort to paper forms&#8230; everything you can tell her in German, because you have been listening to [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/24/upper-intermediate-16-is-your-german-kaputt/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/UP_S1L16_101910_gpod101.mp3" length="17087195" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! Back at the office, you tell your German co-worker all about the experience. How you stood in line for so long, ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Bayer: Hallo Herr Jones… Ich habe Sie in der Mittagspause gar nicht in der Kantine gesehen…
Jones: Ja, das kann sein. Ich war bei der Bank. Ich musste lange am Automaten anstehen und als ich dann an der Reihe war, war der Automat kaputt!
Bayer: Oh, das ist ja ärgerlich!
Jones: Ja. Und dann musste ich die Überweisung mit so einem Überweisungsträger machen…..Haben Sie das schon einmal gemacht?
Bayer: Ja, aber erst ein paar Mal. Ich mache normalerweise immer alles per Online-Banking.
Jones: Hmm. Ja, als ich noch in den USA gelebt habe, habe ich auch viel Online-Banking gemacht…Vielleicht sollte ich das hier auch machen.
Bayer: Na, wenn Sie das nächste Mal zur Bank gehen, können Sie doch Online-Banking beantragen.
Jones: Ja, das werde ich tun. Ich muss eh morgen noch einmal dort hin.
Bayer: Haha, gehen Sie jeden Tag zur Bank?
Jones: Haha, nein. Mir ist aber erst als ich wieder hier war, eingefallen, dass ich ja auch noch einen Kontoauszug für diesen Monat holen muss.
Bayer: Ach so.
Jones: Und ich habe auch noch vergessen meine zweite Überweisung zu machen…
Bayer: Haha, der kaputte Automat hat Sie aber ganz schön durcheinander gebracht!

----Formal English----

Bayer: Hello Mr. Jones...I didn't see you at all in the lunchroom during lunch...
Jones: Yes, that's quite possible.  I was at the bank.  I had to wait in line for the bank machine, and then just as it was my turn, the machine broke!
Bayer: Oh, that's so annoying!
Jones: Yeah, and then I had to do a bank transfer with one of those bank transfer forms...Have you ever done that?
Bayer: Yes, but only a few times.  I normally do everything through online banking.
Jones: Hmm.  Yes, when I was still living in the USA, I also did a lot of online banking.  Maybe I should do that here too.
Bayer: Well, next time you go to the bank, you can sign up for online banking.
Jones: Yeah, I'll do that.  I have to go back there again tomorrow anyway.
Bayer: Haha, do you go to the bank every day?
Jones: Haha, no.  It just occurred to me once I got back here, that I still need to make a withdrawal for this month.
Bayer: Ahh, okay.
Jones: And I still forgot to do my second bank transfer...
Bayer: Haha, the broken bank machine really got you mixed up!

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Throwback Thursday</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>13:44</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/24/upper-intermediate-16-is-your-german-kaputt/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Throwback Thursday</dc:subject><dc:subject>  confusing words</dc:subject><dc:subject>  conjunctions</dc:subject><dc:subject>  lunch break</dc:subject><dc:subject>  office</dc:subject><dc:subject>  talking about an experience</dc:subject><dc:subject>  words</dc:subject><dc:subject>  work</dc:subject><dc:subject>  worktime</dc:subject><dc:subject>disambiguation</dc:subject><dc:subject>going to the bank</dc:subject><dc:subject>smalltalk</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Intermediate S4 #21 - Are the Trams Behaving in an un-German Way?</title>
		<description>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! The tram in Germany is your best mode of transportation but today the political parties have the road blocked. You have not done your research on what political party has the best values but at the moment, they are making your life a little harder by stopping the tram in its [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/22/intermediate-s4-21-are-the-trams-behaving-in-an-ungerman-way/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/I_S4L21_052212_gpod101.mp3" length="18510487" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! The tram in Germany is your best mode of transportation but today the political parties have the road blocked. You have ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Anke: Mann, wann kommt die Straßenbahn denn endlich!
Joe: Das frage ich mich auch. 
Anke: Wenn wir noch länger warten, hätten wir fast schon laufen können.
Joe: Eigentlich sollte alle zehn Minuten eine Straßenbahn kommen und jetzt stehen wir schon mehr als 15 Minuten hier. Ich weiß nicht, was heute los ist.
Anke: Ja, und hier hängt auch kein Zettel, dass es heute Probleme mit dem normalen Fahrplan gibt... 
Joe: Was sollen wir tun? Sollen wir ein Taxi nehmen?
Anke: Ein Taxi wäre am bequemsten, aber ich glaube, die U-Bahn reicht auch. Es gibt um diese Zeit immer viel Verkehr. Davon sind die U-Bahnen nicht betroffen. Vielleicht sind wir mit der U-Bahn sogar schneller da als mit dem Taxi.
Joe: Okay. Die U-Bahn ist auf jeden Fall besser als laufen.
Anke: Die nächste U-Bahn Haltestelle ist da links um die Ecke. 
Joe: Okay.
...
Anke: Oh, was ist denn da vorne los?
Joe: Lauter Polizisten...
Anke: Das ist eine Demonstration! Die ganze Straße ist abgesperrt! 
Joe: Ah, das erklärt, warum die Straßenbahn nicht gekommen ist.
Anke: Wow. So viele Menschen! Die Gewerkschaften und die Parteien sind vertreten...
Joe: Wofür demonstrieren die denn alle?
Anke: Die meisten Leute in dieser Menschenmenge demonstrieren für sicherere Energie.

----Formal English----

Anke: Man, is the tram ever going to get here?
Joe: I'm wondering that too.
Anke: If we wait any longer, we might as well have walked.
Joe: Actually, the trams are supposed to come every ten minutes, and we've already been here more than fifteen minutes. I don't know what's up today.
Anke: Yes, and there's no notice here that there are any problems with the normal schedule...
Joe: What should we do? Should we take a taxi?
Anke: A taxi would be the most comfortable, but I think the subway is sufficient. At this time there's always lots of traffic. The subway isn't affected by that. Maybe we'll be even faster on the subway than with a taxi.
Joe: Okay. The subway is better than walking, in any case.
Anke: The next subway station is to the left, around the corner.
Joe: Okay.
...
Anke: Oh, what's going on up ahead?
Joe: So many policemen...
Anke: That's a demonstration. The whole street is blocked!
Joe: Ah, that explains why the tram didn't come.
Anke: Wow, so many people! The unions and the political parties are here too...
Joe: What are they all demonstrating about?
Anke: Most people in this crowd are demonstrating for safer energy.

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Intermediate Season 4</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>15:01</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/22/intermediate-s4-21-are-the-trams-behaving-in-an-ungerman-way/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Intermediate Season 4</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/22/intermediate-s4-21-are-the-trams-behaving-in-an-ungerman-way/</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Survival Phrases #41 - A Guide to Foreign Exchange in Germany</title>
		<description>Learn German travel phrases with GermanPod101.com! A little German can go such a long way! Whether you&#8217;re traveling, visiting, or sightseeing, GermanPod101.com has all the essential travel phrases just for you!
Today we&#8217;re going to review some previous phrases, asking where to find a cash machine (ATM) or a bank and then we&#8217;re going to introduce [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/21/survival-phrases-41-a-guide-to-foreign-exchange-in-germany/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/S_S1L41_052112_gpod101.mp3" length="15945758" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Learn German travel phrases with GermanPod101.com! A little German can go such a long way! Whether you&amp;rsquo;re traveling, visiting, or sightseeing, GermanPod101.com has all the ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Gibt es einen Bankautomaten in der Nähe?
Gibt es eine Bank in der Nähe?
Wo kann ich Geld wechseln?
In kleinen Scheinen bitte.
Können Sie es bitte kleiner machen?

----Formal English----

Is there a cash machine (ATM) near here?
Is there a bank near here?
Where can I exchange currency?
Smaller denominations please.
Break this please.

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Survival Phrases</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>9:07</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/21/survival-phrases-41-a-guide-to-foreign-exchange-in-germany/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Survival Phrases</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/21/survival-phrases-41-a-guide-to-foreign-exchange-in-germany/</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Absolute Beginner #2 - To Live and Work in Germany, You Have to Start Here!</title>
		<description>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! You are flying to Berlin and know it will be a long flight. But who says you have to keep to yourself? You just have to wait for the right time to speak to the German man sitting next to you. Because it is polite in German to wait until an [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/17/absolute-beginner-2-to-live-and-work-in-germany-you-have-to-start-here/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/ABS_S1L2_011110_gpod101.mp3" length="9412276" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! You are flying to Berlin and know it will be a long flight. But who says you have to keep to ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101.com!
Go to Germanpod101.com, and get your FREE Lifetime Account.

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

D: Herr Cardigan...
A: Bitte nennen Sie mich nur Joe.
D: Also gut. Ich bin Anke. 
D: Joe, kommst du als Tourist nach Berlin oder beruflich?
A: Als Tourist. 
D: Und wie lange bleibst du?
A: Ich bleibe zwei Wochen.

----Formal English----

D: Mr Cardigan...
A: Please just call me Joe.
D: Alright. I am Anke.
D: Joe, are you coming to Berlin as a tourist or for business reasons?
A: As a tourist.
D: And how long are you staying?
A: I am staying two weeks.

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101.com!
Powered by InnovativeLanguage.com.</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Throwback Thursday</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>10:24</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/17/absolute-beginner-2-to-live-and-work-in-germany-you-have-to-start-here/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Throwback Thursday</dc:subject><dc:subject>  formal</dc:subject><dc:subject>introducing yourself</dc:subject><dc:subject>meeting new people</dc:subject><dc:subject>Polite</dc:subject><dc:subject>regular verbs</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Intermediate S4 #20 - Anke to the Rescue in Germany</title>
		<description>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! After losing your phone in Germany, your friend is helping you make a police report. Trying to remember the events leading up to losing it is important when talking to the police, kind of like getting your word order right so they can understand you!&#160;
In this German Intermediate lesson, you will [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/15/intermediate-s4-20-anke-to-the-rescue-in-germany/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/I_S4L20_051512_gpod101.mp3" length="18105943" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! After losing your phone in Germany, your friend is helping you make a police report. Trying to remember the events leading ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Anke: Anke Löwen.
Joe: Hallo Anke, hier ist Joe.
Anke: Hallo Joe. Du rufst nicht von deiner normalen Nummer aus an?
Joe: Nein, ich benutze mein Ersatzhandy. 
Anke: Bist du nicht gerade auf der Konferenz?
Joe: Doch. Aber ich hätte gern deine Meinung zu etwas... 
Anke: Ja?
Joe: Ich habe gerade meine Mails gecheckt und da war eine Nachricht von meinem Telefonanbieter, dass ich mein Guthaben verbraucht habe und wieder aufladen muss.
Anke: Ja und?
Joe: Ich habe gestern früh mein iPhone verloren und die Mail ist von heute Mittag. Es ist möglich, dass sie die Mail einfach sehr spät verschickt haben...
Anke: Joe, diese Mails gehen wahrscheinlich automatisch raus. Ich denke, dass jemand dein Handy hat und seit gestern auf deine Kosten telefoniert. Deshalb hast du heute die Nachricht gekriegt.
Joe: Du meinst, jemand hat es geklaut?
Anke: Na ja, entweder er hat es geklaut, oder er hat es gefunden und dir nicht zurückgegeben. Es kommt auf das Gleiche hinaus.
Joe: Sch... ! Was mache ich jetzt?
Anke: Also ich würde zur Polizei gehen, und ihnen den Diebstahl melden. Wenn du willst, komme ich mit.
Joe: Mensch, Anke, das wäre super nett von dir! 
Anke: Im Moment ist die Innenstadt voll, also werde ich nicht mit dem Auto fahren. Treffen wir uns an der Straßenbahnhaltestelle vor dem Konferenzgebäude? In einer halben Stunde?
Joe: Ja, geht klar. Vielen Dank!
Anke: Kein Problem.

----Formal English----

Anke: Anke Löwen.
Joe: Hello Anke, this is Joe.
Anke: Hello Joe. You're not calling me from your normal number?
Joe: No, I'm using my spare phone.
Anke: Aren't you at the conference right now?
Joe: That's right, I am. But I'd like your opinion on something...
Anke: Yes?
Joe: I just checked my email and there was a message from my phone service provider saying that I used up my credit and I have to refill it.
Anke: Yes, and?
Joe: I lost my iPhone yesterday morning and the message is from noon today. It's possible that they just sent the message really late...
Anke: Joe, these emails are probably sent out automatically. I think that someone has your phone and has been calling on your dime since yesterday. That's why you got the message today.
Joe: You think someone stole it?
Anke: Well, either he stole it, or he found it and didn't give it back. It's the same result either way.
Joe: Sh...! What do I do now?
Anke: Well I would go to the police and report the theft to them. If you want, I'll come with you.
Joe: Man, Anke, that would be really nice of you!
Anke: At the moment, the inner city is full, so I won't take the car. Shall we meet at the tram stop in front of the conference building? In a half hour?
Joe: Yes, alright. Thanks a lot!
Anke: No problem.

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Intermediate Season 4</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>14:57</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/15/intermediate-s4-20-anke-to-the-rescue-in-germany/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Intermediate Season 4</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/15/intermediate-s4-20-anke-to-the-rescue-in-germany/</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Survival Phrases #40 - Using the Post Office in Germany Part II</title>
		<description>Learn German travel phrases with GermanPod101.com! A little German can go such a long way! Whether you&#8217;re traveling, visiting, or sightseeing, GermanPod101.com has all the essential travel phrases just for you!  As we&#8217;re covering the second part of the post office series, we&#8217;ll introduce you to some useful phrases when it comes to sending [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/14/survival-phrases-40-using-the-post-office-in-germany-part-ii/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/S_S1L40_051412_gpod101.mp3" length="9942653" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Learn German travel phrases with GermanPod101.com! A little German can go such a long way! Whether you&amp;rsquo;re traveling, visiting, or sightseeing, GermanPod101.com has all the ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Ich möchte das nach Vancouver schicken.
Was beinhaltet das Paket?
Was ist im Paket drin?

----Formal English----

I would like to send this to Vancouver.
What does the package contain?
What’s in the package?

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Survival Phrases</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>5:36</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/14/survival-phrases-40-using-the-post-office-in-germany-part-ii/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Survival Phrases</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/14/survival-phrases-40-using-the-post-office-in-germany-part-ii/</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>News #78 - German Is A Pretty Big Deal</title>
		<description>Knowing German is a pretty big deal. And we don’t mean knowing just words and phrases. We mean hopping on a plane to Germany, reading German signs, ordering at restaurants, and striking up conversations with German speaking people along the way. That’s a pretty big deal, which, despite what many say, can be done by [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/13/news-78-german-is-a-pretty-big-deal/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/N_L78_051312_gpod101.mp3" length="5370975" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Knowing German is a pretty big deal. And we don’t mean knowing just words and phrases. We mean hopping on a plane to Germany, reading ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>News</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>3:58</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/13/news-78-german-is-a-pretty-big-deal/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>News</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/13/news-78-german-is-a-pretty-big-deal/</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Advanced Audio Blog S3 #5 - Are You Addicted to German Bread and Rolls?</title>
		<description>Today Sarah talks about a problem many Germans face when going abroad: bread and rolls. German breads and rolls are totally unlike their American, British or even French equivalents, so that many Germans are showing withdrawal symptoms when on holiday unless they were forewarned and brought some good old German &#8220;grey bread&#8221; (wholegrain bread) or [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/10/advanced-audio-blog-s3-5-are-you-addicted-to-german-bread-and-rolls/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/AB_S3L5_021210_gpod101.mp3" length="2898222" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Today Sarah talks about a problem many Germans face when going abroad: bread and rolls. German breads and rolls are totally unlike their American, British ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Was fängt mit „B“ an und kommt bei uns Deutschen morgens, mittags und abends auf den Tisch? Nein! Nicht Bier! Brot! Die Amerikaner haben ihre Cornflakes, die Briten ihre Würstchen und die Deutschen ihr Brot.

Ja, wir Deutschen sind eindeutig die Brotweltmeister. Ob aus Roggen oder Weizen, mit Leinsamen, Sonnenblumenkernen oder Mohn – in deutschen Bäckereien gibt es Brotlaibe in den verschiedensten Arten.

Während viele Menschen zum Frühstück gerne die süße Variante mit Marmelade oder Nougatcreme (Nutella) essen, werden das Pausenbrot am Mittag oder das Abendbrot am Abend eher mit verschiedenen Wurst- und Käsesorten belegt.

Außer dem dunklen Vollkornbrot sind in Deutschland auch Brötchen sehr beliebt. Vor allem beim gemütlichen Frühstück am Wochenende dürfen frische Brötchen vom Bäcker nicht fehlen. Doch aufgepasst! Die Zubereitung will gelernt sein. Meine Freundin Bianca hat mir letztens von einem japanischen Freund erzählt, der Brötchen statt waagerecht in zwei flache Hälften, senkrecht in der Mitte durchschnitt und sich dann wunderte, dass das Brötchen so schwer zu belegen war. Tja, so lecker Brötchen auch sind, so schwer kann es sein, ein Brötchen zu schmieren!

Aber zugegeben, wir machen es anderen Nationen auch ganz schön schwer, wenn es um Brötchen geht. Das fängt beim Schneiden an und hört bei der Bezeichnung auf. Während der Berliner „Schrippe“ sagt, kauft man in Bayern „Semmeln“ und in Hessen „Wecken“.  Kein Wunder, dass man da verwirrt ist! 

Und kein Wunder, dass andere Nationen die Deutschen für verrückt halten! Als ich in den USA gelebt habe, hatten meine amerikanischen Mitbewohner einen liebevollen Spitznamen für mich - &quot;crazy German girl that eats too much bread&quot;… Tja, was soll ich dazu sagen…Hallo alle zusammen, mein Name ist Sarah und ich bin brotsüchtig.

----Formal English----

What starts with &quot;B&quot; and can be found on German tables in the morning, around noon and in the evening? No! Not beer! Bread! Americans have cornflakes, Brits have sausages, and Germans have bread.

Yes, we Germans are clearly the world champions of bread. Whether rye or wheat, with flaxseed, sunflower seeds or poppy seed - in German bakeries there are loafs of bread of many different types.

While many people like to eat the sweet kind with jam or nougat creme (Nutella) for breakfast, the sandwich for lunch break or the bread for supper are rather topped with different types of lunchmeat or cheese.

Apart from the dark wholemeal bread, rolls are also very popular in Germany. Fresh rolls from the baker especially must not be missing when you're having a nice comfy breakfast on the weekend. But beware! You have to master the preparation. My friend Bianca recently told me about a Japanese friend, who cut the roll vertically in the middle rather than horizontally in two flat halves, and was then surprised to find that it was difficult to put anything on the roll. Well, as yummy as rolls are, as difficult it can be to spread something on it!

Though admittedly we aren't making it easy for other nations, when it comes to rolls. From the cutting to the term that is used for a roll, everything is difficult. While the Berliner calls it &quot;Schrippe&quot;, you buy &quot;Semmeln&quot; in Bavaria, and &quot;Wecken&quot; in Hessia. No wonder people are confused!

And no wonder that other nations think that Germans are crazy! When I lived in the USA, my American flatmates had an affectionate nickname for me - &quot;crazy German girl that eats too much bread&quot;... Well, what can I say... Hello everybody, my name is Sarah and I am addicted to bread.

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forge [...]</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Throwback Thursday</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>6:47</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/10/advanced-audio-blog-s3-5-are-you-addicted-to-german-bread-and-rolls/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Throwback Thursday</dc:subject><dc:subject>     bakery</dc:subject><dc:subject>     bread</dc:subject><dc:subject>     rolls</dc:subject><dc:subject>     talking about bakery goods</dc:subject><dc:subject>baking</dc:subject><dc:subject>talking about baking</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Intermediate S4 #19 - An Intriguing German Job Offer</title>
		<description>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! You were just approached in Germany with a job offer, all because someone heard you speak about your skills. You might take the job considering you need to fill your time up with something while in Germany. Besides, you&#8217;ve never been approached with a job&#8212;you&#8217;re wanted!&#160;
In this German Intermediate lesson you [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/08/intermediate-s4-19-an-intriguing-german-job-offer/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/I_S4L19_050812_gpod101.mp3" length="22725014" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Learn German with GermanPod101.com! You were just approached in Germany with a job offer, all because someone heard you speak about your skills. You might ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Birke: Sie arbeiten nicht gern, wenn Sie in Deutschland sind? Das sollten Sie ändern.
Joe: Wozu? Ich bin nie lange hier. Ich möchte meinen Urlaub genießen.
Birke: Ich habe mich noch nicht vorgestellt. Mein Name ist Birke Pfarrer, ich arbeite in der Personalabteilung von Berlin Translated.
Joe: Ah, angenehm Sie kennen zu lernen.
Birke: Mir hat ihr Vortrag eben wirklich gut gefallen, und ich denke, wir könnten Sie gebrauchen.
Joe: Entschuldigung... wovon reden Sie?
Birke: Ich meine, wir könnten Ihnen vielleicht eine Stelle anbieten. Also natürlich müssten Sie sich noch bewerben, aber ich denke, dass Sie qualifiziert sind.
Joe: Ich bin mir nicht sicher, ob ich wieder eine feste Stelle haben oder weiter freiberuflich arbeiten möchte.
Birke: Ja, es gibt ein paar Dinge, über die wir sprechen müssten...
Joe: Worüber müssen wir sprechen?
Birke: Na, zum Beispiel darüber, warum Sie Ihren alten Job aufgegeben haben. Und auch über das Visum und so.
Joe: Ja. Woran würde ich bei Ihnen arbeiten?
Birke: Hauptsächlich an Webseiten. Wenn es da mal nichts zu tun gibt, können wir sehen, wofür Sie sich sonst interessieren.
Joe: Klingt gut. Und ist Ihr Büro in Berlin?
Birke: Ja. Die Hauptstelle ist in Berlin und wir haben auch Niederlassungen in Dresden und Nürnberg.

----Formal English----

Birke: You don't like to work when you're in Germany? You should change that.
Joe: What for? I'm never here for long. I'd like to enjoy my vacation.
Birke: I haven't introduced myself yet. My name is Birke Pfarrer, I work in the personnel department of Berlin Translated.
Joe: Ah, pleased to meet you.
Birke: I really enjoyed your lecture, and I think we could use you.
Joe: Excuse me... what are you talking about?
Birke: I think we could possibly offer you a position. Naturally you'd have to apply, but I think that you're qualified.
Joe: I'm not sure whether I want a permanent position, or if I want to continue working as a freelancer.
Birke: Yes, there are a few things that we would need to discuss...
Joe: What do we need to talk about?
Birke: Well, for example, why you left your old job. And also about the work visa and things like that.
Joe: Yes. What would I work on, with you?
Birke: Mainly on websites. If there's nothing to do there, then we can see what else you're interested in.
Joe: Sounds good. And is your office in Berlin?
Birke: Yes. The head office is in Berlin, and we also have branches in Dresden and Nuremberg.

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Intermediate Season 4</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>12:53</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/08/intermediate-s4-19-an-intriguing-german-job-offer/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Intermediate Season 4</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/08/intermediate-s4-19-an-intriguing-german-job-offer/</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Survival Phrases #39 - Using the Post Office in Germany Part I</title>
		<description>Learn German travel phrases with GermanPod101.com! A little German can go such a long way! Whether you&#8217;re traveling, visiting, or sightseeing, GermanPod101.com has all the essential travel phrases just for you!  During your trip, travel or vacation in Germany, you will reach the point where you want to send some postcards or letters to [...]</description>
		<link>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/07/survival-phrases-39-using-the-post-office-in-germany-part-i/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/S_S1L39_050712_gpod101.mp3" length="14319258" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Learn German travel phrases with GermanPod101.com! A little German can go such a long way! Whether you&amp;rsquo;re traveling, visiting, or sightseeing, GermanPod101.com has all the ...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Ich möchte das nach Vancouver schicken.
Ich möchte diese Postkarte nach Vancouver schicken.
Ich möchte diese Priesen Brief nach Vancouver schicken.
Ich möchte diese dieses Paket nach Vancouver schicken.

----Formal English----

I would like to send this to Vancouver.
I would like to send this postcard to Vancouver.
I would like to send this this letter to Vancouver.
I would like to send this this package to Vancouver.

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don't forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>Survival Phrases</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>8:08</itunes:duration>
		<comments>http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/07/survival-phrases-39-using-the-post-office-in-germany-part-i/#comments</comments>
		<dc:creator>GermanPod101.com</dc:creator>
		
	<dc:subject>Survival Phrases</dc:subject>		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.germanpod101.com/2012/05/07/survival-phrases-39-using-the-post-office-in-germany-part-i/</guid>
	</item>
<item>
	<title>Video #2 - Video Vocab Lesson #2: Get Your Fruits!</title>
	<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2006 18:29:58 +0900</pubDate>
	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/V_L2_071709_gpod101_video.m4v</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/V_L2_071709_gpod101_video.m4v" length="5346407" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>

	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
	<itunes:duration>2:43</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Video #1 - Video Vocab Lesson #1: Get Your Vegetables!</title>
	<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2006 18:29:58 +0900</pubDate>

	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/V_L1_071009_gpod101_video.m4v</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/V_L1_071009_gpod101_video.m4v" length="5638874" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
	<itunes:duration>2:41</itunes:duration>

</item>

<item>
	<title>Learn with Pictures and Video #1 - Talking About Your Daily Routine in German</title>
	<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2006 18:29:58 +0900</pubDate>
	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/V_S3L1_010711_gpod101_video.m4v</guid>

	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/V_S3L1_010711_gpod101_video.m4v" length="39817242" type="audio/mpeg"/>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
	<itunes:duration>3:20</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Advanced Audio Blog #1 - Fun at German Christmas Markets</title>
	<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2006 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/AB_S4L1_010411_gpod101.mp3</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/AB_S4L1_010411_gpod101.mp3" length="5847877" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Weihnachtsmärkte

Weihnachten ist noch nicht einmal gefeiert, da sind die Weihnachtsmärkte auch schon wieder weg.Habt ihr es dieses Jahr auf einen Weihnachtsmarkt geschafft? Ich bin ja nicht so der Fan vom Getümmel auf dem Weihnachtsmarkt, aber für viele Menschen sind Besuche auf dem Weihnachtsmarkt ein Muss im Dezember.

Auf Weihnachtsmärkten gibt es aber auch viel zu entdecken. Neben Süßigkeiten wie gebrannten Mandeln, heißen Maronen, Lebkuchen, kandierten Äpfeln und Printen gibt es viele Stände, an denen man Weihnachtsdekorationen, Filzwaren oder Schmuck kaufen kann. Und natürlich darf ein Stück Christstollen und ein Glas Glühwein nicht fehlen.

Irgendwo auf dem Weihnachtsmarkt steht auch immer eine Weihnachtskrippe, die Szenen aus der Weihnachtsgeschichte darstellt. Oder es gibt Weihnachtskonzerte und Krippenspiele werden aufgeführt. Auf Weihnachtsmärkten gibt es also mehr als Süßigkeiten und Verkaufsstände.

Weihnachtsmärkte haben in Deutschland eine lange Tradition. Schon seit dem 15. Jahrhundert gibt es Weihnachtsmärkte. Je nach Region nennt man sie auch Christkindlmarkt, Adventmarkt oder Glühmarkt. Entstanden sind sie aus normalen Wochenmärkten, auf denen man Waren für den alltäglichen Gebrauch kaufen konnte, doch mit Wochenmärkten haben die heutigen Weihnachtsmärkte wenig gemeinsam.

In vielen Städten in Deutschland stehen die Weihnachtsmärkte jedes Jahr an der gleichen Stelle und haben eine langjährige Tradition. Zu den bekanntesten Weihnachtsmärkten gehört der Christkindlmarkt in Nürnberg, der Markt auf dem Münchener Marienplatz oder der Leipziger Weihnachtsmarkt auf dem Marktplatz. Als ältester Weihnachtsmarkt in Deutschland zählt der Striezelmarkt in Dresden, der seit 1434 stattfindet. Jährlichen kommen mehr als 2,5 Millionen Besucher auf den Striezelmarkt.

Also, ich kann ehrlich gesagt, nicht so viel mit Weihnachtsmärkten anfangen. Gerade in Berlin sind mir die großen Weihnachtsmärkte einfach viel zu voll und sie gleichen mehr einem Jahrmarkt mit Buden, Karussells und Essensständen. Außerdem ist es doch viel zu kalt draußen zum Spazieren! Da bleibe ich lieber zuhause und trinke einen warmen Tee und esse Lebkuchen bis ich platze!

----Formal English----

Christmas markets

Christmas is barely over, and the Christmas markets are already gone again.  Did you manage to get out to one this year?  I\'m not really a fan of all the hustle and bustle of the Christmas market, but for a lot of people, visiting Christmas markets is a must in December.

There\'s actually a lot to discover in a Christmas market. Besides the sweets and treats like roasted almonds, roasted chestnuts, gingerbread cake, candied apples, and gingerbread cookies, there are many stands where you can buy Christmas decorations, felt crafts, or jewelry. And of course, you can\'t miss out on a slice of Christstollen cake and a glass of mulled wine.

Somewhere in every Christmas market there\'s always a nativity scene representing the story of Christmas. Or there\'ll be a Christmas concert and a nativity play.  So, a Christmas market is more than just candy and vendor stands.

Christmas markets have a long tradition in Germany.  They\'ve been around since at least the 15th century.  Depending on the region, they\'re called variously \&quot;Christchild market\&quot;, \&quot;Advent market\&quot;, or \&quot;Candlelight market\&quot;.  Originally, they came from the regular weekly market where you could purchase everyday items, although the weekly markets have little in common with present-day Christmas markets.

In many cities in Germany, the Christmas markets are set up in the same spot every year, and are a long-standing tradition.  Among the most well-known Christmas markets are the Christkindlmarkt in Nuremberg, the market in Marienplatz square in Munich, or the Leipzig Christmas market in Marktplatz square.  The oldest Christmas market in Germany is the Striezelmarkt in Dresden, which has occurred since 1434.  Every year, more than 2.5 million visitors come to the Striezelmarkt.

Honestly, Christmas markets aren\'t really my thing.  Even in Berlin, the big Christmas markets are too full for me, and they seem more like a fairground with vending booths, carousels, and food stands.  And anyway, it\'s actually too cold outside to be walking around!  So I prefer to stay home drinking warm tea and eating gingerbread cake until I burst!

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>	<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>

	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
	<itunes:duration>3:15</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Intermediate #3 - This is Your German Captain Speaking</title>
	<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2006 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>

	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/I_S4L3_011712_gpod101.mp3</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/I_S4L3_011712_gpod101.mp3" length="21412217" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Kapitän: Meine Damen und Herren, herzlich Willkommen an Bord dieses Air France Fluges von Paris Charles de Gaulle nach Berlin-Tegel.
Kapitän: Mein Name ist Andreas Büchner und ich bin der Kapitän dieses Flugzeugs.
Kapitän: Wir möchten Sie darauf hinweisen, dass dieser Flug ein Nichtraucherflug ist. Auch in den Toiletten ist das Rauchen verboten.
Kapitän: Die Notausgänge dieser Maschine sind vorne und an den Seiten. Bitte sehen Sie jetzt nach, wo der nächste Notausgang ist, damit Sie sich später nicht verlaufen. 
Kapitän: Das Wetter ist heute gut, also erwarten wir einen ruhigen Flug. In etwa einer Stunde sind wir in Berlin.
Kapitän: Im Moment sind es 26 Grad in Berlin und die Sonne scheint. Hoffentlich bleibt es so bis zu unserer Ankunft. Wir sagen Ihnen am Ende unseres Fluges noch einmal Bescheid.
Kapitän: Vielen Dank und guten Flug!

----Formal English----

Captain: Ladies and Gentlemen, welcome on board this Air France flight from Paris Charles de Gaulle to Berlin-Tegel.
Captain: My name is Andreas Büchner and I\'m the captain of this aircraft.
Captain: We would like to point out that this flight is a non-smoking flight. Smoking is also forbidden in the washrooms.
Captain: The emergency exits of this craft are at the front and on the sides. Please find your nearest emergency exit now, so that later you won\'t get lost.
Captain: The weather is good today, so we expect a calm flight. We\'ll be in Berlin in about an hour.
Captain: Currently it\'s 26 degrees in Berlin and sunny. Hopefully it\'ll stay that way until our arrival. We\'ll give another report at the end of the flight.
Captain: Thanks very much, and have a good flight!

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>	<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>

	<itunes:duration>12:10</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Intermediate #2 - Planning a Flight to Germany	</title>
	<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2006 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/I_S4L2_011012_gpod101.mp3</guid>

	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/I_S4L2_011012_gpod101.mp3" length="18525453" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

A: Anke Löwen.
J: Ja, hallo Anke, hier ist noch mal Joe. 
A: Hallo Joe...
J: Störe ich gerade?
A: Ich bin gerade beim Kochen, aber ein bißchen Zeit habe ich.
J: Okay, dann mache ich\'s kurz.  Ich habe jetzt meinen Flug.
A: Ah, sehr gut. Wann kommst du hierhin?
J: Am dritten August. Wenn alles gut geht, landet mein Flugzeug um 18 Uhr 26 in Berlin.
A: An welchem Flughafen? Berlin-Tegel?
J: Ja, Berlin-Tegel. 
A: Ist das ein Direktflug aus Washington oder steigst du irgendwo um?
J: Ich steige in Paris um... der Flughafen dort heißt Charles de Gaulle.
A: Ja, das ist der große Pariser Flughafen. 
J: Warst du schon einmal dort? Wie ist dieser Flughafen?
A: Paris ist eine wunderschöne Stadt, aber der Flughafen ist nichts besonderes. Irgendwie sind alle Flughäfen gleich.
J: Stimmt.  
A: Wenn du da ankommst, dann lass dir direkt von irgendjemandem den Weg zeigen. In diesem Flughafen kann man sich verlaufen.
J: Mhmm. Ich habe drei Stunden Zeit bis zu meinem nächsten Flug. Das ist genug Zeit, um sich zu verlaufen und den Weg wieder zu finden. Irgendetwas muss ich doch in der Zeit tun. 
A: Okay, wie du willst. Schickst du mir eine SMS, falls dein Flug Verspätung hat?
J: Na klar.
A: Toll! Ich freue mich schon darauf, mit dir zu plaudern.
J: Ich auch, und ich freue mich darauf, wieder in Berlin zu sein. Die Stadt ist einfach toll!
A: Okay, dann bis bald!
J: Bis bald!

----Formal English----

A: Anke Löwen
J: Yes, hello Anke, it\'s Joe again.
A: Hello Joe...
J: Am I interrupting?
A: I\'m currently cooking, but I have a bit of time.
J: Okay, then I\'ll make it short. I have my flight now.
A: Ah, great. When are you coming here?
J: On August 3rd. If all goes well, my plane will land at 6:26pm in Berlin.
A: At which airport? Berlin-Tegel?
J: Yes, Berlin-Tegel.
A: Is it a direct flight from Washington, or are you transfering somewhere?
J: I\'m transfering in Paris... the airport there is called Charles de Gaulle
A: Yes, that\'s the big Paris airport.
J: Have you been there? What\'s this airport like?
A: Paris is a gorgeous city, but the airport is nothing special. Somehow all airports are the same.
J: It\'s true.
A: When you arrive there, then get directions from somebody right away. You can get lost in that airport.
J: Mhmm. I have 3 hours until my next flight. That\'s enough time to get lost and then find my way again. I\'ll have to do something with my time.
A: Okay, whatever you want. Will you send me an SMS if your flight is delayed?
J: Sure.
A: Great! I look forward to chatting with you.
J: Me too, and I\'m looking forward to being back in Berlin again. The city is simply great!
A: Okay, then until soon!
J: Until soon!

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>	<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
	<itunes:duration>15:24</itunes:duration>
</item>

	
<item>
	<title>Intermediate #1 - Long Time, No See in Germany</title>
	<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2006 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/I_S4L1_010312_gpod101.mp3</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/I_S4L1_010312_gpod101.mp3" length="21175231" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

A: Anke Löwen.
J: Hallo Anke, hier ist Joe!
A: Joe? Oh, Joe Cardigan aus Kanada?
J: Ja, genau.
A: Schön von dir zu hören, Joe! Wie geht es dir?
J: Gut, danke, und dir?
A: Auch gut.
J: Wie ist das Wetter in Berlin?
A: Es ist ein wunderschöner Tag hier. Nicht zu warm und nicht zu kalt. Ich werde gleich wieder nach draußen gehen, um die Sonne zu genießen.
J: Ahh, sehr gut! Hier regnet es im Moment, aber heute Nachmittag soll es schön werden.
A: Das ist gut. Warum rufst du an? Nur um zu plaudern?
J: Nein. Ich möchte dir auch sagen, dass ich im August wieder in Deutschland bin.
A: Oh, in welche Stadt reist du dieses Mal?
J: Wieder nach Berlin. Es gibt dort eine interessante Konferenz und ich komme, um Kontakte zu knüpfen.
A: Toll! Das freut mich, dass du wieder hierhin kommst. Denkst du, dass du neben der Konferenz auch Zeit haben wirst, dich mit mir zu treffen?
J: Bestimmt. Die Zeit nehme ich mir.
A: Dann gib Bescheid, wenn du weißt, wann du ankommst und wie lange du bleibst.
J: Ja, mache ich.
A: Bis dann!
J: Bis dann!

----Formal English----

A: Anke Löwen.
J: Hello Anke, it\'s Joe!
A: Joe? Oh, Joe Cardigan from Canada?
J: Yes, exactly.
A: Great to hear from you, Joe! How are you?
J: Good, thanks, and you?
A: Also good.
J: How\'s the weather in Berlin?
A: It\'s a gorgeous day here. Not too warm, and not too cold. I\'m going back outside again soon, to enjoy the sun.
J: Ahh, great! Here it\'s raining currently, but this afternoon is supposed to be nice.
A: That\'s good. Why are you calling? Just to chat?
J: No. I\'d also like to let you know that I\'ll be back in Germany in August.
A: Oh, which city are you going to this time?
J: Back to Berlin again. There\'s an interesting conference there, and I\'m coming to do some networking.
A: Great! I\'m happy that you\'re coming back here. Do you think that you\'ll have time outside the conference in which to meet me?
J: Certainly. I\'ll take the time.
A: Then let me know when you know when you\'re arriving and how long you\'re staying.
J: Yes, I\'ll do that.
A: Until then!
J: Until then!

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>	<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>

	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
	<itunes:duration>12:32</itunes:duration>
</item>

	
<item>
	<title>Upper Beginner #3 - Hobbies: Paying to Play in Germany</title>
	<pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2006 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/UB_S1L3_072110_gpod101.mp3</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/UB_S1L3_072110_gpod101.mp3" length="17707559" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Joe: Du hast ja viele Tennisschläger hier, Anke!
Anke: Oh ja! Tennis ist mein Lieblingssport! Magst du Tennis?
Joe: Tennis? Nein, ich mag Tennis nicht … 
Anke: Oh, wirklich?! Aber Tennis ist doch toll! Ich spiele jede Woche mit Freunden Tennis.
Joe: Hmm, jede Woche. Also ist Tennis dein Hobby …
Anke: Ja, genau. Hast du ein Hobby?
Joe: Ja, ich habe viele Hobbys. Meine Hobbys sind Lesen, Schwimmen und Fahrradfahren. Und ich mag Musik. 
Anke: Du hast aber viele Hobbys. Und du machst viel Sport!
Joe: Ja. In meiner Familie mögen wir alle Sport. Meine Brüder spielen Basketball und natürlich Eishockey. Und meine Schwester und meine Eltern tanzen.
Anke: Wow. Ihr mögt Sport wirklich sehr!
Joe: Ja. Und ich reise auch gern.
Anke: Oh, ich auch! 
Joe: Du kannst mich ja mal in Washington besuchen!
Anke: Ja gerne!
Joe: Ich werde nächste Woche nach München fahren und dann fahre ich vielleicht noch nach Zürich.
Anke: Oh toll, ich mag München! Und Zürich ist auch eine schöne Stadt! Du musst mir eine Postkarte schreiben!
Joe: Ja, werde ich!

----Formal English----

Joe: You have a lot of tennis racquets here, Anke!
Anke: Oh yes! Tennis is my favorite sport! Do you like tennis?
Joe: Tennis? No, I don\'t like tennis...
Anke: Oh, really?! But tennis is so great! I play tennis every week with friends.
Joe: Hmm, every week. So tennis is your hobby...
Anke: Yes, exactly. Do you have a hobby?
Joe: Yes, I have many hobbies. My hobbies are reading, swimming and bicycle-riding. And I like music.
Anke: You have a lot of hobbies. And you do a lot of sports!
Joe: Yes. In my family, we all like sports. My brothers play basketball and ice-hockey of course. And my sister and my parents dance.
Anke: Wow.You really like sports!
Joe: Yes. And I also like to travel. [travel gladly]
Anke: Oh, I do, too!
Joe: You can visit me in Washington some time!
Anke: Yes, gladly!
Joe: I am going to go to Munich next week and then I am maybe going to go on to Zurich.
Anke: Oh great, I like Munich! And Zurich is also a nice city! You have to write me a postcard!
Joe: Yes, I will!

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>	<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>

	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
	<itunes:duration>14:48</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Upper Beginner #2 - Did You Know He's A Walking German Lexicon?</title>
	<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2006 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/UB_S1L2_071410_gpod101.mp3</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/UB_S1L2_071410_gpod101.mp3" length="17971437" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Anke: Ach, Fußball ist ein toller Sport!
Joe: Ja, Fußball gucken macht immer Spaß!
Anke: Ja. Das stimmt.
Joe: Aber es gibt auch Menschen, die nicht gern Fußball gucken …
Anke: Ja, aber das kann ich nicht verstehen.
Thomas: Ich auch nicht.
Joe: Thomas, du weißt aber wirklich viel über Fußball.
Thomas: Ja. Wisst ihr, dass Lothar Matthäus mit 25 WM-Spielen den Weltrekord hält?!
Joe: Lothar…wer?
Anke: Haha, Thomas, du weißt Dinge!! So etwas wissen wir natürlich nicht!
Thomas: Haha …Ja, so etwas vergesse ich nicht, aber Telefonnummern und Geburtstage vergesse ich immer!
Joe: Haha…
Thomas: So, jetzt muss ich aber los…
Anke: Okay. Wir sehen uns ja morgen auf der Arbeit.
Thomas: Nein, morgen bin ich nicht da. Du weißt doch, ich habe Urlaub!
Anke: Ach stimmt, das weiß ich ….
Thomas: Nächste Woche bin ich aber wieder da.
Anke: Ja, gut…
Thomas: Tschüss Joe, vielleicht sehen wir uns ja auch noch mal wieder...
Joe: Ja, vielleicht. Gute Heimfahrt!
Thomas: Danke. Tschüss!
Anke: Tschüss!
…
Joe: Thomas ist echt nett.
Anke: Ja.
Joe: Und er weiß wirklich viel über Fußball!
Anke: Das stimmt!
Joe: Er ist also ein Fußball-Lexikon!
Anke: Haha, genau.

----Formal English----

Anke: Ah, soccer is a great sport!
Joe: Yes, watching soccer is always fun!
Anke: Yes. That\'s right.
Joe: But there are also people who don\'t like to watch soccer...
Anke: Yes, but I can\'t understand that.
Thomas: Me neither.
Joe: Thomas, you do really know a lot about soccer.
Thomas: Yes. Do you know, that Lothar Matthäus holds the record by having played in 25 world championship games?!
Joe: Lothar... who?
Anke: Haha, Thomas, you know stuff!! Of course we don\'t know that kind of thing!
Thomas: Haha... yes, I don\'t forget this kind of thing, but I always forget phone numbers and birthdays!
Joe: Haha...
Thomas: Well, I have to get going now...
Anke: Okay. We shall see each other tomorrow at work.
Thomas: No, tomorrow I won\'t be there. You know that it\'s my holidays!
Anke: Ah right, I know that...
Thomas: I shall be there again next week.
Anke: Yes, good...
Thomas: Bye Joe, maybe we\'ll also see each other again...
Joe: Yes, maybe. Have a good drive home!
Thomas: Thanks. Bye!
Anke: Bye!
...
Joe: Thomas is really nice.
Anke: Yes.
Joe: And he really knows a lot about soccer!
Anke: That\'s right!
Joe: So he is a soccer lexicon!
Anke: Haha, exactly.

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>	<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>

	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
	<itunes:duration>15:20</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Upper Beginner #1 - Ordinary Friends in Germany</title>
	<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2006 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>

	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/UB_S1L1_070710_gpod101.mp3</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/UB_S1L1_070710_gpod101.mp3" length="20045800" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Anke: Ach, na endlich! Das ist sicher Thomas.
Joe: Ah, gut! 
Anke: Hallo Thomas!
Thomas: Hallo Anke.
Anke: Schön, dass du da bist. Das Spiel fängt gleich an!
Thomas: Oh, bin ich also zu spät?!
Anke: Nein, du bist nicht zu spät. Thomas, das ist Joe. Joe, das ist Thomas.
Thomas: Hallo Joe.
Joe: Hallo Thomas.
Anke: Thomas, willst du etwas trinken?
Thomas: Hmm, ja. Ich nehme ein Bier.
Anke: Okay.
Thomas: Und woher kennen Sie Anke, Joe?
Joe: Ich kenne sie aus dem Flugzeug.
Anke: Ja, Joe ist aus Kanada, aber er wohnt in Washington.
Thomas: Ach so. Das ist ja interessant.
Joe: Und woher kennst du Thomas, Anke?
Anke: Ich kenne ihn von der Arbeit.
Joe: Ach so.
Anke: Ah, das Spiel fängt an!
Joe: Und, was meinen Sie Thomas… wie viele Tore wird es geben?
Thomas: Joe, wollen wir nicht "Du" sagen?
Joe: Oh, ja, gerne. Also, was meinst du, wie viele Tore wird es wohl geben?
Thomas: Oh, frag mich nicht! Meine Tipps sind nie richtig….
Anke: Haha, das stimmt. Dich kann man so etwas wirklich nicht fragen…
Joe: Und für wen bist du, Thomas?
Thomas: Na für uns natürlich!
Joe: Uns? Ach ja, Deutschland spielt ja….
Anke: Mensch Joe, du vergisst aber viel!
Joe: Oh ja, das stimmt!!

----Formal English----

Anke: Ah, now finally! That\'s surely Thomas.
Joe: Oh, good!
Anke: Hi Thomas!
Thomas: Hi Anke.
Anke: Nice that you\'re here. The game\'s about to start!
Thomas: Oh, so I\'m too late!
Anke: No, you\'re not too late. Thomas, this is Joe. Joe, this is Thomas.
Thomas: Hi Joe.
Joe: Hi Thomas.
Anke: Thomas, do you want something to drink?
Thomas: Hmm, yeah. I\'ll take a beer.
Anke: Okay.
Thomas: And from where do you know Anke, Joe?
Joe: I know her from the airplane.
Anke: Yes, Joe is from Canada, but he lives in Washington.
Thomas: I see. That\'s interesting indeed.
Joe: And where do you know Thomas, Anke?
Anke: I know him from work.
Joe: I see.
Anke: Ah, the game is starting!
Joe: And, what do you (formal) think Thomas... how many goals will be scored?
Thomas: Joe, don\'t we want to say \&quot;Du\&quot;?
Joe: Oh yes, with pleasure. So, what do you think, how many goals will be scored?
Thomas: Oh, don\'t ask me! My guesses are never right...
Anke: Haha, that\'s right. One can\'t really ask you something like that...
Joe: And who are you rooting for, Thomas?
Thomas: Well, for us, of course!
Joe: Us? Oh yeah, Germany\'s playing indeed...
Anke: Man Joe, you sure do forget a lot!
Joe: Oh yes, that\'s true!

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>	<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>

	<itunes:duration>17:18</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Newbie #3 - Düsseldorf Arc - How it all began</title>
	<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2006 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/007_NB3_041708_gpod101.mp3</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/007_NB3_041708_gpod101.mp3" length="11887733" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101.com!
Do not forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal German----

#2:  Ist hier noch frei? 
#1:  Ja.
#2:  Danke. Ich heiße Michael Schmidt.
#1:  Angenehm. Ich heiße Lena Wagner.
#2:  Angenehm. Kommen Sie oft hierhin?
#1:  Ja, das Café ist sehr gut.
#2:  Ich wohne in Bremen, aber ich komme oft nach Düsseldorf. Wohnen Sie hier in Düsseldorf?
#1:  Nein, ich wohne nicht in Düsseldorf. Ich wohne in Köln. Duzen wir uns doch.
#2:  Okay, gut.

----Formal English----

#2:  Is [this seat] here still free?
#1:  Yes.
#2:  Thanks. I am called Michael Schmidt.
#1:  It's a pleasure [to meet you]. I am called Lena Wagner.
#2:  It's a pleasure [to meet you]. Do you often come here?
#1: Yes, the café (the ice-cream parlour) is very good.
#2: I actually live in Bremen, but I often come to Dusseldorf. Do you live here in Dusseldorf?
#1: No, I don't live in Dusseldorf. I live in Cologne. Let's call each other "du" (= switch to informal language).
#2: Okay, good.

----Informal German----

#2:  Ist hier noch frei? 
#1:  Ja.
#2:  Danke. Ich heiße Michael Schmidt.
#1:  Freut mich. Ich heiße Lena Wagner.
#2:  Freut mich. Kommst du oft hierhin?
#1:  Ja, das Café ist sehr gut.
#2:  Ich wohne in Bremen, aber ich komme oft nach Düsseldorf. Wohnst du hier in Düsseldorf?
#1:  Nein, ich wohne nicht in Düsseldorf. Ich wohne in Köln. Duzen wir uns doch.
#2:  Okay, gut.

----Informal English----

#2:  Is [this seat] here still free?
#1:  Yes.
#2:  Thanks. I am called Michael Schmidt.
#1:  I'm pleased [to meet you]. I am called Lena Wagner.
#2:  I'm pleased [to meet you]. Do you often come here?
#1: Yes, the café (the ice-cream parlour) is very good.
#2: I actually live in Bremen, but I often come to Dusseldorf. Do you live here in Dusseldorf?
#1: No, I don't live in Dusseldorf. I live in Cologne. Let's call each other "du" (= switch to informal language).
#2: Okay, good.

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101.com!
Do not forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>	<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>

	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
	<itunes:duration>14:06</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Newbie #2 - Introductions</title>
	<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2006 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>

	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/005_NB2_033108_gpod101.mp3</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/005_NB2_033108_gpod101.mp3" length="10805897" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

#1:  Guten Tag! Ich heiße Judith Meyer. Ich komme aus Deutschland und ich arbeite hier, bei Germanpod101.com. 

#2:  Guten Tag! Ich heiße Chuck Smith. Ich komme nicht aus Deutschland, aber ich wohne in Deutschland. Ich arbeite auch bei Germanpod101.com.

----Formal English----

#1:  Hello! I am called Judith Meyer. I come from Germany and I work here, at Germanpod101.com 

#2:  Hello! I am called Chuck Smith. I don't come from Germany, but I live in Germany. I also work at Germanpod101.com.

----Informal ----

#1:  Hallo! Ich heiße Judith Meyer. Ich komme aus Deutschland und ich arbeite hier, bei Germanpod101.com. 

#2:  Hallo! Ich heiße Chuck Smith. Ich komme nicht aus Deutschland, aber ich wohne in Deutschland. Ich arbeite auch bei Germanpod101.com.

----Informal English----

#1:  Hello! I am called Judith Meyer. I come from Germany and I work here, at Germanpod101.com 

#2:  Hello! I am called Chuck Smith. I don't come from Germany, but I live in Germany. I also work at Germanpod101.com.

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>	<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>

	<itunes:duration>12:49</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Newbie #1 - Guten Tag!</title>
	<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2006 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/003_NB1_031008_gpod101.mp3</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/003_NB1_031008_gpod101.mp3" length="5264818" type="audio/mpeg"/>
	<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

----Formal ----

Frau Höhne:  Guten Tag, Herr Jäger!
Herr Jäger:  Guten Tag, Frau Höhne!
Frau Höhne:  Wie geht es Ihnen?
Herr Jäger:  Gut, danke, und Ihnen?
Frau Höhne:  Auch gut, danke.
Herr Jäger:  Auf Wiedersehen!
Frau Höhne:  Auf Wiedersehen!

----Formal English----

Ms Höhne:  Hello, Mr Jäger!  (literally : Good day, Mr Jäger!)
Mr Jäger:  Hello, Ms Höhne! (literally: Good day, Ms Höhne!) 
Ms Höhne:  How are you?  (literally: how goes it to you?)
Mr Jäger:  Good, thanks, and you?
Ms Höhne:  Also good, thanks.
Mr Jäger:  Goodbye!  (literally: till seeing-again)
Ms Höhne:  Goodbye!  (literally: till seeing-again)

----Informal ----

Lisa: Hallo Thomas!
Thomas: Hallo Lisa!
Lisa: Wie geht es dir?
Thomas: Gut, danke, und dir?
Lisa: Auch gut, danke.
Thomas: Tschüss!
Lisa: Tschüss!

----Informal English----

Lisa: Hey Thomas!
Thomas: Hey Lisa!
Lisa: How are you?
Thomas: Good, thanks, and you?
Lisa: Also good, thanks.
Thomas: Bye!
Lisa: Bye!

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>	<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>

	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
	<itunes:duration>12:12</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
	<title>All About #1. Why You Should Learn German</title>
	<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2005 14:45:59 +0900</pubDate>
	<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/ALL_L1_080910_gpod101.mp3</guid>
	<enclosure url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/ALL_L1_080910_gpod101.mp3" length="6865170" type="audio/mpeg"/>

	<itunes:summary>Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!

-------Lesson Dialog-------

---------------------------
Learn German with GermanPod101!
Don\'t forget to stop by GermanPod101.com for more great German Language Learning Resources!</itunes:summary>	<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
	<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
	<itunes:duration>7:00</itunes:duration>
</item>
	<item>
		<title>How This Feed Works</title>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2005 05:38:53 +0900</pubDate>
		<guid>http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/german_pubfeed_l1.mp3</guid>
		<enclosure
			url="http://media.libsyn.com/media/germanpod101/german_pubfeed_l1.mp3"
			length="1429027"
			type="audio/mpeg"
		/>
		<itunes:subtitle>Listen to Me First!</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:author>GermanPod101.com</itunes:author>
		<itunes:summary>Go to GermanPod101.com to get your FREE Lifetime Account! Subscribing to our free iTunes podcast feed is the easiest way to get our newest audio and video lessons. Subscribe to our free podcast now, and automatically get our newest lessons. Also get an example of the lesson notes and other study tools that accompany each lesson on our site.
However, this free podcast feed contains just a tiny fraction of our lessons. Every time a new lesson is released, one lesson is moved to the library on our website. So right now you're only accessing SOME of our lesssons. To INSTANTLY ACCESS our ENTIRE LIBRARY of audio and video lessons, go to GermanPod101.com and sign up for a free lifetime account.</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:keywords>learn, german, language, culture, travel, germanpod101</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:block>No</itunes:block>
		<itunes:duration>1:29</itunes:duration>
	</item>
	</channel></rss>
