<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>
<ttl>30</ttl>

<title>PRI's The World: Technology</title>
<language>en-us</language>
<link>http://www.theworld.org/technology-podcast</link>
<copyright>2010 Public Radio International</copyright>
<description>The World's weekly Technology Podcast brings you all the latest and
greatest news from the field of global technology.  The World is a US-based
international news and analysis program co-produced by the BBC World Service,
Public Radio International, and WGBH Public Radio in Boston.</description>
<itunes:summary>The World's weekly Technology Podcast brings you all the latest
and greatest news from the field of global technology.   </itunes:summary>
<itunes:author>Public Radio International</itunes:author>
<itunes:owner>
	<itunes:name>Public Radio International</itunes:name>
	<itunes:email>interactive@pri.org</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:category text="Technology">
<itunes:category text="Tech News" />
</itunes:category>
<itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public, radio, pri, technology, npr, tech,
podcast, internet,clark boyd</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:image href="http://www.theworld.org/images/podcast_images/Technology_v4.jpg" />


<!--
 <a href="http://odeo.com/claim/feed/1f599c51cf2ab1c6" >My Odeo Channel</a>
-->
<item>
  <title>A New Flame, More Flame, and Danger in the Download Part III
</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast366.mp3</link>
  <description>In this episode, we'll take a look at a new piece of malware called Flame which has been found on computers throughout the Middle East. Sophisticated and dangerous malware, or a big piece of bloatware? And we'll give you part three of Ed Butler's "Danger in the Download" series. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod. Or Twitter at www.twitter.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast366.mp3" length="15869609" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast366.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 1 Jun 2012 10:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>32:51</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Flame, virus, malware, Stuxnet, Duqu, hacking, infosec, worm, cyberwar, cyberespionage, Iran</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Special Towel Day Episode: Gbooza!, Norway Data Farm, Italian Garbage Drones, Mine Kafon, and Robofish!</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast365.mp3</link>
  <description>In honor the late, great Douglas Adams, we have a special "Towel Day" episode. It comes complete with an African social network built in China. We also will talk about the trend to put server farms in cold climates. Plus, we have Italian drones patrolling mafia garbage dumps, something called a Mine Kafon, and RoboFish! Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast365.mp3" length="12373004" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast365.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 07:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>25:34</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Douglas Adams, Towel Day, Gbooza, Norway, Drones, UAVs, Mine Kafon, robots</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>B-Side, Vol. 11: The BBC's "Danger in the Download" Series, Part 2</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast364.mp3</link>
  <description>In this episode, we listen in to the BBC's Ed Butler as he explores the world of cyberthreats. This is Part 2 of a 3 part series to follow in the coming weeks. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast364.mp3" length="11665153" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast364.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 08:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>24:06</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>cyberthreats, cyberwar, hacking</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>B-Side, Vol. 10: The BBC's "Danger in the Download" Series, Part 1</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast363.mp3</link>
  <description>In this B-side episode, we listen in to the BBC's Ed Butler as he explores the world of cyberthreats. This is Part 1 of a 3 part series to follow in the coming weeks. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast363.mp3" length="11778838" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast363.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2012 09:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>24:20</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>cyberthreats, cyberwar, hacking</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Gaming and Genomics, Interview with Linus Torvalds, Smog-Busting Paint, and A Conversation with a Chinese "Hacker"</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast362.mp3</link>
  <description>This week, we hear about a crowd-sourced game that allows players the chance to help researchers better understand genomics. Also, an interview with Linus Torvalds, father of the Linux operating system. Plus, smog-busting paint in Manila, and a conversation with a Chinese hacker. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast362.mp3" length="11527854" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast362.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 08:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>23:45</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Gaming, video games, crowdsourcing, Linux, Linus Torvalds, paint, hacking, China</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Apple's 'Factory Girls,' Enigma Machines in the Spanish Civil War, The Wonderbag, and…The Theremin</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast361.mp3</link>
  <description>This week, we hear from the author of a book about some of Apple's workers in China. It's called "Factory Girls." Also, we have two history stories. One is about the use of Engima code-breaking machines during the Spanish Civil War. The other is about the birth of the Theremin. And we'll also tell you about…The Wonderbag! Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast361.mp3" length="12421744" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast361.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 07:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>25:37</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Apple, Mike Daisey, TAL, Enigma, Bletchley Park, Spain, Wonderbag, Theremin</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Greek Geeks Seek Hi-Tech Recovery, Electronics on Planes Revisited, Micro-chipping Brazilian Kids, and The Camera That Can See Around Corners</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast360.mp3</link>
  <description>In this episode, we take you to Greece to hear from some serious geeks who think hi-tech might help the country find some relief from the dire financial situation its in. Also, the FAA revisits the ban on electronics during flights. Then, to Brazil to hear about a plan to track kids with micro-chips, and finally…the camera that sees around corners. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast360.mp3" length="7958510" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast360.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 09:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>16:18</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Greece, crisis, tech, hi-tech, FAA, planes, microchips, Brazil, cameras, MIT</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Energy From Footsteps, The WayC Tablet, Webcams in Russian Elections, Fooling Body Scanners, and ROBOBRAIN!</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast359.mp3</link>
  <description>In this week's…show…we have an item on a British company that's trying to make energy out of every step you take. Also, Africa's WayC Tablet computer, webcams in the Russian elections, and a RoboBrain. Oh, and we meet a guy who can beat those full body scanners at the airport. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast359.mp3" length="11144181" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast359.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 09:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>22:57</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Pavegen, energy, kinetic, piezoelectricity, tablets, webcams, body scanners, brains</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Google's New Privacy Guidelines, Raspberry Pi, Salamworld, and LuminAID</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast358.mp3</link>
  <description>In this episode, we'll explore the ins and outs of Google's new privacy regulations. Also, you'll hear about Raspberry Pi, the $35 computer. We'll also offer some LuminAID to go with that pi; LuminAID is an inflatable, solar lantern designed to assist in post-disaster situations. And we'll also tell you about Salamworld, which bills itself as a Muslim alternative to Facebook. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast358.mp3" length="9236141" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast358.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 09:30:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>18:58</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Google, privacy, Raspberry Pi, Salamworld, Facebook, LuminAID</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP B-side, Vol. 9: Deep Blue v. Gary Kasparov…and a Bit of Stonehenge</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast357.mp3</link>
  <description>In this B-side episode, we'll take you back 16 years…back to the first time a computer beat a Grand Master in chess. It's a full-out tech v. man smackdown between Deep Blue and Gary Kasparov. And then, because we needed an excuse to get Spinal Tap on the show, we have a segment about the sounds…of Stonehenge. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast357.mp3" length="7848797" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast357.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 08:30:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>16:05</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Deep Blue, chess, Kasparov, IBM, Stonehenge, Spinal Tap</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Carpooling.com, Eolas vs. The Web, Spider Silk, Virtual Therapy, and Celebrating Tetris</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast356.mp3</link>
  <description>A German company goes online, and on apps, to connect drivers and passengers for cheap rides across Germany and beyond. Also, a Texas company that's thinking of suing, well, a heck of a lot of websites. We'll also talk spider silk, and virtual therapy for burn victims. And we'll end with a look at the wonder of Tetris. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast356.mp3" length="15173058" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast356.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 08:30:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>31:21</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Carpooling, ride-sharing, Eolas, Spiders, silk, virtual reality, Tetris</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>EU Online Privacy Rights, Invisibility Cloak, Magnetic Soap, and A New Plan to Save Venice</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast355.mp3</link>
  <description>This week, an in-depth look at the new online privacy laws that the European Union wants to enact. Do you have the right to be forgotten online? And practically speaking, is it possible? Also, scientists get to work on that invisibility cloak we've all wanted, and some magnetic soap too. And we'll end with a new plan to save Venice, which, as we've been told for hundreds of years, is sinking. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast355.mp3" length="12861160" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast355.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 11:15:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>26:30</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>EU, privacy, internet, online, invisibility cloak, soap, Venice </itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Megaupload, SOPA Protests, Cruise Ship Technology, Angry Brides, Apps in India, and Ash Cloud Detection</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast354.mp3</link>
  <description>We've got a great show this week. We'll hear about the takedown of file-sharing site MegaUpload, and the retaliation by Anonymous. Also, protests against SOPA and PIPA. And why didn't modern cruise ship technology keep the Costa Concordia from foundering? We'll end with two stories on apps in India, and a personal tale of travel woe, and tech-driven hope, related to 2010's ash cloud fiasco in Europe. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast354.mp3" length="14068030" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast354.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 09:15:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>29:01</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Megaupload, Anonymous, SOPA, PIPA, Costa Concordia, cruise ships, Apps, India, Ash</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Conflict Minerals in Congo, Digital Detox, Sweden's File-Sharing Religion, Kodak's Legacy, and The Toaster Experience</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast353.mp3</link>
  <description>This week, we'll hear a plea from a Congolese man. He wants Apple to produce a conflict mineral-free iPhone by 2013. Also, how to do a "digital detox." Plus, Sweden gets a new religion…based around file-sharing. We'll also examine Kodak's photographic legacy, digital and otherwise. And we'll end with the story of a man who wanted to build a toaster, from scratch, all by himself. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast353.mp3" length="10767839" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast353.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 08:45:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>22:09</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Apple, Congo, conflict minerals, digital, sweden, file-sharing, kodak, toaster</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>WTP B-sides, Vol. 8: Diamond Light Source Synchrotron</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside8.mp3</link>
  <description>Happy New Year. Happy New Podcast. Happy New App. That's right: WTP is now available in a handy app for your mobile device. And to celebrate, we offer a B-Side podcast on Britain's Diamond Light Source Synchrotron. Very B-side, very cool! Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside8.mp3" length="9923915" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside8.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 06:45:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>20:23</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Diamond, Light, Synchrotron, X-ray</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Militants and Twitter, Radio in Rwanda, OLPC From the Skies, and a Christmas Cracker</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast351.mp3</link>
  <description>We finish the year with a cracker of a podcast. We'll talk about militant groups on Twitter, and about how an old school technology like radio can have a big impact in a place like Rwanda. Also, OLPC is planning on dropping laptops from helicopters. Yes, that's right. And we end with the ultimate B-Side story: Augusta Chiwy and the Siege of Bastogne. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast351.mp3" length="16834215" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast351.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 09:15:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>34:47</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Twitter, Islam, militants, radio, Rwanda, OLPC, Bastogne, WW II</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>The Wikileaks Effect, China Microblogs, Twitter and Revolutions, and An App for Diagnosing Diseases</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast350.mp3</link>
  <description>This week, we look at what effect Wikileaks has really had on intelligence gathering and sharing. Also, we hear about new microblogging rules in China, and about some academic research into the role of Twitter in recent social movements. We end with a Tech That Matters segment on the search for an app that can diagnose malaria, HIV, and tuberculosis. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast350.mp3" length="10521643" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast350.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 07:20:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>21:38</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Wikileaks, Manning, China, Weibo, blogs, Twitter, apps</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>New Rules for Cyberwar, The Tech Monitoring South Sudan, Random Hacks of Kindness, and Helping Amputees</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast349.mp3</link>
  <description>WTP 349 will both terrify and inspire. First, learn about how experts are debating the rules of engagement for wars that have moved online. Then, you'll hear an in-depth interview about the Satellite Sentinel Project in South Sudan. Also, some geeks help inspire Random Hacks of Kindness. And we end with a story of a young woman who is helping amputees fight their phantom limb pain. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast349.mp3" length="10814218" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast349.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 05:20:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>22:14</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>cyberwar, sudan, south sudan, george clooney, hacking, amputees</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Pepper Spray, Tear Gas, A Bionic Eye, Soft Robots and Bletchley Park</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast348.mp3</link>
  <description>On this week's podcast, we look at two compounds that are making news around the world of late: pepper spray and tear gas. Also, would you wear a contact lens that could project your email onto your eye? Then, we talk about soft robots, and we end with a check-in on Britain's code-breaking HQ, Bletchley Park. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast348.mp3" length="11687300" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast348.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 08:30:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>24:03</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>pepper spray, occupy, tear gas, Egypt, bionic eye, robots, bletchley park </itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>WTP B-sides, Vol. 7: Iconic Geometry of The Great Pyramid</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside7.mp3</link>
  <description>In this B-side episode, we explore the iconic geometry of The Great Pryamid. I love triangles. Don't you? Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside7.mp3" length="11663883" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside7.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 08:15:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>24:01</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Egypt, Great Pyramid, Cecil Balmond, triangles </itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Syrian Net Censorship, Instant Wild App, Liberia Gets Fiber, Uganda's Electric Car, and Nigeria's Plastic Bottle House</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast346.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 346 has some great stories for you. First, an extended interview about the US technologies that Syria seems to be using to monitor the Internet. Also, an app called Instant Wild lets you explore the animal kingdom. Then, Liberia gets fiber, Uganda gets an electric car, and some clever Nigerians recycle plastic bottles into houses. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast346.mp3" length="11908904" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast346.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 08:15:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>24:31</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Nigeria, plastic, recycling, Uganda, evs, electric cars, Syria, censorship, apps</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Hidden Tech Heroes, Magnetic Tongue, Scammers Go Pro, Tunisians Occupy Obama's Facebook Page, and The Sound of Falling Stock Prices</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast345.mp3</link>
  <description>This week's podcast has some great stories in it. You'll hear about bubble wrap, post-its, and the other "Hidden Heroes" of tech. Also, we explore the Magnetic Tongue, and hear about how click-jackers are going pro. Very pro. We end with Tunisians occupying President Obama's Facebook page, and some Germans who have turned falling stock prices…into music. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast345.mp3" length="11339664" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast345.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 06:15:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>23:20</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>tongue, scammers, hacking, Obama, Occupy, Tunisia, Greece, economy, visualization</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

  <item>
  <title>Aakash Tablet Computer, Congo Conflict Minerals, Hydrogen Cars in Britain, and Solar Power in the Middle East</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast344.mp3</link>
  <description>WTP 344 has stories about the Aakash tablet computer in India, conflict minerals in Congo, hydrogen cars in Britain, and solar power in Israel. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast344.mp3" length="10809454" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast344.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 05:15:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>22:14</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Aakash, tablets, tablet computing, Congo, minerals, hydrogen, solar power, Israel</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Duqu, Dark Market, Mobile Phone Shopping, Solar Power Decathalon, Mr. Mummy</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast343.mp3</link>
  <description>WTP 343 has a great lineup. We'll talk about Duqu, the "Son of Stuxnet" variant that's turning up on computers in Europe. Also, Misha Glenny discusses his new book "Dark Market." We'll hear about shopping by mobile phone in South Korea, and about the Solar Power Decathalon. And we'll end with none other than Mr. Mummy. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast343.mp3" length="13343695" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast343.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 10:15:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>27:30</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Duqu, Stuxnet, Dark Market, cybercrime, mobile phones, solar power, mummies</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>WTP B-Sides, Vol. 6: Iconomic Geometry, The Taj Mahal</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside6.mp3</link>
  <description>In this B-side episode, we continue with structrual engineer and designer Cecil Balmond as he explores iconic geometric shapes. This time, we're focusing on the square, and on the Taj Mahal in India. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside6.mp3" length="12176740" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside6.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 04:40:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>25:05</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Cecil Balmond, engineering, Taj Mahal, India, square, shapes</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Steve Jobs' Influence in Africa, Environmental Cost of Gadgets, Robotics in Ghana, and the Alma Array Fires Up</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast341.mp3</link>
  <description>WTP 341 bids farewell to Steve Jobs. We'll hear how his thinking and his products influenced Africans. Also, we'll take stock of the environmental costs of a world filled with Jobsian gadgets. Then, we'll hear about a robotics program in Ghana. And we'll end with a tour of a new radio telescope in Chile. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast341.mp3" length="10348641" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast341.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 08:40:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>21:16</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Steve Jobs, Apple, Macintosh, Africa, robotics, Ghana, Alma, Chile, astronomy</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Drones, Memory Suppressing Tech, Digital After-Life, Resomation, and Ashes to the Cosmos </title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast340.mp3</link>
  <description>WTP 340 looks at the use of drones in war, and the ethics of using drugs and technology to suppress memories. Then, three segments on your favorite topic: death. We'll look at what happens to your online life after you die. Also, two alternatives to cremation, and a service to shoot your ashes into space. RIP. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast340.mp3" length="13676424" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast340.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 07:20:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>28:12</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>drones, UAVs, memory, death, digital, resomation, cremation, ashes, space</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>WTP B-sides, Vol. 5: The Iconic Geometry of Stonehenge </title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside5.mp3</link>
  <description>Time for this month's "B-side" edition of The World's Technology Podcast. This time, we hear about some iconic geometry. More specifically, we talk about circles. And Stonehenge! Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside5.mp3" length="12017280" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside5.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 07:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>24:45</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>geometry, circle, Stonehenge, design, building</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>DigiNotar and Comodohacker, Twitter and Hedge Funds, Social Media and Mexico Violence, mHealth, and Treycycle Bold </title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast338.mp3</link>
  <description>WTP 338 will not disappoint. We'll talk about the Comodohacker and DigiNotar. Also, Twitter takes on the markets, and how social media can be a dangerous thing to use in Mexico. In addition, we'll hear about mHealth projects in Africa. And what do NASA engineers do when they get laid off? Build the Treycycle Bold, of course. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast338.mp3" length="11819019" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast338.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 03:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>24:30</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>DigiNotar, hacking, Twitter, Mexico, mHealth, mobiles, NASA, Trecycle Bold</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Syrian Electronic Army, Tech Aids Repression in Bahrain, Nuclear Power in Africa, and Spies in the Sky </title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast337.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 337 begins with two segments about tech and the so-called Arab Spring. We'll talk about the Syrian Electronic Army and about Nokia-Siemens in Bahrain. We'll also hear a great piece about nuclear power in Africa. And we'll end with a look back into the history of aerial surveillance. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast337.mp3" length="10560118" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast337.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 07:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>21:43</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Syria, electronic army, Bahrain, Africa, nuclear power, surveillance</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>PlantLab, Internet Addiction, DMZ Augmented Reality, and Space Junk</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast336.mp3</link>
  <description>WTP officially returns…to the lilting sounds of bagpipes of course. On the tech front, we've got a story about a new way of growing plants being tested in the Netherlands. Also, fighting Internet addiciton in South Korea. We'll hear about an app that augments the reality of the DMZ. And we'll end with an item on that orbital scourge, space junk. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast336.mp3" length="10943358" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast336.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 08:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>22:30</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>internet, plantlab, DMZ, Korea, internet addiction, space, space junk</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>WTP B-sides, Vol. 4: The Internet Cafe Hobo, Part 1</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside4.mp3</link>
  <description>Our August B-sides podcasts continue as we follow the BBC's Nick Baker, aka "The Internet Cafe Hobo." Nick had a great idea - go to an Internet cafe somewhere in the world, and then let what he found there take him to another cafe, in another part of the world. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside4.mp3" length="13229573" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside4.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2011 08:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>27:16</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>technology, internet, internet cafe, hobo, nick baker</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>WTP B-sides, Vol. 3: Tracking the Lincolnshire Poacher</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside3.mp3</link>
  <description>Our August "B-Sides" podcasts continue with this gem. We try to
track down the Lincolnshire Poacher, and find some mysterious radio transmissions
along the way. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside3.mp3" length="14873204" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside3.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 05:45:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>30:42</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>numbers, number stations, cold war, science fiction, Fringe,
Lincolnshire Poacher</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP B-sides, Vol. 2: Ray Kurzweil</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside2.mp3</link>
  <description>Our August selection of "B-Sides" continues. In this episode, an
in-depth interview with Ray Kurzweil, the man who wants to live forever. Visit the
homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside2.mp3" length="13671553" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside2.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 04:45:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>28:11</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Ray Kurzweil, singularity, longevity</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP B-sides, Vol. 1: The Foghorn</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside1.mp3</link>
  <description>We're back. Sort of. Until we start new episodes in September,
we're bringing you all of those great semi-tech stories that never found their way
onto a podcast. It's the WTP B-sides. Enjoy. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside1.mp3" length="16115154" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPbside1.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 09:45:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>33:17</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>foghorn, foghorns, oceans, art, literature</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>So Long and Thanks for Listening</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast331.mp3</link>
  <description>Items this time around on a begging robot, North Korea's supposed
cyber-army, and Japan's virtual pop star. We'll also discuss adding sounds to
electric cars, and a video game designed to help with rehab. We'll end with a
listener segment on Ears to our World. And, we'll say goodbye. For real. Visit the
homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast331.mp3" length="19209067" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast331.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 09:15:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>39:44</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>North Korea, robots, electric cars, computer games, cyberarmy,
Japan</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>SETI Search Gets New Telescope, Syria's E-Army, Cell Phones in North
Korea, Machine Translation in the US Military, and Dutch Band Helps Your Webcam
See Better</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast330.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 330 will, we hope, not disappoint. You'll hear about a new
kind of radio telescope helping researchers scan the skies for possible signals
from an alien civilization. Also, Syria's E-Army, and how cell phones may be
opening up reclusive North Korea. We've got a piece on machine translation, and we
end with a Dutch band that's helping your webcam see a bit better. Visit the
homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast330.mp3" length="11397347" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast330.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 05:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>23:27</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>SETI, LOFAR, Syria, mobile phones, North Korea, machine
translation, C-Mon and Kypski</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Solar Impulse Landing, Space Shuttle Endeavor Launch, FrontlineSMS Radio,
and Planking</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast329.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 329 will astound, delight and entertain. We hope. We'll
have a follow-up to last week's historic flight of the world's first completely
solar-powered airplane. Also, we'll take stock of the last mission of the Space
Shuttle Endeavor. Then, we'll revisit FrontlineSMS - they're getting into radio
now! And we'll end with planking. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology,
or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast329.mp3" length="11599693" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast329.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 08:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>23:52</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Solar Impulse, solar plane, solar power, Endeavor, Shuttle,
space shuttle, FrontlineSMS, radio, planking</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>A Conversation with Andre Borschberg, Pilot of the Solar Impulse
Plane</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast328.mp3</link>
  <description>A special podcast to end the week! I got the chance to interview
Andre Borschberg, pilot of the Solar Impulse plane, as he attempts to complete the
first international flight of the world's only all-solar powered aircraft. If all
goes well, Andre and his plane will be landing in Brussels later this evening.
Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast328.mp3" length="4800174" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast328.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 09:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>09:43</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Solar Impulse, solar plane, solar power, Andre Borschberg,
Bertrand Piccard, Switzerland, Belgium, Brussels</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Sci/Tech and Osama, Rethinking Black Box Technology, The Enigma Machine,
and SETI Shutdown</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast327.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 327 is a corker. We've got four sci/tech items on Osama bin
Laden, including a look at how technicians might get information off of the hard
drives collected during the raid. Also, is it time to replace black box cockpit
recorders with a better system? We'll end with a look back at The Enigma Machine,
and we'll hear about SETI's struggle to keep scanning the skies for alien
messages. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook
at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast327.mp3" length="16236007" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast327.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 05:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>33:32</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Osama bin Laden, Pakistan, Navy Seals, Air France 447, black
box, Enigma Machine, SETI, raid, assassination</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Biofuels in Denmark and Kenya, Happy Birthday Microchip!, and The
Institute of Brilliant Failures</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast326.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 326 will bring you two stories on biofuels, one from
Denmark and one from Kenya. We also look back on the importance of the microchip.
And we'll end with a tour of Amsterdam's Institute of Brilliant Failures. Visit
the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast326.mp3" length="11584515" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast326.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 12:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>23:50</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>biofuels, ethanol, Denmark, Kenya, microchip, failure, Kathryn
Schulz, Institute of Brilliant Failures, Holland</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Inspire Japan, Yuri Gagarin's Legacy, and The Oramics Machine</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast325.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 325 has stories on a global effort by architects and
designers to help in the rebuilding of Japan. It's called PechaKucha, and it's
happening on Saturday, April 16. Also, we delve into the legacy of cosmonaut Yuri
Gagarin, who became the first human being in space 50 years ago this week. And we
end with a tribute to the Oramics Machine. Good times. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast325.mp3" length="17157773" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast325.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 09:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>35:27</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Japan, Pecha Kucha, Architecture for Humanity, Yuri Gagarin,
Daphne Oram</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Nuclear Accidents Past: Chernobyl, Three Mile Island, and
Tokaimura</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast324.mp3</link>
  <description>This podcast will take a look back into nuclear accidents past to
help us better understand the ongoing crisis at the Fukushima plant in Japan.
We'll revisit Chernobyl, Three Mile Island, and Tokaimura. We'll end with an
interview with a blogger who is translating Japanese twitter messages. Visit the
homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast324.mp3" length="17497171" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast324.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 07:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>36:09</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Japan, nuclear, Fukushima, Chernobyl, Three Mile Island,
Tokaimura</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Global Nuke Jitters, Assessing Risk, A German and His Cellphone, FBI
Crowdsources Crypto, Inside Virgin Galactic, and Superglue Inventor, RIP</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast323.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 323 is packed with global technology goodness. You'll hear
about global nuclear power jitters, and a risk expert assesses the, you guessed
it, risk. Also, a German man finds out just how much his government knows about
him. We'll also take a tour of the Virgin Galactic spaceship, and hear about why
the FBI is crowdsourcing a crytography conundrum. That, plus the inventor of
Superglue dies.
Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast323.mp3" length="13125063" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast323.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 11:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>27:03</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Japan, nuclear, Fukushima, risk, FBI, crytography, virgin
galactic, malte spitz, henry coover, superglue</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Satellite Sentinel Project, Age-Appropriate Tech, and Danish Postage Goes
Digital</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast322.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 322 brings you stories on the Satellite Sentinel project in
Sudan. Also, designing age-appropriate technologies in Surrey, England. We'll talk
about a plan to drill down to the center of the earth, and we'll hear about a new
idea that's got Danes asking, "To Lick or to Text?" Yummy. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast322.mp3" length="8112125" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast322.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 06:30:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>16:36</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Sudan, Satellites, Clooney, Surrey, Denmark, postage, mobile
phones, Earth</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>The Nuclear Crisis in Post-Quake Japan</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast321.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 321 deals exclusively with the unfolding nuclear crisis in
Japan, after last week's devastating earthquake and tsunami. Don't get caught up
in the hype and hyperbole. Get answers, context and perspective in this episode.
Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast321.mp3" length="11820946" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast321.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 06:30:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>24:20</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Japan, earthquake, tsunami, nuclear, Fukushima,
meltdown</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Libya Citizen Video, Bradley Manning Charged, Computerized School Exams,
CeBit, and South Korean Language Robots</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast320.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 320 includes items on getting citizen video out of Libya,
and on the charges facing Bradley Manning in the WikiLeaks case. Also, is it time
to give up pen and paper in school exams? Then, items on CeBit, and language
teaching robots in South Korea. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology,
or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast320.mp3" length="13170488" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast320.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 07:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>27:08</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Libya, One Day on Earth, Bradley Manning, Wikileaks, CeBit,
robots</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Being Wrong: A Conversation with Kathryn Schulz</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPspecialbeingwrong.mp3</link>
  <description>We aim to misbehave in this special podcast. We have a conversation
with Kathryn Schulz, who calls herself "the world's leading wrongologist." Find
out why failing can be good for you. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPspecialbeingwrong.mp3" length="9524779" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPspecialbeingwrong.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>19:33</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Kathryn Schulz, Being Wrong, wrong, error, TED, failure,
fail</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Clinton's Internet Freedom Speech, UK and US Uncut, Cryonic Freezing
Craze, and The Backpack Heart</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast319.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 319 will get one Iranian's take on the Secretary of State
Hillary Clinton's Internet Freedom Speech. Also, UK and US Uncut use social media
to protest. Then, we revisit the cryonics craze of the 1960s, and we hear about a
man who carries his heart, or at least the pump for it, in his backpack. Visit the
homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast319.mp3" length="15047330" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast319.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 07:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>31:03</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Clinton, internet freedom, censorship, Iran, UK Uncut,
cryonics, cryogenics, heart, backpack, valentine's day</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Expiration Dates for Online Data, and The Wireless World of Gerry
Wells</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast318.mp3</link>
  <description>This week, a story about two projects looking to help you put
expiration dates on your online data. And then, a mini documentary on radio guru
Gerry Wells. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on
Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast318.mp3" length="13994246" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast318.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 12:45:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>28:51</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Xpire, expiration dates, social networking, online privacy,
wireless, radio, Gerry Wells</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Egypt: Tech Shutdowns and Work-Arounds</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast317.mp3</link>
  <description>This week, it's all about the dramatic events in Egypt. When the
Egyptian government shut down most telecommunications, Egyptians and activists
across the globe jumped in to keep communications flowing. Hear all about that,
plus a very nice email from listener Paul Gearon. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure
url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast317.mp3" length="12277254" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast317.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 05:15:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>25:17</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Egypt, #jan25, jan25voices, telecomix, censorship, filtering,
revolution, protests</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Sputnik Moment, Social Networks Past and Future, Clay Shirky, and Polar
Bears with Spycams</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast316.mp3</link>
  <description>This week, we've got a look back at the original "Sputnik moment."
Also, we start a multi-part series on social networking, and hear from big thinker
Clay Shirky on what socnets can, and can't do. And we'll end with polar bears
playing with spycams. All that, plus unicorns, double rainbows and cherry pie.
Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast316.mp3"
length="13137040" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast316.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 05:15:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>27:04</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Sputnik, Obama, Facebook, social networks, Clay Shirky, polar
bears, spycams</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Tunisian Update, Gaza Cyber-Activism, Stuxnet Update, Cyberwar!
Overhyped!!, and Wikipedia Turns 10</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast315.mp3</link>
  <description>In this week's episode you'll hear how one Tunisian tech
entrepreneur went from being an outspoken critic of the government, to being a
part of the government...with a brief stop in jail in between. Also, an update on
Stuxnet, and a new study that says "cyberwar" is both overhyped, and
misunderstood. Plus, we'll hear about cyber-activists in Gaza. And we'll wish
Wikipedia a happy 10th birthday. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology,
or join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast315.mp3"
length="13553538" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast315.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 05:45:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>27:56</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Tunisia, Stuxnet, computer virus, Gaza, Israel, cyberwar,
cyberattacks, wikipedia, Jimmy Wales</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Tunisian Update, DNA Spray Helps Nab Crooks, Computer History Museum, and
the Thing-o-Matic!</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast314.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 314 has an update on the situation in Tunisia, with a
special eye toward what's going on online. Also, a British company is making a
spray laced with synthetic DNA to help the cops connect crooks to a crime scene.
Then, a tour of the newly opened Computer History Museum in California. And we'll
end with, what else, the Thing-o-Matic! Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast314.mp3"
length="10709940" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast314.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 07:30:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>22:01</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Tunisia, DNA, synthetic DNA, Selectamark, Computer, computing
history, thing-o-matic</itunes:keywords>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>Tunisian Protests Go Online, Tech Helps Haitians Find Jobs, and Openleaks
is Open for Business</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast313.mp3</link>
  <description>WTP 313's got a great line-up for you. We'll talk Tunisia, where
street protests have spilled onto the Internet, and it's having serious
consequences for bloggers and activists in the country. Also, Konbit: a melding of
high and low-tech that's helping Haitians find jobs a year after a devastating
earthquake. And finally, we'll hear from Daniel Domscheit-Berg, formerly of
Wikileaks. He's launched a new whistleblowing site called Openleaks, and he'll
tell us about it. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on
Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast313.mp3"
length="15763910" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast313.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 11:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>32:33</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Haiti, MIT, Tunisia, Wikileaks, Openleaks, Konbit, bloggers,
censorship</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Mobile Banking in Haiti, IAEA Inspector Gadgets, Cuba's Homegrown
Wikipedia, and Robotic Limbs in Japan</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast312.mp3</link>
  <description>Episode 312 sees out 2010 with, what else, bagpipes! Yes, a little
Auld Lang Syne for you. Plus, some great tech stories, including a look at how
Haitians are banking on mobile banking. Also, the gadgets that an IAEA weapons
inspector gets to use, Cuba's homegrown Wikipedia, and robotic limbs to help the
disabled in Japan. Awesome sauce. Here's to a great 2011. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast312.mp3"
length="14495722" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast312.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 09:30:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>29:54</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>Haiti, mobile banking, IAEA, gadgets, Cuba, Wikipedia,
Terminator, robots, Japan</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>Leaks, Leaks and More WikiLeaks</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast311.mp3</link>
  <description>It's all about the leaks...WikiLeaks that is. We'll hit the story
from every angle, from the technical, to the poltical to the social. Don't just
hear about what's going on with WikiLeaks. Understand it. We'll hear from smart
'net people like Kevin Mitnick, Jeff Jarvis and Evgeny Morovoz. Visit the
homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast311.mp3"
length="15712871" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast311.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 10:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>32:26</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>WikiLeaks, Julian Assange, Kevin Mitnick, Evgeny Morozov, Jeff
Jarvis</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 310: Surely You Don't Expect Me to Download this Podcast...</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast310.mp3</link>
  <description>WTP 310 pays tribute to a giant in British computing, and a giant
in Canadian acting. Surely you don't mean Leslie Nielsen? Yes, we do...and stop
calling us Shirley. Also, we'll talk about the SIPRnet system and how hundreds of
thousands of State Department cables went from there to WikiLeaks. And the
European Commission is going to investigate Google, while engineers try to figure
out what's wrong with those Airbus 380 engines. Good luck, we're all counting on
you. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast310.mp3"
length="12529508" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast310.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 10:00:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>25:48</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, WikiLeaks,
Leslie Nielsen, Google</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 309: I Thought Turkeys Could Fly...</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast309.mp3</link>
  <description>Our special Thanksgiving Episode (for our US listeners), in which
no turkeys were actually thrown from a helicopter. We go deep into some newly
released, detailed forensic work on the Stuxnet computer worm. Also, we run a long
interview with Japanese entrepreneur, venture capitalist and web guru Joi Ito.
Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast309.mp3"
length="16771557" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast309.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 08:15:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>34:39</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Stuxnet, virus,
computer, worm, Joi Ito, internet</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 308: Tetris and Memory, Ushahidi Maps Sexual Harassment, iPhone App
Maps Israeli Settlements, and Cell Phone Learning in South Africa</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast308.mp3</link>
  <description>And...we're back. Great stories this week. We hear about a new
study looking at the effects of playing Tetris just after witnessing horrific
visions. Also, mapping sexual harassment in Cairo using Ushahidi. We'll talk about
a new iPhone app that looks at Israeli settlements, and find out how cell phones
are being used in South African schools. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast308.mp3"
length="9699694" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast308.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 05:45:00 EST</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>19:55</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Tetris,
Ushahidi, iPhone, apps, mobile, cell phones, South Africa,
Israel</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 307: The Relentless Deluge of Unwanted Drivel</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast307.mp3</link>
  <description>WTP 307's got some great stories. We'll talk about the new
supercomputer smackdown between China and the U.S., and hear about how some
Chinese are getting serious about gaming. Also, Russia's Spam King under fire.
Plus, Sony decides that the cassette Walkman has had its day, at least in Japan.
Oh, and we've got a big, juicy Star Trek appreciation, and some spooooky Halloween
fun. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast307.mp3"
length="15668852" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast307.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 05:45:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>32:21</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, China,
supercomputers Star Trek, Sony Walkman, spam</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 306: Oldweather.org, Flying Humvees, Inflatable Tanks, and
Remembering Benoit Mandelbrot</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast306.mp3</link>
  <description>This week, we hear about a citizen science project that allows you
to help climate scientists and naval historians at the same time. Also, the
Pentagon wants flying Humvees, while the Russians are getting inflatable tanks.
And we remember the father of fractals, Benoit Mandelbrot. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast306.mp3"
length="13362943" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast306.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 09:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>27:32</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, citizen science,
humvees, tanks, fractals, benoit mandelbrot</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 305: Robot Miners, Google's Self-Drive Cars, Internet Eyes, Cell
Tower Power for Vaccines, and A Whole New Chewing Gum</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast305.mp3</link>
  <description>WTP 305 has got it all, from non-stick, dissolving chewing gum, to
novel ideas for keeping vaccines cool in the developing world. In between, we'll
talk robot miners, self-driving cars, and the joys of watching the neighbors get
up to mischief on CCTV. Good times. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast305.mp3"
length="14022086" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast305.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 08:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>28:55</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Chile, miners,
Google, cars, Internet, vaccines, gum</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 304: Stuxnet, Haystack, and Hossein Derakhshan</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast304.mp3</link>
  <description>In this edition of our monthly Tech Roundup, we talk about the
Stuxnet computer worm that's invaded Iran. Also, what happened to the promise of
some anonymity software called Haystack? And, the fate of Canadian-Iranian blogger
Hossein Derakhshan. All that, plus -- the Internet gets nominated for the Nobel
Peace Prize! Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on
Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast304.mp3"
length="11432975" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast304.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 04:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>23:32</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Iran, Stuxnet,
computer virus, Haystack, Austin Heap, Hossein Derakhshan, Hoder</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 303: Iranian Blogger May Face Death Penalty, Germans say "Nein" to
Google Street View, Greener Electronics, and Whales Get High-Tech Help</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast303.mp3</link>
  <description> In this episode, you'll get an update on Hossein Derakhshan, the
Canadian-Iranian blogger who may be facing the death penalty in Iran. Also,
Germans say "nein" to Google Street View. Then, you'll hear about an effort to
make greener, fairer electronics. And we'll end with some high-tech help for
whales. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast303.mp3"
length="13375043" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast303.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 10:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>26:09</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Google, Iran,
Hoder, blog, street view, whales, fair trade</itunes:keywords>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>WTP 302: War Data, Smartphone Eye Exam, iStethoscope, The Optigan, and
Mario Turns 25</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast302.mp3</link>
  <description> WTP 302 has a ton of great stuff in it. We start with a story on
the millions of biometric records collected in Iraq during the past seven years.
Then, two segments on ingenious uses for smartphones - one for an eye exam, and
the other as a stethoscope. Then, we hear about the rebirth of a primative
electronic organ called the Optigan. And we end with a birthday celebration for
Mario. He's 25, but he doesn't look at day over 52. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast302.mp3"
length="13565040" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast302.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 07:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>27:58</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Iraq,
biometrics, smart phone, iPhone, Optigan, Mario Brothers, video
games</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 301: Tanzania Tries Solar, Your Brain on Internet, Things Speak Up,
and Mad Texting Skills</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast301.mp3</link>
  <description> WTP 301's got some great stories. We'll hear an in-depth report on
efforts to bring solar power to Tanzania, one of the world's poorest countries.
Also, how the Internet may be rewiring our brain circuitry. Yikes! We'll also look
at a project designed to  get everyday objects to tell their stories. And we end
with a woman who claims the crown of World's Fastest Texter. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast301.mp3"
length="11408185" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast301.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 08:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>23:28</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, texting, SMS,
solar power, Internet, brain, internet of things, Chris Speed</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 300: WikiLeaks, BlackBerry Bans, Google in Germany, NoKo No on
Twitter, and Rubik's Cube</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast300.mp3</link>
  <description> Well, we made it to Episode 300. Thanks for buying the ticket and
taking the ride. In this Tech Roundup episode, we're joined by Jonthan Fildes of
the BBC, and Cyrus Farivar of Deutsche Welle. We discuss WikiLeaks, BlackBerry
Bans, Google Streetview, North Korea's possible attempts at using social media,
and the maximum minimum number of moves needed to solve a Rubik's Cube. Fun.
Guaranteed. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on
Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast300.mp3"
length="17406735" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast300.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>35:58</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Twitter, North
Korea, WikiLeaks, Rubik's Cube, Google, Germany, Cyrus Farivar</itunes:keywords>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>WTP 299: Engineering the Indus, North Korea Turns to Twitter, Vietnam and
the Net, Einstein@Home, and Giant Humanoid Electrical Pylons</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast299.mp3</link>
  <description> A great line-up for WTP 299. We've got citizen scientists finding
pulsars, and electrical pylons shaped like giant humans. What, you want more? OK.
We'll also talk about how the Indus has been engineered, or mis-engineered. And
did you know North Korea's on Twitter, and YouTube? It's true! Plus, Vietnam tries
to figure out what to do with this thing called The Internet. All that, from the
Bayswater Hilton in London. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or
join us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast299.mp3"
length="12983705" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast299.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 06:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>26:45</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Twitter, North
Korea, Pakistan, Vietnam, Einstein@Home, pylons, Indus, engineering,
rivers</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 298: BlackBerry Bans, Indian Cops Turn to Facebook, Green Data
Centers in Finland, and Talking Tutor</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast298.mp3</link>
  <description> TThe tech desk is back in action with a full show. We'll talk
about plans to ban some BlackBerry services in Saudi Arabia and the United Arab
Emirates. Also, Delhi's Transit Police have turned to Facebook to out violators.
Then, to Finland where we'll hear about a scheme to harvest the heat from data
centers and use it to heat the local water supply. And, we end in Birmingham,
England, where we'll hear about the Talking Tutor! That's Tutor, not Tudor. Visit
the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast298.mp3"
length="11526045" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast298.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>23:43</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Facebook, India,
BlackBerry, green IT, Finland, Talking Tutor</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 297: Monthly Tech Roundup 2.0</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast297.mp3</link>
  <description> The second of our monthly tech roundups, with Jonathan Fildes of
the BBC. Jonathan and I talk about Facebook's 500,000 users worldwide. We also
look at some stories that Jonathan worked on from the TED conference in Oxford,
England. And we'll end with a trans-atlantic take on British hacker Gary McKinnon.
And we get help from Lisa Simpson herself! Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast297.mp3"
length="16349430" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast297.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>33:46</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Facebook, Lisa
Simpson, Ethan Zuckerman, SwiftRiver, Sugata Mitra, Twitter, Gary McKinnon, The
Simpsons, Yeardley Smith</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 296: WikiLeaks, Google Maps, Conflict Minerals, and Gary
McKinnon</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast296.mp3</link>
  <description> Wow. Just when we thought the tech news was slowing down for the
summer, we're hit with the WikiLeaks story. We've got two takes on WikiLeaks, tech
and the Afghan War. Also, Google Maps wades into some border disputes, and we hear
about some recently passed legislation on the so-called "conflict minerals" that
are in your precious electronic equipment. We end with an update on Gary McKinnon.
Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast296.mp3"
length="12752934" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast296.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>26:16</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, WikiLeaks,
Afghanistan, Google Maps, conflict minerals, Gary McKinnon</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 295: A Shameless Repeat of the Most Hated Episode Ever (w/ Ricky
Gervais)</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast295.mp3</link>
  <description> Yep. It's that time of year. News is slow, Clark is lazy. So,
we're doing what we hardly ever do. We're bringing you a repeat of one of the most
beloved, and loathed, episodes of all time. Yep, from February 2006, here's the
interview with Ricky Gervais, Stephen Merchant and Karl Pilkington. We wonder if
you *still* hate it? Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us
on Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast295.mp3"
length="14773356" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast295.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>30:29</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Ricky Gervais,
Stephen Merchant, Karl Pilkington, Monkey News</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 294: Solar Plane Soars, China and Google Make Nice, and The Pleasure
Telephone</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast294.mp3</link>
  <description> Here's the lineup for WTP 294. We've got an update on the Solar
Impulse project, which aims to have a solar-powered plane circumnavigate the
globe. Also, some interesting developments in China regarding Internet filtering.
And we end with an amazing look at some old school tech that resonates strongly
today. It's...The Pleasure Telephone! Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast294.mp3"
length="17271705" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast294.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>35:41</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Solar impulse,
solar power, Bertrand Piccard, Google, China, The Pleasure
Telephone</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 293: FITS.ME, Criminals on Facebook, Estonia's Johnny Appleseed of
Free Wi-Fi, and Lego World Cup Madness</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast293.mp3</link>
  <description> WTP 293 spends some more time in Estonia. We profile a start-up
that's using some serious robot technology to help you buy better fitting clothes
online. We also profile Veljo Haamer, the "Johnny Appleseed" of free wi-fi in
Estonia. Also in this episode: Interpol uses social networking sites to track down
some of the world's most wanted criminals, and a German Lego enthusiast recreates
the World Cup's finest, and worst, moments. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast293.mp3"
length="10515833" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast293.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>21:37</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, World Cup, FIFA,
Lego, Estonia, Fits.me, robots, wi-fi, Veljo Haamer, Facebook</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 292: Our Newly Minted Monthly Technology Round-Up</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast292.mp3</link>
  <description> WTP 292 is different, but in a good way. We're trying out
something new: a monthly tech round-up. At the end of each month, the BBC's
Jonathan Fildes and I will choose five or so stories that intrigue us, and we'll
talk in-depth about them. This month we've got Wikileaks, .XXX domain name, an
OLPC update, more on cyber-war, and whether technology and soccer refs will ever
mix. Good stuff. Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on
Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast292.mp3"
length="14724409" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast292.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>30:23</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, World Cup, FIFA,
Wikileaks, XXX, ICANN, soccer, cyber-security, OLPC, Jonathan
Fildes</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 291: Belgian Turf Tech at World Cup, Adopt a Flemish Person or
Walloon, and Cyber-Security Conference in Estonia</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast291.mp3</link>
  <description> Another cracking episode for you. We take a look at some high-tech
turf designed by a Belgian company that's getting a work out at the World Cup in
South Africa. Also, Dutch speakers and French speakers in Belgium just try to
create one big happy family online. And we end with some in-depth coverage from a
recent cyber-security conference in Tallinn, Estonia. Visit the homepage:
www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast291.mp3"
length="13269475" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast291.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>27:21</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, World Cup,
Desso, Cyber-security, cyber-war, Estonia, Bruce Schneier</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 290: Salad Spinner Centrifuge, Haiti Cell Phone Survey, Erasing
David, Solar Internet Cafe, Mars Mission in Russia, and World Cup Soccer
Ball</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast290.mp3</link>
  <description> WTP 290 is a bit late, but full of great stuff. We've got stories
on students modifying salad spinners into blood centrifuges, and on statisticians
using cell phones to survey Haitians. Also, one man's bid to outwit Britain's CCTV
cameras. Plus, astronauts strap themselves in for a manned mission to Mars, in
Russia. And finally, the World Cup soccer ball. Perfection, or perfidy? Visit the
homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast290.mp3"
length="15907329" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast290.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>32:50</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, salad spinner,
mobile phones, cell phones, Haiti, Computer Aid, World Cup</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 289: Google's Europe Woes, Facebook Blocked in Pakistan, Digital
Genome, ATM Inventor Dies, and Pac-Man Fever!</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast289.mp3</link>
  <description> This week we've got another great program. First up, Google's
privacy woes in Europe. Then, Pakistan cracks down on Facebook and YouTube. We'll
hear about how our digital genome is being buried in what's called the Swiss Fort
Knox. Also, a homage to the inventor of the ATM, and another homage to that pesky
little dot muncher, PacMan. That ravenous yellow mouth is now 30 years old. Visit
the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast289.mp3"
length="10981972" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast289.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>22:46</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Pac-Man, Google,
Facebook, Pakistan, ATM, Digital Genome, Swiss Fort Knox</itunes:keywords>
  </item>


<item>
  <title>WTP 288: Oil Spill Update, Laser Turns 50, Haystack in Iran, Latvia's
Robin Hood, and Robot Nurses in Japan</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast288.mp3</link>
  <description> WTP 288 features sharks with frickin' laser beams attached to
their heads. OK, not really. But we do have a birthday celebration for the laser,
which turned 50 this week. Also, an oil spill update and how the Soviets dealt
with gas leaks back in the day. Yikes. Also, Latvia's digital Robin Hood is
unmasked, and the Japanese might choose robots over immigrants. Visit the
homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast288.mp3"
length="16996735" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast288.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>26:01</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, oil spill, BP,
laser, Dr. Evil, Latvia, Iran, Austin Heap, Haystack, robots, nurses,
Japan</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 287: Hair and Hosiery vs. The Oil Spill, Inside GCHQ, and Design for
the First World</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast287.mp3</link>
  <description> In this episode, we hear about a plan to use human and animal
hair, and hosiery, to combat the effects of the oil spill in the Gulf of Mexico.
Also, we go deep inside Britain's top secret listening post, GCHQ, and hear about
the tech that makes it tick. Finally, an NYU grad student asks people in the
developing world to solve the developed world's problems. All that, plus the
Jetsons! Visit the homepage: www.theworld.org/technology, or join us on Facebook
at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast287.mp3"
length="16996735" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast287.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>35:18</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, oil spill, BP,
hair, matter of trust, gchq, Britain, sigint, signals intelligence, design for the
first world</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 286: Eruption!, Haiti Trash Turns to Charcoal, Russia's Hackers,
Spain's DVD Pirates, and Loudening Electric Cars</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast286.mp3</link>
  <description> And, we're back, following volcanoes, a transatlantic move to
Brussels, and super slow Internet. Hope it was worth the wait. We've got Haitians
turning trash into charcoal. We also try to find out why Russia produces such
great computer criminals, and why Spaniards won't pay for their DVDs. But the best
is the professor who wants to put more sound in the electric car. You know, for
safety's sake. More info at www.theworld.org/technology. We're on Facebook at
www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast286.mp3"
length="12274085" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast286.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>25:27</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Haiti, DVD,
piracy, Russia, hackers, electric cars, green tech </itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 285: Sats and Nukes, Online Extremism, CO2 into Fuel, and Such Tweet
Sorrow</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast285.mp3</link>
  <description> It's a great lineup with week. We'll hear about the role
satellites play in keeping track of nuclear weapons worldwide. We'll also have two
segments on online extremism, and hear about an academic who is carrying on an
ongoing online conversation with a jihadist. Then, some interesting research that
seeks to eventually turn CO2 into usable fuels. And we end by revisiting the
Apollo 13 mission, and hear about what happens when Romeo and Juliet met each
other on Twitter. Forsooth. More info at www.theworld.org/technology. We're on
Facebook at www.facebook.com/worldstechpod.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast285.mp3"
length="16445388" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast285.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 07:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>33:53</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, satellites,
nuclear weapons, Twitter, Shakespeare, Apollo 13, CO2 </itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 284: Geo-engineering, China's Shadow Network, and Cell Phones Fight
Drug Fakes</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast284.mp3</link>
  <description> In this tech podcast, we hear about a company that is using cell
phone text messaging and scratch off labels to help tackle the trade in
counterfeit drugs in Nigeria. We also have the story of China's Shadow Network of
hackers, and also the story of Red Star, North Korea's open source, but
not-so-open,operating system. And,we hear about how the Finnish post office wants
to scan snail mail, and email it on to you. More info at
www.theworld.org/technology.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast284.mp3"
length="17048909" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast284.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>35:09</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, China, Shadow
Network, geo-engineering, mobile phones, cell phones, drugs </itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
<item>
  <title>WTP 283: LHC Does the Business, Google and China, Afghan Net Censorship,
and I'm Halal Search Engine</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast283.mp3</link>
  <description> Perfect timing for a Tuesday relaunch of The World's Tech Podcast!
We've got some really big fireworks from the Large Hadron Collider in Switzerland.
Also, Google and China continue to make some online fireworks of their own. It has
us asking: is the Internet somewhere, or nowhere? Then, we hear that more Afghans
are getting online, and the government is getting nervous. And we end with "the
world's first halal search engine." Hmmm. All that, plus Ricky Gervais, Stephen
Merchant and Karl Pilkington. More info at www.theworld.org/technology.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast283.mp3"
length="12915259" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast283.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>26:32</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Large Hadron
Collider, Google, China, censorship, halal</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 282: Silicon Sweatshops, Wikileaks, Hacktivism, and Four Views on the
Internet's Future</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast282.mp3</link>
  <description> This week, we hear about a factory in China that helps make your
groovy high-tech touch screens. Trouble is, they're using a solvent that may be
causing them serious health problems. Also, we explore the Wikileaks website, and
hear about the rise of hacktivism. We end with four opinion pieces on the future
of the global Internet. 
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast282.mp3"
length="14491200" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast282.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>29:49</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, wikileaks,
hacktivism, silicon, Apple</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 281: South Koreans Go Off-Grid, Nigerians Go On-Grid, and Indians Try
to Find Love Online</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast281.mp3</link>
  <description> This week, we stay online (mostly). The US Treasury Department
gives the go-ahead to some new communications exports. Also, South Koreans fight
cyber-bullying. Then, the BBC asks a couple of South Korean families to disconnect
from the 'net, and connects a couple of farmers in Nigeria. Interesting things
ensue. And we end with a lovely little piece about Indians turning to the web to
find love.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast281.mp3"
length="13673905" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast281.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>28:07</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, South Korea,
cyberbullying, Nigeria, mobile phones, India, match-making, Austin
Heap</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 280: New Body Scanners, Cross Cultural Training Goes Online, Reliving
the Dot Com Bubble, and Voice Recognition Study</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast280.mp3</link>
  <description> This week, we take a few sideways glances at tech. First, new body
scanners are going in at some US airports. Will they make a difference? Also, Alex
Gallafent explores how cross-cultural business training is going online. We relive
those heady days before the dot com bubble burst a decade ago, and we hear about
some new research on voice recognition. Take the survey at
https://www.surveymonkey.com/s/pritechnology.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast280.mp3"
length="11956316" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast280.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>24:32</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, body scanners,
cross cultural training, dot com bubble, stephan paternot, voice
recognition</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 279: FUmanoids Prepare for RoboCup 2010, Google's Europe Woes, and
Latvia's Virtual Robin Hood</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast279.mp3</link>
  <description> This week, we start with a listener-generated segment on the team
that is currently second in the world when it comes to robotic soccer, at least in
the KidSize Humanoid league. They're called FUmandoids, and they're from Germany.
We'll also hear about Google's woes in Italy and beyond, and hear about Latvia's
virtual Robin Hood. We end with a segment on one library's plea to archive the
ever-changing Internet. Take the survey at
https://www.surveymonkey.com/s/pritechnology.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast279.mp3"
length="14622220" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast279.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 16:15:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>30:05</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, robots, soccer,
football, FUmanoids, Google, Europe, Italy, Foundem, Latvia, Robin Hood, British
Library</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 278: Robowarriors, Make Your Own Newspaper, and Pecha Kucha Redux,
and Goodbye</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast278.mp3</link>
  <description> We've got an in-depth look at the robowarriors of the future.
Also, the chance to make your own newspaper. And find out what the finished piece
on Pecha Kucha sounds like. Take the survey at
https://www.surveymonkey.com/s/pritechnology.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast278.mp3"
length="11708591" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast278.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 15:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>24:01</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Haiti, robots,
robowarriors, ron arkin, ethics, newspaper club, Pecha Kucha, Tokyo, design,
architecture</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 277: Swedish High-Tech Skiing Treadmill, sOccket, Iran Info Embed,
and Pecha Kucha for Haiti</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast277.mp3</link>
  <description> You'd be hard pressed to find another tech podcast quite like
this. We've got a high-tech cross-country skiing treadmill designed by Swedes, and
a soccer ball that stores energy and can power an LED light. Also, Cyrus Farivar
"embeds" with a group of information junkies trying to help Iranians communicate.
And we end with a "cool stuff listeners are doing" segment on Pecha-Kucha and
Haiti. Give to the podcast at www.pri.org/give.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast277.mp3"
length="15253118" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast277.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 13:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>31:24</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Haiti, skiing,
Olympics, GPS, sOccket, Iran, protests, censorship, Pecha Kucha, Tokyo, design,
architecture</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 276: Haiti Crisis Camps, Blue Nile Footbridge, Better Pint Glasses,
and Internet Addiction and Depression</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast276.mp3</link>
  <description> A great mix this week. We visit a Crisis Camp for Haiti, and hear
about the role radio played in the wake of the quake. Also, the design and
technology that goes into building a footbridge over the Blue Nile. And some new
designs for a better, safer pint glass for beer in Britain. And we end with a
study on Internet addiction and depression. Give to the podcast at
www.pri.org/give.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast276.mp3"
length="15475082" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast276.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 14:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>31:52</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Haiti, Crisis
Camps, radio, Blue Nile, pint glasses, Internet, addiction,
depression</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 275: Nope, Not a Single Thing About Apple's iPad</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast275.mp3</link>
  <description> This week, rural Nigerians weigh in on what an Internet connection
might mean. We revisit the push to make Internet access a human right for every
Finn. We have a wonderful history piece on the technology of television, and look
ahead to a day when 3D TV might go mobile. Give to the podcast at
www.pri.org/give.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast275.mp3"
length="15761063" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast275.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>32:28</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Nigeria,
Finland, broadband, television, John Logie Baird, Spunkshine, 3D
TV</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 274: Mapping Haiti, Tweak the Tweet, Clinton's Net Freedom Speech,
Two Views on Google and China, Haiti Redux</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast274.mp3</link>
  <description> More Haiti, and lots more on Google and China. Also, Clinton's
Internet Freedom Policy speech. Give to the podcast at www.pri.org/give.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast274.mp3"
length="18087996" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast274.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>37:19</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Haiti,
earthquake, Open Street Map, Ushahidi, google, china, Internet, Clinton,
censorship</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 273: Haiti, Google in China</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast273.mp3</link>
  <description> We have two stories on Haiti, and two takes on Google's decision
to possibly leave China. Give to the podcast at www.pri.org/give.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast273.mp3"
length="9351076" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast273.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2010 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>19:06</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Haiti,
earthquake, Ushahidi, Telecoms sans Frontieres, google, china</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 271: The Last Podcast...of 2009</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast271.mp3</link>
  <description> Back to the drones this week. We explore a report that insurgents
are pulling down the video feeds from Pentagon drones. Also, a former proponent of
social networking tools like Twitter in combatting repressive regimes has a change
of heart. Then, we hear about how different tech tools and platforms are helping
in times of crisis. And we end in Copenhagen, on a bicyle. Give to the podcast at
www.pri.org/give.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast271.mp3"
length="15806777" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast271.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>32:33</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, drones, evgeny
morozov, twitter, Iran, China, Wikipedia, crisis mapping, copenhagen, bicycles,
wheel, MIT</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 270: Drones, Virgin's SpaceShipTwo, NASA Telescope, Space Beer, and
The Bladerunner's Blades</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast270.mp3</link>
  <description> We spend alot of time in space this week. But first, the drones
that are patrolling the airspace over Pakistan and Afghanistan. Then, Virgin
Galactic rolls out its commercial spaceship for viewing, and NASA readies a really
cool new space telescope. Meanwhile, on Earth, Sapporo brews up a beer made with
barley that spent some time, as seeds, in space. Oh, and just what are Oscar
Pistorius' amazing prosthetic legs made of? We'll find out. Give to the podcast at
www.pri.org/give.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast270.mp3"
length="15020529" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast270.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>30:55</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, drones, Danger
Room, Virgin Galactic, NASA, beer, homer simpson, bladerunner</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 269: Cybercrime, Spam and How To Stop Them (Maybe) </title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast269.mp3</link>
  <description> In this episode, we tackle cybercrime. We've got our yearly
round-up of trends in cybercrime with Graham Cluley of the British anti-virus firm
Sophos. Also, law professor Susan Brenner offers up a new approach to combating
cybercrime. And we have an update on the story of Simon Cox, the intrepid BBC
reporter who set out to nail one of the world's most prolific spammers. Give to
the podcast at www.pri.org/give.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast269.mp3"
length="15890451" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast269.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>32:44</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, cybercrime,
spam, Sophos, virus, trojans, worms, Brenner, Cluley, Atkinson </itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 268: Homemade African Windmill, Internet Governance, Semtex, and Book
Six in the H2G2 Trilogy </title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast268.mp3</link>
  <description> Marvin the Paranoid Android gives the podcast a boost this week.
And fair enough, as we have an interview with Eoin Colfer, author of Book Six of
the Unaptly Named Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy Trilogy. Also, we talk Internet
governance, Semtex and homemade windmills in Africa. Cool. Give to the podcast at
www.pri.org/give.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast268.mp3"
length="16866456" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast268.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 15:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>34:46</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
William Kamkwamba, IGF, ICANN, Semtex, Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy, Eoin
Colfer </itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 267: Churchill Flunks Computer Test, Comet Fun, Samasource, and the
Pandemic Ventilator Project</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast267.mp3</link>
  <description>Happy Friday the 13th. We celebrate with music and stories about
luck, both good and bad. Churchill's speeches don't pass electronic muster, while
shorthand makes a case for itself. Also, trying to land a probe on a comet, and
trying to get IT work for those with few prospects at all. And, listener Clarence
Graansma tells us about his open source hardware project, the Pandemic Ventilator.
Give to the podcast at www.pri.org/give.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast267.mp3"
length="15407985" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast267.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>31:44</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
Churchill, shorthand, comet, space, Samasource, outsourcing, pandemic, flu, open
source </itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 266: World's Smallest FM Transmitter, Hossein Derakhshan and Persian
Blogs, and Digital Memory Redux</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast266.mp3</link>
  <description> This week, we hear about what's billed as the world's smallest FM
transmitter. Also, we ask you to weigh in on our discussion about appropriate
technologies for the developing world. Then, the strange case of Hossein
Derakhshan, and the wider world of Persian language blogs. Then, we revisit
digital memory. Give to the podcast at www.pri.org/give.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast266.mp3"
length="14683135" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast266.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>30:07</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd, FM,
blogs, Kenya, Iran, Persian, Hossein Derakhshan, Hoder, digital memory
</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 265: "Internet's" Birthday: 40 Years of Modulated Anarchy</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast265.mp3</link>
  <description> It's all about Internet this week. Our raison d'etre turned 40,
and we're here to celebrate in style with half an hour of stories about how it
came to be, what it is today, and where it's going tomorrow. Enjoy.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast265.mp3"
length="16590750" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast265.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2009 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>34:11</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
internet, UCLA, Kleinrock, Kline, Isaac Mao, ICANN, IDN, domain
names</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 264: EpiCollect, Electric Cars, and Political Tweets in the US and
UK</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast264.mp3</link>
  <description> This week's tech podcast comes to you not from Boston, but from
London. We speak to a researcher who is trying to bring the power of smartphones
to field data collection in the fight against infectious diseases. Also, as more
car makers come out with electric cars, how far does the technology still have to
go? And we end with a transatlantic comparison of political Tweets.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast264.mp3"
length="14114362" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast264.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 16:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>29:02</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
epicollect, david aanensen, mobile, applications, electric cars, green technology,
twitter, tweets</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 263: Cuba Cable Capers, Finns Get Right to Broadband, Twitter Trumps
Newspapers, and The Value of Forgetting</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast263.mp3</link>
  <description> Cuba gets word that not one, but possibly two, fiber optic cables
are headed its way. Also, the Tsunami Early Warning System gets a test run in the
Pacific, and Finns get the right to have broadband Internet access. Twitter gets a
big jump on a big story in Britain. And we have an extended conversation with
Viktor Mayer Shoenberger, author of Delete: The Value of Forgetting in a Digital
Age.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast263.mp3"
length="17368260" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast263.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>35:49</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
Cuba, fiber optic, finland, Internet, Twitter, tsunami, viktor mayer-schoenberger,
delete</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 262: Moon Crash, Peruvian Fog Nets, Nobel Prize in Physics, and
Trongs!</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast262.mp3</link>
  <description> Oh, what a show! NASA crashes two spacecraft into the moon. Don't
worry, they meant to do that. Also, in Peru, some ingenious folks are harvesting
water with huge fog nets. We give an audio nod to the winners of the Nobel Prize
in Physics. And we end with a nod to one of the interesting folks who listens to
The World's Technology Podcast. Eric Zimmerman tells us about Trongs! 
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast262.mp3"
length="15500842" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast262.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 14:40:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>25:40</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
Iran, Europe, electricity, meters, nanotechnology, Ignobels </itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 261: Europe takes on Iran Net Filtering, Smart Electricity Meters,
Nanotechnology Update, and the Ignobels</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast261.mp3</link>
  <description> Cyrus Farivar reports on an attempt by the EU to ban the sale of
Internet filtering hardware to Iran. Also, French and British takes on the idea of
smart electricity meters. We also hear an in-depth report on the future of
nanotechnology. And we end with a short preview of the World Science Podcast with
Rhitu Chatterjee.  
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast261.mp3"
length="15531311" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast261.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 14:40:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>31:59</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
Iran, Europe, electricity, meters, nanotechnology, Ignobels </itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 260: Potential AIDS Vaccine, Embrace Thermoregulator, Scottish
Earthworms, and Mumbai Cell Phone Symphony</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast260.mp3</link>
  <description> Scottish accordionist leads us off with a tune called Exhausted.
Then, on to big news about an AIDS vaccine that researchers contend can prevent
infections. Also, the Embrace thermoregulator, designed to save low birth weight
babies in the developing world. We chat about Scottish earthworms, and we hear a
cell phone symphony in Mumbai.</description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast260.mp3"
length="15303311" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast260.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2009 14:40:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>31:43</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
AIDS, HIV, vaccine, Embrace, Scotland, earthworms, cell phones, mobiles 
</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 259: Iraq Internet Regs, Africa Connected, NComputing, and Autism
Detection Software </title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast259.mp3</link>
  <description> It's Friday, I'm in Love. With technology, I mean. We've got a
look at a new measure that may curtail Internet access in Iraq. Also, Africa's
broadband fibre-optic cable goes live, and we'll get reactions. Stephen Dukker
from NComputing talks about how to turn one PC into 10 or more. And we end with
some software designed to detect autism in infants and children.</description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast259.mp3"
length="15917460" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast259.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 14:45:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>33:00</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
Africa, Internet, Kenya, Iraq, NComputing, Stephen Dukker, autism, software
</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 258: High-Speed Rail, Bamboo Trains, Bio-Truck Expedition,
Coltan/Congo Redux and Winston the High-Speed Pigeon </title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast258.mp3</link>
  <description> We take a look at global models for America's proposed high-speed
rail system, and then keep it real by dipping into the podcast archive for a piece
on Cambodia's Bamboo Railway. We talk about a unique bio-truck that will attempt
to go around the world, and hear about the downside of hybrid vehicle technology.
We go to Congo to hear about how mining for the materials that make your cell
phone work is making life miserable for the locals. And we end with Winston, the
high-speed data pigeon.</description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast258.mp3"
length="14119875" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast258.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 10:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>33:05</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
high-speed rail, bamboo trains, bio-truck, andy pag, coltan, congo, hybrid
vehicles, Winston, pigeon, internet</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 257: Recreating Pre-War Nagasaki in 3D, Ars Electronica 2009, and A
Brief History of GPS Drawing </title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast257.mp3</link>
  <description> Great show this week. Find out how students in Japan are using 3D
technology and people's memories to recreate pre-war Nagasaki. Also, we take you
to Linz, Austria for the Ars Electronica 2009 festival. We hear about a wind-up
vibrator. Yes, you read that correctly. And we'll explore a way to turn your urine
into fertilizer. We end with a tech podcast listener who imparts some serious
knowledge about GPS drawing on your host.</description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast257.mp3"
length="15960951" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast257.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 14:45:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>33:05</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
Nagasaki, 3D, Sketchup, Ars Electronica, vibrator, green, urine, fertilizer,
GPS</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 256: Cell Phones in the Classroom, Steam Car Redux, New Wikipedia
Guidelines, and Artificial Trees </title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast256.mp3</link>
  <description> No More Whining, that's our motto. This week: we meet a history
teacher who is letting his students fully embrace the tech that they are carrying
around. Also, we revisit the British steam car team trying to break a 100 plus
year old record. We have an interview with Wikipedia's Jimmy Wales on new editing
guidelines, and we hear about the trade in conflict minerals in Congo. We end, of
course, with artificial trees.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast256.mp3"
length="14636025" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast256.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2009 13:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>30:20</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd, cell
phones, mobiles, wikipedia, Jimmy Wales, steam car, artificial
trees</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 255: Botnets, Russia v. Georgia, Steam-Powered Car, Creative Commons
Flamenco, and Zombies!</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast255.mp3</link>
  <description> No one's listening anyway, so let's have some fun. We talk about
attempts to get international law to catch up with botnets. Also, a study details
last year's cyberspat between Russia and Georgia. We hear about a seriously fast
steam-powered car, and also about a flamenco and hip-hop mash-up that's got a real
creative commons feel about it. We end with zombies. How much more do you want? Oh
yeah, Dan Deacon and Quincy Jones provide light entertainment.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast255.mp3"
length="14100796" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast255.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>29:13</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
botnets, russia, georgia, steam, creative commons, flamenco, hip-hop,
zombies</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>WTP 254: Castle Building Gets Medeival, Solar Impulse, Driverless Cars,
and GPS Atari Art!</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast254.mp3</link>
  <description> We start with a tribute to the pioneer of that outstanding piece
of technology, the single body electric guitar. RIP Les Paul. Then, some builders
in France use 13th century tools and technology to build a castle from scratch.
Also, Bertrand Piccard and his quest to fly a solar powered plane around the
world. Then, driverless cars may be coming to Heathrow Airport. And we end by
featuring podcast stalwart Vicente Montelongo, who makes, well, some very
Atari-like art out of his San Francisco bike rides.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast254.mp3"
length="12347674" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast254.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 14:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>25:34</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark Boyd,
guedelon, solar impulse, bertrand piccard, geo-spatial drawing, gps,
atari</itunes:keywords>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>WTP 253: Sand Dunes Made from Bacteria, Electronically Enhanced
Borders, and WE CARE Solar</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast253.mp3</link>
    <description> We start with a geek's audio tribute to the late John Hughes,
director of Weird Science. Then, architect Magnus Larsson wants to build sand
dunes out of bacteria. Not just any sand dunes. We're talking thousands of miles
long in the Sahara. Whoah. Also, countries try to enhance their borders with, wait
for it, technology. And we end with an interview with Dr. Laura Stachel of WE CARE
Solar.
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast253.mp3"
length="14672154" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast253.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2009 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>30:24</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd, magnus larsson, DUNE, sand, bacteria, borders, WE CARE solar, solar
suitcase</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>WTP 252: Gary McKinnon Update, New Military Tech in Afghanistan, and
Pirate Parties Go Global</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast252.mp3</link>
    <description> Briton Gary McKinnon stands accused by the US government of
committing the biggest military computer hack of all time. McKinnon's been
fighting extradition to the US for three years. Today, we have an update on the
case. Also, the US Army tries out some new military technology in Afghanistan. We
explore the rise of Pirate Parties worldwide, and we hear about how outdated
Japanese political campaign laws are hampering Obama style elections. 
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast252.mp3"
length="11952291" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast252.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2009 14:45:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>24:44</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd, Gary McKinnon, hacking, military, Afghanistan, Pirate Party, Sweden, Japan,
elections</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>WTP 251: Apollo Mission Computers, Undersea Net Cables in Africa, and
Bamboo Bikes from Zambia</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast251.mp3</link>
    <description> Vertigo is now gone, so back to your regularly scheduled
technology podcast. We've got a great story on the computers used 40 years ago on
the Apollo 11 mission. Also, a series of fiber-optic cables go live in Africa,
bringing hope that affordable high-speed Internet access will be coming soon. And
also, a Zambian company starts to export its bamboo bicycles. 
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast251.mp3"
length="16733119" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast251.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>34:42</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd, Apollo 11, africa, seacom, cables, bamboo, bicycles,
Zambia</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>WTP 250: Tech in China and Iran, Air France 447, Codex Sinaiticus, and
Hal and the Big 5</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast250.mp3</link>
    <description> The Chinese government's trying to control information,
especially online information, coming from the city of Urumqi, which has been the
scene of violence this week. Also, global geeks try to help Iranians keep the flow
of information coming. We check in on the search for the black boxes for Air
France flight 447. Next, an ancient Bible finds a new home on the Internet, which
also happens to be the ONLY place the band Hal and the Big 5 have ever jammed
together.  
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast250.mp3"
length="13527788" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast250.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 14:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>28:01</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd, Iran, protests, Twitter, China, Facebook, AF 447, Codex Sinaiticus, Hal and
the Big 5</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
  
  
  <item>
    <title>WTP 249: Updates on Internet Filtering in Iran and China, One-on-One
with Ken Banks, and an Intercontinental Wedding via Skype</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast249a.mp3</link>
    <description> Updates on two stories we've been following in recent weeks.
First, the Iranian government continues to try to control the flow of on-line
information out of the country. We try to sort out Twitter fact from fiction with
regard to Iran. Also, China's new Internet filtering plan gets delayed. Then, we
have an extended conversation with Ken Banks, founder of FrontlineSMS. We end with
a Skype-enabled wedding ceremony between someone in China, and someone in Denver.
Cool.   
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast249a.mp3"
length="14198034" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast249a.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 14:05:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>29:25</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd, Iran, protests, Twitter, China, Skype, Green Dam, Ken Banks, Kiwanja,
FrontlineSMS</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
  
  
  
  
  <item>
    <title>WTP 248: Eco-cooker, Generation Google, Kiva in the US</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast248.mp3</link>
    <description> Three stories today: the first is a look at an impressive piece
of engineering – a cooker that its makers claim reduces carbon emissions by a
staggering degree.
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast248.mp3"
length="13402957" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast248.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2009 14:45:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>22:33</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd, Iran, protests, Twitter, Facebook, Apple, Persian, Farsi</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>WTP 247: Twitter and Other Social Media Tools in Iran</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast247.mp3</link>
    <description> It's all Iran this week, folks. Violence and protests have
flaired in Iran following last week's disputed election results. The government
moved quickly to shut down the flow of information out of, and into, the country.
But Twitter and other social media tools are keeping that flow of information
going. In fact, it's not a flow, but a flood. We'll take an in-depth look at how
vital social media tools have become in Iran in the wake of the elections.  
    Show notes, links and pics at tinyurl.com/wtpblog.
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast247.mp3"
length="13402957" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast247.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 14:45:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>27:46</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd, Iran, protests, Twitter, Facebook, Apple, Persian, Farsi</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>WTP 246: China Net Surveillance Gets Personal, Video Technology in
Sports, and Google Earth in Mozambique</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast246.mp3</link>
    <description> China announced new rules regarding PCs this week. Starting July
1, all PCs sold in China must contain a government mandated piece of software
designed to "protect Chinese youth" from pornography and violent content. Rights
groups are calling foul, and Internet experts say it's ripe for exploitation by
hackers and criminals. Also, we answer your calls for a segment on the use of
video technology in sports. And we end with a look at how a discovery on Google
Earth may help save a rain forest in Mozambique. Show notes, links and pics at
tinyurl.com/wtpblog.
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast246.mp3"
length="16413396" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast246.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>34:02</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd, China, censorship, Internet, sports, football, soccer, google, google
earth</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
  
  
  
  <item>
    <title>WTP 245: Iranian Elections Online, US Cybersecurity, Emergency ICT in
Pakistan, and Chinese Students Surveilled</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast245.mp3</link>
    <description> For this week's podcast, we look at how Iran's presidential
candidates are taking to the Internet to win votes. Also, President Obama's plans
to beef up America's cybersecurity. We check-in with ICT emergency responders in
Pakistan, and then we hear about just how many surveillance cameras will be
trained on Chinese students during their national exams this weekend. Music by The
Hold Steady. Show notes, links and pics at tinyurl.com/wtpblog.
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast245.mp3"
length="13536412" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://www.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast245.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2009 14:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>28:02</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd,Iran, cybersecurity, Obama, Pakistan, World Food Program, China, surveillance
</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>WTP 244 "Vacation Edition:" Wind Power in Antarctica, OR318, Sherlock
Holmes Lives!, and The Photographer</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast244.mp3</link>
    <description> A special "vacation" episode this week. We have two tech stories
to start. The first is out of Antarctica, where the Belgians have built a base
camp that produces all of its own energy by using a Scottish company's wind
turbines. Then, an online movement to commemorate the life and death of Iranian
blogger Omid Reza Mirsayafi. In honor of vacation, we take a break from tech. We
talk about the enduring legacy of Sherlock Holmes, and we hear about an amazing
new graphic novel that charts the journey of one photographer into war-torn
Afghanistan in the mid-1980s. Show notes, links and pics at tinyurl.com/wtpblog.
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast244.mp3"
length="17242633" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://www.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast244.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 20:50:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>35:46</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd, wind energy, bloggers, iran, sherlock holmes, sir arthur conan doyle, the
photographer, comics, graphic novel</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>WTP 243: EU Puts Hurt on Intel, Persian Bloggers on Saberi's Release,
Google Oceans Goes Deep, and SixthSense at MIT</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast243.mp3</link>
    <description> We start this week with a look at how, and why, the European
Union leveled a world of financial hurt on US chip-maker Intel. Wow, the EU
dislikes someone more than it dislikes Microsoft! Also, journalist Roxana Saberi
is released from prison in Iran, the Persian language blogs are buzzing. We'll
have a sample. Then, Google Oceans tries to bring mapping help to endangered coral
reefs. And finally, a very interesting MIT Media Lab project called SixthSense.
No, it's not about seeing dead people. But it will display your email on an
airport wall. Show notes, links and pics at tinyurl.com/wtpblog.
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast243.mp3"
length="13035896" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://www.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast243.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2009 16:30:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>27:00</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>WTP 242: Vodafone Wireless Innovation Project, UK DNA Database, Swine
Flu Listener Questions Answered, and Airplanes!</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast242.mp3</link>
    <description> We start the show with three projects that have been chosen as
the winners of Vodafone's Wireless Innovation Project. All three harness the power
of wireless technologies in pursuit of social good. Then, an in-depth look at the
UK's DNA database, and what America's plans are for a similar database. Also, we
try to answer some of the great questions you sent in about the swine flu virus.
And we end with another competition; Airbus wants to know if you can figure out
how to use engineering to make flights cheaper. Show notes, links and pics at
tinyurl.com/wtpblog.
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast242.mp3"
length="18741459" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://www.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast242.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2009 17:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>38:53</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>WTP 241: Google Book Search, World Digital Library, E-Books, Psiphon,
and Yahoo's Purple Pedals</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast241.mp3</link>
    <description> We start out all bookish this week. We hear about Google's plan
to digitally scan every book in the world, and make those books available to
everyone with an internet connection. Also, UNESCO wants in on that action too,
with a project called The World Digital Library. Then, an in-depth look at
e-publishing; are paper books a thing of the past? Then, we hear about some
Internet filtering circumvention technology called Psiphon. And we end with
Yahoo's bid to trick out bikes with net cams and geo-location software. Show
notes, links and pics at tinyurl.com/wtpblog.
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast241.mp3"
length="12672021" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://www.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast241.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>26:14</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
  
  
  <item>
    <title>WTP 240: Pirate Bay Founders in the Brig, Obama Tech Policy, and Domo
Arigato Mr. Roboto</title>
    <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast240.mp3</link>
    <description> Sorry we're a couple of days late, but so it goes. First, we
look at the Swedish court ruling against the founders of The Pirate Bay. We have
an explainer and analysis on that. Also, how is Barack Obama's embrace of new
technologies during the campaign playing out now that his administration is in
power? And we end with a segment on robots. Lovely. Show notes, links and pics at
tinyurl.com/wtpblog.
    </description>
    <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast240.mp3"
length="13453594" type="audio/mp3" />
    <guid>http://www.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast240.mp3</guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2009 14:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:duration>27:52</itunes:duration>
    <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech
podcast, technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

<item>
  <title>WTP 239: Twitter Revolution in Moldova?, Urban Pac-Man, Spies in the
Electricity Grid?, Extremist Websites, A Winning Solar Oven, and
GoogleLitTrips</title>
  <link>http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast239.mp3</link>
  <description> An incredibly packed show this week. First, to Moldova to find out
what role Twitter and other social networking sites have played in the protests
there. Then to France for Urban Pac-Man! Also, two hits on tech and security. Are
there Russian and Chinese spies pinging the US electricity grid? And are extremist
websites being hosted on servers in the United States? Good questions. We also
hear about an award-winning solar cooker, and about GoogleLitTrips. Show notes,
links and pics at tinyurl.com/wtpblog.
  </description>
  <enclosure url="http://media.theworld.org/pod/tech/WTPpodcast239.mp3"
length="22214766" type="audio/mp3" />
  <guid>http://64.71.145.108/pod/tech/WTPpodcast239.mp3</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 15:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:duration>46:07</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>the world, bbc, wgbh, public radio, pri, world's tech podcast,
technology podcast, tech podcast, the world's technology podcast, Clark
Boyd</itunes:keywords>
  </item>

</channel>
</rss>

