<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West</title>
<description>"Getting Your Money's Worth", the new TV talk show hosted by Judith West, a well-known New York manufacturer and longtime guest on other TV and radio talkshows, is about added value for your dollars and your life.</description>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com</link>
<image>
<url>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/Value.jpg</url>
<title>Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com</link>
<description>"Getting Your Money's Worth", the new TV talk show hosted by Judith West, a well-known New York manufacturer and longtime guest on other TV and radio talkshows, is about added value for your dollars and your life.</description>
</image>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2009</copyright>
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
<webMaster>bachmaster@bachorgan.com (Dan Long)</webMaster>
<ttl>60</ttl>
<atom:link href="http://gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

<item>
<title>Amy J. Schwartz / Katherine S. Lobach</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-142b.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-142b.wmv</guid>
<description>New York State has a mandate that school children have 120 minutes each week of physical education.  Guess what?  Many educators are unaware of this requirement.  One of the missions of Amy Schwartz, Physical Education in City Public Schools Task Force Chair, N. Y Women's City Club, and Katherine Lobach, former Assistant Commissioner of Child and Adolescent Health, NYC Dept. of Health, is to raise awareness of this requirement. And, more importantly, to emphasize the importance and benefits of physical education for our children. They are organized and they are serious.  Learn more about what's being done on Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-142b.wmv" length="75060000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 17:26:52 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dr. Robert F. Hurley</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-142a.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-142a.wmv</guid>
<description>Management and leadership in business are enhanced by learning the ability to "trust" and trust can be learned, according to Dr. F. Robert Hurley, author, THE DECISION TO TRUST.  There are certain elements to consider when deciding to put your trust others.  Assess similarities between you and the other person; does that person care about others; is the person capable; does the person communicate well; do you have an alignment of interest and do you share the same network? "If you go through life not trusting, you lose out, " asserts Dr. Hurley. Learn more on Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-142a.wmv" length="71704000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 17:23:07 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Curtis Rodgers</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-141b.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-141b.wmv</guid>
<description>Veterans have served their country well and are now ready to move on.  Columbia University School of General Studies aggressively recruits veterans to do just that. The broad-based student veteran population is older and experienced and there is interest by the work force in corporate America in attracting these individuals.  Columbia has a "robust career center for education that assists in resume preparation and contacting employers," says Curtis Rodgers, recruiter for Columbia.  Some people don't realize that the G.I. Bill that started with World War II still exists today. Learn more about how this top-notch Ivy League University works with it's veteran population on Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-141b.wmv" length="77036000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 17:20:42 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Kathleen Kalmes</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-141a.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-141a.wmv</guid>
<description>SIBL is an acronym for the N.Y. Science, Industry and Business Library on Madison Ave. and 34th Street that offers financial literacy programs.  All for free. Library personnel give information, not advice, but Certified Financial  Planners are available from the N. Y. Financial Planning Association for one-on-one consultations. Programs include classes, literature and data bases, credit crises counseling and a job search center. This month, anyone with an income of $48,000 or less can receive assistance in filing their taxes on line.  Kathleen Kalmes, Financial Resources Specialist for the library gives Money Matters information to Judith West on Getting Your Money's Worth.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-141a.wmv" length="79502000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 17:15:58 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Kate Maxwell</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-140b.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-140b.wmv</guid>
<description>JETTERSETTER.com is an on-line concierge service for members only, but membership is open to everyone.  Specialty is matching travelers up with curated hotels, hotels that have been vetted by a Jetsetter correspondents who have actually slept in the rooms, ordered room service and tried out Wi-Fi services. For $200 you can get three hours of planning services for one trip. Hotels have actually been pulled from the service due to bad feed-back from consumers. They offer a Flash for limited sales of up to 30 to 50 percent hotel discounts. Members receive weekly or monthly emails.  Kate Maxwell, editor-in-chief, JETSETTER, gives more information to Judith West on Getting Your Money's Worth.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-140b.wmv" length="75000000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 22:46:19 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>David Gillcrist</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-140a.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-140a.wmv</guid>
<description>Project FIND is a "find".  This not-for-profit organization, headed by David Gillcrist, executive director, assists seniors in living independently providing housing and essential services. Funded with city, state and private monies, Project FIND operates five senior centers serving over 730 people a day and more than 215,000 meals annually; a range of healthy aging activities; and nearly 600 units of affordable housing with in house social services. Their services are explored on Getting Your Money's worth with Judith West.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-140a.wmv" length="75000000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 22:43:49 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Marie Danielle Vil-Young</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-139b.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-139b.wmv</guid>
<description>"I'm a sucker for weddings", says Marie Danielle Vil-Young, founder, A Votre Service Events.  And weddings are a big part of her event business.  Anyone can benefit from a wedding planner, with average weddings in the Northeast costing upwards of $28,000.  Vil-Young gives tips on areas to consider if you want to be economical: (1) The guests list. Invite people who are really important to you; (2) Control the formality such as style of reception (buffet, cocktail hour), and (3) Day of the week - a Sunday morning or afternoon as opposed to a Saturday evening. Learn more on Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-139b.wmv" length="75000000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 23:16:26 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Kate Adamick</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-139a.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-139a.wmv</guid>
<description>There are two myths about serving good food to children in schools:  One, there's not enough money and two, kids wont eat it.  Kate Adamick, co-founder, Cook for America, proves the reverse and her program teaches school food service workers around the country how to cook. As for money, Adamick has found ways to use the funds from government sources more efficiently for schools and she says, "kids absolutely eat real food". Former attorney turned chef, Adamick gives details of her program on Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-139a.wmv" length="75000000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 23:11:55 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Marshall Ulrich</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-138b.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-138b.wmv</guid>
<description>Three-thousand sixty-three miles in 52 days at age 57, running from San Francisco to New York City, one of Marshall Ulrich's extreme accomplishments. His book, RUNNING ON EMPTY, details his life from learning that his first wife was dying of cancer at age 28, and escaping his problems through running to coming full circle learning to love again. Now he's learned to run for pleasure, but still inspires other to accomplish more than they think they can.  Hear his motivating story on Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-138b.wmv" length="75000000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 23:08:05 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dr. Mark Banschick</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-138a.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-138a.wmv</guid>
<description>Most important rule during a divorce, according to Dr. Mark Banschick, is take a deep breath, realize that life isn't fair, but you're going to have a life ahead and protect the innocence of your children.  Author of THE INTELLIGENT DIVORCE, Banschick advises parents considering divorce to keep animosity behind closed doors observing inter-generational boundaries.  More good advice from Banschick is available on Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-138a.wmv" length="75000000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 23:05:12 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dr. Michael Uttendorfer</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-137b.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-137b.wmv</guid>
<description>The volume of homework for kids has drastically increased proportionately to the emphasis in the past few years on testing.  Dr. Michael Uttendorfer, Dean, NYIT School of Education, believes there can be too much homework. He feels most homework is just practice rather than work that builds skills. Studies show that the amount of homework for elementary ages has no bearing on their ability to perform.  Dr. Uttendorfer and Judith West have an interesting discussion on this topic on Getting Your Money's Worth.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-137b.wmv" length="75000000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 10:30:34 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Larry Gutman</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-137a.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-137a.wmv</guid>
<description>Larry Gutman, retired New York City teacher, stated in a Letter to the Editor that "there is no mystery about quality education".  Small classes, individualized attention, enrichment and remediation lead to good students. The dilemma is that urban public schools don't have resources to provide these advantages.  "Starting in lower grades with small classes, especially in areas with many social problems, would be a way to start changing things," Gutman says.  More ideas are generated on Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West. </description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-137a.wmv" length="75000000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 10:28:28 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Mark Solasz</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-136b.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-136b.wmv</guid>
<description>Master Purveyors, a New York, family-owned business opened by Sam Solasz in 1957, is committed to handling only the country's finest meats. Carrying on the tradition, Mark Solasz, assistant vice-president, gives tips on the tastiest cuts of beef (from the steer, the male animal, not the cow, the female). He points out that tastier cuts are more muscular.  To economize during holidays, he suggests shell steaks which hold their price while rib eye and filet mignon prices soar.  Learn more from Mark about good meat eating on Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-136b.wmv" length="75000000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 10:26:11 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>James Adams</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-136a.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-136a.wmv</guid>
<description>From hedge fund manager to fast food employee, James Adams has a fascinating story. Burnt out by the Wall Street debacle and suffering a job loss, Adams needed a complete change.  He couldn't get hired by McDonald's, but Waffle House, a southern chain, gave him an opportunity to clear his head and learn that "there's no such thing as a free lunch."   Working with people who had fewer opportunities in life confirmed his belief  in the Golden Rule.  He gives advice to the unemployed on Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-136a.wmv" length="75000000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 10:22:55 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Craig Shields</title>
<link>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW-135b.htm</link>
<guid>http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-135b.wmv</guid>
<description>We borrow a billion dollars a day to send to people who virtually hate us to purchase oil.  Craig Shields, author, RENEWABLE ENERGY, states that "few people do not believe that we have to wean ourselves off fossil fuels".  We're running out of oil while renewable energy such as wind, sun and water never go away. Shields points out that we receive 6,000 times more energy from the sun every day than all seven billion of us can use. He presents a strong argument on Getting Your Money's Worth with Judith West.</description>
<enclosure url="http://www.gettingyourmoneysworthnyc.com/GYMW/GYMW-135b.wmv" length="71758000" type="video/wmv" />
<category>Education</category>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 22:00:29 EST</pubDate>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>

