<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Alert! Podcasts</title>
<link>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/</link>
<language>en</language>
<copyright>Jazztronaut</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle>The Exclusive Podcasts of Alert!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>These Podcasts are made by the artists performing in Alert!, wich is part of the VW Spring Sessions music festival, and contains interviews, fun stories, new tracks, special recordings...</itunes:summary>
<description>These Podcasts are made by the artists performing in Alert!, wich is part of the VW Spring Sessions music festival, and contains interviews, fun stories, new tracks, special recordings...</description>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Tony Lemarinel</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>tony@jazztronaut.be</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/images/logo-itunes.jpg" />
<itunes:category text="Music"/>

<item>
<title>Marcus</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Marcus aka Stephane Matten, Davy Standaert and Geert Standaert is a live electro trio that stands for fat riffs and floating atmospheres.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Marcus aka Stephane Matten, Davy Standaert and Geert Standaert is a live electro trio that stands for fat riffs and floating atmospheres. Their first single 'Weekend in Paris' was played on Belgian radios such as Studio Brussel, Pure FM and NRJ. 
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/alert2008marcus.mp3" length="23240923" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/alert2008marcus.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 2 May 2008 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>24:12</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>marcus, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>The dIPLOMAT</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>The dIPLOMAT is a newcomer in the Belgian music scène but the band definitely didn’t miss it’s entry.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>The dIPLOMAT is a newcomer in the Belgian music scène but the band definitely didn’t miss it’s entry: their recently released debute is getting wildly acclaimed. And the single “Sentimental Zoo” immediately got picked up by Pure FM radio. Expect high quality melodic poprock from a band that will convince you to add their album to your record collection. Can you face the challenge?
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/alert2008diplomat.mp3" length="18389368" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/alert2008diplomat.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 April 2008 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>9:35</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>dIPLOMAT, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Dallas Explosion</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>The Dallas Explosion just released it's first official single "The Closer You Can Get".</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>The Dallas Explosion just released it's first official single "The Closer You Can Get". In the meantime computers are slowly but steadily taking over the world. That's what this podcast is all about. Que? Just listen.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/alert2008dallasexplosion.mp3" length="6949292" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/alert2008dallasexplosion.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 1 April 2008 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:14</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>the dallas explosion, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Team William</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Team William offers an orchestrated chaos of poppy tunes and vocal experiments.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Team William offers an orchestrated chaos of poppy tunes and vocal experiments. Rock attitude combined with the catchiness of pop. Last Sunday they won the bronze medal in the final of Humo’s Rock Rally, Flanders most prestigious rock competition. We dedicated a podcast to this nice performance. 
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/alert2008teamwilliam.mp3" length="7930462" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/alert2008teamwilliam.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 20 March 2008 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>11:01</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>team william, humo’s rock rally, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Sedan Vault</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Check out The Sedan Vault podcast.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Dirty Classic Rock that ain't classic yet? or Retro influences with a 21st century sound? or Soul, rhythm and blues influenced rock music? You decide! Check out The Sedan Vault podcast. 
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/tsv.mp3" length="626410" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/tsv.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 March 2007 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>4:40</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>the sedan vault, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Amon Tobin</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Check out the Amon Tobin podcast and listen how his newest album 'Foley room' sounds like.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Elektronica, samples and experimental soundscapes... Amon Tobin got'em all! Check out the Amon Tobin podcast and listen how his newest album 'Foley room' sounds like. 
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/amontobin.mp3" length="4846190" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/amontobin.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 March 2007 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>36:09</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>amon, tobin, foley room, elektronica, sounscapes, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Scarrots</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>This exclusive Scarrots podcast starts with the rough demo – garage – acoustic version of track ‘Arrows of light’ to result in the final studioversion.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>The Sound Of Being Lost, an album full of contagious tracks. This exclusive Scarrots podcast starts with the rough demo – garage – acoustic version of track ‘Arrows of light’ to result in the final studioversion.
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/scarrots.mp3" length="925545" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/scarrots.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 March 2007 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>6:54</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>scarrots, arrows of light, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>DJ Prinz</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>DJ Prinz, resident @ Cafe d'Anvers</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Live from Cafe d'Anvers, the set from DJ Prinz during Push-It 1 year Birthday Bash. Some deep tunes, old skool house, minimal en electro from Belgium most colourfull DJ!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/djprinz.mp3" length="3550940" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/djprinz.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 March 2007 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>26:29</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>dj prinz, push it, cafe d'anvers, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Las Vegas Basement</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Las Vegas Basement is a wicked, energetic Irish band.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Las Vegas Basement? Las Vegas Basement is a wicked, energetic Irish band. We let the quotes speak for themselves: “Las Vegas Basement "play it like it's 1967 all over again" - Ritchie Taylor (The Sun), "At last a band that makes you want to dig out your old vinyl collection" - Eddie Rowley (Sunday World), "This group is very convinced of something and is screaming out it's soul to us in music and strange shuddering noise" - Tara McCarthy (Hot Press), "I sat with a plate of peppermints and sugarcubes, with bubbles of music floating round my head" - Paul O'Mahoney (Hot Press).
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/lasvegas.mp3" length="3375775" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/lasvegas.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2006 17:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>14:03</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>las vegas basement, irish, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jack Lukeman</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Irish music? Celtic noises? No, you don’t need to take folkdancing classes for these recordings!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Irish music? Celtic noises? No, you don’t need to take folkdancing classes for these recordings! Jack Lukeman is a multi platina selling singer-songwriter in Ireland. His voice has been compared with those of Scott Walker, Frank Sinatra, Jim Morrison and Tom Waits and last but not least ‘The Voice’ Jacques Brel. At the end of 2005, he released ‘The Brussels Album’ (only in Belgium), dedicated to Brel. Lots of great critics followed. This fall, he will be back with a great new album!
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/lukeman.mp3" length="2410441" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/lukeman.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2006 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>10:02</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>jack lukeman, jacques, brel, irish, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dallas Explosion</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Busy days for Belgian rockband Dallas Explosion...</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Busy days for Belgian rockband Dallas Explosion. A new album ‘Demon In My Pants’ coming up and lots of steaming liveshows. We’re very happy they still found some time to record an exclusive podcast which contains their first single and in which we also get a pre-listening to some other tracks from their upcoming album! (Don’t miss the introduction…)
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/dallasexplosion.mp3" length="4953467" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/dallasexplosion.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2006 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>20:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>dallas, explosion, belgian, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>DEDOS</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>A cocktail of P-funk, disco, chill, psychedelic and rock...</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>A cocktail of P-funk, disco, chill, psychedelic and rock, that’s the best way to describe the music of our own Belgian Dedos. This wicked band recorded an even more wicked podcast. Be prepared...
</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/dedos.mp3" length="2278946" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/dedos.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2006 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>9:29</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>dedos, belgian, funk, disco, psychedelic, rock, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Picastro</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Do you want to hear some tourstories from Canadien band Picastro?</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Do you want to hear some tourstories from Canadien band Picastro? Then check out the exclusive recording of singer Liz Hysen. The recording also contains a fresh new track. So don't miss the premiere! Picastro will be in Belgium for the first time on 6-7-9 April.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/picastro.mp3" length="5030371" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/picastro.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 4 Apr 2006 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>20:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>picastro, canadien, tour, stories, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>10 years of Hospital Records</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Check out this podcast with the exclusive mix of Hospital Records!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>To start preparing for a wicked Drum 'n Bass party, check out this podcast of Hospital Records exclusively mixed for Alert! Attention: we're not responsable for any Hospitalisations...</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/hospitalrecords.mp3" length="4571186" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/hospitalrecords.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2006 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>19:02</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>hospital, records, 10, year, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Lady Linn and her Magnificent Seven</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Get blown away by the accoustic recording of Lady Linn and her saxplayer</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Lady Linn naked? Yes indeed: get blown away by the accoustic recording of Lady Linn and her saxplayer. Convinced by her talent? Then definitely come and join us next Wednesday 29 March at Kultuurkaffee Brussels.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/ladylinn.mp3" length="1721749" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/ladylinn.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2006 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>7:10</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>lady, linn, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Larry</title>
<itunes:author>Jazztronaut</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Check out the exclusive interview in which Larry tells us a bit more about her career and motivation</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Larry is haunting Australia for the moment, but we have our own cyclone... Check out the exclusive interview in which Larry tells us a bit more about her career and motivation but in which she also shares some fun stories. And we even get a pre-listening on her recording for TROS Muziekcafé! The lucky ones that got a ticket will see her live on 31 March at AB-club Brussels. The concert is SOLD OUT.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/larry.mp3" length="8344997" type="audio/mpeg" />
<guid>http://www.vwspringsessions.be/alert/podcasts/larry.mp3</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2006 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>34:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>larry, blue, blot, alert, vw, spring, sessions</itunes:keywords>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>