<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
 
<channel>
<title>100 Marathons for PTSD Awareness</title>
<link>http://www.raceto100.co.uk</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>&#x2117; &amp; &#xA9; 2011 Advanced System Technologies Ltd.</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle>Running 100 Marathons in 100 Weeks to Raise Awareness of PTSD</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Find out what motivated PTSD sufferer Simon to attempt to run 100 marathons in 100 days and keep up to date with his progress</itunes:summary>
<description>Disagnosed with Post Traumatic Stress Disorder after serving in the armed forces Simon has tried to come to terms with living with this condition. This podcast gives you a no holds barred and very candid view into Simon's world and his amazing challenge to run 100 marathons in 100 weeks. You can follow Simon on Twitter - @100mara100weeks.</description>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Simon Buckden</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>simon@raceto100.co.uk</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/images/podcast-image.jpg" />
<itunes:category text="Sports &amp; Recreation">
<itunes:category text="Outdoor"/>
</itunes:category>

<item>
<title>Episode 13 - another tough week</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Our second live show on Ustream.tv, made available as a podcast the following day</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. Another hell of week for Simon but he soldiers on. Another marathon completed and he answers some questions from our listeners. Apologies for the quality of the audio this week but we had a few issues with the connection to Romania. It does get better after the first couple of minutes so hang in there!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-13.mp3" length="28014259" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 21:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>58:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>romania, marathon, barefoot running, mental health, ptsd, depression, anger, charity, foundation, mental illness, help for heroes, h4h, joggin, marathon training</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 12 - Year 2 of the Challenge!</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>We are now broadcasting the show live on uStream at 9pm GMT on a Tuesday</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. As it`s a new year we decided to recap on who the 3 of us are and why Simon is doing the 100 marathons in 100 weeks challenge. Simon also talks about why he is in Romania at the moment and what the plans are for the rest of the year and beyond including the Simon Buckden Foundation.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-12.mp3" length="22640558" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 21:00 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>46:51</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>romania, huaraches, barefoot, marathon, barefoot running, mental health, ptsd, depression, anger, charity, foundation</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 11 - Last Episode of 2011</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>This week we have a special guest in Simon Blackwell who is the Race to 100 Project Manager</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. Simon and Simon announce the next challenge which will take place in the USA! There is some exciting news about an event that will be taking place in 2012 to help raise funds for the challenge. Simon has some equally exciting news about the 2012 olympics. There is a winner in our Sunwise re-tweet competition and Simon and Simon get all excited when discovering the oldest toilets in Leeds!</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-11.mp3" length="20131967" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 13:16 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>41:55</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>olympics, leukaemia, marathon, barefoot running, mental health, ptsd</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 10 - Marathons 36 and 37</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>It's been a busy couple of weeks for Simon with radio, TV and newspaper appearances as well as speaking engagements and oh yeah, 2 marathons as well!</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. After a week off from the podcast we have a packed show with updates from Simon on the 2 marathons he has run since the last episode one of which he rates as his 2nd best so far. Simon also talks about the PTSD symptom of addictions.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-10.mp3" length="96778477" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 14:04 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:20:38</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>drug addiction, alcohol addiction, parkrun, marathon, barefoot running, mental health, ptsd</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 9 - Simon's Back!</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>After food poisoning kept him in bed (and the bathroom!) last week Simon is back and ready for his next marathon</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. Simon attends Remembrance Sunday, has some words of wisdom for Chris and is raring to get out there and run marathon 36. He also talks about the PTSD symptom "emotional numbness".</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-9.mp3" length="34091177" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 16:30 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:11:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>rememberance sunday, luton marathon, barefoot running, , mental health, ptsd</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 8 - PTSD From an Abusive Relationship - Interview</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>PTSD can occur for many reasons. This week we interview a very brave lady who suffered domestic abuse.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>* YOU MAY FIND THIS EPISODE VERY UPSETTING  * Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. Simon ends up in hospital with food poisoning and the lack of sleep means his PTSD symptoms rear their ugly head. He is not able to record the podcast so we have an extended interview with a very brave lady who has PTSD after suffering physical, mental and sexual abuse.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-8.mp3" length="12467431" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 9 Nov 2011 12:36 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>25:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>domestic abuse, sexual abuse, physical abuse, mental abuse, mental health, ptsd</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 7 - A Tough Week</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Simon's PTSD takes him to a very low point but he manages 1 of the 2 planned marathons this week</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. In this week's episode Simon talks emotionally about why he had to miss one of the two marathons planned. We have an interview with a massage / touch therapist specialising in PTSD and we have a new weekly feature - Simon's Stars</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-7.mp3" length="35729995" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 1 Nov 2011 16:21 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:14:23</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>massage, touch therapy, first marathon, newcastle marathon, twitter, facebook, trauma, mental health, injury, help for heroes, ptsd, marathon, running, endurance, jogging, training</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 6 - Marathon 34</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Festival of Pride, Cooking with Rosemary Shrager, Marathon News, Listener's Races, PTSD Sleep Problems, Listener's Questions and Twiffic Tweets.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. Simon spent the weekend at the Festival of Pride where he was on stage cooking with celebrity chef Rosemary Shrager and then ran around the grounds for Marathon 34 of 100. We have an interview with Laura Steward who suffers from depression and talks bravely about how running helps her. We have the winner of the caption competition and the result of last weeks poll.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-6.mp3" length="36823585" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 13:54 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:16:20</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>barefoot, podiatrist, amsterdam marathon, twitter, facebook, trauma, mental health, injury, help for heroes, ptsd, marathon, running, endurance, jogging, training</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 5 - Marathon 33</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Amsterdam Marathon, Marathon News, Listener's Races, KT Tape, PTSD Hypervigilance, Listener's Questions.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. Simon ran the Amsterdam Marathon as 33 of 100 taped up with KT Tape. He talks frankly about Hypervigilance, one of the many PTSD symptoms, Chris enters his first marathon and continues his barefoot running experiment.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-5.mp3" length="76604733" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 15:05 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:09:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>barefoot, podiatrist, amsterdam marathon, twitter, facebook, trauma, mental health, injury, help for heroes, ptsd, marathon, running, endurance, jogging, training</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 4 - Marathon 32</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Liverpool Marathon, Help for Heroes award, marathon news, PTSD, rant and rave, poems, listener's questions.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. Simon ran the Liverpool Marathon as 32 of 100 and received an award from Help for Heroes. He talks frankly about flashbacks, one of the many PTSD symptoms + the usual favourites.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-4.mp3" length="76604733" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 16:51 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:22:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>liverpool marathon, twitter, facebook, trauma, mental health, injury, help for heroes, ptsd, marathon, running, endurance, jogging, training</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 3 - A Bad Week!</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>It's a long one! Injury and frustration, marathon news, PTSD, rant and rave, listener's questions.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. It's not been a good week for Simon for a number of reasons. Find out why and his plans for the next marathon. We introduce a new weekly section on PTSD as well as the usual favourites.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-3.mp3" length="80867080" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 4 Oct 2011 15:59 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>1:23:00</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>loch ness marathon, twitter, facebook, injury, help for heroes, ptsd, marathon, running, endurance, jogging, training</itunes:keywords>
</item>
<item>
<title>Episode 2 - Marathon 31 of 100</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>What have we been up to this week? Simon's last marathon, his next, marathon news, rant and rave, listener's questions.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. Episode 2 sees us trying to improve on the podcast format and includes a lot more marathon related news and views as well as a rundown on what Simon has been up to in the last week.</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-2.mp3" length="55001675" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 18:42 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>57:20</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>help for heroes, ptsd, marathon, running, endurance, jogging, training</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 1 - All about Simon and the 100 Marathons Challenge</title>
<itunes:author>Simon Buckden</itunes:author>
<itunes:subtitle>Simon tells us a bit about himself and what motivated him to take on such an amazing challenge.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Follow Simon on Facebook and Twitter via www.raceto100.co.uk. Simon tells us about his battle with Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD) and what motivated him to run 100 marathons in 100 weeks and to raise money for Help For Heroes</itunes:summary>
<enclosure url="http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/100marathons/100-marathons-episode-1.mp3" length="18028169" type="audio/mpeg" />
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 12:05 GMT</pubDate>
<itunes:duration>18:46</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>help for heroes, ptsd, marathon, running, endurance, </itunes:keywords>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
