<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>
<ttl>60</ttl>
<title>Xtalks - Executive Talks Podcasts</title>
<link>http://www.xtalks.com/</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>#x2117; amp; #xA9; 2006 Honeycomb Worldwide Group of Companies</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle> Xtalks brings industry thought leaders directly to executives around the world.</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Xtalks provides a forum for the world's top business leaders to present their hands-on insight on the issues affecting your business. By leveraging the best of today's Internet and telecom technology, Xtalks reinvents traditional information channels by delivering breaking business issues and analysis while adding high levels of interactivity with live web conferences and archived podcasts. Xtalks produces information for executives involved in Business Strategy, Energy, Finance, Investments, Government, Health, IT, Legal, Life Sciences, Manufacturing, Mining and Telecommunications.</itunes:summary>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Xtalks</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>info@xtalks.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
<itunes:category text="Business">
<itunes:category text="Careers"/>
</itunes:category>
<itunes:category text="Education"/>

<item>
	<title>Dowpharma Case Study: Implementing Technology Transfer for a New Product Using a CMO</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Jeff Dudley, Business Operations Director, Dowpharma and Dow Ventures</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Improving speed to market is critical to gain market share and increase profitability. An effective strategy to ensure this outcome is to outsource manufacturing operations to a credible CMO. Doing this successfully requires partnering with an experienced CMO that can deliver quality results in the most efficient and cost effective manner.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060810_dow/060810_dow.mp3" length="11954930" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060810_dow/060810_dow.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>0:49:48</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>Technology transfer, quality assurance, CGMP compliance, CMO, contract manufacturing, best practices in CMO, process scale up operations, quality assurance, quality control, process development, process engineering, process science, technical operations, pharma manufacturing, pharma CMO, pharma tech</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Collaboration Strategies and Applications for the Enterprise</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Terry Barash (Ford Motor Company), Miranda Mowbray (Hewlett Packard), Neil Lock (BT)</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>This web conference discusses how to design and implement and maximize the benefit of collaboration strategies in the enterprise</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060720_collab/060720_collab.mp3" length="23182017" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060720_collab/060720_collab.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:36:35</itunes:duration>
		<itunes:keywords>HR, Human Resources, HR &amp; IT Collaboration, knowledge management, customer relations management, customer relationship management, enterprise collaboration, human resource management, web conference, webinar, collaboration strategies web conference, collaboration strategies webinar, e-learning</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Corporate E-Filing--Tax Technology </title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Bert DuMars (IRS),  Michael P. Dolan (KPMG LLP), Greg Johnsen (GT Nexus)</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>The question is: how is your organization making the best use of the technology available for your tax preparation? In this special presentation, Bert DuMars, Director of Electronic Tax Administration at the IRS will discuss improvements to e-filing systems and how the IRS is ensuring the safety and quality of the information being delivered electronically. </itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060712_efiling/060712_efiling.mp3" length="18254884" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060712_efiling/060712_efiling.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:16:03</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>IRS, Internal Revenue Service, electronic filing, e-filing, corporate tax preparation, corporate tax electronic filing, e-filing compliance issues, Bert DuMars, electronic tax administration, filing and auditing procedures </itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Service-Oriented Architecture (SOA) </title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Richard Burk (OMB),  Dr. Stéphane Gagnon (University of Quebec in Outaouais), Ernie Ostic (IBM Information Integration Solutions )</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>To ensure a competitive advantage companies today need to allow processes to interconnect easily in a flexible infrastructure based on business needs. Service-Oriented Architecture (SOA) is therefore an ideal approach for the modern enterprise. </itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060711_soa/060711_soa.mp3" length="28526225" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060711_soa/060711_soa.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:58:51</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Infrastructure Interoperability Maximize ROI, Service Oriented Architechure, SOA, open ended data flow, James Mckenney, Information Security, Stephane Gagnon, New Jersey Institute of Technology, Ruchir Rodrigues, IT, Verizon Communication </itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Global Supply Chain Visibility</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Perry Trunick (Logistics Today),  David Simchi-Levi (Massachusetts Institute of Technology), Greg Johnsen (GT Nexus), Razat Gaurav (i2 Technologies, Inc.)</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Global supply chain visibility is becoming increasingly important, particularly as manufacturing is moved offshore.  With supply chains lengthening it's becoming more important to have visibility of your products while they are in transit. </itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060629_SC/060629_SC.mp3" length="27643079" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060629_SC/060629_SC.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:55:10</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Xtalks, Global, Supply Chain, Visibility, transparency, RFID, radio frequency ID, logistics, manufacturing, manufacture, offshore, ship, shipping, transport, transportation,  4pl, fourth party logistics, 3pl, third party </itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Public Wi-Fi</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Dianah Neff, CIO, City of Philadelphia</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>As more businesses and individuals go wireless, there is an increasing demand for public spaces to incorporate Wi-Fi into their offerings. Already, places such as airports, libraries and universities are starting to provide 'hotspots' where users can access wireless internet. However, there is a growing trend to provide greater access to this technology in more diverse settings.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060623_wifi/060623_wifi.mp3" length="28487025" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060623_wifi/060623_wifi.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:58:41</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Wireless city, WiFi, wireless networks, broadband wireless connectivity, integrating wireless systems, public access points, public WiFi systems, wireless systems, wireless signal strength, wireless access points, public wireless access</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>XBRL (Extensible Business Reporting Language)</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Corey Booth, CIO, SEC</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>XBRL (eXtensible Business Reporting Language) provides an identifying tag for each individual item of financial data. Computers recognize these tags in any document form and are able to extract, analyze and store the data automatically and present the data in a variety of formats.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060616_xbrl1/060616_xbrl1.mp3" length="20140894" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2006/060616_xbrl1/060616_xbrl1.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:23:55</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>SEC, Securities and Exchange Commission, Corey Booth, Extensible Business Reporting Language, XBRL, financial data, financial reporting, business reporting, electronic communication, electronic communication financial data, EDGAR filings, XBRL</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Effective Strategies for Implementing HR BPO</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Hugh MacDonald (CIBC), Andy Teng (HRO Today), John Jaeger (YRCI) </itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Outsourcing is not a new concept to HR, but there is a renewed interest and growth in BPO solutions. Researchers predict that demand for HR BPO services will increase dramatically in the next few years. Several factors are driving this growth: need to reduce costs; a desire to improve service levels and quality of delivery; and the business objective for HR to be more global and strategic.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060518_HRBPO/060518_HRBPO.mp3" length="29624937" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060518_HRBPO/060518_HRBPO.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>2:03:03</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Business process outsourcing, BPO, human resource outsourcing, HR outsourcing, HR BPO, HR business process outsourcing, HR administration, BPO cost reductions, reducing HR costs, outsourcing, HRO, HRO solutions, HRO agreements, multiprocess</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>HR and IT Collaboration</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Casey Graves, 2nd VP/HR Support (Aflac), Carl Abercrombie, 2nd VP/IT Business Partnership Management Office (Aflac), Steve Garth, Principal Product Director, Content and Records Management, (Oracle Technology Marketing)</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>As the role of technology within an organization continues to grow, the role of the CIO and IT leadership also increases in exposure and responsibility. Professor J Clark Kelso earned a reputation as a turnaround specialist and as an inspiring leader who was asked to come in and turn around the State of California’s IT department. In this special presentation, Mr. Kelso will share his insights on the key competencies needed of a CIO given today's environment as well as offer a glimpse into the programs he and his team initiated based on his strategic objectives. Learn from an industry expert who has successfully managed change and how you can apply some of his lessons learned to your own organization.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060511_HR/060511_HR.mp3" length="14621904" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060511_HR/060511_HR.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:51:03</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Oracle, Aflac, HR support, HRIS, HR collaboration, IT collaboration, HR  IT, building HR relationships, IT business partnership, Casey Graves, Carl Abercrombie, content management</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Managing Transformation: IT Leadership</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by J. Clark Kelso, State Chief Information Officer, State of California</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>As the role of technology within an organization continues to grow, the role of the CIO and IT leadership also increases in exposure and responsibility. Professor J Clark Kelso earned a reputation as a turnaround specialist and as an inspiring leader who was asked to come in and turn around the State of California’s IT department. In this special presentation, Mr. Kelso will share his insights on the key competencies needed of a CIO given today's environment as well as offer a glimpse into the programs he and his team initiated based on his strategic objectives. Learn from an industry expert who has successfully managed change and how you can apply some of his lessons learned to your own organization.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060509_MA/060509_MA.mp3" length="23236640" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060510_M1/060510_MT.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:00:55</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Due Diligence in Mergers &amp; Aquisition Strategies</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Mark Wolfram, GM, Venture Integration, (Microsoft Corporation) and Paul F. Hartzell, Senior Vice President, (DataSite) </itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>An item concerning smart due diligence will make up a paragraph in the checklist of every Mergers &amp; Acquisitions master, since a process of due diligence is a key part of every successful capital investment. Proper investigation of the potential investment target’s background protects you from misunderstanding the asset price and the possibility of a deal break up.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060509_MA/060509_MA.mp3" length="23236640" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060509_MA/060509_MA.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:36:49</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>MA, mergers  acquistions, business integration, best practices, buyouts, middle markets, appraisal, LBOs, MBOs, data rooms, Seminar, </itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>The Sarbanes-Oxley Section 404 for Non-US Companies</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Chrisan Herrod, Chief Security Officer (SEC)</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>SWhat are the security issues of compliance and what do non-U.S. companies have to do to ensure their systems will be safe and in meet the SEC mandates? Join us for an exclusive presentation from Chrisan Herrod of the Securities &amp; Exchange Commission who will be discussing in detail the Sarbanes-Oxley Act from a security perspective.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/Archives/2006/060426_SOXNonUS/060426_SOXNonUS.mp3" length="21886755" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/Archives/2006/060426_SOXNonUS/060426_SOXNonUS.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:59:07</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Intellectual, Property, Law, Copyright, Infringment, Business, Workshop, Seminar, </itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>The Sarbanes-Oxley Act and Implementing Section 404</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Scott Taub, Acting Chief Accountant (SEC), and  Eric Keller, President and Chief Executive Officer, (MOVARIS) </itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Sustainability and continuous compliance for Sarbanes-Oxley and Learn how companies survived the first year of SOX 404 implementations and their strategies to ensure ongoing compliance.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/Archives/2006/060419_SOX/060419_SOX.mp3" length="23950004" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/Archives/2006/060419_SOX/060419_SOX.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:59:07</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Intellectual, Property, Law, Copyright, Infringment, Business, Workshop, Seminar, </itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Intellectual Property Law</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Chris Israel (Department of Commerce) David H. Kagan, (Schulte Roth amp; Zabel LLP)
</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>The Bush administration has stated that through a stricter enforcement and prosecution it has worked aggressively to combat intellectual property theft and intellectual property crimes. Chris Israel was recently appointed by President Bush as the Coordinator Of International Intellectual Property Enforcement. In this special online presentation, Mr. Israel will discuss how he will be working with various agencies within the US administration to combat the growing problems in international intellectual property violations and enforce intellectual property laws overseas.
	</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060223_IP/060223_IP.mp3" length="28589751" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060223_IP/060223_IP.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:59:07</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Intellectual, Property, Law, Copyright, Infringment, Business, Workshop, Seminar, </itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Information Security: Securing IT to mitigate data loss and information breach
</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by 
Greg Garcia (Information Technology Association of America),Michael Assante (National amp; Homeland Security Idaho National Lab (INL)), James Chou (Apani Networks)
</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Information Security has been thrust to the forefront in recent months with many companies losing information and customer data.  Companies are making the move in a desperate attempt to protect consumer as well as critical data from invasion and security breaches.  The question by many consumers is whether government should make it mandatory for companies to ensure that customer data is properly secure, while government officials are seeing the recent attacks as a threat to National security.  These attacks have therefore left companies clamoring for answers to their now vulnerable IT infrastructures. 
	</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060208_IS/060208_IS.mp3" length="12753128" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060208_IS/060208_IS.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:10:51</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>IT, Informatin, Security, Data, Loss, Breach, Workshop, Seminar, </itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Workplace Wellness Programs</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Dr. Pamella Thomas (Lockheed Martin), Dr. Bruce Hochstadt (Buck Consultants), Samira Kaderali (Health amp; Welfare Canada)  Administration</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>With the aging population and the challenge of recruiting and retaining qualified employees, it is very important that we facilitate the employees we do have in getting and staying healthy. The workplace is the place to influence this action as this reinforces the company as caring for their human resources as well as building employee loyalty and the companys image as an employer of choice. Wellness offerings can no longer be seen as a good thing to do for the employees but as a strategic business investment with ways to document return on investment. Join us as we present the new frontier of Health and Productivity Management as the new tool to control our health care crisis. 
	</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060208_WW/060208_WW.mp3" length="206255124" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/archives/2006/060208_WW/060208_WW.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:54:35</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Workplace, Wellness, Health, Safety, Budgeting, Business, Seminar, Presentation, Educational, SEC, Securities, Exchange, Commision, Lockheed, Martin</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Track and Traceability- How The Bioterrorism Act Affects the Food amp; Beverage Industry</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Nega Beru, Ph.D., Food and Drug Administration</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Do you know where every ingredient in your product comes from?  You need to. The FDA created a series of stringent laws in an attempt to reduce the possibility of contamination in our food chain.  The last of these laws, the "Track and Traceability requirement" comes into effect this December. It will have an impact on all areas of the food chain, suppliers, manufacturers, shippers and warehousers will all need to be in compliance.
	</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/archives/6/011706_TrackTrace/011706_TrackTrace.mp3" length="19601684" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/archives/6/011706_TrackTrace/011706_TrackTrace.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2006 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:48:53</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Food, Beverage, Track, Trace, Tracability, FDA, Food, Drug, Administration, Health, Business, Seminar, Presentation, Educational, SEC, Securities, Exchange, Commision</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Leveraging Compliance Data for Strategic Advantage The Impact of Sarbanes-Oxley</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Chrisan Herrod, Chief Security Officer, U.S. Securities and	 Exchange Commission</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Initial SOX compliance has been painful. Many organizations have invested significant time and money in their efforts. As companies finish their second year of SOX compliance, they are realizing that they have embarked on a governance journey to gain strategic value from compliance. Companies in the forefront of this journey are leveraging technology to move from passive to active compliance in order to gain greater transparency through more accurate, reliable and timely financial and business information.
	</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/archives/2005/12_13_Finance_SOX/sox.mp3" length="16361720" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/archives/2005/12_13_Finance_SOX/sox.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:30:53</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Sarbanes-Oxley, SOX, 404, Compliance, Financial, Business, Seminar, Presentation, Educational, SEC, Securities, Exchange, Commision</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>IPv6 Transition</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Discussion led by Richard Burk (Office of Management and Budget), Yurie Rich (NAv6TF) </itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>The OMB has said that all Federal government agencies switch from internet protocol 4 to internet protocol 6. While some basic switchover has already happened, this is going to be a large scale project. Dick Burk will deliver a keynote presentation on the OMBs vision for IPv6 and offer suggestions on how to implement it seamlessly into your agency.
	</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://xtalks.com/archives/2005/12_13_GOV_IPv6/ipv6.mp3" length="17185088" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://xtalks.com/archives/2005/12_13_GOV_IPv6/ipv6.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>2:09:47</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Legal, Skills, Techniques, secure, e-discovery, legal, litigation, e-data, security, law, Educational, Business, Seminar, Presentation</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>The Use of E-Discovery in Litigation</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Discussion led by The Honorable John J. Hughes (Magistrate Judge for the District of New Jersey), Robert L. Byman (Jenner amp; Block), Montgomery N. Kosma (Jones Day) , Joni Miller (LIT Group), Kathryn Hardie (Attenex Corporation)
	 </itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>In this special two-hour presentation you will hear three seasoned e-discovery professionals share their experience in the growing use and importance of e-discovery in modern day litigation. E-discovery is becoming increasingly important in litigation. The incorrect management of data can lead to overages in time and money. Each of the presenters will provide a different view of the topic and discuss such areas as The importance of implementing a secure e-discovery system before any litigation issues arise, How to prepare your e-data for presentation, Knowing what data to keep and how to preserve it 
	</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/edisc_11082005.mp3" length="23361284" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/edisc_11082005.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>2:09:47</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Legal, Skills, Techniques, secure, e-discovery, legal, litigation, e-data, security, law, Educational, Business, Seminar, Presentation</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>New FDA/USDA Food Security Initiatives and the 5 key steps for improving your plants security</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Discussion led by Louis J. Carson (Food and Drug Administration), Lance Reeve (American Institute of Baking)
	</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Food safety and food security are both integrated and high priority goals for the Food and Drug Administration.  Since 9/11 the Center for Food Safety and Applied Nutrition has devoted significant resources to food defense. In general terms FDA has focused on three main areas in relation to food defense. preparedness, response and recovery. The development of a food defense strategy has involved a variety of approaches one of the most important of which was to determine vulnerabilities using an operational risk management approach. By examining a variety of agents, food commodities and various scenarios between the farm and the table it was possible to determine the quot;higherquot; risk combinations and thus focus resources based on a determination of risk. This approach has driven a number of activities including the development of guidance documents, research activities and emergency response planning. This preventative strategy has been augmented by new research for the development of rapid and sensitive methods, as well as the development of a clear emergency response plan should a deliberate food contamination event occur. Current activities are further focused on CARVER assessments of the higher risk foods and close interaction with stakeholders to further ensure preparedness. The 2002 Bioterrorism Act has further extended the protection of the U.S. food supply through the development of a number of rules.  Overall, while there has been a significant increase in focus on food defense this has been integrated as far as possible into food safety activities which remain an ongoing and high priority for FDA.
	</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/11_16_FOOD_Safety/foodsafety.mp3" length="16720988" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/11_16_FOOD_Safety/foodsafety.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:32:53</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Food, safety, security, Food, Drug, Administration, FDA, Food amp; Beverage, Defense, Educational, Business, Seminar, Presentation</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Boeing and RFID: Beyond the Mandates</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Steve Georgevitch, (Boeing Integrated Defense Systems) </itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Boeing has been working with RFID for over 5 years, with extensive research in factory, supply chain and on-aircraft applications This presentation will discuss Boeing 	apos;s approach to the DoD mandate and how they are supporting the Defense Department 	apos;s strategy, how the technology is being applied within Boeing today, and the direction they are taking with their supply chain partners.  Boeing will also discuss how they are working pilots within their supply base to understand the implications this technology will have on small businesses.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/anticounterfeiting_12102004.mp3" length="16720988" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/anticounterfeiting_12102004.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:32:53</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>RFID, Tools, Application, Tracking, Big, Brother, Deployment, Technology, Defense, Business, Seminar, Presentation, Educational, budgeting, transperency, finance, defense, air, travel, flight, Boeing</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Beyond Budgeting: Linking Strategic Goals to Operational Excellence</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Robert D. Kugel, (Ventana Research), Karey Robb, (PROPHIX Software Inc.), Bruno Ienni, (Charter Bank) </itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Regulatory pressures are demanding unprecedented levels of transparency into performance. Too often, the corporate strategy is developed but fails in its execution. There are a number of factors that contribute to successful operational execution in our performance-based environment, revealing the organizational risks, vulnerabilities and opportunities. Bank budgets have had to morph at an unprecedented rate to reflect a myriad of new line items. This premiere Xtalks event will tackle the challenges now facing the finance departments of community banks, and offer advice to ensure they remain highly competitive, resilient and compliant, in line with the shifting expectations of their customers, the needs of their internal clients and the scrutiny of regulatory bodies and auditors.
	</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/beyondbudgeting_10272005.mp3" length="10654928" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/beyondbudgeting_10272005.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>0:59:11</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>budgeting, transperency, finance, business, bank, financial,seminar</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Data &amp; Consumer Privacy</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Dan Caprio (US Department of Commerce), Kirk Herath (Nationwide), Emily Andrew (United States Postal Service)
	</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Explore the steps that need to be taken to build or evolve a privacy policy or approach, and to put it into practice. Understand how to translate that learning into a privacy strategy and ways to adapt a policy or approach into a logical implementation strategy. Hear overviews of USPS, Nationwide and the Department of Commerce, how privacy fits, the frameworks that built policies and programs and how they were implemented.
	</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/dataprivacy_101220055.mp3" length="16624580" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/dataprivacy_10122005.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:32:21</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>privacy, data, commerce, security, policy, strategy, business, technology, seminar</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>The Elimination of the Foreign Property Rule</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Wayne Foster, Chief, Government Finance, Finance Canada</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Mr. Foster gave an introductory presentation on the historic policy rationale for the FPR and its evolution, the FPRs impact on pension funds and financial markets, the context for the governments decision to eliminate the FPR in the February 2005 Budget, and the potential implications of this decision for Canadas financial markets.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/fpr_10262005.mp3" length="16832996" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/fpr_10262005.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:33:30</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Foreign, Property, Rule Finance, Financial, Seminar, business</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>HSPD-12: Smart Cards for Government</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by William Barker of the National Institute of Standards and Technology and John G Moore of the GSA Office of Technology Strategy (ME)</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Homeland Security Presidential Directive #12 (HSPD-12) of August 27, 2004, directed the Secretary of Commerce to promulgate a Federal Standard by February 27, 2005 that assures secure and reliable forms of identification of Federal and Federal contractor employees. The standard, Federal Information Processing Standard 201 (FIPS 201), Personal Identity Verification of Federal Employees and Contractors, was signed by the Secretary of Commerce on February 25, 2005.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/HSPD12_10182005.mp3" length="21084776" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/HSPD12_10182005.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:57:08</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>HSPD-12, Smart, Cards, Government, security, privacy, protection, business, technology, seminar</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>The Sarbanes-Oxley Act and Implementing Section 404</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Chrisan Herrod, Chief Security Officer, U.S. Securities and	 Exchange Commission</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Sustainability and continuous compliance for Sarbanes-Oxley and Learn how companies survived the first year of SOX 404 implementations and their strategies to ensure ongoing compliance.</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/sox_podcast.mp3" length="21802064" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/sox_podcast.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>2:01:07</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Sarbanes-Oxley, SOX, 404, Compliance, Financial, Business, Seminar, Presentation, Educational, SEC, Securities, Exchange, Commision</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>RFID for Defense Suppliers</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Ed Coyle and LTC. Charles Burke</itunes:subtitle>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/RFIDdod0504.mp3" length="21333128" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/RFIDdod0504.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:58:31</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>RFID, Tools, Application, Tracking, Big, Brother, Deployment, Technology, Defense, Business, Seminar, Presentation, Educational</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>RFID Implimentation II</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Mark Dinning, RFID Leader, Dell</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Identifying opportunity areas for initial RFID deployment: How Dell does it, Tools for building a RFID business case, RFID applications areas: Where RFID can be used in the short term and which applications should be delayed</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/RFID2_04062005.mp3" length="18423808" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/RFID2_04062005.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:35:24</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>RFID, Tools, Application, Tracking, Big, Brother, Deployment, Technology, Defense, Business, Seminar, Presentation, Educational</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>RFID Implimentation I</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Simon Langford - Manager of RFID Strategies, Wal-Mart Stores</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Led by Simon Langford - Manager of RFID Strategies, Wal-Mart Stores</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/RFID102232005.mp3" length="18423808" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/RFID102232005.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2005 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:57:08</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>RFID, Tools, Application, Tracking, Big, Brother, Deployment, Technology, Defense, Business, Seminar, Presentation, Educational, Wal-Mart</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
	<title>Anti-Counterfeiting Drug Strategies Archive</title>
	<itunes:author>Xtalks</itunes:author>
	<itunes:subtitle>Led by Mr. Eshetu Wondemagegnehu and Peter Rost</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:summary>Led by Mr. Eshetu Wondemagegnehu and Peter Rost</itunes:summary>
	<enclosure url="http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/anticounterfeiting_12102004.mp3" length="16720988" type="audio/x-mp3" />
	<guid>http://www.xtalks.com/archives/2005/anticounterfeiting_12102004.mp3</guid>
	<pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2004 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
	<itunes:duration>1:32:53</itunes:duration>
	<itunes:keywords>Assurance, Safety, Medicines, Drugs, Anti-Counterfeiting, Strategies, Pharmaceutical, Pharma, Business, Seminar, Presentation, Educational</itunes:keywords>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.xtalks.com/podcast/image.jpg" />
</item>

</channel>
</rss>