<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss 
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" 
    version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Saints Church Kings Lynn Thought for the Week</title>
        <description>Father Paul&apos;s &apos;Thought for the Week&apos; provides a reflection of weekly topical issues, often related to what is happening in society in the UK as well as worldwide issues.

These podcasts are a tool from which to explore these issues from a moral, ethical and faith perspective. The podcasts provide an opportunity to consider things from a fresh perspective.</description>
        <link>http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thoughtfortheweeklibrary.html</link>
        <copyright>Father Paul Kinsey</copyright>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 08:27:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <managingEditor>danielgibbins@allsaintskingslynn.org.uk</managingEditor>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 08:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
        <webMaster>danielgibbins@allsaintskingslynn.org.uk</webMaster>
        <generator>FeedForAll v2.0 (2.0.2.9) http://www.feedforall.com</generator>
        <itunes:subtitle>Father Paul&apos;s &apos;Thought for the Week&apos; provides a reflection of weekly topical issues, often related to what is happening in society in the UK as well as worldwide issues.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:summary>Father Paul&apos;s &apos;Thought for the Week&apos; provides a reflection of weekly topical issues, often related to what is happening in society in the UK as well as worldwide issues. These podcasts are a tool from which to explore these issues from a moral, ethical and faith perspective. The podcasts provide an opportunity to consider things from a fresh perspective.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:author>Father Paul Kinsey</itunes:author>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Father Paul Kinsey</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>fatherpaul@allsaintskingslynn.org.uk</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">
            <itunes:category text="Christianity"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
            <itunes:category text="Personal Journals"/>
        </itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality"/>
        <itunes:keywords>church sermons, sermon podcast, faith, religion, religious, christian, moral, ethical, society</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/images/thoughtfortheweek.jpg"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/images/thoughtfortheweek.jpg</url>
            <title>All Saints Church Kings Lynn Thought for the Week</title>
            <link>http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thoughtfortheweeklibrary.html</link>
            <description>Father Paul Kinsey&apos;s Thought for the Week</description>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>94</height>
        </image>
        <item>
            <title>New Years Resolutions: The Changes We Choose to Make</title>
            <description>Unfortunately, the changes we choose in life usually involve changes to our own lives and offer little to change someone else&apos;s situation. If we decide to go on a diet, it hardly prompts us to think about someone who may be starving, or if we think about saving our money, do we consider those who have no income or those who cannot provide for themselves? </description>
            <link>http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thoughtfortheweek.html</link>
            <author>fatherpaul@allsaintskingslynn.org.uk</author>
            <enclosure url="http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thought/thought100108.mp3" length="1400000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">E5427C05-F67A-46BD-8513-2B349B21F32A</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 08:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>New Year&apos;s resolutions last for a few days, perhaps a little longer and, yet for many people, they are a complete waste of time and thought.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Unfortunately, the changes we choose in life usually involve changes to our own lives and offer little to change someone else&apos;s situation.  If we decide to go on a diet, it hardly prompts us to think about someone who may be starving, or if we think about saving our money, do we consider those who have no income or those who cannot provide for themselves?</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:26</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Father Paul Kinsey</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>new years resolutions, changing our lives, church sermons, sermon, thought for the week, all saints church</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Be Near Me Lord Jesus, I Ask Thee to Stay</title>
            <description>My favourite Christmas carol is Away in a Manger, although I can hardly ever sing it all the way through to the end without feeling upset and sometimes unable to sing some of the words.   At Midnight Mass we sing the carol kneeling and I am probably effected most by the lines,  &apos;be near me Lord Jesus, I ask thee to stay, close by me for ever, and love me I pray ...  When we are are thoughtless, there is someone who loves us just for who we are, whether we are &apos;mad&apos; or sad, ashamed, selfish, rude or unforgiving, whose only wish is that we should be like Him, and who can only see us as the people He wants us to be.</description>
            <link>http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thought201207.html</link>
            <author>fatherpaul@allsaintskingslynn.org.uk</author>
            <enclosure url="http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thought/thought201207.mp3" length="2420373" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">578141DB-2517-4C3B-A6EC-E86AFE3FE657</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 20:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Christmas is in itself a time beyond reason.  It is a time when our thoughtless activity is eclipsed by divine thoughtfulness, when God sent his Son into a world which had forgotten him.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Christmas is in itself a time beyond reason.  It is a time when our thoughtless activity is eclipsed by divine thoughtfulness, when God sent his Son into a world which had forgotten him.  What God the Father did is neither rational nor reasonable.  The Father knew the cost and still God entered our frail humanity and our &apos;thoughtless&apos; world.  His protection was provided by a young girl and a man almost too ashamed to be her husband.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>4:02</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Father Paul Kinsey</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>christmas sermon, christmas, meaning of christmas, away in a manger, depression, dementia, jesus, religion</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Bad Things Happen When Good People Do Nothing</title>
            <description>Occasionally, I hear people saying that the reason why bad things happen is because good people do nothing. Well, I wish it was that simple! I think we have to begin by categorising ‘bad things’ - illness, someone losing their job, a car accident, freak weather, road rage, to name but a few. Listening to the list, I doubt that the intervention of a good person would have changed many of the bad things. So is it true? Can we prevent disaster, or change the outcome of situations, by adding our voice or doing something?</description>
            <link>http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thought021207.html</link>
            <author>fatherpaul@allsaintskingslynn.org.uk</author>
            <enclosure url="http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thought/thought021207.mp3" length="1965320" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">DCECC0D4-6F16-48ED-A611-910618FBA367</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 2 Dec 2007 22:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>Occasionally, I hear people saying that the reason why bad things happen is because good people do nothing.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>It seems to me that bad things are happening and good people are doing nothing. They may not be responsible for creating the situations but they could be more active in helping to find a solution. There isn’t much that is different between Western and Eastern civilization and there is one thing which definitely they have in common - both are incredibly ‘judgemental’ in their approach and either is equally capable of climbing on to the ‘moral high ground’, without much hesitation.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:16</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Father Paul Kinsey</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>sermon, sudan, darfur, christian, teacher in sudan, inappropriate funding, innocence, why do bad things happen to good people</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>I&apos;m a Celebrity, Get Me Out of Here</title>
            <description>Making people suffer, as a contribution to entertainment is not a new concept by any means.  The Victorians, amongst others, were fond of their &apos;sideshows&apos; at fairs, although the ridicule these poor people suffered was remunerated, and their treatment did stop far short of  &apos;torturing&apos; the subjects with the objects of their fear, which is why, I think, the program in question goes far beyond the boundaries of either decency or entertainment.</description>
            <link>http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thought161107.html</link>
            <author>fatherpaul@allsaintskingslynn.org.uk</author>
            <enclosure url="http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thought/thought151107.mp3" length="147000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1BC8934A-F712-42DF-A103-9856DAF6B7DD</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 17:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>I can&apos;t decide who are more stupid - the two who host it, Ant and Dec, the people who produce it, the contestants who take part in it, or the people who watch it!</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>Making people suffer, as a contribution to entertainment is not a new concept by any means.  The Victorians, amongst others, were fond of their &apos;sideshows&apos; at fairs, although the ridicule these poor people suffered was remunerated, and their treatment did stop far short of  &apos;torturing&apos; the subjects with the objects of their fear, which is why, I think, the program in question goes far beyond the boundaries of either decency or entertainment.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>2:34</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Father Paul Kinsey</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>i&apos;m a celebrity get me out of here, children in need, thought for the week, religious podcasts, sermons, church podcasts</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The X-Factor: Revealing the Truth of God</title>
            <description>I have to admit to being a fan of the ITV television programme &lt;b&gt;&apos;The &apos;X Factor&apos;&lt;/b&gt;. I wouldn&apos;t say that I was a compulsive viewer, although I do watch it most Saturdays. &lt;br /&gt;
What I find most staggering, is that I had simply no idea that there were so many thousands of people who are so desperate to succeed, even to the point of being delusional and &apos;in denial&apos; of what their true talent might be! &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
November, in the church, is generally known as the month of remembrance. Those whom we remember in the various feasts and commemorations, the Saints who fought for and witnessed our faith, those who gave their lives in conflict and war, and the earliest apostles through whom the truth of God was revealed - all had the X Factor. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
It seems to me that participants in &apos;The X Factor&apos; who fail to achieve their dream, might reflect well upon those whose dream was not in wealth or success, but in service, not in the entertainment of humanity, whom the world will long remember, I am sure.</description>
            <link>http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thought041107.html</link>
            <author>fatherpaul@allsaintskingslynn.org.uk</author>
            <enclosure url="http://www.allsaintskingslynn.org.uk/thought/thought151107.mp3" length="1720" type="audio/mpeg"/>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">037C0336-E997-4208-AEC5-9435B3CE68EE</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 8 Nov 2007 08:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
            <itunes:subtitle>We remember the Saints, apostles and soldiers who gave their lives, through whom the truth of God was revealed, all had the X-Factor</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>The X-Factor show broadens our thinking, the programme&apos;s search for a star goes beyond possession of musical ability, an attractive personality, or dogged determination in the pursuit of fame and fortune. The &apos;X Factor&apos; is about a presence of mind which spurs someone on to succeed in the face of criticism, difficulty and disappointment. It is that part of us, that presence of mind, which exhibits courage, and focuses on the perceived goal.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:duration>3:01</itunes:duration>
            <itunes:author>Father Paul Kinsey</itunes:author>
            <itunes:keywords>x factor, remembrance sunday, faith, religion, saints, apostles, church sermons, church podcast, faith</itunes:keywords>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
