<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Mind Your Own Business&#x2122; - mp3 version</title>
    <link>http://www.agincourtproductions.com/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&#x2117; &amp; &#xA9; 2008 Agincourt Productions Inc</copyright>
    <itunes:subtitle>The Antidote To Business Advice</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:author>Guy Kingston</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>By Entrepreneurs for Entrepreneurs – a podcast packed with savvy tips and secrets of success for start-ups, entrepreneurs, small business owners and franchises</itunes:summary>
    <description>By Entrepreneurs for Entrepreneurs – a podcast packed with savvy tips and secrets of success for start-ups, entrepreneurs, small business owners and franchises</description>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Agincourt Productions Inc</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>info@myobpod.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="http://www.myobpod.com/images/MYOB_Video_600x600GreenMP3.jpg" />
    <itunes:category text="Business">
      <itunes:category text="Management &amp; Marketing"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:category text="Education">
      <itunes:category text="Training"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:keywords>myob, smll, buisness, busineses, busness, entrepreneur, startup, entrepeneur, entrepeneurs, entrepreneurs, start up</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <item>
      <title>#131 What A Rogue!</title>
      <itunes:author>Guy Kingston</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Interview with, and tips from, Chris Benjamin, Rogue CFO</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>This Mind Your Own Business podcast features and interview with Chris Benjamin, aka Rogue CFO. Chris offers outsourced Chief Financial Officer services to venture backed start-ups. In this podcast he gives listeners some useful tips on managing their cash and developing a growing business. The interview is followed by a studio discussion between Guy Kingston, John Richards and Christina Jones.</itunes:summary>
      <enclosure url="http://www.myobpod.com/podcasts/kvj/MYOB_2011-05-23.mp3" length="24745840" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <guid>http://www.myobpod.com/podcasts/kvj/MYOB_2011-05-23.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>0:34:12</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:keywords>startup, venture capital, angel investment, start a business</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#130 Young Entrepreneurs</title>
      <itunes:author>Guy Kingston</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Starting a business is a viable career option whatever your age</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>In this edition of the Mind Your Own business podcast we feature an interview with the founder of the Young Entrepreneur Council, Scott Gerber, followed by a studio discussion between Guy Kingston, Christina Jones and John Richards. In an engaging interview, Scott Gerber breaks from the orthodoxy that a start up needs external finance (99% don’t get any) and that every venture has to be based on high tech innovation. Instead, we walk through ‘what it’s like on the ground’ for those of us who really do start a business rather than just talk about doing so one day. What sort of ideas work? How is it going to be financed?</itunes:summary>
      <enclosure url="http://www.myobpod.com/podcasts/bnl/MYOB_2011-04-18.mp3" length="25913514" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <guid>http://www.myobpod.com/podcasts/grn/MYOB_2011-04-18.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>0:35:50</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:keywords>startup, venture capital, angel investment, start a business</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#129 Times of Turmoil</title>
      <itunes:author>Guy Kingston</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Q. How will events in the Middle East effect your business? A. More than you might imagine.</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>To say the events in the Middle East will have far reaching consequences has become a cliché. But, as far as our businesses are concerned those events are likely to have more impact than we may at first realise. Guy Kingston, John Richards and Christina Jones discuss what the effects of all this turmoil may be.</itunes:summary>
      <enclosure url="http://www.myobpod.com/podcasts/grn/MYOB_2011-03-14.mp3" length="19827831" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <guid>http://www.myobpod.com/podcasts/grn/MYOB_2011-03-14.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>0:27:22</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:keywords>Egypt, Libya, Bahrain, Tunisia</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#127 Interview</title>
      <itunes:author>Guy Kingston</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Discussions with three leading thinkers in the world of entrepreneurship</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>In a departure from our regular format we feature interviews with Doug Palmer, Murray Smith and Phil Simon. Each has three top tips for entrepreneurs, ensuring this show is packed with useful advice</itunes:summary>
      <enclosure url="http://www.myobpod.com/podcasts/jru/MYOB_2011-01-24.mp3" length="43431664" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <guid>http://www.myobpod.com/podcasts/jru/MYOB_2011-01-24.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:00:08</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:keywords>advice, guru, start up, small business, growth, success</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#126 The Devil’s Currency</title>
      <itunes:author>Guy Kingston</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>What impact will the Euro crisis have on our businesses worldwide?</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>What future for the Euro? Is it really the work of evil our show title suggests? Following bail outs for Greece and Ireland, with others looking likely to follow for Spain and Portugal in 2011, Guy Kingston, Christina Jones and John Richards examine the impact the current Euro crisis will have not just throughout Europe but on global business as a whole.</itunes:summary>
      <enclosure url="http://www.myobpod.com/podcasts/gmi/MYOB_2010-12-20.mp3" length="25167779" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <guid>http://www.myobpod.com/podcasts/bru/MYOB_2010-12-20.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>34:47</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:keywords>ERM, exchange rates, gold standard, credit crunch, exchange controls, ECB, Eire</itunes:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

