<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"
xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>Signal podcast (Ogg)</title>
<link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/signal-ogg.rss</link>
<atom:link href="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/signal-ogg.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<language>en</language>
<copyright>Released under the Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 3.0 Unported Licence</copyright>
<description>Signal hackerspace radio</description>
<image>
<url>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/img/signal_thumb.png</url>
<title>Signal, hackerspace radio (ogg)</title>
<link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/signal-ogg.rss</link>
</image>
<media:thumbnail url="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/img/signal_thumb.png" />
<itunes:author>signal@hackerspaces.org</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>Hackerspace radio bringing news, gossip, interviews and other audio related to hackerspaces, the hackerscene, technology, science and what have you. Broadcasting live every Thursday from 10 pm - 12 am CEST | 08 pm - 10 pm UTC | 04 pm - 06 pm EDT | 01 pm - 03 pm PDT (aka International Hacker Time).</itunes:summary>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Signal</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>signal@hackerspaces.org</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/img/signal_square.png" />
<itunes:category text="Technology">
</itunes:category>
<item>
  <link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/</link>
  <title>/dev/random 2012-05-10</title>
  <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2012 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">signal201205112200</guid>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:author>gmc, okkie</itunes:author>
  <author>signal@hackerspaces.org</author>
  <description>In this episode a left-over from the last episode, where gmc and okkie looked ahead to the upcoming hacker-camp and con season. From London we have on the phone Jonty Wareing, one of the prime suspects behind EMFcamp. This hackercamp will take place on August 31st - September 2nd, and is the first such camp in the UK.

Next up is Dmitry Kleiner, venture kommunist and part of the Telekommunisten collective. He explains about thimbl, an artistic example of the decentralized nature of the early internet which is taken as a startingpoint to discuss how today capitalism requires centralized solutions and thus take away freedom.

Finally, gmc is reporting from the filmset on location in Amsterdam where a team is shooting footage for the upcoming open-content movie (Project Mango) produced by the Blender Institute. The 3d modelling and rendering software and its motion tracking features are used in this movie to tell the story of Amsterdam being destroyed by robots. Ton Roosendaal, producer, explains how the movie is financed. Gmc briefly spoke to a very busy director, Ian Hubert. Jeremy Davidson shares his love for robots and the open-source Blender software, and Sebastian Koenig explains a bit about motion tracking. Developer Campbel Barton tells us how it is to work with artists on this project.

Shownotes with links and playlist: http://signal.hackerspaces.org/devrandom/?page=archive#20120510</description>
  <enclosure url="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/2012-05-11-2200-dev-random.ogg" length="50158756" type="audio/ogg" />
</item>
<item>
  <link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/</link>
  <title>/dev/random 2012-04-12</title>
  <pubDate>Sat, 12 April 2012 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">signal201204122200</guid>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:author>gmc, okkie</itunes:author>
  <author>signal@hackerspaces.org</author>
  <description>After the introductions and news (featuring the recent DARPA funding discussion, Jack Tramel's passing away and the raspberry pi) this edition kicks off a look-ahead at upcoming hacker cons and camps with Emmanuel Goldstein. From New York City the founder of 2600 talks about the history of HOPE, the bi-yearly conference in New York City. A bit of history about the location, the Penn Hotel, as well as a look-ahead to the content of this conference.
Next up, we discuss the Amsterdam edition of the Hack in the Box conference with fish__. An action-packed quad-trak conference with side-dishes such as a browser security programming challenge, a hackerspace challenge, the commsec village for the ITsec community and more.
Finally, we talk with David Raison about a small-scale yet very stimulating outdoor hacker camp in Dudelange, Luxembourg. With hill-side campfires and work shops on technology, society and even 'health & beauty', this is a must visit this summer.

Shownotes on: http://signal.hackerspaces.org/devrandom/?page=archive#20120412</description>
  <enclosure url="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/2012-04-12-2200-dev-random.ogg" length="59934864" type="audio/ogg" />
</item>
<item>
  <link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/</link>
  <title>Hackerspace Digest 0023</title>
  <pubDate>Sat, 22 March 2012 23:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">signal201203222300</guid>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:author>Makers Local 256</itunes:author>
  <author>signal@hackerspaces.org</author>
  <description>On this episode of Hacker Space Digets, Mog teaches everyone the word Ephemerisle. We find out that 3d printers can write out the United States Constition and print choloclate bunny molds. Also Mid-South Makers one up us on their planned Make-In. All this and more, one episode 23 of HackerSpace Digest.

Show notes are on the wiki: https://256.makerslocal.org/wiki/Hackerspace_Digest/HSD_0023_2012-03-01</description>
  <enclosure url="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/2012-03-22-2300-hackerspace-digest-23.ogg" length="32308847" type="audio/ogg" />
</item>
<item>
  <link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/</link>
  <title>Talking Anthropology 40 - progressbar.sk</title>
  <pubDate>Sat, 22 March 2012 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">signal201203222200</guid>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:author>Tom Lohninger</itunes:author>
  <author>signal@hackerspaces.org</author>
  <description>Bratislava Hackerspace progressbar celebrated it's first birthday and we gave it a visit. You hear the story of several slovaks one week before the national election 2012 talking about their situation as net-citizens. The show concludes by overflow from the metalab talking about a new project.

https://progressbar.sk/events/progressbars-birthday-party
http://www.hackerspaceshop.com/
http://websupport.sk/
http://dada-acta.eu/
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/3d_printer
http://www.tvbgone.com/cfe_main.php</description>
  <enclosure url="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/2012-03-22-2200-talking-anthropology.ogg" length="33771845" type="audio/ogg" />
</item>
<item>
  <link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/</link>
  <title>Eindbaas Radio 2012-03-15</title>
  <pubDate>Sat, 15 March 2012 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">signal201203152200</guid>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:author>Eindbaas</itunes:author>
  <author>signal@hackerspaces.org</author>
  <description>Another edition of Eindbaas Radio, with host gmc and in the studio Frank and Klazien, the dynamic Eindbaas organising duo. We discuss new releases and artists, upcoming parties such as Eindbaas 9 and Blipfest New York and of course play a lot of chiptunes by artists such as Henry Homesweet, Knife City, Meneo, Monodir, Desert Planet, RoccoW, Ultrasyd, Professor Zakamoto, Xyse and Random.</description>
  <enclosure url="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/2012-03-15-2200-eindbaas-radio.ogg" length="55035898" type="audio/ogg" />
</item>
<item>
  <link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/</link>
  <title>/dev/random 2012-02-16</title>
  <pubDate>Sat, 16 February 2012 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">signal201202162200</guid>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:author>gmc</itunes:author>
  <author>signal@hackerspaces.org</author>
  <description>Today we look back at the early days of /dev/random with recordings from the archive. First of all, we go back to late 2010 where gmc and flyko bemoan the state of broadband internet in the united states of america. Next, we go even farther back and listen to an item from the time when fish_ was still the host and we had Johannes Grenzfurtner as a remote guest. Finally, we go back to somem random chatter from 2011 and a random call to a government-less Belgium.</description>
  <enclosure url="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/2012-02-16-2200-dev-random.ogg" length="47430210" type="audio/ogg" />
</item>
<item>
  <link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/</link>
  <title>Creative Commons Charts 2012-02-02</title>
  <pubDate>Sat,  2 February 2012 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">signal201202022200</guid>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:author>Stitch</itunes:author>
  <author>signal@hackerspaces.org</author>
  <description>Stitch takes us through the most popular CC licensed tracks on jamendo.</description>
  <enclosure url="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/2012-02-02-2200-creative-commons-charts-0.ogg" length="44916609" type="audio/ogg" />
</item>
<item>
  <link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/</link>
  <title>/dev/random 2012-01-19</title>
  <pubDate>Sat, 19 January 2012 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">signal201201192200</guid>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:author>gmc</itunes:author>
  <author>signal@hackerspaces.org</author>
  <description>This edition of /dev/random kicks off with the Hackerspace Global Grid (HGG), a distributed ground station system being built by an international team gravitating around hackerspace Shackspace in Stuttgart, Germany. Hadez, one of the prime suspects, explains about this modular and affordable system offering high accuracy timing for various receiver / data gathering modules). Discussed is their collaboration with Constellation, a number-crunching project set up to calculate trajectories of amateur satellites.
Next, on the phone are Sjors Gielen and Mark van Cuick, two of the three initiators of a community-based mobile telephony provider Limesco aiming to bring transparancy and innovation to the Dutch mobile communication landscape. Limesco does not have customers but members, who are united in the Limesco association. This gives the users of the network a great deal of influence into the future of the network. The provider has a very conscious approach to issues such as data-retention, lawful interception, privacy and net-neutrality.
Finally, gmc looks back at the queer geeks panel discussion that was broadcast live from 28c3 in December 2011. Excerpts from the show give an impression of the subjects touched upon, as discussed by Mitch Altman, Jimmie Rodgers, gmc, socialhack, tomate, willow, lisa and Rubin. The full recording is available in the Signal archives.

Shownotes, links and playlist on http://signal.hackerspaces.org/devrandom/?page=archive#20120119</description>
  <enclosure url="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/2012-01-19-2200-dev-random.ogg" length="48823981" type="audio/ogg" />
</item>
<item>
  <link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/</link>
  <title>28C3 congress radio: Binary Voice</title>
  <pubDate>Sat, 29 December 2011 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">signal201112292200</guid>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:author>Brenno de Winter</itunes:author>
  <author>signal@hackerspaces.org</author>
  <description>The final hour live from the BCC in Berlin discusses 28c3, some of the more notable talks that took place and are still to come. The first subject is the 'cold-boot' attack, what is it and what can we do? Brenno de Winter discusses his experience over the past year with exposing security leaks and the resulting legal action. Also covered is the public demonstration on the streets of Berlin that is traditionally taking place during the congres.</description>
  <enclosure url="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/2011-12-29-2200-28c3-piradio.ogg" length="53863024" type="audio/ogg" />
</item>
<item>
  <link>http://signal.hackerspaces.org/</link>
  <title>28C3 congress radio: Year-end round-up</title>
  <pubDate>Sat, 29 December 2011 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">signal201112292000</guid>
  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:author>gmc, socialhack</itunes:author>
  <author>signal@hackerspaces.org</author>
  <description>In this year-end round-up, socialhack and gmc are joined on the table by Tim Pritlove, Mitch Altman, Jeremy Zimmerman, someone from Noisebridge and Oggi from telecomix.

They look back at a year of activism, but also 28 years of congress. What will the future bring for the congress? With the mass-interest in congres, the old atmosphere of a conference for and by the visitors is under threat. Should congress expand, or find other ways of balancing the want to inform the public and the want to be among eachother as hackers?

With a look at the rise, fall and ressurection of Telecomix we look at activism over the past year and organisational forms conducive to positive and effective activism that is sustainable.</description>
  <enclosure url="http://signal.hackerspaces.org/archive/2011-12-29-2000-28c3-year-end-roundup.ogg" length="78001575" type="audio/ogg" />
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
