<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" dir="ltr" lang="en-US">
<head profile="http://gmpg.org/xfn/11">
<meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=UTF-8" />
<title>Business and Finance Issues  </title>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="http://stainescorps.org.uk/wp-content/themes/frankincense/style.css" type="text/css" media="screen" />
<link rel="alternate" type="application/rss+xml" title="Business and Finance Issues RSS Feed" href="http://stainescorps.org.uk/feed/" />
<link rel="pingback" href="http://stainescorps.org.uk/xmlrpc.php" />
<link rel="EditURI" type="application/rsd+xml" title="RSD" href="http://stainescorps.org.uk/xmlrpc.php?rsd" />
<link rel="wlwmanifest" type="application/wlwmanifest+xml" href="http://stainescorps.org.uk/wp-includes/wlwmanifest.xml" /> 
<link rel='index' title='Business and Finance Issues' href='http://stainescorps.org.uk/' />
<meta name="generator" content="WordPress 3.0.5" />
</head>
<body>
<div id="wrapper">
<div id="wrapper2">

<div id="header">
	<div id="logo">
		<h1><a href="http://stainescorps.org.uk/">Business and Finance Issues</a></h1>
		<p>Business and Finance Issues</p>
	</div>
	<!-- end #search -->
</div>
<!-- end #header -->
<div id="menu">
	<ul>
		<li class="current_page_item current_page_item"><a href="http://stainescorps.org.uk/">Home</a></li>
			</ul>
</div>
<!-- end #menu -->
</div>
<hr />

<div id="page">
	<div id="page-bgtop">
	<div id="page-bgbtm">
	<div id="banner">&nbsp;</div>

	<div id="content">

	
		
			<div class="post" id="post-1">
			<div class="post-bgtop">
			<div class="post-bgbtm">
				<h2 class="title"><a href="http://stainescorps.org.uk/repair_your_credit_and_increase_your_credit_score/" rel="bookmark" title="Permanent Link to Repair Your Credit And Increase Your Credit Score">Repair Your Credit And Increase Your Credit Score</a></h2>
				
				<div class="entry">
					<p>Your credit will be important throughout your life. Having good credit can change the way you life your life. Credit can easily be damaged, but it can take a long time to repair it. This article will provide you with great advice on how you can begin the repair process.<br />
<img src="http://stainescorps.org.uk/wp-images/credit.jpg"><br />
Keep your first account open. Whatever credit account you have had open the longest, is the best one to keep on your report. Don&#8217;t close this account because the limit is too low or the rate is too high. Try to get a higher credit limit, or ask for a lower interest rate, but even if they won&#8217;t give that to you, keep the card and keep using it. The longer track record you have with an account, the more it will affect your score in a positive way.<br />
 <a href="http://www.sinspeed.co.uk" title="">sinspeed</a><br />
Check your credit report from all three major credit reporting agencies once a year. This is a great opportunity to check your report for problems or bad information. If you notice a problem on your report then you have the opportunity to fix it. This also gives you an idea of how a prospective lender would view you when pulling your credit report.<br />
 <a href="http://www.101translations.com/" title="">translations</a><br />
When trying to rid yourself of credit card debt, pay the highest interest rates first. The money that adds up monthly on these high rate cards is phenomenal. Reduce the interest amount you are incurring by removing the debt with higher rates quickly, which will then allow more money to be paid towards other balances.<br />
 <a href="http://www.tonik.co.uk/panasonic.html" title="">panasonic toner cartridges</a><br />
After you file for bankruptcy, it is important to check your credit report. Double check that the bankruptcy is listed and that the debts covered under it are all noted with a BK next to them. Having a correct report will show new creditors that those debts no longer apply, allowing you to repair your credit and move forward.</p>
<p>It is easy to find a loan even if you have bad credit, but it isn&#8217;t all positive. If you have bad credit, you are forced to pay higher interest rates and it is hard to find fair companies, that don&#8217;t punish you for negative credit. It is much easier to legally clean up your credit than to pay thousands of dollars more for a loan.</p>
<p>Many people raise their credit card limits as high as they can. This will not improve your credit rating, in fact, it will do the opposite. If you reduce your limit, you will not be able to overspend by an obscene amount, and it shows your credit card company that you are a more responsible borrower.</p>
<p>Don&#8217;t just look at your credit score when looking over a free credit report, read it over very carefully. Credit repair means knowing exactly what credit is in your name and how it&#8217;s being rated, so you need to understand each item and then use that knowledge to repair your credit.</p>
<p>To reduce your overall credit card debt and repair your credit score consider taking a personal loan from a loved one such as a parent. Once your cards are paid off lock them away and do not use again. Be sure to make timely payments to your loved one. They may be more forgiving than a credit agency, but you do not want to put an additional strain on the relationship.</p>
<p>To improve your credit rating, pay off unpaid collection accounts. It&#8217;s better to have paid collections in your credit history than unpaid collections, so make dealing with unpaid collections a priority. You can negotiate to reduce the amount you owe and to have derogatory comments removed, but make sure to get any agreements of this kind in writing.</p>
<p>Don&#8217;t play the transfer game; transferring your credit from one card to another to avoid making a payment is only postponing the inevitable payment. Transferring your credit is not saving you money it is really costing you more, you have transfer fee&#8217;s added with each transfer making the amount you owe grow.</p>
<p>To help you improve your credit score you should settle any bad debts. Bad debts are one of the main reasons why your credit score is low. So if you have many bad debts you need to contact your creditors immediately and see if they will let you settle the account.</p>
<p>To make sure your credit score improves, avoid new late payments. New late payments count for more than past late payments &#8212; specifically, the most recent 12 months of your credit history is what counts the most. The more late payments you have in your recent history, the worse your credit score will be. Even if you can&#8217;t pay off your balances yet, make payments on time.</p>
<p>Build credit to repair credit! To show you are a good credit risk, begin building a better credit history, by applying for a low-limit credit card. You can request a lower limit than the creditor offers you &#8211; to keep it at a manageable level! Next, be vigilant about making payments on time. Don&#8217;t fall into the old trap of putting off payments! This will improve your credit scores.</p>
<p>If you are trying to repair your credit score after an inaccurate item has been placed on your credit report, never dispute the item online. If you end up needing to take the dispute to court, the online dispute you submit will be invalid. If you try to dispute through the website and it is not resolved, use written letters instead.</p>
<p>If you have signed up with a credit repair company and realize that you have been scammed, you should immediately file a complaint with the Fair Trade Commission. If the offer you accepted was deceptive and/or illegal, you may have legal recourse to get back any fees you have paid.</p>
<p>Repairing your credit, once it has been damaged, requires time and effort. When you achieve good credit, you should try your best to keep it in good standing. This article has provided you with advice on how to repair your credit. It is up to you to take the necessary steps.</p>
				</div>
			</div>
			</div>
			</div>

		
		<div class="navigation">
			<div class="alignleft"></div>
			<div class="alignright"></div>
		</div>

	
	</div>
	<!-- end #content -->

<div id="sidebar">
	<ul>
		<li id="tag_cloud-3" class="widget widget_tag_cloud"><h2 class="widgettitle">Categories</h2><div><a href='http://stainescorps.org.uk/category/finance/' class='tag-link-1' title='1 topic' style='font-size: 8pt;'>finance</a></div>
</li>	</ul>
</div>
<!-- end #sidebar -->
<div style="clear: both;">&nbsp;</div>
</div>
</div>
<!-- end #page -->
<hr />
</div>
</div>

<!-- end #footer -->
<div id="footer">
	<div>
		<<p>Copyright 2012 <a href="http://stainescorps.org.uk/">Business and Finance Issues</a></p>
	</div>
</div>

</body></html>