<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>  
  <title>Healthy Wealthy nWise</title> 
  <link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com</link> 
   <description>Rocket your way to a successful, balanced life with Healthy Wealthy nWise. Online monthly magazine with fresh content from world famous Speakers, Authors and Mentors.</description>  
  <language>en-us</language> 
  <lastBuildDate>Wed 2 Apr 2008 07:55:17 GMT</lastBuildDate> 

<item>
<title>Rev. Michael Beckwith and Stephen Lewis "Love Is the Passion  
That Drives Life" 
By: Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5413</link>
<description>
JANET ATTWOOD: You said something really interesting. You 
said there are things that can't be treated, but nothing 
can't be healed.
STEPHEN LEWIS: Absolutely, there's nothing that can't be 
healed. You can read about it anywhere. It's always been the 
case. You read about it in tabloids, you can read about it 
in the New England Journal of Medicine. They publish 
articles about a totally inexplicable spontaneous remission, 
and this and that. It's called healing. It happens all the 
time. 
I knew there must be a technology to it. I didn't know that 
it was a fusion, it was a spiritual technology. Michael is 
the one who opened my eyes to that, the thing that I thought 
was science and wondered about it. That's why ...
(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 2 Apr 2008 08:02:06 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Do What Comes Naturally By: Jennifer Read Hawthorne</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5415</link>
<description>
My career as a professional speaker began when I was about 
seven years old. I'd gather all the children in the 
neighborhood and make them sit in rows in our driveway so 
that I could speak to them!
Later, in the eighth grade, I heard that the ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 2 Apr 2008 08:05:37 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>What Activities Are Preventing You From Exercising? Find Your True Priorities By: Lynn Bode, CFT</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5423</link>
<description>
Do you have every intention to exercise today? Did you wake 
up thinking today will be the day to start your new life, 
yet still find yourself going to bed disappointed in 
yourself? You are not alone! For many, it can seem 
impossible to find time to exercise.
But wait, isn't it time to stop making excuses and examine 
what so-called priorities are sabotaging your good 
intentions? Starting an exercise program doesn't have to 
feel like moving a mountain. 
The vast majority of individuals who don't regularly 
exercise say ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 2 Apr 2008 08:08:53 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Magical Powers of Laughter By: John Carpenter Dealey</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5412</link>
<description>
We have all heard the saying that Laughter is the Best 
Medicine. These days, science is going the distance to show 
that this is far from being just another folk remedy. There 
have been many studies on the beneficial effects and great 
value of a good laugh. Medical research and evidence show 
that laughter can actually help you help reduce stress, 
fight disease, and improve your overall well-being. 
Stress has been called the silent killer. Many physicians 
report that over half of their patients are ...
(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 27 Mar 2008 05:45:45 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Staying Active in Cold Weather Months By: Lynn Bode, CFT</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5402</link>
<description>
With the temperatures plummeting this time of year, many of 
us tend to hibernate inside our homes. But, hibernating is 
for bears. As humans it's important to stay active through 
all four seasons. Yet, a poll of 5,000 people found that 30 
percent get no exercise at all during the winter months. 
Just because it is cold outside doesn't make it open season 
for an excuse not to exercise. There are multiple exercise 
options one can choose to participate in regardless of what 
the outdoor thermometer reads. Depending on your location 
and likes, you can choose to workout inside or outside. 
All that is required for ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 27 Mar 2008 05:48:29 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Fun Shui of Money By: Keith Varnum</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5403</link>
<description>
Would you like an easier and more abundant flow of cash in 
your life? You've come to the right place. This article is 
about the Fun Shui of Money. The Fun Easy Flow of Money.
"Shui" in Chinese means "water" or "flow. If you watch water 
in nature, you can feel the water having fun flowing around 
obstacles to get where it wants to go. Attracting an easy, 
extravagant flow of money into your life is a function
of ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 27 Mar 2008 05:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>How to Create Epic Drama in Your Life By: Scott Kalechstein</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5396</link>
<description>
Are you getting your minimum daily requirements of worry and 
chaos?
Do inner peace, gratitude, and contentment occasionally 
creep up on you and sabotage your ability to indulge in your 
anxiety? 
Here's a quick and handy two step process for making sure 
your world is full of epic drama.
Believe and act like your safety, security, success and 
happiness are dependent on other people and forces outside 
of you that you can't control.
Try to control them.
For those of you who prefer to ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 20 Mar 2008 05:12:27 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
 
<item>
<title>Selling Your Business -- Top 7 Ways to Maximize Your Exit Strategy Now for Maximum Profit By: Harvey Zemmel</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5400</link> 
<description>
Leading financial researchers report that 75 percent of U.S. 
businesses do not sell. It dismays me to see entrepreneurs 
receiving so little in return for all their years of hard 
work. Or, having to shut their doors with no buyers in 
sight. 
It's even more disappointing, since businesses can easily 
take steps to achieve maximum perceived value for a 
potential buyer. It just takes a little planning, know-how 
and application to take a $100,000 a year profit generating 
business and sell it for either $200,000 or for over a 
million bucks? ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 20 Mar 2008 05:18:34 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Garlic is Heart Healthy By: Kathy Kastan and Suzanne Banfield</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5398</link>
<description>
Considered so sacred by the ancient Egyptians, it was placed 
in the tombs of Pharaohs. Believed to be so powerful by the 
Greeks and Romans, they ritually consumed it prior to going 
to war. So loved by the Israelites, they pined for it when 
wandering the desert. Of what are we speaking? Garlic... of 
course.
Hippocrates and Pliny the Elder strongly encouraged ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 20 Mar 2008 05:20:03 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Relationship Advice: Why True Love Isn't A Fairy Tale By: Brenda Novak</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5399</link>
<description>
While doing a signing for my latest romance novel, a woman 
passed by, picked up my book, and immediately wrinkled her 
nose. 
"I don't read these kinds of books," she said.
"What do you read?" I asked.
She slapped it down on the table as if it was so far beneath 
her she couldn't bare to touch it any longer. "Something 
with at least a hint of realism."
"I'm sorry for you," I said. 
And I meant it. 
Why?
Because ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 13 Mar 2008 17:12:43 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Exploring Your Relationship with Money By: Jennifer Read Hawthorne</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5405</link>
<description>
Don't chase money-you'll never catch it.
Debbi Fields
I was once a member of the "I'll Be Happy When" club. If I 
could just find the perfect mate and the perfect job-and 
become a millionaire quickly-then I'd be totally fulfilled.
I set out to achieve these goals with a vengeance. I thought 
success, especially the material kind, required it. In fact, 
I took a ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 13 Mar 2008 17:15:02 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Estate Planning Tips for Parents: How to Choose the Right Guardian for Your Children? By: Alexis Neely</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5401</link>
<description>
Estate planning and choosing a guardian to take care of your 
children is difficult. It's not easy to think of anyone else
raising your children, no matter how loving your family 
members or friends are. 
Yet, you can make a tremendous difference in your child's 
life by planning ahead. And you have nothing to lose except 
a few moments thinking about what you value most in life, 
and in childrearing. You can ensure you have chosen the 
right guardian, by following just three easy steps...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 13 Mar 2008 17:17:53 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Marci Shimoff "The Keys to Being Happy for No Reason" By: Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5395</link>
<description>
JANET ATTWOOD: Happy for No Reason suggests a whole new 
paradigm of happiness. What exactly do you mean by 'happy 
for no reason'?
MARCI SHIMOFF: Happy for No Reason is a whole new paradigm 
of happiness. Before I go into what that paradigm is, I want 
to also say what the deal is about happiness these days in 
our society, because it's hugely hot. Everywhere you turn, 
people are talking about happiness. It's been on the cover 
of Time magazine. Publishers Weekly said in an article 
recently that every once in a while a new trend comes along 
in publishing, and the trend of today is happiness.
In fact, they called it the 'new black'; it's the in-fashion 
thing. Part of why I think people are talking about 
happiness right now so much is that ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 6 Mar 2008 18:42:05 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Moving Free® With Mirabai - Need a Good Night's Sleep? Try Easy Aerobics By: Mirabai Holland</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5407</link>
<description>
Need a Good Night's Sleep? Try Easy Aerobics.
Health experts recommend eight hours of sleep a night for 
most adults. Yet so many of us get fewer than six-and-a-half 
hours during the work- week....
We all love a good night's sleep. But did you know that not 
getting one not only makes you dull and stressed, it can 
also make you pack on the pounds.
Too little physical activity is ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 6 Mar 2008 18:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Timeouts Can Cause Misbehavior By: Dr. Laura Markham</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5406</link>
<description>
Most parents nowadays try not to use physical punishment, 
which they know undermines kids' self esteem. Many experts 
advise using timeouts to "calm" kids down and correct bad 
behavior. But any child can explain to you that timeouts are 
still punishment. And we all know that sending a kid to a 
timeout it is not the best way to calm him!
What's wrong with timeouts for disciplining kids? ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 6 Mar 2008 18:41:57 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>When It Comes To Referrals, Quality Beats Quantity...Hands Down! By: Ivan Misner</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5384</link>
<description>
While it is indeed true that you want to get a good number 
of referrals, it is true only up to a point. Taking it to 
the extreme, you can get as many referrals as you could 
conceivably handle, but if nearly all of them are of low 
quality-hard to close or not very valuable when closed-
you're no better off than if you simply sat at your desk 
and spent all day cold-calling. The same is true if you...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 28 Feb 2008 11:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Moving Free® With Mirabai By: Mirabai Holland</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5382</link>
<description>
Mirabai Holland M.F.A. is one of the leading authorities in 
the Health and Fitness industry, and public health activist 
who specializes in preventive and rehabilitative exercise 
for women. Her Moving Free™ approach to exercise is 
designed to provide a movement experience so pleasant it 
doesn't feel like work. 
February 14th is Valentine's Day. And since 1963, when 
Congress and the American Heart Association declared...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 28 Feb 2008 11:09:33 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Power of Being Present By: Jennifer Read Hawthorne</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5386</link>
<description>
This place where you are right now,
God circled on a map for you. - Hafiz.  
Sometimes we get so involved thinking about the past or the 
future that we simply forget what's going on right in front 
of us. At times like these, I find it valuable to remember 
the advice of my friend Stacy, whose life was turned upside 
down when...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 28 Feb 2008 11:13:47 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Boundaries Protect Who We Are By: Tim Murphy</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5392 </link>
<description>
The human life is precious. Many of us have gone through 
adversities in life that have given us the false impression 
that we are less than, or that we don't belong. Nothing 
could be farther from the truth. There's a purpose and a 
plan for your life. Because you are worth it - you need to 
protect yourself with boundaries.
Those of us, who've allowed our self esteem to go down hill, 
must realize it can't stay down there. To begin to enjoy 
life the way it was intended we all need...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>thu 21 Feb 2008 16:28:36 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Back Pain at the Office By: Jesse Cannone CFT, CPRS, CSPN</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5381</link>
<description>
It's getting to be so bad that by Monday afternoon, you're 
already tired of being at the office. You're not even 
thinking as far ahead as Friday. Just getting to hump day is 
going to be challenge enough.
In reality, it's not the folks you work with who are getting 
you down-they're tolerable, mostly, although there is that 
one guy in accounting. Where do they find these people?
It's not even your boss, who, if he knew even half as much 
as you do, would be a shoo-in for Executive of the Year.
No, the biggest pain in your...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 21 Feb 2008 16:60:47 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Food Allergy - 5 Steps To Healthy Eating Using An Elimination Diet By: Cinda Crawford</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5389</link>
<description>
Whether you suffer with pesky health problems like 
allergies, being overweight, Irritable Bowel Syndrome, 
Fibromyalgia, Chronic Fatigue Syndrome, Lupus, Crohn's 
Disease or certain types of Arthritis, your daily diet plays 
a major role in how you feel, what symptoms you battle and 
how successful you'll be in feeling better. I've lived 
through such an experience; I was sick for fifteen years. I 
started healing five years ago. Now I'm completely well 
using the same strategies and techniques that I share with 
my clients every day.
Step 1...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 21 Feb 2008 16:33:17 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Many Faces of Love - Laughter, Joy, Faith, Forgiveness and Gratitude By: John Carpenter Dealey</title>
<link>http://healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5385</link>
<description>
Since the dawn of time, humanity has been looking for love. 
Ancient cave paintings hint at the importance of love in the 
earliest of societies. Throughout history, as far back as 
the ancient philosophers of Rome and Greece, writers have 
been writing about love. For centuries, scientists have been 
trying to distill the essence of love and merchants have 
been trying to package and profit from this marvelous thing 
we call 'love'. 
What is love anyway?...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 14 Feb 2008 01:38:25 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Rewarding Employees Without a Reward Program By: Ruth Haag</title>
<link>http://healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5383</link>
<description>
Have you noticed that the "Employee of the Month" parking 
places at many department stores are remaining empty? I can 
only assume that this particular reward program has been 
disbanded, but no one thought to remove the sign.
Many reward programs are started with great excitement, and 
then fizzle out. The goal of reward programs is to create a 
gift that the employee will want so badly that they will 
work harder to obtain it. A secondary, unspoken, goal is for 
the supervisor to ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 14 Feb 2008 01:53:07 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Family Dinner : Fast and Simple By: Cheryl Tallman and Joan Ahlers</title>
<link>http://healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5378</link>
<description>
Home made foods are healthier than processed, prepared, or 
restaurant meals. Take-out foods and prepared foods are 
generally much higher in fat, salt and calories than home 
cooked foods. We would encourage you or your spouse to make 
home-cooked dinners at least three times per week 
If just thought of making dinner exhausts you, here are few 
tips to ease the burden of getting dinner on the table 
during your busy week...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 14 Feb 2008 01:58:26 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>James Ray "Be a Student, Not a Seeker" By: Chris Attwood and Scott Martineau</title>
<link>http://healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5377</link>
<description>
SCOTT MARTINEAU: Absolutely, absolutely. Let me ask you 
this. You do have an unusual adult experience, as well. You 
start off in corporate America, and then I don't know if you 
reject it, but you take a different path, and you say, "I'm 
going to study now with shamans in South America. You go 
from that to being featured on "Oprah" and "Larry King." You 
have an unusual path.
JAMES RAY: It is, it is very eclectic; call me eclectic. I 
said I was a weird kid; maybe I'm just weird all the way 
around, as compared to the average individual. Who knows 
whether we can ever prove reincarnation or not? Every great 
spiritual tradition believes in it, including Mystical 
Christianity. Who knows? No one can prove it, and yet one 
of the theories in reincarnation is that you ...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 7 Feb 2008 18:34:18 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Super Bowl Time Management Tips By: Laura Stack</title>
<link>http://healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5380</link>
<description>
By studying the game of football, you can learn a lot about 
how to set and achieve goals and spend your time more 
productively. What does time management have to do with 
Super Bowl football? Everything! Football pros competing in 
the Super Bowl use great goal-setting techniques. 
By studying the game, you too can...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 7 Feb 2008 16:37:38 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Is Cellulite Your Fault? 10 Common Myths and Facts By: Lionel Bissoon</title>
<link>http://healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5390</link>
<description>
Although about 90% of American women suffer from some degree 
of cellulite, it's not uncommon for many to think that, 
somehow, the condition is their own fault - that they must 
have brought it on themselves. Unfortunately, many 
boyfriends, husbands and significant others fuel this 
unwarranted guilt complex by suggesting that...
"You haven't stayed in shape by exercising enough."
"You've gotten fat, which is (obviously) the cause of 
cellulite. Cellulite is something overweight women get, 
right?"
"There's nothing you can do about it. Your mother and 
grandmother had cellulite, so you're doomed to live with it 
- DOOMED! How's your sister doing?"
Nonsense...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 7 Feb 2008 18:41:09 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Mastermind - the Power to Change Your World By: John Carpenter Dealey</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5365</link>
<description>You may have heard the word "Mastermind" before. In fact, 
 you may already be a part of one, two, or even several 
 mastermind groups. Groups of like-minded people focused on 
 the same dream, the same goal, or with simply similar 
 attitudes about life. 
 Or you may not have heard this word. Mastermind. What does 
 it mean? And, more importantly, how can it help you lead the 
 life you want to lead...  article continues at: 
 </description>
 <pubDate>Thu 31 Jan 2008 10:00:01 GMT</pubDate> 
 </item>

<item>
<title>Contrary to What You May Think, the Referral Process is Not 
 Difficult to Measure! By: Ivan Misner</title>
 <link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5364</link>
 <description>Most everyone who has ever tried to keep a truly accurate 
 count of how many "cold calls" led to actual, cash-in-your-
 pocket sales knows that this is not an easy task. The good 
 news is that it is actually quite easy to measure success 
 from referrals! We know this because we've designed a 
 networking scorecard for tracking referrals and the business 
 that results from them. You might want to develop a similar 
 one for your own use. On this card, you...article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 31 Jan 2008 10:05:01 GMT</pubDate> 
</item>

<item>
<title>8 KEY CATALYSTS -- Speak with Good Purpose By: Bobbi DePorter</title>
 <link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5370</link>
 <description>Before reading this second article on Speak with Good 
 Purpose, you may want to look at last month's article where 
 we considered:
 Why Speak with Good Purpose? 
 It's all about awareness 
 Think about the intention of your words
 SPEAK WITH GOOD PURPOSE
 Give positive, honest and direct communication.
 Let's look at some of the more subtle aspects of this Key 
 Catalyst, such as Visible Communication, Communication 
 Killers, and Active Listening. This is all about positive, 
 honest and direct communication, although some of it may 
 appear to be less than positive on the surface. First let's 
 consider the most negative of all communication 
 forms - gossip...article continues at:
 </description>
 <pubDate>Thu 31 Jan 2008 10:10:05 GMT</pubDate>
 </item>
 

<item>
<title>Trusting Your Vision By: Jennifer Read Hawthorne</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5369</link>
<description>If you have built castles in the air, your work need not be 
 lost; that is where they should be. Now put the foundations 
 under them. -- Henry David Thoreau 
   A vision is something that has been seen. It may be a 
 fantasy you had at a young age that never let go, or a 
 passion that emerged in a time of crisis. It might be born 
 when you find yourself at a crossroads, no longer willing to 
 do things the same old way. It may arise out of need, as an 
 answer to a problem, or a deep soul desire felt within. And 
 it may seem impractical-even impossible.
  But remember what the Queen said when Alice in Wonderland 
 noted that one can't believe in impossible things...
 article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 24 Jan 2008 11:30:56 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Laugh Your Way to Pain Relief By: Steven Hefferon</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5373</link>
 <description>A man rushed into a veterinarian's office carrying his limp, 
 lifeless dog. The vet examined the animal and told the man 
 the dog was dead. The man asked if there was any way the 
 doctor could revive the dog. The doctor left the room and 
 returned with a cat, who sniffed the dog from head to tail 
 then looked up at the vet and meowed.
 "Sorry," said the doctor. "There's nothing I can do."
 "Thanks for trying," said the man with a sigh. "How much do 
 I owe you?"
 "Three hundred and fifty dollars," replied the doctor.
 "Three hundred and fifty dollars! Just to tell me my dog is 
 dead?"
 "Well," said the doctor, "it was $50 for the office visit. 
 The other $300 is for the CAT scan."
 Whether the above joke made you laugh or groan, it...
article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu Jan 24 2008 11:32:25 GMT</pubDate>
 </item>
 
 <item>
 <title> Steven E "Give Help to Get Help" By: Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5361</link>
<description>Mark Victor Hansen, the fabulously successful co-author of 
 the Chicken Soup for the Soul series, has said, "Don't wait 
 until everything is just right, it will never be perfect. 
 There will always be challenges, obstacles, and less-than-
 perfect conditions. So what? Get started now. With each step 
 you take, you will grow stronger and stronger, more and more 
 skilled, more and more self-confident, and more and more 
 successful."
 Steven E was partners with Chris and Janet Attwood and Mark 
 Victor Hansen in The Enlightened Millionaire Program. Steven 
 took Mark's advice and...
 article continues at: 
 </description>
 <pubDate>Thu 24 Jan 2008 11:35:56 GMT</pubDate>
 </item>
 
<item>
<title>Hobbies for Couples: How to End Solo Sport Resentment and Create a Lifetime Bond at the Same Time By: Kristie Macdonald</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5372</link>
<description>
One of the best ways to strengthen love is through 
friendship. And one of the best ways to build friendship is 
through good old-fashioned play.
Now, of course, this may require some cozy conversation over 
a good glass of Chardonnay to remember what good old-
fashioned fun was really like. But well worth the effort, 
according to a recent study that showed a strong correlation 
between love and play. 
Couples who...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 17 Jan 2008 10:22:08 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Fun Police By: Scott Kalechstein</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5368</link>
<description>
I have come to believe that how much joy I experience in any 
given moment pretty much boils down to how much permission I 
give myself to have it. Sounds simple enough, but for many 
of us, after a lifetime of withholding permission from 
ourselves, we might notice some subtle resistance to 
increasing our joy allowance.
A few years back I...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 17 Jan 2008 10:25:42 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Find Your Center and Reach Your Goals for 2008 By: Dr. Stephen Ruppenthal</title> 
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5367</link>
<description>
The New Year is a time to wipe the slate clean. With 
heartfelt zeal, we can earnestly make a new start. As the 
great Zen master Suzuki-roshi used to say, we contact what 
is called the beginner's mind, a real hope for keeping new 
resolutions about ourselves. Of course it's great to post
such resolutions in your office or on the refrigerator, 
keeping them right before you as you strive for personal 
change. Since change is so hard, particularly in areas where 
we have shown considerable weakness, here are five helpful 
ways to find your center within yourself and hold fast to 
the new behavior in the New Year...article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 17 Jan 2008 10:33:13 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Mediterranean Diet: How to Lower Cholesterol and Reduce Your Risk of Heart Disease by 22% By: Emilia Klapp</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5375</link>
<description>
For centuries, legumes, or dry beans, have played an 
important part in the fight against heart disease in the 
Mediterranean countries. 
Here's why...
Legumes contain essential minerals and vitamins such as 
iron, magnesium, manganese, phosphorous, zinc, potassium, 
folic acid, and some of the B-complex vitamins.
They are low in fat and sodium, which make them an ideal 
food to keep high...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 10 Jan 2008 19:29:07 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>When is it OK to be Rude? By: Ruth Haag</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5363</link>
<description>
The title of this column is a question that I often ask the 
attendees at my management training classes. Normally we are 
discussing how to discipline problem employees. My answer 
is: It is never OK to be rude. 
I often find that the person who perceives that they are in 
the position of power becomes rude. They get so focused on 
their power that they forget to think about ...
(article continues at:</description> 
<pubDate>Thu 10 Jan 2008 19:33:50 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Art of Relating By: Keith Varnum</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5376</link>
<description>
I cringed at every loaded word in the title of Dale 
Carnegie's celebrated book, How to Win Friends and Influence 
People! My mother-God bless her!-made me take the Dale 
Carnegie Training forty years ago when I was in junior high 
school. The idea that I had to change myself to "win" 
friends and "influence" people felt manipulative and 
distasteful to an idealistic teenager. But once I absorbed 
the authentic attitude of Carnegie's way of connecting with 
people, I ...(article continues at:</description> 
<pubDate>Thu 10 Jan 2008 19:45:25 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Paula Abdul "Desire, Not Timing, Makes Your Dreams Come True" By: Janet Attwood and Debra Poneman</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5360</link>
<description>
PAULA ABDUL: I finally got to work with my idol, Gene Kelly, 
and have tea with him during the last two years of his life. 
DEBRA PONEMAN: That is just beautiful.
PAULA ABDUL: I dedicated my own video, which was where I 
created animation, where I danced with an animated cat, Skat 
Kat. I dedicated it to him. He was my mentor, and I wanted 
to dedicate that animation to him. When it got to him, he 
contacted my agent and asked me over for tea, so it was Tea 
on Tuesday. I arrived at his house like an hour-and-a-half 
early. 
I was sweating in my car because I couldn't...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 3 Jan 2008 21:05:32 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Your New Year's Resolution: Take a Fresh Look at Your Productivity Habits By: Laura Stack</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5362</link>
<description> 
The end of the year is a classic opportunity to look back 
over how things have been going and look forward to see how 
they could improve. January brings that fresh start that we 
all long for - let's make the most of it! 
Think of all the things that drive you crazy - the biggest 
obstacles to your personal and professional productivity. 
For sanity's sake, you might have chosen to pick your 
battles and resigned yourself to some pretty ridiculous 
productivity drains over the years.
Maybe you decided that a staff meeting at work will always 
be a waste of time and have given up the good fight on 
making it better. Or it might be as simple as giving up on 
making it out the door with a decent breakfast in your 
belly.
Not this year! Let's take 2008 by storm and...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 3 Jan 2008 21:07:52 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Moving FreeR with Mirabai By: Mirabai Holland</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5366</link>
<description>
Mirabai Holland M.F.A. is one of the leading authorities in 
the Health and Fitness industry, and public health activist 
who specializing in preventive and rehabilitative exercise 
for women. Her Moving FreeT approach to exercise is designed 
to provide a movement experience so pleasant it doesn't feel 
like work.
Well, it's January again, and we're all wondering if we can 
really stick with those New Year's resolutions. If getting 
in shape and staying there is one of yours, here are my Top 
10 Tips to help you ward off decrepitude... (article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 3 Jan 2008 21:12:08 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>MTO Goals - Be Happy Where You Are! By: John Carpenter Dealey</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5351</link>
<description>
The holidays are here and another full year has flown by.
This is a good time to review your progress.  You will have
plenty of opportunities to celebrate your victories with
others, as well as ample time to revise and reset those
goals you didn't quite reach.
Research has shown that people who have written down and
regularly review their goals earn more money than those
without goals. In addition, similar recent studies have
shown that people with...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Fri 28 Dec 2007 16:53:52 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Moving Free® with Mirabai By: Mirabai Holland</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5352</link>
<description>
Mirabai Holland M.F.A. is one of the leading authorities in
the Health and Fitness industry, and public health activist
who specializing in preventive and rehabilitative exercise
for women. Her Moving Free™ approach to exercise is designed
to provide a movement experience so pleasant it doesn't feel
like work.
Every year at this time people watching their weight and
trying to stay fit start to panic. I've begun to get those
emails saying...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Fri 28 Dec 2007 16:55:57 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Visiting Children and Your Dog By: Colleen Pelar</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5348</link>
<description>
Kevin came over to play today.  For the past two hours, he
and my 6-year-old son Brandon have been running through the
house playing hide and seek. They've gone in every room at
least twice, have repeatedly hollered up and down the
stairs, and have even attempted to sneak up behind me a few
times, but their giggling always gives them away. The boys
are having a wonderful visit.
This whole time, my dog, Gordo, has been in his crate.
Gordo is...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Fri 28 Dec 2007 17:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 

<item>
<title>The Terror-List By: Scott Kalechstein</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5355</link>
<description>
"Resist not evil."
- Jesus The Christ - 
In a cave between my ears there hides a terrorist who has 
been waging a holy war for a very long time. He believes 
that he is justified in using force and fear tactics, and 
that it is necessary to hold my inner child hostage to 
create real change and growth. He presents a running list of 
demands - all the things I must accomplish before I can feel 
good enough about myself to love myself unconditionally. The 
list is never-ending, and somewhat insatiable. Whenever I 
meet a demand...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 20 Dec 2007 11:35:08 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Aging Well - Guard Against Aging with Strong Relationships  By: Dr. Stephen Ruppenthal</title> 
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5354</link>
<description>
As we pass into our forties, dip into our fifties or 
experience the sixties, and as the body inevitably loses 
looks and vitality, it is important to have forces at work 
that support who we truly are. One of these is the power of 
relationships.  "Grow old along with me," says Robert 
Browning, "the best is yet to be:  the last for which the 
first was meant to be." But how do relationships help us?  
Should we have the same kinds of friends all our life? When 
it is time to end a particular relationship? Here are four 
practical strategies to keep in mind...(article continues at: 
</description> 
<pubDate>Thu 20 Dec 2007 11:40:27 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
 
<item>
<title>Creating a Balanced Inner World for Our Children By: Sally Sacks</title> 
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5349</link>
<description>
We are all made up of many parts.  For example, if we are 
fifty, we still have a part of us that is twelve. It may 
show up when we are at a carnival with our kids, or visiting 
a place where we lived at that age. 
We may be 60 and go to our high school reunion, and 
instantly, we are thrown back to being 16, and a junior in 
high school. We can experience the same emotions, feelings, 
and thoughts that we did back then. We may see a person that 
we adored, and cherish that memory. We create parts of 
ourselves that warn us and protect us. 
I remember when I first saw the movie Jaws. After watching 
that movie, I... (article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 20 Dec 2007 11:43:43 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
 
<item>
<title>Dr. Andrew Newberg "Belief: The Essence of Our Being" By: Chris Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5342</link>
<description>
ANDREW NEWBERG: What I was so fascinated by was that, for
example, when we did a scan of a nun in prayer, when we
talked to the nun about the results and we showed her the
changes in the brain, and so forth, she said, "Wow, this is
really great. This helps me to understand how God has an
influence in my life, how religion is so important, and how
my spiritual side is connected with my biological side. This
is great."
She thanked me, and it was so wonderful that this helped to
support and validate her way of believing about the world. I
was equally intrigued by the fact that a number of people
who were not religious, people who would describe themselves
as atheists, would look at the same scans, the same data,
and so forth, and they would come to me and they would
say...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 6 Dec 2007 08:38:24 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Success and Failure of Holiday Office Parties By: Ruth Haag</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5344</link>
<description>
Holiday office parties are a tradition for most companies.
Along with celebrating the holidays, they can provide a
relaxed atmosphere in which employees can find out more
about one another, and their families.  However, if parties
are poorly managed, they can create irritation and strife.
The Best Party
The first staff that I supervised was made up of college
students.  None of us were making much money, and no one
could afford a fancy holiday party.  We decided that a
pot-luck might work.  We found a large room in our own
building, and had a sign-up sheet so that we wouldn't get
too many baked-bean casseroles.  On the assigned day we met.
Everyone was allowed to bring along their Significant Other.
It was a wonderful party.  The food was fun.  The party was
a success and the staff worked better together afterwards.
The Worst Party...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 6 Dec 2007 08:45:06 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Fresh Baby To Go By: Cheryl Tallman and Joan Ahlers</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5347</link>
<description>
These days, families are always on the go, whether it's off
to daycare everyday or to visit friends and family once in a
while. Here are some strategies to help you prepare for your
baby's meals on the go. Start with six golden rules for
serving Fresh Baby food away from home...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 6 Dec 2007 09:03:27 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Work is Necessary; Struggle is Optional By: C.J. Hayden</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5327</link>
<description>
I hear from many entrepreneurs that marketing is a struggle.
They just can't get enough clients to pay the bills, or they
are spending more money to get each client than the sale is
worth. So many of their efforts seem to fail. There must be
an easier way, they tell me.
I think there is. But making the transition from the hard
way to the easy way can be pretty difficult in itself.
That's because it requires the...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 29 Nov 2007 15:13:28 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Rising Above the Pack of Online Content: Promoting Yourself As an Expert Makes the Difference By: Anne Leedom</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5333</link>
<description>
The Internet is now becoming a mainstream media destination
for experts, authors and companies who want to access the
millions of repeat visitors daily to promote their work. It
is more important than ever before that you are aware of the
various kinds of services available. You want to make the
best possible choice in hiring an online marketing company
to help you reach your goals. Here are three of the most
common kinds of services you will find and what you can...
(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 29 Nov 2007 15:17:36 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Advantages of Living Out Loud By: Keith Varnum</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5331</link>
<description>
Every time someone asks us a question, we have a choice to
make, "How much truth shall I express?" "How much of my True
Self should I reveal?"
Among our choices are the "convenient" truth, the
"diplomatic" truth, the "socially accepted" truth, or the
"absolute" truth that is, "the whole truth and nothing but
the truth, so help me God!"
Do any of us even know the absolute truth about any
situation in our lives? And can we ourselves handle the
whole truth all at once about any subject? Let alone share
that depth with others?
I make a practical choice. I state to myself this daily
intention...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 29 Nov 2007 15:25:32 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Aging Well: Building a Legacy for the Future By: Dr. Stephen Ruppenthal</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5341</link>
<description>
Have you ever thought that giving your life to what you do 
best might help you feel the weight of the years much less? 
It sounds implausible, but if you think about it, we are all 
special. All of us have something to pass on to others, so 
that the best of us lives on. Even if we don't think we have 
them, all of us can discover and utilize our unique talents, 
skills, aptitudes, and character--whether we are 35 or 65-- 
to make a life-enriching difference. Even if we are not 
Mother Teresa or Albert Einstein, we may well be an 
extraordinary partner, parent, grandparent, or friend, 
without really knowing it. Or we may be that artist or 
teacher who can ignite the spark of enthusiasm and adventure 
in those who will be here after we are gone. Shakespeare 
lays down the challenge as he says, 
Look in the mirror and tell the face thou viewest
Now is the time that face should form another.
If you are interested not just in the undirected path of 
life, but in consciously leaving a legacy that will enrich 
lives you touch, here are four ways you can start right 
away...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Fri 23 Nov 2007 09:45:23 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jeffrey Smith "Truth Triumphs" By: Chris Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5326</link>
<description>
Maharishi Mahesh Yogi once said, "There is no difficulty 
that enough love will not conquer, no disease that enough 
love will not heal, no door that enough love will not open, 
no gulf that enough love will not bridge, no walls that 
enough love will not throw down, no sin that enough love 
will not redeem. It makes no difference how deeply seated 
may be the trouble, how great the mistake, sufficient 
realization of love will solve it all. If you could love 
enough, you would be the happiest and most powerful being in 
the world."
At times, love for life and for humanity requires pointing 
out directions that do not support us in creating a better, 
healthier, more fulfilled world.  Jeffery Smith has had the 
courage to do the research and bring to light the dangers 
posed by large corporations that put profits ahead of our 
collective health. Jeffrey Smith is the author of Seeds of 
Deception, the world's bestselling book on the dangers of 
genetically modified foods and the recently released...
(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Fri 23 Nov 2007 10:04:37 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Holidays with Ease: A One-Pot Turkey Dinner with All the Trimmings By: Elizabeth Yarnell</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5328</link>
<description>
A holiday meal is typically an occasion for breaking bread 
and sharing the hearth with our family, friends and 
community.
While not everyone wants to cook for an army during the 
holidays, there is still something about having a 
traditional holiday meal that evokes a feeling of 
celebration and custom. It's not only the combination of 
foods particular to that holiday ritual that feeds the 
senses, but also the likelihood that the event offered an 
opportunity to share the workload increases the bonds of 
kinship and friendship.
For those passing a holiday alone or with one other rather 
than a crowd, there can be a sense of deprivation with the 
loss of the opportunity to partake in the traditional feast 
of the season of turkey, cranberries and sweet potatoes.
Here is a great solution to getting the meal with all the 
trimmings without spending hours and hours in the kitchen or 
facing a week of leftovers...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Fri 23 Nov 2007 10:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 

<item>
<title>The Conscious Relationship Workout By: Scott Kalechstein</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5335</link>
<description> 
"As you may have noticed, relationships are not here to 
make you happy or fulfilled. If you continue to pursue the 
goal of salvation through a relationship, you will be 
disillusioned again and again. But if you accept that the 
relationship is here to make you conscious instead of happy, 
then the relationship will offer you salvation, and you will 
be aligning yourself with the higher consciousness that 
wants to be born into this world." 
-Eckhart Tolle
The following questions and exercises are designed to be a 
vigorous ... (article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 15 Nov 2007 16:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Making Sense of Scents: The Truth about Air Fresheners and Scented Household Cleaners By: Beth Greer, Super Natural Mom</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5329</link>
<description> 
If you are buying scented air fresheners and household 
cleaning products, chances are you are exposing yourself to 
chemicals that are bad for you.  For example, The NRDC 
(Natural Resources Defense Council) recently found that 12 
out of 14 popular air freshener brands contained phthalates, 
chemicals that can cause hormonal abnormalities, birth 
defects and reproductive problems. The National Academy of 
Sciences (NAS) reports that...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 15 Nov 2007 14:12:04GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Referrals are Predictable! By: Ivan Misner</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5334</link>
<description>
When you have a fully functioning referral-marketing 
strategy in operation, you will know approximately how many 
referrals you can expect, and of what quality they will 
likely be, over a given period. True, you won't know very 
far in advance exactly whom you're going to be selling to or 
how much the order will be, but that's true of almost all 
marketing techniques. So if you look at each individual 
sale, it may be hard to understand exactly how that sales 
opportunity came to you.
A few years ago, one member of a referral-networking group 
(we'll call him Frank), a business owner who was well-liked 
and had received plenty of referrals, decided to...(article continues at:  
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 15 Nov 2007 14:15:37 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jay Conrad Levinson "Meeting Conventional Goals with Unconventional Means" By: Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5325</link>
<description>
JAY CONRAD LEVINSON: Yes, I can answer that question because
you're not asking it for the first time. When I graduated
from the University of Iowa in 1956, I was drafted on my way
to law school. I enlisted in the Army and I was lucky
enough, of all things, to be assigned to the Counter
Intelligence Corps, which sounds very 'cloak and dagger' and
was.
It was every bit what you'd imagine James Bond's life to be
like as a counterspy, but I was in it for less than two
years, although I was assigned to a section called
'Derogatory,' which meant that I only participated in cases
about people upon whom derogatory information had been
turned up. All the cases I worked on were interesting. I did
surveillances and interrogations and learned quite a bit
about...(article continues at: 
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 8 Nov 2007 08:39:56 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Setting SMART Fitness Goals By: Lynn Bode, CFT</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5332</link>
<description>
Setting SMART Fitness Goals
One of the simplest steps you can take when you embark on
improving your health and wellness is setting your goals.
Right? Actually, creating goals should not be taken lightly.
To improve your success rate with achieving your objectives,
you need to create a specific roadmap.
You need to set up SMART goals. They need to be: Specific,
Measurable, Attainable, Relevant and Time-Oriented.
You need to state specifically what you want to accomplish.
The goal should be very easy to measure. There should be no
question at all whether or not it has been reached. It
should be something you can truly obtain, not just an
unrealistic dream. It should be relevant to your needs. You
should include a deadline.
So, the clichés of simply wanting to "drop some pounds",
"fit back into your jeans" or "get bigger biceps", don't fit
into the SMART model. Reworking these vague goals, though,
will help you get and stay on the road to better fitness.
The first example is losing some weight. Here is the
reworked SMART goal:...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 8 Nov 2007 08:42:12 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Our Children Are Our Teachers By: Penny Dee</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5339</link>
<description>
Having the great privilege and honour to be a parent, I find
it alarming how little we understand the connected minds of
our little ones.
Children are still very much in the source energy and they
can light up our lives and teach us plenty if we would stop
telling for a while and start listening.
Their message is clear.  The bounce, optimism, inability to
understand negatives, all of that and more are their gifts
to us.
When did you last see a child looking into the Ice Cream
Parlour and noting all of the ones they dislike and why??
They go through the list and immediately jump for the one
which to them has neon lights around it and is the absolute
must-have.
That is how we should live our lives.  Look through the menu
of life and pounce on the things which are absolutely lit up
for us.
With my own clients I liken it to...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 8 Nov 2007 08:46:17 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Moving Free with Mirabai By: Mirabai Holland</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5310</link>
<description>
Mirabai Holland M.F.A. is one of the leading authorities in
the Health and Fitness industry, and public health activist
who specializes in preventive and rehabilitative exercise
for women. Her Moving Free™ approach to exercise is designed
to provide a movement experience so pleasant it doesn't feel
like work.
Q I am recovering from breast cancer. I finished my
chemotherapy a few weeks ago and though I still feel weak, I
was wondering if I should start exercising again?
A. If your...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 1 Nov 2007 09:35:28 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ellie Drake "Find a Passion That's Stronger Than Coffee" By: Chris Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5309</link>
<description>
Joseph Campbell said, "People say that what we are seeking
is a meaningful life. I don't think that this is what we're
really seeking. I think what we are seeking is an experience
of being alive."
Ellie Drake has been fully engaged in the experience of
being alive. Raised in Iran, she immigrated to the US with
her parents as a teenager and has since made the 'American
Dream' a real-life experience in her life. After a series of
seven-figure successes, Ellie burst onto the scene as an
inspirational speaker. She is in such demand as a speaker
because her...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 1 Nov 2007 09:45:02 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>How to Improve Your Customer Service Call Center So You Can Achieve Double-Digit Response Rates By: Ernam Roman</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5322</link>
<description>
When your customers buy an important product from you, they
trust your company will support them after the sale. In many
companies, this trust is being violated. Customers are
experiencing "customer service blow-offs" and translate
these experiences into your company saying:
"You've already bought. Now our priority is getting more new
customers."
"You want service? Go figure it out on the Web or wait on
hold for one of our poorly trained customer service
representatives."
Per my company's research findings, the damage from poor
Customer Service Call Center experiences is serious. Here's
how...(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 1 Nov 2007 10:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Lose Weight: 3 Sure-Fire Ways Busy Executives Blow Their Weight Loss Efforts By: Jeanie Callen Barat</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5321</link>
<description> 
Your company's recent merger is on a tidy timetable. Your IT 
department backs up your valuable data every Friday at 9. 
The water cooler guy arrives every Tuesday at noon. Busy 
executives know the importance of structure and regularity 
in juggling business responsibilities. But should you be so 
rigid when it comes to your nutrition and fitness routines 
and choices? 
Having well-established habits and a consistent routine 
is...(article continues at: )
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 24 Oct 2007 21:32:12 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Even If You're Getting All the Referrals You Need, You Still Need to Sell! By: Ivan Misner</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5317</link>
<description>
Anyone who is experienced and successful in referral 
marketing will tell you that sales skills are absolutely 
required. They're needed in every part of the process--not 
just in closing the sale with the prospect. 
>First, you have to sell yourself to your potential referral 
source--she has to buy the concept that there's value in 
introducing you to someone she knows. A referral is not a 
guaranteed sale; it's the opportunity to do business with 
someone to whom you have been recommended. You still have to 
close the deal--most of the time. You have to make it clear 
that you... (article continues at:) 
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 24 Oct 2007 21:43:07 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Intentional Abundance - Tune in and Receive! By: John Carpenter Dealey</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5311</link>
<description> 
How would you like your life to be?  Would you like to make 
a change or stay the way you are?  Most of us have some 
things we would like to change or have more of.  The good 
news is that intention and manifestation can help you create 
the life of your dreams! 
Dr. Gay Hendricks is the author and co-author of more than 
twenty books dealing with personal growth, transformation, 
intention, and manifestation.  He defines manifestation as 
'the art of choosing how you want your life to be and 
turning those choices into reality.'   
Through his research and studies, Dr. Hendricks has found 
that there are...(article continues at: )
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 24 Oct 2007 21:52:57 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Aging Well: Vigorous Movement Means Slower Aging By: Dr. Stephen Ruppenthal</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5318</link>
<description>
I would sum up physical well-being in one word: movement. By 
that I mean moving things through the both body and mind, 
rather than letting what we don't want get stuck there. For 
aging happens rapidly when we are stuck, whether in our 
diet, lack of exercise, or rigid habits. Here are four ways 
to cleanse both our body and mind so that we age much slower 
and live life to the full: 1...
(article continues at: )
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 17 Oct 2007 09:35:26 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Seven Steps to Maximizing the Power of Association By: Jill Koenig</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5319</link>
<description> 
There is a saying that one bad apple can spoil the whole 
bunch. And one negative person can affect everyone they come 
into contact with.
I was recently sharing some of my short term business Goals 
with someone in my professional peer network. While I do 
have a tendency to aim high and set some outrageous Goals, I 
also have the drive and determination to take decisive 
action, advance them at a rapid pace and see them through to 
completion. 
When I shared my exciting Goals with my "friend," their 
response was not encouraging and enthusiastic. All I got was 
negativity and discouragement. I knew this friend was having 
some...(article continues at:) 
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 17 Oct 2007 09:42:17 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Full Stomach Equals a Full Mind By: Elizabeth Yarnell</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5324</link>
<description>
It seems as if the school year begins earlier and earlier 
each year. Politicians would have you believe that as long 
as kids are in the classroom, they are learning. In truth, 
there is so much more to learning than simply showing up: 
eating the right foods helps, too. 
Studies have shown that malnourished children have a harder 
time staying focused in the classroom. Many of the foods 
that make up a Standard American Diet -fast food, packaged 
snack foods, and refined grains - are low in nutritional 
value per calorie. They are literally designed simply to...(article continues at: )
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 17 Oct 2007 09:58:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Wonders of Magnesium By: Dr Christiane Northrup</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5323</link>
<description>
Knowing the vast benefits that magnesium confers on our
bodies, I've always wanted to report on this remarkable
mineral . . . and now the time has come!
I was first introduced to the wonders of magnesium during my
obstetrical training where I saw, up close and personal,
how effective magnesium sulfate was in preventing seizures
and restoring normal blood pressure in pregnant women
suffering from toxemia. Years later, I often gave my
patients magnesium intravenously (along with a series of
other vitamins) as part of an IV mix known as Meyer's
formula. I found that this mixture frequently relieved
muscular pain and also promoted speedy healing from surgery,
sprained ankles, and the like. It also appeared to...(article continues at:)
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 10 Oct 2007 15:05:35 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>10 Truths About Losing 10kg Of Body Fat By: Tim Goodwin</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5320</link>
<description>
How many times have you seen adverts in magazines, on the
tv, or on the Internet that promise overnight weight loss
akin to losing a vital limb in weight. A miracle herbal
remedy, the "secret" diet, or a 5 minute a day exercise
routine that offers to shed kilos off your figure. Do you
think if it was really that simple that we would still be in
the grip of a global obesity problem? Despite all these so
called health foods, increased sales of fitness equipment
and revolutionary diets, why are we still gaining weight!
012345678901234567890123456789012345678901234567890123456789
Sadly, the often very suspect science and marketing of
"health" products has just served to confuse many of us.
Even the lesser educated, but well-meaning, health
practitioners have been suckered into the search for the
latest quick fix, selling supplements and pointless exercise
equipment.
What follows is my 10 truths about losing body fat...(article continues at:)
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 10 Oct 2007 15:12:38 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>This Halloween: Know Where Your Chocolate Comes From By: Beth Greer, Super Natural Mom</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5315</link>
<description>
Sure the costumes are cute, and the house decorations
clever, but let's face it, for kids, Halloween is all about
the candy. If you're like me, and your kids bring home way
too many treats, you might want to consider mailing the
chocolate ones back to Nestlé, M and M/Mars and Hershey. Why?
Because, according to media reports, these and other
chocolate makers buy cocoa from plantations that use child
slaves in the harvesting of cocoa beans. The reports have
unveiled stories about boys, as young as 9 years old, who
were tricked or sold into slavery, to work on cocoa
plantations in the Ivory Coast (Cote D'Ivoire) in West
Africa. This small country is the world's major supplier of
cocoa, providing 43% of the world's supply.
The International Labour Organization, part of the United
Nations, estimates that 284,000...
(article continues at:)
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 10 Oct 2007 15:32:45 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Charlie "Tremendous" Jones "Staying Young through Learning" By: Janet Attwood and Gregory Reid</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5308</link>
<description>
GREG REID:  I love that. Now, you can feel just listening to 
this energy on the phone that Charlie truly is tremendous 
and he got the nickname Charlie "Tremendous" Jones. How did 
you get the nickname "Tremendous"? 
CHARLIE JONES:  It embarrasses me. I never liked it because 
people think I am either a football player, a wrestler, or a 
cleanser. I say this. When I didn't know your name, Greg, I 
would call you 'Tremendous' because I didn't want to call 
you 'Hey, you.' You sign all your letters 'Sincerely'--or I 
think you do--and I sign my letters 'Tremendously.' 
I had a habit when people would say, "We had a baby," of 
saying... (article continues at:)
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 3 Oct 2007 13:12:25 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Stalking: A Crime That Should Never Be Taken Lightly By: John Douglas</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5314</link>
<description>
Everybody has heard of stalking. You hear about it on the 
news and read about it in magazines, especially in the 
celebrity and entertainment reports. But hardly anyone could 
rattle off a working definition of it, and not enough of us 
take stalking seriously as a crime we could all become 
victims of. 
The National Center for Victims of Crime operates a Stalking 
Resource Center (SRC), which can be accessed through their 
website at www.ncvc.org/src. They define stalking as "a 
course of conduct directed at a specific person that places 
a reasonable person in fear for her or his safety." To grasp 
the seriousness of this crime, consider that the SRC states 
that 1 in...(article continues at:)
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 3 Oct 2007 10:17:48 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Is This the Proof that Spirits do Exist? By: Klaus Heinemann</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5316</link>
<description>
"There is no doubt in my mind that the orbs may well be one 
of the most significant 'outside of this reality' phenomena 
mankind has ever witnessed." -- Klaus Heinemann, Ph.D.
At first, it seemed no more than a curious coincidence. 
Professor Klaus Heinemann, a researcher for NASA, the U.S. 
space agency, was studying a collection of photographs his 
wife had taken at a gathering of spiritual healers when he 
noticed that many of them featured the same pale but clearly 
defined circle of light, like a miniature moon, hovering 
above some of the subjects.
Like most rational people, he assumed that the pictures 
were...(article continues at: )
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 3 Oct 2007 10:28:15 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Workin' It Out Together By: Jim Sniechowski and Judith Sherven</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5289</link>
<description>
In the early days of love it all seems so bliss filled and 
romantic -- and it feels like it will last forever.  
Then you settle down, get married, create a home, have kids 
and...where did the magic go!?
There's so much to do, the errands never end, the house 
always needs work, the kids are demanding, and your love 
seems to have slipped away.  
Or has it?
You wish you felt more connected. You wish it was more like 
it was in the beginning when you couldn't get enough of 
being together. And perhaps you feel overburdened and 
lonely doing the chores and making a living and taking care 
of the kids and... 
Well, please be kind to yourself, your partner, and your 
relationship and check to see if you both feel the same way. 
Chances are you do. And chances are really good that because 
you've...(article continues at:)
</description>
<pubDate>Fri 26 Sep 2007 10:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Discovering Everyday Gratitude: How to Live a Life Filled With Appreciation and Enjoyment By: Mike Robbins</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5302</link> 
<description>
Have you ever had something taken away from you only to 
realize how much you appreciated it after it was gone? 
I ask this question every time I start one of my speeches 
and seminars on appreciation. As I pause and wait for people 
to respond, many hands go up. 
Most of us have taken someone or something for granted. We 
only truly realized how much that person or situation meant 
to us after the fact. 
For example, at the age of 23, my professional baseball 
career ended abruptly when...(article continues at:) 
</description>
<pubDate>Fri 26 Sep 2007 10:42:25 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bullying Our Kids in Our Homes: Welcome to Cyber-Bullying By: Derek Randel</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5304</link>
<description>
Last night Tom's daughter, Sue, came out of her room and 
said, "I got another one of those instant messages. It says, 
'tomorrow you had better not show up at school or else'." 
She has been getting messages frequently. The result of this 
is that she no longer likes to turn her computer on.
Sue is 14 years old and in the 8th grade. She has been 
bullied at school for a number of years and she has had a 
difficult time getting the Principal and teachers to end it. 
Sue has two disadvantages that make her a target. First, she 
has always had a weight problem, not extremely heavy but 
overweight. Second, her last name is hard to pronounce. 
This has led to numerous ways to say and spell her name. 
Others have been very creative and cruel. Tom is aware that 
she needs to lose weight but what can he do about his last 
name....change it? 
This should come as no surprise to anyone, but as technology 
changes so do the bullies. Bullying has gone wireless...(article continues at:)
</description>
<pubDate>Fri 26 Sep 2007 10:18:15 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>When Nothing Seems to Work--Try the Opposite! By: Steve Hefferon</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5298</link>
<description>
From working with back pain sufferers my entire adult life,
I've learned that when people are suffering, they will go to
great lengths to find relief. Unfortunately, too many people
are given very useful but incomplete information about what
to do in order to get relief and regain control of their
lives.
I also know that people who are suffering can develop
feelings of fear, anger, betrayal, and even hopelessness
when their treatments don't deliver as promised. The trust
they once had with their health care provider starts to
diminish, and they don't know where to turn. Here is an
e-mail I got from a young girl that illustrates my point:...
(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wedn 12 Sep 2007 06:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Pet Astrology - How Lakota Found Me By: Christina Collins</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5295</link>
<description>
Recently, the contaminated pet food scare terrorized my
friends and clients, many requesting transit and timing
consultations for their dear pets. Yes, a horoscope can and
should be elected for animals - especially for observing
health related concerns, also helpful in choosing a new pet
for the family. (A pet that gets along with you, your family
and with your other pets.) Your 6th house from your rising
sign and your 6th house from your Moon is the house of pets
(those that serve you). So you can look at the transits to
your own 6th houses for the current situation for your pet.
Well, I have been happily making my own pet food, cooking
chicken, veggies and basmati rice (plus vitamins) for my 4
canine companions for the last 18 years. I felt such empathy
for those who were worried about their pets, and such relief
that I home cook for mine. . . and then my little rescue dog
number 5 came into my life 2 weeks ago....and
(article continues at</description>
<pubDate>Wed 12 Sep 2007 06:10:57</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>8 Tips to Lose Weight Easily: Just Cut Out Soda and Sugary Drinks Research Shows Those Sweet Beverages Pack on Pounds By: Connie Bennett</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5297</link>
<description>
8 Tips to Lose Weight Easily: Just Cut Out Soda and Sugary
Drinks Research Shows Those Sweet Beverages Pack on Pounds By: Connie Bennett
Soda and other sugar-sweetened drinks are on my mind lately.
Not because I drink them myself, but because just cutting
out the non-nutritive, sugar-filled, potentially harmful
beverages is a highly effective way--if not the most easy
way--to lose weight and improve your health.
That's right. Just making that one simple diet change---
removing chemically created soda and other sugar-sweetened
drinks such as sports drinks and juice drinks--could enable
you to peel off the pounds - possibly to the tune of 15
pounds in one year.
In fact, a recent scientific review published in the
American Journal of Clinical Nutrition pointed out that a
mere 12 ounces of sugar-laced soda a day could...
(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 12 Sep 2007 06:15:27 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Roger Hamilton "Let Go and Get into the Flow" By: Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5288</link>
<description>
Roger Hamilton:  I was in Singapore at the time, and I was
in a position where they had actually flown out a guy who
was coming out because of all the dotcoms that had gone down
and so on. He'd come out to look at our business as well. I
still remember really clearly he said to me at a board
meeting there, he said, "Look, Roger, we could give you some
more money but frankly, I think you're a terrible CEO."
That's what he said.
I was quite blown away by what he said. I remember seeing my
sister that evening at a barbeque, and I just didn't even
want to socialize or anything. My sister looked at me at me
and said, "What's your problem?" I said, "I've just been
told by this guy who's flown all the way from England that
I'm a terrible CEO." My sister said, "What's the problem
with that? You are!" I said, "How can you say that?"
She said, "First of all, you are because you...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Thu 7 Sep 2007 16:27:56 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Back to School Brain Boosters By: Kymythy Schultze</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5293</link>
<description>
When your child's verbal loop switches from "I'm bored,
there's nothing to do" to "I don't wanna go to school!" you
know the time has come to do your parental duty and properly
prepare them for another academic year. You'll buy them
notebooks, backpacks, pencils and books. But, are you also
putting every effort into insuring that their brain is fully
charged? A child with good brain health has the opportunity
to be more successful in their schoolwork, and that
translates to a better school year for both of you. There
are many factors that affect brain health, and in this
article we'll focus on a few things you can do to make a
positive difference in your child's learning and memory
function.
Fortunately, there are...(article continues at</description>
<pubDate>Thu 7 Sep 2007 14:31:15 GMT </pubDate>
</item> 

<item>
<title>Looking Good Could be Hazardous Makeup, Perfume and Moisturizer May Contain Harmful Chemicals By: Beth Greer, Super Natural Mom</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5306</link>
<description>
By the time you walk out the door in the morning, after
slathering, and spritzing yourself with toner, moisturizer,
eye cream, foundation, blush, eye shadow, eyeliner, mascara,
lipstick, gloss and perfume, you may have put enough
chemicals onto your body to be hazardous to your health.
Many of the chemicals in makeup have been linked to cancer,
hormone imbalances and skin irritation.
According to the Environmental Working Group, a nonprofit
environmental research organization, which conducted an
assessment of more than 1,000 cosmetic brands, less than 1
percent are made from ingredients that have...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Thu 7 Sep 2007 14:48:42 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>THE 5 STAGES OF A "SIZZLING" SALESMAN By: Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5275</link>
<description>
When each of us had the privilege of becoming a sales 
professional, we all had our own unique experience. There 
was one common denominator however that we all shared. We 
all had to go through the following 5 stages. As you read 
through them see what stage you are in, ask others what 
stage they think you are in, and become aware if you are 
stuck in a stage that you don't want to be in any longer.
I think awareness is the key to personal and business 
growth. When I discovered that I was...
(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Thu 30 Aug 2007 18:56:35 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 

<item>
<title>Slowly Is Holy By: Scott Kalechstein</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5274</link>
<description>
We're seeing a lot of interest these days in slowing down 
the aging process. We take Human Growth Hormones and state 
of the art vitamins. We take power walks and veggie juices. 
But how many of us take our time? 
There's a new time-release super-food-for-thought supplement 
that I've been chewing on lately: "The more I take my time, 
the more time I have to take." This may boggle the mind for 
a moment, but a quick review of Einstein and physics will 
help it make sense. Time is relative, and how fast or slow I 
experience its passing depends entirely on my state of mind. 
The presence of peace is found in the absence of rushing, 
and my peace of mind clearly depends on my slowing myself 
down.
Do I want peace of mind? Is it a priority? Well, yes, it 
is...but first...(article continues at</description>
<pubDate>Thu 30 Aug 2007 19:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Moving Free with Mirabai By: Mirabai Holland</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5287</link>
<description>
Q: Now that the weather is getting warmer, I have decided to 
take my running workout out of the gym and into the great 
outdoors. I usually run for an hour three to four times a 
week at about 8 minutes a mile. As the weather gets hotter I 
have noticed that I'm having trouble keeping up my pace. Is 
there anything I can do to help me hang in there? 
A: Actually your body is telling you to slow down and you 
need to listen! It takes about 2 weeks to get use to running 
in warmer weather. You need to acclimate slowly to higher 
temperatures. Here are a few pointers to help you do that.
When you exercise in the heat you can... (article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Thu 30 Aug 2007 19:05:15 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 

<item>
<title>Exercising Safely In Heat By: Lynn Bode, CFT</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5279</link>
<description>Summer is officially here. Finally you can pack away your 
jackets and get outside. Summer offers extras hours of 
daylight and with it the opportunity to spend even more time 
enjoying outdoor activities. For many, this means more time 
doing physical activities and playing sports. So, it's 
important to remember the potential dangers that also come 
with exercising in hot conditions. As long as you know the 
dos and don'ts of working out in the heat, then you can 
fully take advantage of all the fun of summer.
What you should do:...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Thu 23 Aug 2007 14:57:26 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Business Fashion for Women Executives: Why Pearl Jewelry Should Be Present at Your Next Sales Presentation
 By: Amanda Raab</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5281</link>
<description>Power Point Presentation... Check. Killer Suit... Check. Great 
Hair... Check. Nails... Check. Pelosi South Sea Strand of 
Pearls... Check! 
No, I'm not kidding! Yes, you are reading it right. 
I added pearl jewelry to the list of things you must have 
for a successful sales presentation if you want to be a 
successful businesswoman executive.  
Here's why...(article continues at</description>
<pubDate>Thu 23 Aug 2007 15:04:57 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>What Next After "An Inconvenient Truth"? By: Karen Fiala ND and George W Fiala B.Com</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5272</link>
<description>Wow. Al Gore certainly impressed people all over the world 
with his ability to show the effects of Global Warming in 
his documentary. Suddenly governments, environmentalists, 
scientist and others are taking notice - big time!
We regular folks are also being affected by this global 
shift in climate and realize this is going to alter our 
world forever - if we don't make some drastic changes - and 
fast! 
The question on everyone's lips is ... "Now that we know that 
our planet - and humanity in general - are in serious 
trouble, what are we going to do about it?"
Being aware of the problem is simply not enough. 
We have to take action!
It's not just ecological and climactic change which is a 
threat to our immediate future. We also face major... (article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Thu 23 Aug 2007 15:09:07 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Block Rocks! By: John Carpenter Dealey</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5285</link> 
<description>Eric Butterworth wrote a book called "In the Flow of Life". 
In it, he said 'As the removal of earth by a farmer digging 
a ditch, opens up a channel for water to flow to his crops, 
so does the removal of obstacles by the student, open up a 
channel of energy to flow into his being.' 
This quote got me thinking. Here in Texas, we call something 
that interrupts the natural flow of things a Block Rock. A 
'Block Rock' can be something that causes disruptions 
anywhere in your life - in your physical world, your 
emotional arena or even in your spiritual realm. 
Recently, I was watching the 1993 classic movie, 'Tombstone' 
about part of marshal Wyatt Earp's life. Many people 
consider this to be one of the five best westerns ever made. 
In this movie, Wyatt arrived in Tombstone and heard the 
story of...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Thu 16 Aug 2007 15:25:37 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item> 
<title>10 Ways to Get Your Marketing Unstuck By: C.J. Hayden</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5283</link>
<description>Have you ever found yourself knowing exactly what you need 
to do about marketing your business... and then not doing 
it? You are not alone. Many self-employed professionals 
find that the hardest part of marketing isn't figuring out 
what to do. What's hard is actually doing it. 
Marketing yourself can be a confronting process. Making 
phone calls to strangers, writing marketing letters, and 
talking about yourself and your accomplishments can bring up 
fear of rejection, harsh commentary from your inner critic, 
feelings of incompetence, and the discomfort of performing 
unfamiliar activities. If you let them, these inner 
saboteurs can stop you dead in your tracks. 
The good news is that you don't have to completely eliminate 
these internal roadblocks in order to move forward in 
marketing. It is possible to feel afraid or uncomfortable 
and still take useful action despite the presence of these 
feelings. Here are ten ways to quickly break through 
internal barriers and get your marketing unstuck...(article continues at</description>
<pubDate>Thu 16 Aug 2007 15:29:01 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Aging Well - Four Ways that Nature can Turn Back the Clock By: Dr. Stephen Ruppenthal</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5278</link>
<description>Aging can be a frightening experience for us all. This came 
home in a message I got recently from a reader, who says 
frankly: "No matter how many miracle products I buy, I feel 
my body is betraying me. It makes me want to give up. Just 
as I am beginning to figure things out, I feel it is so 
unfair that life is slipping away from me."  
These words touched me deeply, for I too, see what formerly 
were lines on my face now turning into creases. But there is 
a miracle that does not come in any package which is all 
around us, ready to give us ample nourishment far greater 
than that which is slipping away. Whether we choose to work 
with it or relax amidst it, nature is infinitely larger than 
ourselves and never grows old. Here are four ways we can 
draw sustenance from nature that will help us feel a 
freedom from our body's relentless clock... (article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Thu 16 Aug 2007 15:37:32 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Eggs: Some Are Not All They're Cracked Up to Be By: Beth Greer, Super Natural Mom</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5286</link>
<description>It's not so simple to buy eggs anymore. Choices abound, from
organic, cage-free, farm-raised, free-range, omega-3,
biodynamic, local, pastured, fertilized, vegetarian, and
natural, to the other end of the spectrum - irradiated. Then
there's shell color: white, brown, speckled, and if you're
lucky enough to find them, blue. What's an omelet-eating,
soufflé-making, frittata-loving, eggs-over-medium person to
choose? According to the USDA, all eggs are... article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Thu 9 Aug 2007 14:25:37 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Career Building Tips: Avoid the Top 5  Career-Killing Mistakes People STILL Make... By: Linda Lopeke</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5284</link>
<description>
Unless you are very wealthy or extremely good at winning
lotteries, you can expect to be working for 40 years of your
life or more. And while not everyone has what it takes to
become a top executive, you do have complete control over
how far you go and how much you earn in your career.You can 
crack the corporate success code! But only if you
stop making career-killing mistakes...
Here are the Top 5 Career-Killing Mistakes People Still Make
and Then Wonder Why They're Not Advancing Their Careers:
Career-Killing Mistake #1...article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Thu 9 Aug 2007 14:38:27 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Speed Networking...and Beyond! By: Ivan Misner</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5273</link>
<description>Speed networking programs are showing up all around the
world. These events tend to be a fun, exciting, and
effective way to make a lot of initial connections in a very
different environment from the standard business networking
meetings. Speed networking programs generally involve people
meeting each other one at a time for a short interval and
then moving on to the next person in line. They are fairly
structured in the way people queue up to meet. For example,
one variation is to have two concentric circles of people.
The individuals sit across from one another and after...(article continues at</description>
<pubDate>Thu 9 Aug 2007 14:32:17 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title> Dr. Joe Vitale "Follow Your Passions, and Everything Else Will Fall into Place" by: Chris Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5268</link>
<description>CHRIS ATTWOOD:  That's so cool. A lot of people tell us, 
Joe, that they just don't know how to make a living 
following their passions. You've made an incredible good 
living following your passions. Would you go back to that 
time when your passions were just hobbies or just somehow 
not your primary source of income? Tell us how you made your 
first dollar following those passions. How did you get 
started earning an income doing what you love? 
JOE VITALE:  That's a big question. I remember Jack Benny, 
who was a famous radio and early TV comedian. When he was in 
his eighties he was on a talk show and somebody asked him, 
and it might have been Johnny Carson, he asked, "Can you 
remember the very first laugh you got as a comedian?" Jack 
Benny was quiet for the longest time. He was known to be 
able to do this deadpan for the longest time. 
He finally came back and said...(article continues at: </description>
<pubDate>Thu 2 Aug 2007 22:18:26 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Is Coffee Really a Health Risk? By: Dr Christiane Northup</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5270</link>
<description>I don't know about you, but I love coffee. And I'm a big fan 
of Starbuck's when I'm traveling. It's a great place to 
meet, chat, and enjoy a good beverage. Coffee and I go way 
back. I started to drink it back in college in the 1970's. 
At the time, my dorm room brew was made from freeze-dried 
Maxwell House. That's what was available. And besides, it 
was cheap. When I was home, I liked to visit my grandmother 
who always made pots of fresh-perked coffee for me and my 
boyfriend. I continued to drink coffee throughout medical 
school. And while doing my ob/gyn residency, which often 
involved staying up all night, I lived on coffee--sometimes
as much as six cups a day.  
I stopped drinking coffee when I decided to get pregnant. 
And interestingly, once I actually was pregnant, I, like so 
many women, couldn't stand the smell of it or the taste. I 
resumed drinking coffee after my children were born, 
however. But by the time I hit age 35, my body decided that 
it was time to...(article continues at</description>
<pubDate>Thu 2 Aug 2007 22:28:48 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
 
<item>
<title>Monday Momentum: The Best Way to Begin Your Week By: Jill Koenig Author, Coach, Motivational Speaker.</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5276</link>
<description>Let me ask you, how did you begin your day today?
And how do you approach your week?
With positive determination and strength, eager to seize the 
day and opportunities before you?  
Or with apprehension, dreading all you have to do? 
I learned very quickly that Mondays are a crucial day.
Some people are going to have a rough week simply because...>article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Thu 2 Aug 2007 22:45:17 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Healing Your Body - Finding Your Deeper Self By: Michele Germain, LCSW</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5258</link>
<description>The body never lies. Its posture, movement, vitality and 
tension are an expression of your personal emotional state. 
Feelings are the life of the body and they will move through 
you like waves of sensations. Therefore, the relationship 
you have with your feelings reflects the relationship you 
have with ...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Fri 27 Jul 2007 21:40:03 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 

<item>
<title>To Bow or To Shake Hands?--Cultural Differences and Networking Etiquette By: Ivan Misner</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5253</link>
<description>We now live in a fully global society where it is imperative 
> to have an awareness of cultural differences as they relate 
> to networking etiquette. We often notice differences within 
> our own states. Certainly between regions of the nation, but 
> what about businesses that are networking with businesses in 
> other parts of the world? We actually cross cultures with 
> every person we meet.  In business, when we concentrate on similarities with each 
> other, the differences aren't that important. Problems arise 
> when...(article continues at</description>
<pubDate>Fri 27 Jul 2007 21:44:58 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item> 
<title>Men Are Human Too By: Jim Sniechowski and Judith Sherven</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5266</link>
<description>To hear many relationship "experts" tell it, men are still 
stuck in primitive, caveman mentality. These experts 
admonish women to be passive and play hard to get. Why? 
Because, in order for a woman to interest them, they claim 
that men need to be on the hunt. If men aren't made to feel 
the need to pursue and capture they won't feel sufficiently 
masculine and driven to conquer and protect the woman who 
excites these primitive urges.  But these experts never say...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Fri 27 Jul 2007 21:52:04 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Make Life Easier to Enjoy Greater Success By: Susan Friedmann</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5262</link>
<description>I can't even tell you the number of times I've talked with 
skilled professionals who can't figure out why their career 
has stalled. "I don't understand," they say. "I'm working so
hard!"
Perhaps the answer is that they're working too hard. It's a 
common problem for generalists: those professionals who 
offer a wide range of services in an effort to meet every 
conceivable need the buying public might have. 
Being a generalist is very demanding. You need to be...(article continues at:</description> 
<pubDate>Wed 18 Jul 2007 22:24:26 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 

<item>
<title>Saving the Soul of a Nation By: Dan Solomon</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5257</link>
<description>Nations have come and gone down through the years. Some 
nations or tribes have stayed in existence for thousands of 
years, while others have become extinct before the year 200. 
So many nations have left a mark in our history. One must 
entertain the thought, is it fate or a pattern that keeps a 
nation from fading away? Out of love, one must be willing to
sacrifice in order to keep the nation vibrant. 
If we can look at a nation as a membership, each member 
plays an important role in determining the...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 18 Jul 2007 22:36:42 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Hurry Up and Wait By: Liz Tahir</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5261</link>
<description>Recently, I walked over to my bank for what I hoped would be
a quick transaction, and felt I was in luck as one of the 
five tellers had only one person in her line, while the 
others all had two or three. So I headed for that teller. 
Big mistake. 
The customer being helped obviously had some sort of 
problem, and the teller moved back and forth taking care of 
it. And of course, I was afraid to change lines, for fear of 
getting in an even slower one. As I have so many times 
before, I wondered why... (article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 18 Jul 2007 22:47:27 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Why Exercise is Important After Baby By: Tracey Mallett</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5259</link>
<description>Post-natal exercise offers a whole range of benefits for new
moms. However, it's important to remember that you should
always consult with your doctor before starting up an
exercise program. What kind of delivery you had will
determine how quick you can resume back to your exercise
plan. It's generally advised that you wait until your 6 week
post-natal check up.
Caution is required before jumping back into an exercise
program, especially with your abdominals. During pregnancy,
your abdominals will separate from the added pressure of the
baby. This is called diastasis recti. It's important that
you minimize the separation, allowing the abs to function
properly, and also before...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 11 Jul 2007 14:23:36 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Magic of Enthusiasm By: John Carpenter Dealey</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5264</link>
<description>Norman Vincent Peale often taught that "There is real magic
in enthusiasm. It spells the difference between mediocrity
and accomplishment. Those who are fired with an enthusiastic
idea and who allow it to take hold and dominate their
thoughts find that new worlds open for them. As long as
enthusiasm holds out, so will new opportunities"
When One Door Closes...
One day, many years ago, Frank Bettger, a young and
ambitious professional baseball player got the biggest shock
of his life. He was fired!
He had thought he was... (article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 11 Jul 2007 14:36:07 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Suppress or Express? By: Dr. Ted Morter, III</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5254</link>
<description>"Big boys/girls don't cry." "Don't hit." "Don't shout."
"Don't be angry." Our society has long advocated emotional
"control." From childhood, we are bombarded with
instructions to sanction outward responses to emotions.
What's a body to do with all of these robust emotions
bottled up all the time? Explode?
More or less. Actually, it's more like "implode" -
"collapse" inward. If the energy of emotions can't be vented
to the outside, it will be released on the inside.
Eventually, the body "implodes" with some sort of release.
It "implodes" in a headache, or back pain, or knee pain, or
stomach pain, or some other kind of pain. Pain is an excess
of energy in one place. It's congested. And that congested
energy can come from suppressed...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 11 Jul 2007 14:44:52 GMT</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
<title>What Did I Do to Deserve and Create This? By: Cody Johnson</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5248</link>
<description>The other day there was a news item in the New York Times 
telling that 20 million Americans have lost their homes 
because of mortgage foreclosures and that many more are to 
be expected. So what do you think these people did to draw 
this into their lives?  
Last year, when our organization presented The Prophets 
Conference series "Just for the Health of It!" the question 
would often come up, "What did I do to create this health 
challenge?" From this, we began to ask why it is that many 
people have spontaneous healings and others don't. Why is 
that cancers...(article continues at:</description> 
<pubDate>Fri 15 Jun 2007 03:24:25 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bust the Old Habits That Ruin Your Diet.  By: Linda Spangle</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5243</link>
<description>"Once I lose this weight, I'll never gain it back!" Sound 
familiar? Unfortunately, these are famous last words for 
many dieters. It takes more than determination and willpower
to make that declaration stick. In fact, when a group of 
dieters were asked what contributed to them re-gaining 
weight, their answers had a common theme. Nearly all of them
said...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Fri 15 Jun 2007 03:27:45 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Juggler's Approach to Wealth.  By: Jim Bunch</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5247</link>
<description>How long do you think you can keep all that debt in the air 
before it crashes down on you?!
As a life coach, I work with thousands of people who want to
put themselves on the path to prosperity in every part of 
their lives. When it comes to helping them get on track 
financially, my first step is to identify their goals, 
assess their current situation and review the strategies 
they've used to create their current reality. One of the 
most common problems I see is what I call "The Juggler." 
The Juggler is someone who has... > (article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Fri 15 Jun 2007 03:32:08 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Rhonda Byrne "Faith is the Greatest Joy in Life"
By: Janet Attwood and Marci Shimoff  Marci Shimoff</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5230</link>
<description>That's great, Rhonda! Earlier you mentioned 
that you had challenges. Challenges came up in doing the 
film. Many people have challenges in going after what's 
right for them. How would you recommend to our listeners 
that they deal with the challenges they face as they apply 
the law of attraction or The Secret in their own lives?
Rhonda Byrne:  One of the first things is to take 
responsibility for your life. If something appears to you as
a challenge, you've got to know that you created it. You may
have created it by default, but you created it. One of the 
things that I think we do as a challenge comes along and we 
look at it as something separate from us, and we go, "Whoa,
whoa, whoa - that person did that", or "How did this 
happen?" 
If you do look at something that appears as a challenge and 
just ask yourself...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Fri 8 Jun 2007 16:20:10 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>You Can Be an Expert at Losing Weight By: Kenneth And Julie Schwarz</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5238</link>
<description>Here's a difficult spot many women find themselves in. Is 
this where you are? 
You're overweight, and you don't like it. It's really making
you unhappy. How in the world did this happen? It's almost 
as though it happened without your permission. It just 
seemed to creep up on you when you weren't looking - you 
know, one or two extra cookies here or there, maybe more 
sometimes. But that isn't nearly enough to pack on all those
pounds. It remains a mystery.
Have you been too sedentary? No, you've actually been 
exercising. You've been taking walks or going to the gym or 
going to yoga classes or using your treadmill. So just where 
did this weight come from?...(article continues at</description>
<pubDate>Fri 8 Jun 2007 16:15:49 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>How Long Will it Take? By: Mike Scogna</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5232</link>
<description>My girls are 3 and 4.5 years old. They are brimming with 
energy and questions about everything: they want to know how
it works. They are fascinated by growth--their own and 
everything around them. One day, the girls decided they 
wanted to plant something and watch it grow. They filled a 
small plastic box with soil, sprinkled grass seeds into the 
dirt, watered it and placed it on a sunny window sill. Then 
they sat and quietly, intently stared at the box for 10 
minutes (shattering all previous records for silent time in 
our home). 
Just as I was getting used to the quiet, I heard excited 
shouts...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Fri 8 Jun 2007 16:20:35 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 

<item>
<title>Aging Well - How Creativity Stops the Years in Their Tracks By: Dr. Stephen Ruppenthal</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5220</link>
<description> There is a vital relationship between creative expression 
and healthy aging. When we draw and paint, certainly we 
delve deep into the springs of vitality, increasing our 
sense of self worth, determination, and achievement. But the
University of Kentucky's Prof. David Snowdon, who tracked 
the health of 678 Catholic nuns over 70 in his important 
Alzheimer's study, showed us much more: he was once given a 
priceless ceramic sculpture of Santa Claus perched atop a 
John Deere tractor by one of the nuns. She was Sister Esther
Boor, who had taken up ceramics at age 97. When asked by 
Prof. Snowdon to join his project, Sister Esther had 
originally told him...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 30 May 2007 14:54:54 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>You Have to be a Real "People Person" to be Good at Networking. . . Right? By: Ivan Misner</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5228</link>
<description>A common assumption is that a "people person" is the best 
type of networker. But this isn't necessarily true. 
Actually, the only people who can't profit from networking 
or referral marketing are those who don't like people at 
all. But these are people who are not likely to be 
entrepreneurs or involved in sales of some kind in the first
place. Most of them will be in careers that allow them to 
work alone in a back room where they don't have to come in 
contact with people. They're not going to be out there 
drumming up business.  Most people who have started their own businesses and who 
depend directly on others buying their products or services
have...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 30 May 2007  15:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Greg Reid "There Are Mentors All around You" By: Chris Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5212</link>
<description>Woodrow Wilson once said, "You are not here merely to make a
living. You are here in order to enable the world to live 
more amply with greater vision, with a finer spirit of hope 
and achievement. You are here to enrich the world and you 
impoverish yourself if you forget the errand."
Greg Reid is a man who is absolutely enriching the world, 
and is poised to enrich millions and millions of people 
around the world, as he's about to release a new film. 
Well-known for his kinetic energy level and his contagious 
enthusiasm for life, Greg is CEO and founder of Work Smart, 
Inc. and the author of The Millionaire Mentor and The 
Millionaire Mentor Corporation.  
  Greg is also a partner in Wish Entertainment, Inc., which is
now producing the soon to be released film, Pass It On. Greg
has...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 30 May 2007 15:09:45 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 

<item>
<title>The Ostrich Approach to Wealth-- Do you have your head in the sand? By: Jim Bunch</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5214</link>
<description>Over the years, I have had the pleasure of working with a
fascinating array of people. While I relish all of the
variations of personalities and circumstances that flavor
each coaching relationship, I've noticed patterns and
personality types when it comes to wealth creation and
management. One of the most obvious dynamics involves those
who seemingly have it all and wear it well, but beneath the
surface are tattered, torn and overwhelmed. We all know
people like this. They see a large cash flow every month.
Behind the façade, though, they are caught up in a vicious
circle. That is, the more money the make, the less they know
how to manage it...the more they hide from the growing
responsibility that comes with prosperity.
I call this the Ostrich Approach: stick your head in the
sand and try to hide from the chaos! There's just one
problem...(article continues at:</description>
<pubdate>Thursday, 24 May 2007 02:24:29 GMT</pubdate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Becoming a "Walking Meditation" By: Dr. Sue Morter</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5213</link>
<description>It is important to realize that meditation is not a practice
that one uses to escape in order to hide from a disruptive
life, nor is it a practice for relaxation alone. It is so
much more and provides the opportunity to experience
ourselves from an entirely different perspective. We are
afforded a way of 'being with' the circumstances in our
lives and 'being with' ourselves in a way that removes the
stresses of seeing life from a dualistic viewpoint. Good or
bad, should be or shouldn't be, right and wrong begin to
disappear. Peace surfaces.
When we meditate, we...(article continues at:</description>
<pubdate>Thursday, 24 May 2007 02:29:15 GMT</pubdate>
</item>

<item>
<title>
The Top Ten Things You Can Do to Improve Your Health and Wellness By: Jackie Hart</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5215</link>
<description>Jackie Hart, founder of HealthWealth Inc. in Austin Texas,
says 'your health is the most important thing you take care
of every day. It doesn't have to be complicated or
confusing, and it shouldn't be.' Here's her list of the top
ten things you can do to get your health and wellness back
on track...(article continues at:</description>
<pubdate>Thursday, 24 May 2007 02:34:35 GMT</pubdate>
</item>

<item>
<title>How Do You Define Success? By: Bobbi DePorter</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5221</link>
<description>Success means different things to different people. Part of
it is conditioning - if our parents thought one way, we did.
How often do we sit back, go inside and think, what is 
success to me? What do I strive for? How do I know when I've
achieved it? 
So think about, how do you define success? What does success
mean to you? 
Traditionally, success may mean achievement of an objective 
or goal. It could mean gaining fame or prosperity. Or it 
might simply mean the opposite of failure. 
There is a different way to define success. Success can 
be...(article continues at:</description>
<pubdate>Wednesday, 16 May 2007 23:59:53 GMT</pubdate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Healthy Habits: Make the Most of Your Child's Day By: Cheryl Tallman And Joan Ahlers</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5225</link>
<description>It's a fact - eating and good eating habits makes you and 
your children brighter and better throughout the day. Here 
are a few tips that will help you and your family make the 
most out of each day: 
Breakfast: Eating a good breakfast can do a lot more for 
your children than you may realize. Studies show that eating 
breakfast both reduces risk of obesity, and boosts school 
performance - both learning and behavior. With the early 
morning havoc of getting ready for work and school, 
breakfast runs the risk of being short changed. Don't let 
this happen, here are few tips for breakfast success: 
A healthy breakfast is just like any other meal; it should 
consist of...(article continues at</description>
<pubdate>Thurdday, 17 May 2007 00:06:53 GMT</pubdate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Overcoming Rejection: 5 Secrets for Turning Failure Into Success in 6 Months Guaranteed By: Richard Fenton</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5227</link>
<description>What if, starting today, the word 'no' didn't stop you 
anymore? 
What if every time you heard the word no, you became 
stronger, more powerful, and more resilient? 
What if the greatest success strategy in the world was not 
to go for yes, but to go for no? 
Well, it is. 
The word 'no' doesn't have to debilitate you. In fact, it 
can empower you to achieve a whole new level of greatness
you never dreamed possible. You might think this is just a 
sales strategy. It is a sales strategy. But, it's a life 
philosophy too. 
Whether we define ourselves as salespeople or not, we are 
all engaged in the sales process. We all must overcome fears
of failure and rejection to be successful and achieve what 
we want. 
Here are My Top 5 Secrets to Help You Turn Failure into 
Success Immediately!...(article continues at:</description>
<pubdate>Thursday, May 17 2007 00:12:14 GMT</pubdate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Kiss of Life By: Scott Kalechstein</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5222</link>
<description>May I laugh all my laughter, may I cry all my tears
May I love the rain as deeply as the sun when it clears
-Scott Kalechstein, An Open Heart
Did you ever have a moment, a single moment that forged such 
an impact that you knew your life would never quite be the 
same? Often such moments involve facing death in some 
manner. Near death experiences can be an effective wake-up 
call that directs us to examine our direction, values and 
priorities. For me, my moment came through a near life 
experience! You see, I received the kiss of life. In 
Brooklyn. In a fast food restaurant. While waiting for the
bathroom. I will explain...(article continues at: </description>
<pubdate>Thurs, 10 May 2007 20:38:39 GMT</pubdate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Astounding Benefits of Soy By: Dr Christiane Northup</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5217</link>
<description>As soy has made its way into Western diets, consumers have 
become interested in the many claimed health benefits. Soy 
products are often marketed specifically to women in part 
because of scientific evidence gathered over fifteen years 
suggesting that soy may be helpful for conditions and 
diseases associated with...(article continues at:</description>
<pubdate>Thurs, 10 May 2007 20:40:15 GMT</pubdate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Sales Letter Copy Secrets By: Yanik Silver</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5224</link> 
<description>Do you remember the stupid beer commercial a few years back 
with the tagline "Why Ask Why?"
Well, completely unknown to the ad agency, they had almost 
stumbled onto a breakthrough marketing concept. Telling 
people the reason why you are doing something is one of the
most powerful influencers of human behavior. 
Robert Cialdini, Ph.D. in his book "Influence: The 
Psychology of Persuasion" talks about an experiment by 
Harvard social psychologist, Ellen Langer, that concluded 
people like to have a reason for what they do. Her 
experiment consisted of people waiting in line to use a 
library copy machine and then having... (article continues at:</description>
<pubdate>Thurs, 10 May 2007 20:50:28 GMT</pubdate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Fail-Safe Holiday Diet Plan By: Kenneth Schwarz, PhD</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5128</link> 
<description>Everyone knows the equation: holidays = pressure + stress. 
Even when you try to reduce the stress, it's still 
stressful. Even when you're not being a host, just a guest,
it's still stressful. 
When you're under stress, you can more easily be captured 
by the most prominent temptations in the environment. When 
it comes to the holidays and someone who struggles with her 
weight, the most prominent temptation is food. 
"I can't help myself," you think. "There's so much good 
food all around. It's just too tempting." All of this is 
real and true. However, it is what is in between the lines,
what you're not saying, what you're not thinking about, that
counts here. What is behind those words, beneath the 
surface? What is really driving your behavior?...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 6 December 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Staying Positive When It Seems Impossible By: Allie Ochs</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5138</link> 
<description>We all know the power of positive thinking. Yet, when the 
going gets tough, staying positive is a challenge. Your 
husband lost his job, your daughter failed her exams and the
car needs a new transmission. That doesn't even cover the 
migraine you had for days or your project deadline. Too 
much at once! You peak at this little book on your desk 
entitled: Pick Yourself Up and Go. Oh No! Not another book 
about...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 6 December 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Stewart Emery 'Balancing Your Passion Portfolio' By: Chris Attwood and Greg Link</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5123</link> 
<description>Stewart Emery: As long as I can remember, Greg, I have been 
fascinated to try and understand why some people seem to 
just do well in life and live successfully. I mean success 
as a total concept, I don't just mean collecting bright, 
shiny objects. I'm talking about being satisfied and happy. 
And why most of the world struggles; I've studied 
philosophy, psychology, and economics at Sydney University 
until the artistic genes kicked in and I went into the 
advertising business. I came over to the United States in...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 6 December 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Gratitude Becomes You By: Judith Sherven, PhD and Jim Sniechowski, PhD</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5114</link> 
<description>Yes, it's that time again, when giant turkeys and homemade
pies threaten to keep us at the table far longer than our
waistlines can endure. But every year endure they must 
because we know how to show our gratitude for a well cooked
meal. We do, we do!
We gobble it up, ask for seconds, and then return for
leftovers before we're finally ready to call it a day.
But what about the rest of your life?...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 November 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Saving for College By: Martin Weil</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5117</link> 
<description>If you're like most parents, saving for your children's
college education is a priority and a big challenge. Tuition 
and related costs at both public and private universities
have been rising at 5% per year or more, far exceeding the
rate of inflation. To put that into perspective, a child
born in 2006 should plan on $110,000 in total expenses for 
four years at the average in-state public college; $300,000
for four years at a private university.
Financing these costs for one or more children is going to
take planning and, most importantly...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 November 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ten Tips for a Peaceful Holiday Season: Helping Kids Relax By: Patti Teel</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5107</link> 
<description>OKids get pretty anxious over the holidays. It's a time of
excitement and wonder, and they often have a hard time
relaxing, staying calm and sleeping well. Here are some tips 
to help your kids stay relaxed and on a healthy sleep schedule.
Don't over schedule your children. Cut back on the tasks and
activities which are likely to overwhelm them. For example,
avoid long trips to the mall with young children; short 
spurts of shopping will be more fun for everyone. Don't try
to change your child's...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 November 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>B.E.S.T. was one of the best By: Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5120</link> 
<description>Oh Boy....Another incredible seminar that I get to turn you
all on to! Last weekend I was invited along with Dr. Barbara
De Angelis to speak at a B.E.S.T. seminar.
All I knew about the seminar was that a good friend of mine,
Dr. Sue Morter, and her family of chiropractors put them on.
Sue had called me a few months earlier and asked if I wanted
to present 'The Passion Test' at one of her seminars.
Knowing Sue as one of my most brilliant friends, I said
'yes!' without a moment's hesitation.
Little did I know what a surprise I was in for!...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 November 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ayurveda Answers Diabetes Epidemic in America By: Pankaj Naram and Smita Naram</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5104</link> 
<description>Diabetes and obesity are walking hand-in-hand in America.
9.3 percent of the population actually has diabetes. All
these people are now in the pipeline of what? Possible
heart disease, circulatory problems, stroke, gangrene and
kidney failure. But there is hope! This is one of our big
specialties in Ayushakti Ayurveda.
--Pankaj Naram
Did you know that according to the latest research, one
third of the adults in this country - that's 73 million
people - have diabetes or its precursor, impaired fasting
glucose?...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 November 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Aging Well Staying Connected Through Service and Community By: Dr. Stephen Ruppenthal</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5111</link> 
<description>Mother Teresa of Calcutta used to say that the world is
hungry for our help and our love. Whether we seek to help
people, animals, or the earth itself, the world's need for
our service has never been greater. And the funny thing is,
the more we help, the more energy we get. That's because
when we make a difference in life, we forget about our own
problems, which are really what make us feel old.
Of course, it fills us with sadness when youth passes away
and we face deeper, very difficult issues of life. This may,
for example, mean coming to grips with spendthrift
tendencies not reconcilable with our earning power; or even
the onset of depression, due to...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 November 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
<title>Crazy Talk or Clear Communication By: Layne and Paul Cutright</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5115</link> 
<description>Kevin apologized to Melissa after he missed an appointment.
It was a simple misunderstanding, so Melissa said she wasn't
really upset, just frustrated and disappointed.
But Kevin sensed there was more to it. Melissa's smile seemed
forced, and he felt there was more she wanted to say, but
Melissa insisted they forget about it and move on. Still,
Kevin had an... article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 November 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>'Mom, Am I Fat?' By: Abigail Natenshon</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5108</link> 
<description>Your child's room is strewn with clothing as she searches
desperately for something to wear that "looks decent." As
the piles become heaps, still nothing looks good enough. She
peers into the mirror and sees only that her physical
appearance does not measure up to the standards she has set
for herself. Her eyes see "fat" everywhere she looks, her
belly, her thighs, her face, her hips. She turns to you and
the dreaded question emerges. "Mom, am I fat?" You look at
your daughter in wonderment. To you, she is the... article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 November 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Chicken Nuggets: The Not So Healthy White Meat By: Beth Greer</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5103</link> 
<description>It finally happened, the thing I had been dreading since she
started to have playdates away from my watchful eye. My
nine-year-old daughter came home from a friend's house and
sheepishly announced that she had eaten MacDonald's chicken
McNuggets."Oh, really," I said, nonchalantly, attempting to hide my
shock and disappointment. Even though I raised my daughter
on organic produce with little or no processed food, I knew
this day would come. She would eventually eat this highly
processed food made of... article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 November 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>High-Income Seller Behaviors By: Bill Caskey</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5087</link> 
<description>Read almost any book about sales and you'll see some
reference to, "you need to have a good attitude." So what
does that mean? Sometimes my most effective selling is when
I have a "bad attitude" - when I'm more discerning and
skeptical about whether a prospect has money or is willing
to make the change. I get tougher then and force the
prospect to fit into my procedure. So, for the purpose of
this article, I'd like to redefine attitude and not talk
about it in terms of good or bad, but instead...
 article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 October 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Healthy Diet By: Elizabeth Yarnell</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5080</link> 
<description>It's time for kids to gear up for school. So what does that
mean for your child's diet? Hopefully not a strict diet of
fast food five days a week as you run to football practices
and dance lessons. The start of the school year can indeed
be a busy time for families, but it is possible to make
healthy meals even with time constraints. It just takes a
little know-how.

According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention
(CDC), "The percentage of children who are overweight has
more than doubled, and among adolescents the rates have more
than tripled since 1980." Being overweight can be associated
with diabetes and other physical and mental health issues
for young people such as...
 article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 October 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Success Through Consciousness By: Scott Martineau and Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5075</link> 
<description>As a Pulitzer Prize nominated author, Frederick Buechner
said, "To find your mission in life is to discover the
intersection between your heart's deep gladness and the
world's deep hunger." This is exactly what our guest tonight
has been doing. Scott Martineau is co-founder and president
of ConsciousOne. With over 600,000 active members,
ConsciousOne is now the largest Internet based personal
growth course provider in the world, offering courses with
such visionary leaders as...
 article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 October 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Diagnosed With a Herniated Disc? By: Dr. Robert Duvall</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5058</link> 
<description>People in America get just too much information moment-to- moment. The result? Short circuits that lead to high stress.
Do we have a solution?  Ayurveda's remarkable ancient secrets have worked for 1000's of years. It's guaranteed!
            -- Pankaj Naram
Four years ago a desperate young man walked inside the door of our Mumbai Ayushakti Ayurved Clinic. Unkempt with dark, furtive eyes, Ashish was not even 20 years old but was so anxious that he could hardly sit still while I saw his pulse. Weak digestion had created so much... 
(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 27 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>How You Can Say Goodbye to Stress By: Dr. Pankaj Naram</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5058</link> 
<description>People in America get just too much information moment-to- moment. The result? Short circuits that lead to high stress.
Do we have a solution?  Ayurveda's remarkable ancient secrets have worked for 1000's of years. It's guaranteed!
            -- Pankaj Naram
Four years ago a desperate young man walked inside the door of our Mumbai Ayushakti Ayurved Clinic. Unkempt with dark, furtive eyes, Ashish was not even 20 years old but was so anxious that he could hardly sit still while I saw his pulse. Weak digestion had created so much... 
(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 27 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Six Ways to Protect Your Latchkey Kids By: Steve Cross</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5069</link> 
<description>As a parent, you don't choose to have your kids at home alone, but sometimes the pressures of two parents working, school schedules, and baby sitting problems conspire to leave your kids home alone.  But there are some very easy things you can do today to reduce the risk for your kids.  
Every parent can do these things.  Here are 6 ways to protect your latchkey kids. 
1) Set some rules.  Sit down and tell the kids what the rules are.  Write them down.  Then post the rules in plain view.  Your kids will be more aware, and that's a good thing.
If you don't want them near the... 
(article continues at: </description>
<pubDate>Wed 27 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Diagnosed With a Herniated Disc? By: Dr. Robert Duvall </title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5066</link> 
<description>What is a herniated disc?
You've probably heard people say they have a "slipped" or "ruptured" disc in the back. Sometimes they complain that their back "went out". What they're most likely describing is a herniated disc. This condition is a common source of back and leg pain. 
Discs are soft cushions found between the vertebrae that make up the spinal column (your backbone). In the middle of the spinal column is the spinal canal, a hollow space that contains the spinal cord. The nerves that supply the arms, leg, and torso come from the spinal cord. The nerves from the neck supply the... 
(article continues at: </description>
<pubDate>Wed 27 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Pregnancy and Lower Back Pain: The Hidden Cause By: Dr. Thomas Sullivan </title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5068</link> 
<description>The decisions of picking a name... The anticipation and
excitement... Painting the new room... Clothing, diapers and
family celebrations. The joy of a pregnancy is one of life's
greatest pleasures. Unfortunately however, for many women
the later months of pregnancy can prove to be quite
challenging. One common problem many women face is lower
back pain.
Lower back pain can be a horrible interruption in day-to-day
activities for a pregnant woman. More importantly, it
interferes with their quality of life, not to mention the
enjoyment of one of the most...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 20 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>In Sickness and In Health: How What You Eat Can Affect Disease By: Elizabeth Yarnell </title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5062</link> 
<description>Chronic disease sufferers typically receive detailed
instructions regarding dosages of medication, but the
conventional medical community is just starting to recognize
the effects of diet on disease. For almost any type of
ailment, choosing to practice a healthy diet can be an
effective tool in any disease management strategy.
Diet, of course, is only one part of an overall healthy
lifestyle that includes exercise, sleep and stress
management. However, thinking logically, if we have plaque
build-up in our arteries that led to a heart attack,
continuing to eat foods that add to that plaque could lead
to another...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 20 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Mandossian 'Choices: When Passions Collide' By: Patrick Coffey and Chris Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5064</link> 
<description>The great Indian sage Patañjali is said to have given this
beautiful insight into the nature of a life that is lived
with purpose. He said, "When you are inspired by some great
purpose, some extraordinary project, all your thoughts break
their bonds.  Your mind transcends limitations, your
consciousness expands in every direction, and you find
yourself in a new, great and wonderful world.  Dormant
forces, faculties and talents become alive and you discover
yourself to be a greater person by far than you ever dreamed
yourself to be."Our guest tonight has followed his passion to create an...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 20 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Nine Ways to Help Children to Cope With Loss and Grief By: Sally Sacks</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5063</link> 
<description>The biggest problem children have in coping with their grief
is the inattention and lack of awareness adults have in the
need to talk about it, express all kinds of feelings around
it, and to help children to find a way to compensate for the
loss.
Often parents are ill equipped to deal with grief in their
children, because they have a hard time dealing with it
themselves. For example, many stoic type families just held
it in, enforcing the need to be strong. If you grew up in a
family like this, you would have no outlet to express your
feelings. It would not be welcome and you would know it, so
you hold your feelings in. These people become...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 13 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Are You Satisfied? By: Jill Koenig</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5071</link> 
<description>Within each of us exists a burning desire to achieve our
full potential. Self-improvement is a discipline, a habit, a
skill that can be learned. I utilize one question that
automatically leads to greater results in every endeavor I
pursue.
This past weekend I celebrated another birthday. Lately I
have been working extended hours on some special projects
so I carved out some time to absorb the majesty of
wilderness, in my favorite place to reflect. I decided to...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 13 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Keys to Survival By: Dan Castro</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5057</link> 
<description>What's the difference between those who survive and prosper
in the midst of adversity and those who are crushed by it?
It's what people focus on, what they believe and what they
expect - in the heat of the moment.  There are seven natural
laws that determine what you focuson, what you believe and
what you expect in any given situation.  They are called
The Seven Laws of Critical Focus?:
1. Our most recent experience influences what we focus on -
whether we like it or not. We have a natural tendency to let
our circumstances and surroundings choose our focus for us.
Here's a simple example...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 13 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Time Management Training By: Denise Landers</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5072</link> 
<description>What lessons you can learn from small children!  One day I
was watching two youngsters, ages 3 and 5, playing with
"bricks" constructed out of heavy cardboard.  The brick
blocks came in three sizes:  a 10" x 16" rectangle, a 10"
square, and the standard 3" x 10" brick size.  Over time
they spent hours creating structures.  At the beginning
there was no understanding of larger pieces providing a
stronger foundation for the smaller pieces and so things
would come tumbling down without using all of the bricks.
With lots of trial and error the children discovered...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 6 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Cool School Lunches By: Cheryl Tallman and Joan Ahlers</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5061</link> 
<description>As you know by now, all parents have a different idea of
what is healthy food and what is not. For years, you have
had the opportunity to hand select and monitor what your
child eats for lunch. Now it is time to test their ability.
It is only natural for your child's eyes to wander and
notice, and be envious of, what the other kids are eating.
Here are a few tips that may help your child's lunch be
healthy, fun and get noticed by the other kids.
The lunchbox: It is important to have the right gear and the
lunchbox is an important asset. Consider letting your child
pick out...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 6 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Art Linkletter 'Attitude: The Key to Success' By: Mark Victor Hansen and Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5056</link> 
<description>Malcolm Forbes hit the nail on the head when he said, "The
biggest mistake people make in life is not making a living
at doing what they most enjoy."
Our guest tonight has made a profession, and in fact, he
has made several professions of doing what he most enjoys.
Art Linkletter is a true legend. He continues to show the
world what is possible. He began his career at KGB Radio in
San Diego more than 70 years ago and went on to host two of
the longest running shows in broadcast history, House Party
and People Are Funny. House Party ran for 25 years on CBS
winning...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 6 September 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Change Your Thoughts and You Change Your World: Teaching Kids the Art of Productive Thinking Sally Sacks</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5048</link> 
<description>Sometimes we think our thoughts are just there, immovable
with no room for change. It is important as parents to teach
your kids that they run their mind, and they can pick and
choose their thoughts. You want to teach kids to choose
thoughts that are productive vs. non productive.
Kids think non productive thoughts all the time and often
believe their thoughts. But their thoughts, just like adults,
can be negative and self defeating and we, as parents, need
to know how to help kids change and manage non productive
thoughts. Thinking stems from learning, and random energy
that can often produce...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 30 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>4 Things Paypal Users Should Know To Improve Their Online Safety B. Hopkins</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5044</link> 
<description>Online ecommerce is growing rapidly, and with that is the
growing opportunity for fraud and scams. As Internet users,
it is our responsibility to take some precautions that will
make our online transactions safer.
One area we need to take responsibility for is protecting
our online payment information. Online payment providers
have come and gone, but one of them, PayPal, has been
around for a while and has become the target of scammers.
While this may be alarming, there are actually some very
simple steps...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 30 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Life Changing Tips For Boomers: Rewire Your Brain To Control Your Emotions, and Make Positive Life Choices By: Karen Sherman</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5047</link> 
<description>Do You Seem to Get Caught Up in the Same Old Reactions?
Have you ever blown up at your spouse only to realize -
after the smoke cleared - that you might have over-reacted
just a tad? Maybe you learn that you haven't been invited to
your uncle's friend's sister's birthday party and you behave
as if it's the slight of the century.
Sometimes even the most minor snafu can send us storming out
of the room, slamming down a phone, or just shutting down
entirely. It's like we just can't...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 30 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Junk Food Juveniles By: Cheryl Tallman and Joan Ahlers</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5042</link> 
<description>Obesity is such a major issue with children that some researchers predict that today's children will be the first
generation of Americans whose life expectancy will actually be shorter than that of their parents.
What can you do to change this?
1. Offer your children fruits and/or vegetables at every
meal. Once in a while, French fries are OK but, they should
not be a daily staple.
2. Do not introduce...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 23 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>High Probability Selling and Telephone Prospecting: Turn Cold Calling into Warm Sales Leads By: Jacques Werth</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5040</link> 
<description>Like most sales lead consultants, I do not advocate cold
calling. However, I acknowledge that cold calling is necessary at times.
You need prospective clients and customers. Cold-calling to
a highly targeted list can be the fastest route to finding
high probability prospects. A High Probability Prospect is one who wants, needs, can
afford, and is ready to buy your product or service now.
Those who only want, need, and can afford- but are not ready
to buy now- are prospects that you will not...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 23 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Seven Steps to Help Reduce Arthritis at Any Age By: Dr. Pankaj Naram</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5054</link> 
<description>What wouldn't you give to right now have that nagging pain in your back, arms, legs and shoulders suddenly just stop
within a few minutes so you felt free to move in any direction -- without pain? 70 Million American Suffer from
Chronic Back Pain. What if we told you that with our 2000-
year old health secrets, you will experience relief from
that constant stiffness when you get up each morning and
throughout the day? Wouldn't it be a new life for you to go
from morning until night without any pain or discomfort?(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 23 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>What You are Marketing is Yourself By: C.J. Hayden</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5045</link> 
<description>"Call us today and change your life," proclaimed the hot pink flyer on the bulletin board. It was signed "Sunrise
Hypnotherapy" with a phone number and a blind email address. No practitioner's name appeared anywhere on the flyer.Posted near it were numerous other leaflets, advertising
everything from life coaching to bookkeeping. Fully two-thirds of the flyers I spotted were similarly anonymous. 
Some displayed a business name; others simply described the service, e.g. "acupuncture." But the names of the people
offering many of these services were...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 17 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Exercising Safely In Heat By: Lynn Bode</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5046</link> 
<description>Summer is officially here. Finally you can pack away your jackets and get outside. Summer offers extras hours of
daylight and with it the opportunity to spend even more time enjoying outdoor activities. For many, this means more time
doing physical activities and playing sports. So, it's important to remember the potential dangers that also come
with exercising in hot conditions. As long as you know the dos and don'ts of working out in the heat, then you can...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 17 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>How to Integrate Your Spirit, Your Business and Your Life By: Christine Kloser</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5051</link> 
<description>Integration seems to be the new buzz-word. Lately I've been hearing many of my customers and clients talk about wanting
their business to blend with their life and their life to blend with their business... and for both to be guided by a 
deep feeling of fulfillment and spiritual connection. Some people will say it's impossible to have an integrated life.
I, like you, may believe it's not only possible, but also how our lives are meant to be. As a multi-business owner and founder of the Network for
Empowering Women Entrepreneurs, it's been a journey for me to learn about...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 17 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Four Pillars of Health By: Tom Goode</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5043</link> 
<description>Optimal health involves nurturing all facets of your life.
This includes your physical, mental, and spiritual health.These components are woven into the fiber of your being and
your well being. Neglecting one causes problems in another.Conditions such as heart disease can trigger depression.
Mental malaise can lead to migraines and ulcers and a lack of spirituality may create despondency and apathy that
affects you on all levels.The good news is that enriching one facet of your life
improves another. There are certain fundamental actions that, when practiced with intent, lead to a better quality
of life: physically, mentally, and spiritually. I call them the four pillars of health.(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 9 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dean Graziosi 'Focus On the Finish Line, Not the Race' By: Chris Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5055</link> 
<description>We're interviewing a man who has used his talents to build a multi-million-dollar fortune. Dean R. Graziosi is the author
of the recently-released book Totally Fulfilled--It's Easier than You Think. He is also the creator and founder of "Motor
Millions" and "Think A Little Different," both of them successful business opportunity infomercials that teach
people how to make money with cars and real estate. Dean's been on TV consistently since 1999. Some of you may
have seen him. He's shipped over a million manuals, tapes and videos to his customers. Beginning at the tender age of
17, Dean built a...(article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 9 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>How to balance your work and your life with EASE By: Andrew McCombe</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5041</link> 
<description>Too often we become caught up in the 'doing' of every day life and we forget that it is meant to be enjoyed.
Establishing a system for ease will help you to put the fun back into your life. The following are six systems will help
you identify and create your ideal career and live your ideal life with a lot more energy and productivity on a daily
basis. (article continues at: )</description>
<pubDate>Wed 9 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Origin of Success By: Freddy Davis</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5050</link> 
<description>I remember when I used to do a lot of scuba diving. I lived in Okinawa at the time and it was a fantastic place to
participate in that sport. The water was clear, there was a lot of beautiful coral and many varieties of tropical fish. On top of that, you didn't even need a boat. There were
numerous places where it was possible to just swim out from the shore a few feet and do a tremendous dive. But in the beginning, it was quite a chore. First I had to
take the diving course to become certified. You could not rent or refill tanks without showing your...(article continues at: </description>
<pubDate>Wed 3 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>10 Questions to Ask Before You Start Day One of Your Diet By: Ken and Julie Schwarz</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5039</link> 
<description>So you've decided to go on a diet. Maybe you've told yourself 'I can do it this time. It just takes willpower.'
What you may not be aware of is that ongoing willpower requires many different things. Willpower is fueled by commitment, belief in yourself, awareness of your problem,
good information, common sense, and hope. These are among the things you need in order to keep up your 'willpower'
and reach your goal. Before you take one bite of your first diet meal on Monday
morning, ask yourself the following essential questions. (article continues at: </description>
<pubDate>Wed 3 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Barbara DeAngelis 'Emotional Courage: The Courage to Live Passionately' By: Chris Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5036</link> 
<description>Harold Whitman described why passion is so important to all of us when he said, 'Don't ask yourself what the world
needs. Ask yourself what makes you come alive, and then go and do that, because what the world needs are people who
have come alive.' We're going to be interviewing someone whom the world
absolutely needs and someone who is... (article continues at:</description>
<pubDate>Wed 3 August 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>'James Ray 'Born into Greatness, Conditioned into Mediocrity' By -  Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5034</link> 
<description>We're interviewing a man who has enjoyed great success in the corporate arena and then followed his passions to the far corners of the globe to learn the wisdom of the most ancient cultures in the world. James Ray spent five years as one of American Telecom and Telegraph top sales managers, four years as a personal and business-growth expert with American Telecom and Telegraph School of Business, and four years working with best-selling author, Stephen Covey. 
He left the corporate world to study the wisdom of the ancients in Peru, the jungles of the Amazon and the deserts of Egypt. Today, he is...
(article continues at...
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 27 July 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Your Landing Strip By: Karl Stadler</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5035</link> 
<description>The traffic had been hectic, parking as per usual was a nightmare and you are almost late, the plane will land in less than 5 minutes as you rush through the front entrance. 
You spot the brightly lit up board with arrival times and soon you are fighting your way through the mass of lingering body's to get close enough to see. You have risked a lot and spent a fortune to get to here.
Eventually you get a good view as the six foot guy in front of you decides to... 
(article continues at...
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 27 July 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Prosperity Can Be Easy and Fun! By: Keith Varnum </title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5031</link> 
<description>When I was nineteen, I read my first self-improvement book. 
Wow, I could make my living doing something I loved to do? 
Amazingly good news? ... Not! 
When I encountered this exciting proposition, I got really depressed. Depressed? The message of these books was supposed to be uplifting and inspiring. I should be rejoicing! Instead I felt discouraged and disheartened. 
Why? Because this optimistic suggestion felt so...
(article continues at...
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 27 July 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>'C'eeing Your Way to Success and Profitability By: J.P Riley</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5025</link> 
<description>Create - Develop action plans (business/marketing and
product/service plans) and explore all opportunities to
improve exposure and increase client base: profits will
follow. Clearly convey the purpose and benefits of your
product(s) and/or services.
Computer - Immediately develop a web presence. You'll have
an unlimited slate to promote your products and services.
Market the site properly and you'll...
(article continues at...
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 19 July 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Father Child Bond By: Ron Huxley </title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5024</link> 
<description>One of the most magical moments of my life was being at the
birth of my child. I wouldn't have missed it for the world.
I remember watching him squirm and cry as he met the world.
I remember how he paused to listen to my voice as I
whispered my love for him and commitment to him. To this
day, spending time with my kids continues to be one of my
favorite activities. To not spend time with my children is
unfathomable.
For many fathers, this isn't the case. They sit in hospital
waiting rooms, clapping each other on the back and
congratulating one another on a job well done, while their
child...
(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 19 July 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Staying Positive When It Seems Impossible By: Allie Ochs</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5032</link> 
<description>We all know the power of positive thinking. Yet, when the
going gets tough, staying positive is a challenge. Your
husband lost his job, your daughter failed her exams and the
car needs a new transmission. That doesn't even cover the
migraine you had for days or your project deadline. Too much
at once! You peak at this little book on your desk entitled:
Pick Yourself Up And Go. Oh No! Not another book about
positive thinking. This author has no idea what you are
going through!
Why do once positive people fall victim to negativity
when ...
(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 19 July 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Immaculée Ilibigiza 'Clean Your Heart and Let Love Be There' By: Wayne Dyer</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5033</link> 
<description>We're interviewing a woman who has endured some of the most
trying conditions imaginable. For more than 90 days,
Immaculée Ilibigiza survived certain death during the
Rwandan genocide in 1994 only by hiding in a bathroom with
seven other women.
Immaculée emerged from a world where atrocities were a daily
occurrence with a new relationship to God and her fellow man.
She is the author of Left To Tell: Discovering God Amidst
the Rwandan Holocaust, which she wrote in the hopes that her
experience will help everyone who faces unbearable challenges
in their life. .
She has devoted her life to sharing the importance of...
(article continues at...
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 5 July 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Stop Worrying By: Peter Cajander</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5029</link> 
<description>Many times it looks like we live for our worries. They
surround us and follow us everywhere we go. There might be a
lot to worry about or just many tiny issues that pile up and
make us uncomfortable. Worries are always subjective and
they also evolve over time. We learn to cope in life and do
not stress about the same things over and over again. Our
subjects of worrying change, but the basic concept remains
intact--we keep constantly stressing about our future and
survival.
We build up expectations and then start to stress about
possible future outcomes. What-if scenarios with different
variations fill our mind and we cannot...
(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 5 July 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Foolproof Plan for Weight Loss By: Kenneth Schwarz</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5012</link> 
<description>Any endeavor as important as losing weight requires that you
have a solid plan in place before you start. You may think
that choosing a diet is enough, but the diet is only one
part of it. You don't need to make a very complex plan, but
you need one that includes techniques for handling the
issues that will come up.
You want the process to go as smoothly as possible. You
don't want to be thrown off guard by roadblocks you didn't
anticipate. You want very much to succeed and making your
own ...
(article continues at:
</description>
<pubDate>Wed 5 July 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Best Leadership Advice: Business Success Secrets from 7 Top Leaders By: Paul Thornton</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5017</link> 
<description>Fortunemagazine once published an article entitled "The Best Advice I Ever Got." It was 
a great article that offered wit and wisdom about achieving business success. I liked it so much, 
that it motivated me to produce my newest book, Leadership--Best Advice I Ever Got, which describes 
the best leadership advice 136 successful CEOs, coaches, consultants, professors, managers, executives, 
presidents, politicians, and religious leaders received that most helped them become effective and 
successful leaders. 
Here are 7 secrets to leadership success...
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 29 May 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Creating Agreements that Work By: Layne and Paul Cutright</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5019</link> 
<description>People yearn for relationships they can trust. They want to be able to depend on people. They want relationships characterized by ease, clarity and harmonious cooperation. 
But, is there any adult who hasn't felt let down or betrayed by someone who didn't live up to his or her agreements? 
What Is an Agreement?
What is an agreement really? An agreement is a method for coordinating action between two or more people. It is supposed to smooth the way for efficient harmonious interaction. But why do people so frequently not live up to their word? Usually an agreement fails because...
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 29 May 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wealth Secrets of Millionaires: Become Wealthy By Not Repaying Your Debt By: Loral Langemeier</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5012 </link> 
<description>Wealth. Does that sound like a foreign word to you? If you're saddled with loads of consumer debt the way so many Americans are, it is probably a very unfamiliar word. 
Commercial and consumer debts are the greatest barriers to wealth. And when you're suffocated by thousands of dollars of debt, it may seem impossible to get out.
There's good news! It's not impossible to eliminate your debt and move toward wealth. Most people and small businesses simply don't have a system for paying off their debt, and as a result they perpetuate bad habits and remain stuck in it. By using the proper debt management system, you can...
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 29 May 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Making Time for Marketing By: C.J. Hayden</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4099 </link> 
<description>
"I don't have time to market." It's a common complaint from
self-employed professionals. When you are the only one who 
can serve the clients, manage the business, and perform all
the sales and marketing functions, time becomes the most
precious commodity you have. How can you find time for
marketing with so many other important priorities? 
There are many time management techniques at your disposal,
of course. You can defer tasks or delegate them, chunk down
projects to smaller steps, and set aside time on your
calendar for making calls, writing letters, or updating 
marketing materials. Perhaps you have...
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 18 May 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>How to Achieve Lifelong Fitness Success By: Joey Atlas</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4095 </link> 
<description>
Every week countless numbers of people rededicate themselves
to starting a new diet and exercise program, only to find 
that they have fallen off their program by the end of the
following week. This scenario plays out all too often
especially for people who are attempting to keep their
fitness program based at home or the office. 

The problem here is not where the program is being
attempted, but the fact that there actually is no program to
follow. No matter what the endeavor, when one sets out to
accomplish something without a well thought out plan or a 
'roadmap', the chances for success are...
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 18 May 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>How to Be Happy and at Peace when Your Whole Life is Turning Upside Down By: Dr. Janette Freeman</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=5000 </link> 
<description>
It seems like we all go through it. You know- those times of
change, when everything that we hung our hats of self-esteem
on- are cast aside. Perhaps it's the loss of a job, spouse, 
friends, health, children, youth and beauty, or some less
dramatic change that causes us to experience our share of
fear and worry. I'm sure there is no one reading this
message that hasn't experienced it more than once, and I 
would venture to guess it may even be going on now for many
of you. After all, this is a time of...</description>
<pubDate>Thu 18 May 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Les Brown - Unique Amongst a Crowd of Many By: Janet Attwood and Stephen Pierce</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4068 </link> 
<description>
Our guest this month is one of the most dynamic and powerful
speakers of our time.
He is Mrs. Mamie Browns baby boy as he tells us in his 
best-selling books Live Your Dreams and It's Not Over Until
You Win! Adopted by Mrs. Mamie Brown when he was six weeks
old, Les grew up to be a three-time State Legislator from
Ohio, host of his own television talk show, and a hugely 
successful speaker, winning over 80 awards for his work.
Those awards include the...</description>
<pubDate>Fri 14 April 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>What Web Are You Weaving? By: Keith Varnum</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4078</link> 
<description>In Native American lore, the spirit medicine of the spider
is to remind us that we are the source of our life 
adventures. The spiders message is that we are the weavers
of our own web of life experiences. We are the creator of
our own reality—the authors of our own karma.
If we want to change the life experiences that we're 
attracting, we need to...</description>
<pubDate>Fri 14 April 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>How to Handle Resentment By: Dr. Stephen Ruppenthal</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4070</link> 
<description>Recently, a friend told me she saw Susan Saint James and her
husband on the Oprah Show. Having lost their 14 year old son
in a plane crash last year, Susan was asked how she got 
through the experience without bitter anger. She said, "I
have found resentment to be futile. It is like taking poison
and hoping the other guy dies."
When I ponder those words, I look at my own teeming
resentments—against friends, colleagues, and indeed against
life—and wonder how I, who have not suffered her terrible
loss, can...</description>
<pubDate>Fri 14 April 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Truth about Teen Blogging By: Barbara McRae</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4062</link> 
<description>Four million teens are blogging! What's a blog you ask? A
blog 0(web +log) is an online journal often hosted free of
charge by such companies as MySpace.com, Live Journal, and
FaceBook.com.
Blogging is quickly becoming the 'teen' pastime of choice.
It has huge appeal because it's fast and easy; if you can
write, you can blog. It's a place that allows free self
expression and it's interactive; young people post their
replies to individual blogs. It's also...
</description>
<pubDate>Thu 23 March 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>'Soft News' Programs By: George McKenzie</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4057</link> 
<description>My grandmother used to say, "You can ask for anything if
youre not afraid to take no for an answer."
Grandmother wasnt talking about asking the media for free
publicity, but she could have been.
Shrinking ad revenues and an ever-growing number of cable
stations have caused massive cuts in news operations
everywhere. And with fewer people doing more work, you can
score some big publicity coups simply by making yourself
available.
This is especially true with...</description>
<pubDate>sat, 18 March 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>'Soft News' Programs By: George McKenzie</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4057</link> 
<description>My grandmother used to say, "You can ask for anything if
youre not afraid to take no for an answer."
Grandmother wasnt talking about asking the media for free
publicity, but she could have been.
Shrinking ad revenues and an ever-growing number of cable
stations have caused massive cuts in news operations
everywhere. And with fewer people doing more work, you can
score some big publicity coups simply by making yourself
available.
This is especially true with...</description>
<pubDate>sat, 18 March 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Change That Event and Be Free By: Dr. Stephen Ruppenthal</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4056</link> 
<description>If you had your life to live over, what decisions from the
past would you like to do over? Would you choose a different
partner or family, or find a new way to handle things better
with that childhood bully who picked on you? Psychologists
tell us that we can often trace our least desirable patterns
of behavior to telling events in the past, where we made up
our minds as a child does, without wisdom or experience.
Such snap decisions often set a mold for unfavorable
behavior patterns like anger or insecurity, that still get
activated today. But if we revisit such decisions and
mentally redo them as we would choose to act now, we can
free ourselves from such patterns and...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 March 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Springtime Planting By: Dr. Janette Freeman</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4055</link> 
<description>As spring has sprung in many places throughout the world, it
is a time to remember the call of spring's new growth.
Farmers and gardeners throughout time have used this time to
plant that which they would like to harvest in the fall.
What would you like to harvest? What fruits would you like
to enjoy?
Through many sources we are told that what we sow, we shall
reap; what goes out from us must return to us; what we think
comes back to us, etc. These timeless truths are repeated
for us in many ways. What seed thoughts will we consciously
plant?....</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 March 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Springtime Planting By: Dr. Janette Freeman</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4037</link> 
<description>Many people think that a happy, loving relationship descends
upon them by conicidence, because they are lucky, or because
they have been blessed by the Gods. Not true! The fact of
the matter is that loving and being loved is intentional. It
doesnt happen to the lucky. It happens to the skilled!
When my partner and I got together, we gradually realized
two basic things: We were soul mates, life partners, twin flames, or...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 March 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Classroom of Relationship By: Scott Kalechstein</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4037</link> 
<description>Many people think that a happy, loving relationship descends
upon them by conicidence, because they are lucky, or because
they have been blessed by the Gods. Not true! The fact of
the matter is that loving and being loved is intentional. It
doesnt happen to the lucky. It happens to the skilled!
When my partner and I got together, we gradually realized
two basic things: We were soul mates, life partners, twin flames, or...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Failsafe Fat Loss By: Dr. Pankaj Naram</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4034</link> 
<description>This art and science of our Siddha Ved lineage is 2000 years
old. Its been handed down through the ages and is a
complete, holistic health system that deals with body, mind,
emotions and soul altogether. It is very reliable and best
of all, there are no side effects with Ayurveda!
Are you a person who each morning looks in the mirror, gasps
and pictures yourself half your size? Imagine someone
handing you a magic key to permanent weight loss. Wouldn't
you treasure such a gift?</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Where is Your Mystical Park Bench By: Paul Bunting</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4042</link> 
<description>Jose often wondered when his life was going to take off.
Throughout schooling Joses teachers has always given him
praise and complements. Jose excelled in sports and was
even rewarded a college scholarship. As you can imagine
Jose developed great expectations throughout this period of
time.
Jose used to daydream of being a successful businessman who
made a lot of money and had a lot of power. He was going to
be...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>India is Calling By: Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4048</link> 
<description>Have you been thinking that India is calling you lately?
Well, here is a chance to take Janet Attwoods Passion Test
in Rishikesh, India, and meet amazing Gurus, do some
incredible yoga, and learn the culture of India as well!
All of the readers of Healthy Wealthy n Wise Magazine are
warmly invited to the International Yoga Festival, hosted
at Parmarth Niketan Ashram, Rishikesh (Himalayas), India
from March 1 - 7, 2006. In cooperation with...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Power of Purpose By: Freddy Davis</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4045 </link> 
<description>Some time ago I read a news report that was, actually, quite
disturbing. It seems that there was a grossly overweight
woman who was so immobile that she, literally, could not get
up from the couch. That couch had been her home for about
six years. She couldnt get up to eat or even go to the
bathroom.
 I can only imagine how disgusting the situation was simply
from the point of sanitation. But...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Movie Mystic  Favorite Films of 2005 By: Stephen Simon</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4032</link> 
<description>My criteria for inclusion in this special yearly double
column is that the films must fit into the definition of
SpiritualCinema that we use for choosing films to
distribute through the Spiritual Cinema Circle: films that
ask who we are and why we are here and films that help us
feel better about human beings. Its that last phrase--
feeling better about being human that made 2005 one of
the ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 
<item>
<title>Forgiveness By: Sonia Devine</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4046</link> 
<description>Your ability to forgive those who have hurt you in the past
is a crucial stepping stone to your spiritual and emotional
growth. Throughout the course of our lives we collect
emotional baggage. This is unavoidable and even though it
can cause us a great deal of pain it helps us to define who
we are as people the result is we grow even more and...
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 
<item>
<title>Living a Life of Integrity and Success By: Raquel Smith</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4038</link> 
<description>Do you want to live a life of integrity? In order to have
integrity you need to know what your values are. Defining
your values will lead you to a path of integrity.Values are
the things that influence how we live our lives.
Unfortunately those values may be what was handed down to
us through family friends society and our environment on a
whole. We go through life in a fog, just...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 
<item>
<title>Cover Article - Mike Love - Unleash the Love By: Chris Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4033</link> 
<description>Our guest is a living legend and a founding member of the
band which has been called "an American musical institution"
The Beach Boys Mike Love has made music history as lead
singer and co-author of many of the bands top hits. The
Beach Boys exquisite harmonies and unique sound have led
writers to call them "Americas first best rock band."</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 
<item>
<title>Stop Your Destructive Inner Voice By: Chris Green</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4029</link> 
<description>Stress. Depression. Anxiety. They're powerful words that
conjure up all kinds of images and prejudices in our minds.
People who suffer from these illnesses find it hard to cope
with life. They can feel deeply unhappy, they can find no
joy in anything life has to offer, and of course, their
levels of self-esteem, confidence and self-respect plummet.
But how can this happen to someone?</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 
<item>
<title>Places to Stay in India By: Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4019</link> 
<description>The Indus Valley Ayurvedic Center, located in Mysore, India,
is in many ways "a little piece of heaven!"
Some time ago I met my South African friend Martin Gluckman
in Nepal, who told me about the incredible Ayurvedic
facility in Mysore his dear friend, Dr. Talavane Krishna had
built."You absolutely have to go stay there, Janet. Its
incredible! The grounds are fantastic, the food is some of
the best in India, the rooms are at least 4 star, the
Ayurvedic healing practiced there comes from the oldest
tradition of Ayurveda. I promise you will be blown away by
the...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item> 
<item>
<title>The Movie Mystic - It Begins! By: Stephen Simon</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4018</link> 
<description>The first day of shooting Conversations with God was filled
with the high spirits of the cast and crew, along with
typical Oregon winter weather. Cold and wet. It was the
introduction of the crews long 14-hour days (a typical day
of shooting usually starts at 6am), regardless of the
weather. Nearing our halfway point of production, it has
been a good reminder of Neale Donald Walschs life story as
he himself lived through those cold nights, doing whatever
he...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2006 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Keeping on When You Want to QuitBy: Freddy Davis</title>
<link>hhttp://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4005 </link> 
<description>I've started a lot of different exercise programs in my
life. Some I started because I wanted to lose weight, some 
because I enjoyed a particular sport, and others because I
just wanted to get into shape.
I have been variously successful. When I joined a team and
had to show up regularly for practice and games, I was able 
to...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Enjoying the Holidays Without Overindulging By: Lynn Bode</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4007  </link> 
<description>For those watching their waistlines, the holiday season can
be a truly stressful time. However, there's some good news 
- most people don't gain as much during that time as they
might think. But, the bad news is that the weight gained
during the festive season turns into an unwanted gift that
can't be returned.
Researchers from the National Institutes of Health and the 
Medical University of South Carolina studied 195 people and
found that...
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The 12 Gifts of Life By: Michael Norwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4006 </link> 
<description>There is a great mystery about the deeper meaning of the well
-known Christmas carol, "The 12 Days of Christmas."
Many believe the 12 Gifts described in the song ( i.e., a
partridge in a pear tree) are just nonsensical lyrics made up
for children.
Others believe these Gifts contain hidden meaning about the
essence of faith.
No one but the long-ago deceased writer of the song will ever 
know.My personal belief is that...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hugging for Health By: Kevin Eikenberry</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4001</link> 
<description>For our business holiday card, I have a tradition of sending
a thought-provoking story or anecdote along with the card.
This year's story was about a woman, her letters to U.S.
Servicemen during the Gulf War, and the simple act of
sending them a photocopy of a yellow paperclip in her hand.
She said the picture represented a hug that she couldn't
deliver across the miles. I included a yellow paper clip
with each copy of this letter.
At Christmas, in our house, there is lots of hugging. I am
not too macho to say that at age thirty-seven the first
thing I want to do...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 7 Dec 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>One Humanity By: Judith Pennington</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4014</link> 
<description>There's a wonderful story about Milarepa, the Tibetan
Buddhist saint who as a young man went out into the world to
experience life and returned home to find his house filled
with demons. He was angry and afraid at first and wanted to
fight them or flee. Instead, he did the unexpected.
First he took a deep breath and bowed. Half of the demons
disappeared. Then he opened his heart and mind, expanded his
field of awareness and...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 7 Dec 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Meet Me for Breakfast onTuesday Morning By: Chris Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=4000</link> 
<description>Jim Rohn is someone whom many consider America's foremost
business philosopher. He's been sharing his success
philosophies and principles for over 40 years, with over
6,000 audiences and over four million people worldwide. Jim
is the recipient of the coveted CPAE Award for Excellence
in Speaking, as well as the 2004 recipient of the Masters of
Influence Award from the National Speakers Association.
He's authored over 25 books, audio and video programs and...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 7 Dec 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Joy is the Juice By: Keith Varnum</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3091</link> 
<description>If you work for money, you are no better than a slave. If 
you do anything you do not enjoy in life, you are no better 
than a slave!”Wow! Strong words from my first spiritual teacher. Michio 
Kushi was my adopted second father, so his pronouncement hit
home. When he first expressed his view, I was upset. When he
repeated his perspective at every opportunity, I got angry.
Angrier and angrier each time he shared.
Anger Reveals the Truth Because my upset was distancing me from my beloved mentor,
I finally ask myself,“Keith, why are you so angry at 
Michio?” Digging deep, I realized he irritated me so much 
because...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 1 Dec 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nine Insights By: Michael Norwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3083</link> 
<description>When my father was slowly progressing through the phases of
a terminal illness, as a final legacy he revealed to me a 
sequence of 9 extraordinary "wealth-building" steps he 
nicknamed, "The 9 Insights of the Wealthy Soul." 
On the surface, his lessons appeared to be about building 
material wealth. On a much deeper level, these insights held the secret
for... </description>
<pubDate>Wed, 1 Dec 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Movie Mystic Overture By: Stephen Simon</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3084</link> 
<description>Opening in theaters everywhere in November and December, 
The Overture is a thrilling and totally engrossing film
about both an artists passion for his music and also his
unrelenting commitment to protect the human need to express
that passion. Think of a Thai combination of the dedication 
of Mr. Hollands Opus mixed in with the passion of Ray and
you get some sense of the pure joy that music brings to its
lead character--and...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 1 Dec 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>What's Your Business Model By: C.J. Hayden</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3095</link> 
<description>If you have enough clients to keep you busy, you must be
making a good living, right? Well, not necessarily. Some of
the busiest professionals around are not earning enough to
pay their bills. On the other hand, there are some
consultants, coaches and other service providers who have
plenty of time on their hands but also earn quite a bit of
money.The difference between the income levels of these two groups
is not just because...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Prosper and Be in Health By: Ann Stewart</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3094 </link> 
<description>That is a Promise - yes, with a capital P. Why? Because it is
in the bible; God said it. In fact, He said it this way:
"Beloved, I wish above all things that you may prosper and
be in health, even as your soul prospers." That can be found
in the third book of John near the back of the bible, which
may account for the reason why it seems to have been hidden
from so many.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Live Outside Yourself and Your Limitations By: Lisa Jimenez, M. Ed.</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3097</link> 
<description>Did you know that NASA, with all of its super computers and
billion dollar budget cannot duplicate the flight pattern of
a dragon fly or a bumble bee? Aerodynamically, neither the
dragon fly nor the bumble bee should be able to fly. Yet,
even today, I have seen dozens of them fly around my back
yard.The dragon fly and the bumble bee deny logic.
When was the last time you denied logic?</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Choose Your Friends Wisely  By: Eva Gregory</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3087</link> 
<description>As individuals concerned about quality of life and the
environment, I am sure that you frequently consider how the
environment affects your well being. Asking questions about
what is being spewed into the air that is breathed, dumped
into the water what is drunk, or absorbed into the food that
is eaten has become commonplace. What about your social
environment?</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ending Procrastination By: Jim Rohn</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3092</link> 
<description>"Perseverance is about as important to achievement as
gasoline is to driving a car. Sure, there will be times when
you feel like you are spinning your wheels, but you will always
get out of the rut with genuine perseverance. Without it,
you won't even be able to start your engine.
The opposite of perseverance is ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cover Article, Byron Katie Reid By: Janet Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3085</link> 
<description>"Judge your neighbor, write it down, ask four questions and
turn it around" is the simple formula Byron Katie has used
to give freedom from suffering, unhappiness, and pain to
hundreds of thousands of people throughout the world. Katie,
as she is generally known, has been hailed as "A spiritual
innovator for the new millennium" by Time magazine and as
someone who "burns away all illusions" by the Times of
London. She is the author of the bestselling books, Loving
What Is and I Need Your Love, Is That True? Her story is
extraordinary and...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Harmonic WealthTBy: James Ray</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3075</link> 
<description>We all know someone who has all their financial ducks in a 
row - a real go-getter with a flourishing business and an 
impressive portfolio - whose personal life is in shambles. 
There's no one to share their success with, or their "life
partner" is someone they don't even know anymore. In one
area of life, this superstar earns rave reviews, yet in
another area, they're hurting bad!
It's possible, and likely, to focus so much on one thing 
that your life becomes...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Qualities of Skillful LeadershipBy: Jim Rohn</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3078</link> 
<description>If you want to be a leader who attracts quality people, the 
key is to become a person of quality yourself. Leadership is
the ability to attract someone to the gifts, skills, and 
opportunities you offer as an owner, as a manger, as a 
parent. I call leadership the great challenge of life.
What's important in leadership is...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Aching for Love: Giving Birth to Soul By: Celia Sue Hecht</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3067</link> 
<description>For years, I took my good health for granted despite Dad's 
heart condition, brother's bronchitis and mother's asthma 
and ulcers. I didn't seem to fit in.
Eventually, at age 19, I became seriously ill with mononu-
cleosis, and had to sleep 12-14 hours a night or else I'd
suffer from...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>7 Secrets to Finding Joy By: Keith Varnum</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3070</link> 
<description>To pursue happiness is an inalienable right. To experience 
happiness is not. No one owes you happiness. No one can
ensure your happiness. Happiness is a choice - your choice.
The key to experiencing happiness is to put joy on your life 
agenda along with completing tasks and goals. Joy is a 
direct result of intention. Your intention determines how
you experience each moment of your day, each aspect of your 
world. As you go through your daily activities, ask
yourself...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Web Technology in Marketing By: C.J. Hayden</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3071</link> 
<description>Every independent professional should have a web site, an
ezine, and an email marketing strategy, right? If you're not
taking maximum advantage of web technology to market your 
professional services, you are behind the times, and missing 
out on huge opportunities. At least that's what most
marketing experts would have you believe. But how valid is 
this advice? And is it for everyone? </description>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>It’s All About Timing By: Christina Collins Hill</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3065 </link> 
<description>If you drop the ball it’s going to fall!  
The trick is to reach out and catch it on the way back up.
Gravity is a law of nature. Earth magnetism and the rising 
and ebbing of the tides - is a law of nature. “It’s not nice
to fool Mother Nature….” but what if you can? Or at least be
“in tune” with nature by beginning action and activities 
when you will enjoy them the most and get the best and most
rewarding results?</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Letting Go of Someone You LoveBy: Wendy Nickerson</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3072</link> 
<description>Dealing with the loss of a relationship is the pain that
most often brings us to our knees. When a relationship ends,
we usually think that the pain is about the relationship
that just ended. What we do not realize is that it is truly
an accumulation of pains from different types of perceived
and...ention to some causes and less to
others, especially...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Diabetes, Find a Cause, Do not Fight the Symptoms By: Adam Newhouse</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3079</link> 
<description>Everything under the sun has its causes. Our lives are
nothing but cycles of never-ending causes reaching out for
yet another and another cause. Viewed from that perspective,
everything is a cause for something else. Nothing is neutral.
We often pay more attention to some causes and less to
others, especially...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Small Talk, Big Love By: Alex Watson</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3079</link> 
<description>As women we talk a lot. Not only do we like to talk to
friends and loved ones, we also spend quite a bit of time
talking to ourselves. The truth is talking to yourself is
not a sign of madness as some would have you believe, but
something we do naturally and constantly. It is this small
self talk that counts because if we do talk to ourselves a
lot, then it is essential to ensure that what we say is...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Masks We Wear By: Jim Sniechowski and Judith Sherven, Ph.D.</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3073</link> 
<description>Halloween - the official holiday of disguise. A time to act
out your fantasy-self, your wildest dream-self. A time to
wear masks and costumes.
But what about the other 364 days of the year? Have you ever
put on an act then? You know, trying to appear a particular
way, hoping  people will believe something special about you,
something that is not real but...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Avoiding Distractions While Working at Home By: Eva Gregory</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3076</link> 
<description>If you have worked from home for more than a few days, you may
have discovered it can be a little (OK, a LOT) distracting.
How do you work from home, do the things you need to do for
your business, and still occasionally find time to slip in
taking a bath? Give this a try...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Formula for Success, Brain Surgery without a Scalpel - John Assaraf By: Chris Attwood</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3064</link> 
<description>Chris: Would you tell us how you discovered the things
you are passionate about? A lot of people say, I know that
passions important, but I don not know how to get there. I
do not know how to figure out what my passions really are.
How did you discover the things you are passionate about?
John: It was not very easy for me. When I was a kid...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>A Dogs Trip to the Chocolate Shop - David Lynch By: Chris Attwood and Robert Roth</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3062</link> 
<description>David Lynch is an acclaimed and widely recognized writer 
director as well as television producer, photographer, 
cartoonist, composer, and graphic artist. More than any 
other arthouse filmmaker of his era, he has enjoyed
considerable mass acceptance and has helped to redefine
commercial tastes, creating a style so...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Top Ten Ways to be Happy By: Lenora Boyle</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3049</link> 
<description>What is happiness, anyway? We all have our own definitions. 
It could be feeling joyful, optimistic, content, or even just
truly relaxed. Some may say that happiness is freedom from
the kind of strain or unhappiness they used to feel. Some 
folks are not even sure happiness is something they have time
for. They may think...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>How to Cope with Back to School Stress By: Debbie Mandel</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3053</link> 
<description>The school year presents an opportunity for a fresh start, 
getting together with old and new friends, new accomplish-
ments and exciting activities - a measure of growth. A new 
vibration can be felt in the air.Instead, in many households anxiety, stress and even sadness
reign. Parents need to..</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Truth About Using Affirmations By Jack Roberts</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3024</link> 
<description>Does the practice of saying affirmations really work?
 We have all been exposed to the philosophy of using affirmations
 as part of our personal growth. But have you ever tried them?
 Most people who have tried using affirmations have done so
 with mixed results. Some people have trouble with affirmations
 because...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Getting Onto the Field by Jaci Rae</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3015 </link>
<description>So you have made it into the Football Stadium of Love and you
 are now stepping onto the playing field for your first day of
 practice with the Dallas Cowboys. Nervous excitement courses
 through your veins as the coach talks about the various
 exercises he is going to run the team through and begins to
 discuss the different plays and strategies he will be using
 during this seasons games.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Building a Successful Team By Jim Rohn</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3020 </link> 
<description>Once you have set a goal for yourself as a leader - whether it
 is to create your own enterprise, energize your organization,
 build a church, excel in sports, etc. the challenge is to
 find good people to help you accomplish that goal. Gathering
 a successful team of people is not only helpful, it is necessary.
 So to guide you in this daunting task of picking the right
 people...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Movie Mystic - Star Wars By Stephen Simon</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3017</link> 
<description>The sixth and final STAR WARS film marks the end of a 30-year
odyssey that has truly been a watershed cultural phenomenon
throughout the world. This final film in the series takes us
full circle and reveals how Annakin Skywalker actually
transformed into Darth Vader and also sets up the entire
underpinning of the original STAR WARS.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>From Disaster to Millionaire By Albert Siebert, PhD</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3016</link> 
<description>Resilient people do not wait for others to rescue them from
business disasters. They work through their feelings, set
goals, work to reach their goals, and often emerge from the
process better than before. The resiliency response may take
a long time...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Love Is In the Air By Judith Pennington</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3025</link> 
<description>What is it that brings about healing and attracts love, joy,
peace and prosperity into our lives? As a journalist, writer
and author, I have studied science and spirituality for decade
 and perhaps like you have formed a seamless belief system
that makes sense of everything.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bill Harris - Focus on What You Want with Chris Attwood and Paul Scheele</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3026</link> 
<description>Paul: It is a pleasure for me to introduce Bill Harris. He is
a person I have known for a number of years. Bill has been
involved in personal development for over 35 years, as a
seeker, teacher, public speaker, author, musician, composer,
therapist, workshop leader and business owner. 
A student of ancient and modern research into the nature of
the mind, Bill has studied and practiced a variety of
traditional and modern transformational techniques and
approaches..</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Exercising Safely in Heat by Lynn Bode</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3021</link> 
<description>Summer is officially here. Finally, you can pack away your
jackets and get outside. Summer offers extras hours of daylight
and with it the opportunity to spend even more time enjoying
outdoor activities. For many, this means more time doing
physical activities and playing sports. So, it is important to
remember the potential dangers...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Elder Care and Elder Rage - If I Only Knew Then What I Know Now! by Jacqueline Marcell</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3013</link> 
<description>For eleven years, I begged my obstinate elderly father to
allow a caregiver to help him with my ailing mother, but after
55 years of loving her, he adamantly insisted on taking care
of her himself. Every caregiver I hired to help him sighed in
exasperation, "Jacqueline, I just can not work with your father -
his temper is impossible to handle. I don not think you will be
able to get him to accept help until he is on his knees himself."</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Waht is Your number1 Excuse? By Dr. Joe Vitale</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=2096</link> 
<description>Before my latest book, The Attractor Factor, became a number1
bestseller at Barnes and Noble online, people told me I was
nuts to try to promote a book when Harry Potter was already
in the top spot."You don not stand a chance," one author wrote. "Why don not you
wait until Potter is off the list?"</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Resilience of Women CEOs By Robin Wolaner</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3010</link> 
<description>What is the best business mistake you ever made? I interviewed
dozens of women CEOs and C-level executives for my book, Naked
in the Boardroom: A CEO Bares Her Secrets So You Can Transform
Your Career, to ask what they learned from mistakes. How can you
recover faster? What insights did you gain as a result of
the mistake?</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bodybuilding Sins Part 3 By Jesse Cannone and Steve Hefferon</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=2091</link> 
<description>Welcome to article number 3 in our series "Bodybuilding Sins
That Cause Back Pain and Missed Workouts". In this article,
we are going to talk about how bodybuilders tend to create
massivemuscle imbalances and what you can do to not be one
of them. If you missed the first articles.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Gartle By Howard Cohn</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=2098</link> 
<description>Many years ago, in a little village deep in the Carpathian
Mountains, there lived a simple Jewish man named Reb Dovid.
Although he was extremely poor and far from a Jewish scholar,
he had strong faith in God and was happy with his lot in life.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pay It Forward By Winn Claybaugh</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3009</link> 
<description>Sometimes you are not nice and, for whatever reason, you cant
go back and apologize to people for having been mean, malicious,
or unkind to them. The main thing to realize is that feeling
guilty will only delay and obstruct the lessons and practices
of becoming a nicer person. It seems and feels better to
recognize...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Everything You May Wish to Know Before Starting a Yoga Class By Gary Halperin</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=2097</link> 
<description>
What is Yoga? Yoga literally means union. Yoga was developed
in India thousands of years ago by people who were exploring
how to feel more "unified" or connected in their lives. They
discovered that by doing various activities, such as prayer,
physical exercise, meditation, serving others, or studying
spiritual teachings...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Healing Codes - By Dr. Alex Loyd</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3011</link> 
<description>In the spring of 2001, Dr. Loyd discovered a simple physical
mechanism that eliminates stress in the body. Since 2001,
thousands of clients all over the world have reported healing
from illness and disease by using The Healing Codes. The
treatment is non-invasive. There is nothing to take. It does
not involve diet or exercise. </description>
<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
  <item>
<title>Marketing in a Virtual World By Steven Van Yoder</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3006</link> 
<description>Before the Internet, small business owners like you were usually
limited to a local market resorting to expensive advertising
and brochures, direct mail, cold-calling, networking at the
local Chamber of Commerce or Rotary. You hoped customers found
you through word-of-mouth or a Yellow Pages ad. 
Today, you can work with a consultant, a financial planner, or a
business coach across the country as easily as someone across town. </description>
<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
  <item>
<title>Clutter Clearing Tips That Work By Stephanie Roberts</title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3003</link> 
<description>Coping with clutter is rarely easy. There is more involved than
just catching up on overdue housework, and staying focused and
motivated over the weeks or months it may take to get the job
done can be one of the biggest challenges. Here are some tips
to help you stick with it until it is done: </description>
<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item> 
<title>FREE live interview with Real Life True Wealth Principles Legend - Raymond Aaron</title>
<link>http://www.1shoppingcart.com/app/adtrack.asp?AdID=117183</link> 
<description>Raymond Aaron, co-author of Chicken Soup for the Canadian Soul, has appeared on virtually every radio and TV program in Canada. He has been sharing his "true wealth principles" for over two decades. Hundreds of people credit Raymond for their becoming millionaires. This year, he will appear on the same venue with Donald Trump, Robert Kiyosaki, Harv Eker, and other leading speakers. Besides all that, he's an incredibly warm, caring person with the greatest integrity.  In this interview, we're going to get Raymond to tell you: 

*How his passions turned into a successful business which has connected him with people like Robert Kiyosaki, Jack Canfield, Mark Victor Hansen, Brian Tracy, and many more 

*The secrets he's learned from many years of interviewing the most successful about how you turn your passions into wealth 

*Why he believes everyone should own their own business 

*The two vital success factors of all entrepreneurial success 

*What it takes to ensure your business success </description>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2005 12:47:44 GMT</pubDate> 
</item>
<item>
    <title> The Movie Mystic - The Upside of Anger By Stephen Simon </title>
    <link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3000</link> 
    <description>The Upside Of Anger jumps off the screen into our
hearts as a powerful whirlwind of emotions with
fascinating, provocative questions about family and
the elusive emotion of anger with which most of us
seem to flirt on a daily basis. (If you commute to
work in a big city, that sentence might better
read "hourly basis.") 
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2005 09:39:21 GMT</pubDate> 
</item>
<item>
    <title> Top 10 Reasons We don't Achieve Prosperity By Sandra Baptist </title>
    <link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3002</link> 
    <description>
If it were easy, everyone would do it; everyone
would have it. That "IT" is prosperity and we're all
trying to achieve that stage in our lives where
wealth, health, success are a daily part of our lives. 
So what's the problem? Why aren't some of us living
a prosperous life?Read on, my friends...
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2005 09:39:21 GMT</pubDate> 
</item> 
<item>
    <title>4 Steps to Creating a Turnkey Business By Stephanie Frank  </title>
    <link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3004</link> 
    <description>
You are a smart, hardworking entrepreneur, and you are
moving fast. You are highly educated in your field
and your business is growing and getting busier each
day. But, somehow, you find yourself stuck. You are
doing more tasks that take you away from your core
business; you are working more and earning less.
You need help.
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2005 09:39:21 GMT</pubDate> 
</item>  
<item>
  <title>Ask The Results Coach - May Session #1 May 17th</title> 
  <link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com </link>
  <description>
Here's some of what we'll cover in Session #1 - Time Management
* How to gain control of your time
* How to prioritize your activities
* How to eliminate unnecessary "energy drains"
* How to take effective action
</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/coaching/pod/050517.mp3" length="10628258" type="audio/mpeg" />  
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2005 09:39:21 GMT</pubDate> 
  </item>
 <item>
  <title>Ask The Results Coach - May Session #2 May 31st</title> 
  <link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com </link> 
  <description>
Here's some of what we'll cover in Session #2 - The Power 
of Focus
* How to eliminate distractions
* How to use The Power of Focus to Double your sales
* How to apply The power of Focus to create optimal Health
* How to FINISH pending projects
</description> 
<enclosure url="http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/coaching/pod/050517.mp3" length="10944512" type="audio/mpeg" />  
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2005 09:39:21 GMT</pubDate> 
  </item>
<item>
 <title> Stephen Simon - The Force is With His Spiritual Cinema By: Chris Attwood </title>
 <link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3005</link>
 <description>Paul: It is my pleasure to be able to introduce Stephen Simon.
He is a veteran producer whose career includes the presidency
of two major production companies and the development and
production of a myriad of well-known films such as: Smokey
and the Bandit, The Goodbye Girl, The Electric Horseman,
Somewhere in Time, the Academy Award winning What Dreams May
Come, and the Emmy-nominated Lifetime television movie
Homeless to Harvard: The Liz Murray Story.
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2005 09:39:21 GMT</pubDate> 
</item>
<item>
<title> Vasant Paranjape - A Saint Speaks Out By Janet Attwood </title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=3007</link> 
<description>
Vasant Paranjape, at 84 years of youth, is an amazing man who
today is the worlds most vocal proponent of the value of
Agni Hotra, or the ancient Vedic fire ceremony, for health
and organic farming. In 2004, my business partner, Chris
Attwood, and I visited Vasants Tapovan, an oasis of organic
farming in northern Maharashtra, about 8 hours north of
Bombay, India...
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2005 09:39:21 GMT</pubDate> 
</item>
<item>
<title>Loving Without Losing Yourself By: Allie Ochs  </title>
<link>http://www.healthywealthynwise.com/article.asp?Article=2092</link> 
<description>
You are in love and it feels wonderful. This love is
different and you are prepared to do anything to make it
last. To prevent this ship from sinking, you work hard to
steer this relationship into a safe harbor. In the process
you lose...
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2005 09:39:21 GMT</pubDate> 
</item>
</channel>
</rss>