<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" media="screen" href="/~d/styles/rss2enclosuresfull.xsl"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" media="screen" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~d/styles/itemcontent.css"?><rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:rawvoice="http://www.rawvoice.com/rawvoiceRssModule/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:feedburner="http://rssnamespace.org/feedburner/ext/1.0" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Budacast</title>
	
	<link>http://www.budacast.com</link>
	<description>Hungary's English-language, online radio show (and podcast)</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 14:41:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.2.1</generator>
<meta name="generator" content="deStyle 0.9.3" />
<!-- podcast_generator="Blubrry PowerPress/2.0.3" -->
	<itunes:summary>Budacast is Hungary’s first weekly English-language online radio show (podcast). The show features produced interviews, feature stories, and commentary in English.&#xD;
&#xD;
The show is about experiences in Budapest and Hungary. It offers tips on living well in the Hungarian capital for expatriates and locals alike.</itunes:summary>
	<itunes:author>Drew Leifheit</itunes:author>
	<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:image href="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/images/logo_blue.png" />
	
	<managingEditor>drew@budacast.hu (Budacast)</managingEditor>
	<itunes:subtitle>Hungary's online radio show</itunes:subtitle>
	<itunes:keywords>Budapest,Hungary,Online,Radio,Show,Arts,Culture,Expatriate,living,guide,Eating,out</itunes:keywords>
	<image>
		<title>Budacast</title>
		<url>http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/plugins/powerpress/rss_default.jpg</url>
		<link>http://www.budacast.com</link>
	</image>
	
		<atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/Budacast" /><feedburner:info uri="budacast" /><atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="hub" href="http://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" /><media:copyright>Copyright 2011</media:copyright><media:thumbnail url="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/images/logo_blue.png" /><media:keywords>Budapest,Hungary,Online,Radio,Show,Arts,Culture,Expatriate,living,guide,Eating,out</media:keywords><media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Society &amp; Culture/Places &amp; Travel</media:category><itunes:owner><itunes:email>drew@budacast.hu</itunes:email><itunes:name>Drew Leifheit</itunes:name></itunes:owner><itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture"><itunes:category text="Places &amp; Travel" /></itunes:category><item>
		<title>Chillin’ &amp; Swillin’ (Budapest Retro Beer Garden)</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Budacast/~3/sb4GORcodX0/</link>
		<comments>http://www.budacast.com/2012/05/31/budapest-outdoor-drinking-venu/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 14:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>drew@budacast.hu (Drew Leifheit)</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Eats & Drinks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hanging Out in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leisure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest’s City Park]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cultural misunderstandings hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer satisfaction budapest handyman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nostalgic bar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[outdoor boozing venues Hungarian capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reliable handyman flat maintenance budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[retro beer garden Pántlika Bisztró]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Városliget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wine spritzer]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.budacast.com/?p=525</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Coming up in this edition of Budacast&#8230; Uncle Drew, his wife Andrea and the rest of the gang sip some spritzers in Budapest’s City Park (Városliget) at a retro beer garden called “Pántlika Bisztró,” one of our favorite outdoor boozing venues in the Hungarian capital. Among the collection of Hungarian nostalgic items at this bar, [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coming up in this edition of <strong><em>Budacast</em></strong>&#8230;</p>
<p>Uncle Drew, his wife Andrea and the rest of the gang sip some spritzers in Budapest’s City Park (Városliget) at a retro beer garden called “<a href="http://www.pantlika.hu/" target="_blank">Pántlika Bisztró</a>,” one of our favorite outdoor boozing venues in the Hungarian capital.</p>
<p><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/hHjhOsz4qok" frameborder="0" width="640" height="360"></iframe></p>
<p>Among the collection of Hungarian nostalgic items at this bar, Drew especially loves the socialist-era, low-slung, vinyl chairs, but the funky, bulbous lamps ain’t too bad either.</p>
<p>A great place to wile away a relaxing summer day, Pántlika is quite popular with people of all ages in Budapest. In the winter, Drew has witnessed a group of old timers basking in the little kocsma’s atmosphere, talking over old times.</p>
<p>What Drew is trying to say in the video is that almost everyone in the group is drinking some kind of spritzer (“fröccs” in Hungarian): rosé wine and soda water for the adults and raspberry (málna) or elderberry (bodza) syrup and soda water for the kids (and for his mother in law…).</p>
<p>Drew introduces Attila, who’s a very important element of his wife Andrea’s team in the work she does for <em><a href="http://helpers.hu/expat-services" target="_blank">Helpers</a></em>. He’s a handyman that can fix almost anything in your flat or house in Budapest, at a nice price and always making sure that the customer is satisfied with his work.</p>
<p>“And he speaks English,” remarks Drew, but Attila tells him not to exaggerate: “Ne tulozz!”</p>
<p>Witness the magnificent stunts of Drew’s mother in law, Kati, as she lifts her lemon wedge out of her mug. Amazing!</p>
<p>Andrea misunderstands something when Drew says, “There’s Attila’s wife and their two beautiful kids.”</p>
<p>Cultural misunderstandings do happen when two people from different cultures make a commitment to each other for the rest of their lives.</p>
<p>Pántlika is located in Városliget near Hermina út.</p>
<p>Stay tuned!</p>
<p>Uncle Drew &amp; Andrea</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Budacast/~4/sb4GORcodX0" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.budacast.com/2012/05/31/budapest-outdoor-drinking-venu/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://www.budacast.com/2012/05/31/budapest-outdoor-drinking-venu/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Summer Hit (Budapest Band Breakthrough)</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Budacast/~3/HbJnpNWNILk/</link>
		<comments>http://www.budacast.com/2012/05/24/budapest-rock-band-ekonomi/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 08:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>drew@budacast.hu (Drew Leifheit)</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Arts & Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Going out in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[best Budapest band ekonomi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bohemian club Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ekonomi new video spring 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Expatriate services hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[favorite hungarian rock bands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[how to succeed in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian nostalgia lake balaton]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungarian rock band]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[live music in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[new club in Budapest puder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nyári slágerek 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[raday utca Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[summer activities on lake balaton]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.budacast.com/?p=513</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It’s a funky summer hit this week on Budacast, Hungary&#8217;s online radio show (and podcast). Hear how one of the professionals from Helpers lives a quadruple life, pushing the envelope to make his rock and roll dreams come true. Stay tuned! We speak to Gergely Mócsai who is the lead singer and rhythm guitarist for [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s a funky summer hit this week on <em><strong>Budacast</strong></em>, Hungary&#8217;s online radio show (and podcast). Hear how one of the professionals from Helpers lives a quadruple life, pushing the envelope to make his rock and roll dreams come true. Stay tuned!</p>
<p><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/YqaxMusjeUk" frameborder="0" width="640" height="360"></iframe></p>
<p>We speak to Gergely Mócsai who is the lead singer and rhythm guitarist for a Budapest band called <a href="http://ekonomimusic.blogspot.com/">Ekonomi</a>, which has just released a video for their song called Diszkóhajó. Gergely explains that “disco boats” on Hungary’s Lake Balaton were a phenomenon from his childhood. (Check out the video!)</p>
<p>“At that time, in the late 70s, there were disco boats circulating on the lake with disco shows on top and hundreds of people having fun during the whole night, going around the lake,” he recalls. “This is an image that gave me the first hint to write the song about this period of music and period of my life. I was only five years old when I first saw a boat like this on the Balaton Lake. And the first time my bandmate and friend, Laci, who’s sitting next to me, hit the first chords of this song, I knew that these were the lyrics I had to give.”</p>
<p>His bandmate László is Ekonomi’s bass player.</p>
<p>In his day job, Gergely Mócsai, incidentally, helps clients start companies at <a href="http://helpers.hu/">Helpers</a>.</p>
<p>“Our aim is to help expats in Hungary to be able to form companies, hire apartments or to register their cars – all sorts of things that you might have already heard about.”</p>
<p>László explains that he was just 15 years old when he met Gergely, who was a university student at the time.</p>
<p>“It was a typical high school band,” he says, “with the slight difference that I am seven years younger than Gergely. I was a bassist in a music school and my best friend was a drummer. My sister dated Gergő’s brother for a period of time and that’s how we met.”</p>
<p>The present lineup of Ekonomi has been together for three years, explains Gergely, after some former band members left Hungary to live abroad.</p>
<p>He says that describing the band’s music is the most difficult question.</p>
<p>“It’s rock music. There must be some Hungarian folk influence in the melodies that we make. I wouldn’t say it’s UK or American based tradition, but maybe a mixture of these two things, plus the Hungarian tradition in alternative music.”</p>
<p>Uncle Drew notes that the band is starting to take things more seriously with the release of their video and completion of some studio recordings.</p>
<p>László says: “This is really meant to be a milestone for our breakthrough – that’s true. But 15 years ago, 10 years ago, five years ago, we’ve always wanted this. The reason we’ve reached this point right now is because of some processes that led us here so that we can say we are mature as musicians, our material is authentic and, I would say, a new thing, and this is the moment we have to show to everybody. This is why we made this video; a highly professional, young artist made this video who is finishing his studies at the university of fine arts.”</p>
<p>Gergely adds, “It’s a constellation of good stars, good feelings and good professionals making things together at one time. We met and this is the right place and the right moment to show it now.”</p>
<p>But how difficult is it to be a successful band in Budapest?</p>
<p>For one, Gergely says that it is easy to find rehearsal space in the Hungarian capital, compared to the rat-filled cellars that he used to play in.</p>
<p>“The audience today went somewhere else. This scene does have a basic and standard audience. If we look at festivals here in the summer, alternative bands are liked, sometimes even loved and crowds go to see them, but there are only 10-12 bands that are really well known. The rest of the audience went for the electronic music. Youngsters from 15-25 have sort of disappeared from the scene compared to 20 years ago. Now you have to be 10-20 times more professional than years ago.</p>
<p>“Too many Eskimos and too few seals. The hardest thing to put together is to have time for this, because there’s no way to live from this. Every bandmate is working somewhere else, so it’s difficult to have the time together and to have a perspective.”</p>
<p>Laci describes what it is like for him to play in a live band.</p>
<p>“Playing in a live band permits you to live your life as you want. You can touch such surfaces when you deal with the expression of your thoughts – they are tangible and touchable and that’s what’s best in pop rock music. That it’s live is the most important thing, even when I’m walking on the street and listening to some music, that’s the light that I’m trying to put into my music. That’s what live music means to me,” he said.</p>
<p>Regarding what bands Laci and Gergely like, Gergely says they have a running joke between them that László doesn’t know half of the music that Gergely does.</p>
<p>“It’s too difficult for me to answer this question,” László says when Drew asks him to name some of his favorite Hungarian bands. “Please listen to what I do, if you ask about what contemporary rock music can mean in Hungary.”</p>
<p>“I would say the same,” says Gergő. “There must be bands that we don’t know that must be cool. There are bands that are well known and there are a couple of really cool songs from them. The most honest thing from me is that I like <a href="http://www.tankcsapda.com/">Tankcsapda</a>’s early music, of course their lyrics, the energy they have. I know this is not that contemporary, not that new or modern, but that’s real rock and roll. I can show that to any American rocker and say ‘that’s cool.’ But I couldn’t really mention other bands.”</p>
<p>To celebrate the release of their video, Ekonomi is holding a special concert at a new, bohemian bar called <a href="http://puderbar.blogspot.com/">Púder Bárszínház és Galéria</a> on Budapest’s popular Ráday utca (which is also where you can find Helpers).</p>
<p>Púder and Helpers are actually located in the same building, says Gergő.</p>
<p>“We saw this place and had the idea that it was the right place. When I was talking about this constellation, I thought this was a sign that we should have a gig here. We are expecting a big amount of people, not only friends but friends of friends. It’s important that the video and the music are persuading people to come and not our personalities.”</p>
<p>He says Ekonomi will play at Púder on 1 June at 8:30.</p>
<p>“This place reminds me of 20 years ago,” Uncle Drew says of Púder, “when people did things with their heart. They basically let a bunch of art students go crazy in here, let them paint and do a wild variety of things, so it’s a very chaotic and interesting place. You could just sit here and look and talk about the different paintings and installations. It’s a place to have a beer, and it’s a museum. That would be how I would describe it.”</p>
<p>Gergő adds: “It’s a kind of message to people today, to have that spirit again, and that’s why I like this place.”</p>
<p>“The prices are really normal, considering this is a really touristy street. The prices are made for locals,” said Drew.</p>
<p>As for the summer, László plans to watch the clouds, while Gergely hopes to work less than last summer, so he has time to spend more time at Lake Balaton.</p>
<p>“Eating some fish, drinking as much beer as I can, having some fun on the beach and watching the Balaton and the clouds.”</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Budacast/~4/HbJnpNWNILk" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.budacast.com/2012/05/24/budapest-rock-band-ekonomi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
<enclosure url="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/budapest_rock_band.mp3" length="43929251" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:keywords>best Budapest band ekonomi,bohemian club Budapest,ekonomi new video spring 2012,Expatriate services hungary,favorite hungarian rock bands,how to succeed in Budapest,hungarian nostalgia lake balaton,Hungarian rock band,live music in Budapest,</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:subtitle>How a rock band in Hungary pulls itself out of rat infested cellars and does its best to make a summer hit</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>It’s a funky summer hit this week on Budacast, Hungary's online radio show (and podcast). Hear how one of the professionals from Helpers lives a quadruple life, pushing the envelope to make his rock and roll dreams come true. Stay tuned!



We speak to Gergely Mócsai who is the lead singer and rhythm guitarist for a Budapest band called Ekonomi, which has just released a video for their song called Diszkóhajó. Gergely explains that “disco boats” on Hungary’s Lake Balaton were a phenomenon from his childhood. (Check out the video!)

“At that time, in the late 70s, there were disco boats circulating on the lake with disco shows on top and hundreds of people having fun during the whole night, going around the lake,” he recalls. “This is an image that gave me the first hint to write the song about this period of music and period of my life. I was only five years old when I first saw a boat like this on the Balaton Lake. And the first time my bandmate and friend, Laci, who’s sitting next to me, hit the first chords of this song, I knew that these were the lyrics I had to give.”

His bandmate László is Ekonomi’s bass player.

In his day job, Gergely Mócsai, incidentally, helps clients start companies at Helpers.

“Our aim is to help expats in Hungary to be able to form companies, hire apartments or to register their cars – all sorts of things that you might have already heard about.”

László explains that he was just 15 years old when he met Gergely, who was a university student at the time.

“It was a typical high school band,” he says, “with the slight difference that I am seven years younger than Gergely. I was a bassist in a music school and my best friend was a drummer. My sister dated Gergő’s brother for a period of time and that’s how we met.”

The present lineup of Ekonomi has been together for three years, explains Gergely, after some former band members left Hungary to live abroad.

He says that describing the band’s music is the most difficult question.

“It’s rock music. There must be some Hungarian folk influence in the melodies that we make. I wouldn’t say it’s UK or American based tradition, but maybe a mixture of these two things, plus the Hungarian tradition in alternative music.”

Uncle Drew notes that the band is starting to take things more seriously with the release of their video and completion of some studio recordings.

László says: “This is really meant to be a milestone for our breakthrough – that’s true. But 15 years ago, 10 years ago, five years ago, we’ve always wanted this. The reason we’ve reached this point right now is because of some processes that led us here so that we can say we are mature as musicians, our material is authentic and, I would say, a new thing, and this is the moment we have to show to everybody. This is why we made this video; a highly professional, young artist made this video who is finishing his studies at the university of fine arts.”

Gergely adds, “It’s a constellation of good stars, good feelings and good professionals making things together at one time. We met and this is the right place and the right moment to show it now.”

But how difficult is it to be a successful band in Budapest?

For one, Gergely says that it is easy to find rehearsal space in the Hungarian capital, compared to the rat-filled cellars that he used to play in.

“The audience today went somewhere else. This scene does have a basic and standard audience. If we look at festivals here in the summer, alternative bands are liked, sometimes even loved and crowds go to see them, but there are only 10-12 bands that are really well known. The rest of the audience went for the electronic music. Youngsters from 15-25 have sort of disappeared from the scene compared to 20 years ago. Now you have to be 10-20 times more professional than years ago.

“Too many Eskimos and too few seals. The hardest thing to put together is to have time for this,</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:author>Budacast</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:duration>26:21</itunes:duration>
	<media:content url="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/budapest_rock_band.mp3" fileSize="43929251" type="audio/mpeg" /><feedburner:origLink>http://www.budacast.com/2012/05/24/budapest-rock-band-ekonomi/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Lazy Sunday Lunch (Margitkert Restaurant)</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Budacast/~3/Z0w4kOs-zJI/</link>
		<comments>http://www.budacast.com/2012/03/07/budapest-traditional-hungarian-restaurant/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 14:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>drew@budacast.hu (Drew Leifheit)</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Budapest Eats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest Surroundings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hanging Out in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungarian Traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leisure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest bem mozi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest english language videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest good service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest good time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest gul baba turbe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest laughing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest margaret bridge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest margit hid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest margitkert restaurant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest old city remnants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest online tv show]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest podcast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest restaurant good waitstaff]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest restaurant review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest show in english]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest sites second district]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budapest turkish occupation siteseeing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian goose liver]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungarian palacsinta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian stews porkolt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian sunday lunch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian traditional meals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary desserts palacsinta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary podcast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary traditional houses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[margitkert etterem budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[olaf palme in budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[willy brandt in budapest]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.budacast.com/?p=505</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In this episode of Budacast, Hungary&#8217;s online media empire, we take a little trip back in time to a traditional Hungarian restaurant in Budapest called &#8220;Margitkert,&#8221; where the food is hearty and the prices are nice. Enjoy the Budapest sites in the 2nd district and Uncle Drew&#8217;s entertaining and cheeky chit chat, because that&#8217;s where [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/Bg2G6nGyXtw" frameborder="0" width="480" height="360"></iframe><br />
In this episode of <em><strong>Budacast</strong></em>, Hungary&#8217;s online media empire, we take a little trip back in time to a traditional Hungarian restaurant in Budapest called &#8220;Margitkert,&#8221; where the food is hearty and the prices are nice. Enjoy the Budapest sites in the 2nd district and Uncle Drew&#8217;s entertaining and cheeky chit chat, because that&#8217;s where it&#8217;s at.</p>
<p>Our pre-lunch launch starts not far from the bridgehead of Budapest&#8217;s Margaret bridge. On a sunny day approaching spring, Drew and Andrea were in search of some comfort food on a Sunday, when the Magyars typically do some lazy Sunday lunching in which they are munching a bunch.</p>
<p>They happened upon an old-school, traditional Hungarian restaurant called <a href="http://www.margitkert.hu" target="_blank">Margitkert</a>, an eatery that has hosted the likes of Olof Palme and Willy Brandt whose photographs you can witness on the walls. Margitkert also has a nice terrace, which hopefully should be open to greet the warmer temperatures in Budapest.</p>
<p>To get there, just take a short walk up Margit utca and you&#8217;ll find the restaurant on your right. If you have some time to kill, be sure to turn right on Mecset utca, where you can find <a href="http://www.museum.hu/museum/index_en.php?ID=27" target="_blank">the tomb of </a><em><a href="http://www.museum.hu/museum/index_en.php?ID=27" target="_blank">Gül Baba</a></em>, a revered Turkish pasha who used to live in Budapest during the occupation. Drew also stops to show a giant key suspended from one of the buildings along the way, likely indicating the former workshop of someone who made keys. It&#8217;s those remnants of the past that Andrea and Drew enjoy so much when they take walks around Budapest&#8217;s various neighborhoods.</p>
<p>Margitkert is located inside what looks like a traditional Hungarian house from the countryside. The first thing Drew notices is that all their dishes are half price on Sunday. &#8220;This place has been here forever, I think,&#8221; he says, &#8220;and I&#8217;ve never even heard of it.&#8221;</p>
<p>Drew, Andrea and their friend Viktor start things off with a &#8220;vadmalac leves,&#8221; a wild boar stew, which is nice and hearty. For mains, Drew enjoyed the goose liver cooked in traditional Hungarian ratatouille (lecso), Andrea had lamb stew with spaetzel (fairly satisfied) and Viko had traditional veal stew, which he says was good. Andrea particularly enjoyed the palacsinta stuffed with walnuts. Drew was not that impressed with the Somloi galuska, a Hungarian sponge cake with chocolate sauce and raisins. They washed everything down with a half liter of rose; Viko had a beer.</p>
<p>Fully watered and fed, their Sunday meal for three cost HUF 13,000 including tip.</p>
<p>For Viko, the most delicious part of the meal was the waitress, who was very open and funny. Andrea and Drew particularly appreciate such genuine service as it is a rarity in Budapest.</p>
<p>The best part of this video is Viko&#8217;s laugh. Be sure to watch until the end!</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Budacast/~4/Z0w4kOs-zJI" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.budacast.com/2012/03/07/budapest-traditional-hungarian-restaurant/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://www.budacast.com/2012/03/07/budapest-traditional-hungarian-restaurant/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Almost Anything (Problem Solving in Hungary)</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Budacast/~3/XBwtlgmLWI4/</link>
		<comments>http://www.budacast.com/2012/03/01/budapest-problem-solving/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 10:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>drew@budacast.hu (Drew Leifheit)</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Leisure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trips in Central Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest best thermal baths]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest expatriate services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest expats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest personal assistant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest problem solving service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest problem-solving approach]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest solving problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eger hotel flora thermal baths]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eger hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eger hungary accommodation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eger hungary great service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eger hungary historic hotel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eger hungary wine tasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eger Turkish bath]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eger Turkish bath cold water]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[how to speak hungarian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian bars kocsma]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian expatriate experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian health treatments thermal baths]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian pastries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian Turkish bath painful experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungarians and friendly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary architecture eger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary best bread]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary best destinations eger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary charming destinations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungary expatriate services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary expats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary fake foods]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary personal assistant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungary problem solving service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary solving problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary thermal baths egerszalok]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary trip to eger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary trips outside Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary Turkish baths eger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary Turkish hamam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary valentines day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jo kenyer bakeries Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[szenator haz eger hungary]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.budacast.com/?p=489</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Coming up in this episode of Budacast, “Almost Anything.” First, we transport you to one of our favorite Hungarian cities, Eger; give you a nasty taste of Hungary’s walnut substitute, and talk about how you can do “almost anything” in Hungary if you know where to find the help. Contact Helpers Hungary. Uncle Drew and [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coming up in this episode of <strong><em>Budacast</em></strong>, “Almost Anything.” First, we transport you to one of our favorite Hungarian cities, Eger; give you a nasty taste of Hungary’s walnut substitute, and talk about how you can do “almost anything” in Hungary if you know where to find the help. Contact <a href="http://helpers.hu/expat-services" target="_blank">Helpers Hungary</a>.</p>
<p><a title="View of Eger from the castle by globalclaire, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lanchutt/2495016539/"><img class="alignleft" src="http://farm4.staticflickr.com/3197/2495016539_64ec5e5cb6_m.jpg" alt="View of Eger from the castle" width="240" height="180" /></a><br />
Uncle Drew and Andrea talk about what they did for Valentine’s Day weekend, when they took a little jaunt to Eger. Andrea had never been there before.</p>
<p>She says, “It’s a beautiful, charming little city with a lot of history. It’s a quiet, almost sleeping town in February – I don’t know about summer time, but I guess it’s a little bit more crowded. I really liked it. It’s a nice town.”</p>
<p>“We happened upon a place called the <a href="http://www.senatorhaz.hu/" target="_blank">Hotel Senator-Ház</a>,” recalls Drew, “which is a lovely hotel right in the main square of Eger.”</p>
<p>Andrea adds that the hotel is located in a 250-year-old house and the management have been able to retain the lovely, old atmosphere. They maintain two houses containing two different classes of rooms: rooms in the older, main building are smaller and not as luxurious as the rooms in a separate building that one can reach by walking a short way through a passage.</p>
<p>“The atmosphere was kind of funky, they had lots of antiquities and lots of junk all over the place,” jokes Drew.</p>
<p>“The restaurant is very quaint. Since my family’s background is in the food service industry, and Andi has her international cruise ship experiences, we really appreciate when you get good service in Hungary.”</p>
<p>Andi pipes in: “We had good service here. It’s a family-run place and the waiters and everyone there – you could feel that they were good team players, and that they’d worked with each other for a long time. It was like a family feeling.”</p>
<p>Drew and Andrea highly recommend the Senator-Ház in Eger.</p>
<p>Drew adds that it’s possibly to do some wine tasting at a little bar just on the right-hand side of the hotel; there’s a wine shop next door, where you can buy wines from Eger.</p>
<p>Andrea and Drew also visited the <a href="http://www.magyarorszag.utazas.hu/A8386557591D1C929C161F0B96A43EFB/Content/EN/807EB95E8436D68255774248DBA2993B/The+Turkish+Bath+of+Eger.html" target="_blank">Turkish baths in Eger</a>.</p>
<p>“It’s a nice building but don’t expect to find really hot thermal water there,” Andrea recalls, “because it felt a little bit cold.”</p>
<p>“We’re big fans of the Lukacs baths here in Budapest; we also like the Szechenyi and the Rudas. Especially in the dead of winter – in February – we were freezing our buns off walking around in downtown Eger, and we were looking forward to getting warmed up.</p>
<p>“The Turkish bath has been really nicely renovated in Eger. Strangely, there was almost no one there.”</p>
<p>Once inside, they discovered why.</p>
<p>“Every pool of water was basically tepid,” Drew reports. “Quite strange.”</p>
<p>They did, however, experience the bath’s “scrub down” service, modeled after the tradition of a Turkish hamam.</p>
<p>Drew comments: “It reminded me more of housecleaning that it did of some kind of pleasurable experience.”</p>
<p>“Basically, you first go to the steam room to soften up your skin,” Andrea explains, “and then there’s a room with a huge marble table that you lie down on. This gentleman comes and gives you a good rub.”</p>
<p>Drew’s not sure he would term him a gentleman.</p>
<p>“For me it was more of a medieval experience. It kind of reminded me of crucifixion. The guy took this rag, which was kind of like a grater and scrubbed the outer layers of my skin – it was especially painful on my calves. I didn’t even want to look. I had my eyes closed and I was wincing the whole time while he was scrubbing my calves and I was convinced that they were bleeding. And then he poured scalding hot water on my calves. So I was glad at the end to get the heck out of there.</p>
<p>“Andi enjoyed it,” he adds.</p>
<p>“I didn’t have that rash that you had afterward, because my skin is thicker than your skin,” she quips.</p>
<p>Drew reports: “I had some abrasions that I saw a couple of days later, that there were a couple of places where I was almost bleeding.</p>
<p>“Eger’s a great town, but the Turkish bath… There was a thermal bath that we should’ve gone to actually. Sounds like it would’ve been a lot better, but when we got there we didn’t have our own towels and they didn’t rent them.”</p>
<p>Andrea says she spoke to the gentleman at the desk of the hotel who suggested going to the thermal baths at <a href="http://www.hunguesthotels.hu/en/hotel/eger/hunguest_hotel_flora/" target="_blank">Hotel Flóra</a>, but for a really nice experience one should drive to <a href="http://www.salirisresort.hu/en/spa_and_water_park" target="_blank">Egerszalók</a>, which is a few kilometers from Eger. Bogacs also has thermal baths.</p>
<p>She sums up, “If you visit Eger, visit it for the architecture, wine and the general small town feeling. If you want to go to the baths, go by car if you can and visit the neighboring thermal baths.”</p>
<p>It’s the different pace of life in Eger, says Drew, which makes it such a relaxing experience, at least in the off season.</p>
<p>“It’s not too far from Budapest. It took us two hours to get there by train. The train station is not far from the city center, so everything is within walking distance. It was just so quiet and so relaxing. You can just pop into a kocsma, have a palinka somewhere – we met a group of people who’d just come back from a wedding – they just started talking to us. And the service is really good and you feel that it’s more sincere, so you feel like people actually care whether you feel good there.”</p>
<p>Then, Drew recalls a scary experience he had with a Hungarian food substance: “dejos,” a walnut substitute used in pastries.</p>
<p>“Smart guy here – ‘yeah, that dude that’s lived in Hungary for almost 20 years, thinks he knows everything in Hungarian?’ – I actually thought that ‘dejós búrkifli’ was supposed to be a clever name in ‘tájszólás’ (dialect), that it actually meant ‘dios,’ but it turns out I was wrong.”</p>
<p>Andrea confirms that it’s a nut substitute. “God knows what it has in it.”</p>
<p>Incidentally, you can buy wonderful, more healthy types of bread – “<a href="http://www.jokenyer.hu/" target="_blank">Jókenyér</a>” – where Drew ingested the scary, fake walnut paste.</p>
<p>Last topic: “Almost Anything…”</p>
<p>“I think I can do anything in Hungary, because I’ve lived here for so long,” says Drew.</p>
<p>Speaking of her work at Helpers Hungary, he says: “We want to talk about how Andrea can help you with almost anything in Hungary, within the confines of the law.</p>
<p>“You told me recently that someone wrote to you, that they needed your help but realized that it wasn’t something that you do – which is totally not true, right?”</p>
<p>Andrea replies: “They said, ‘Andrea, I realize that this is not your field of expertise.’ This is how the letter started and I realized that maybe our clients don’t know that basically everything is our field of expertise, because we are a contact between expats and the locals. So whatever they need, we can find a way to help them get it, solve it – whatever that could be, from very simple things to very delicate personal matters. We basically deal with everything.</p>
<p>“Don’t think about whether it is our field of expertise, just ask us. You never lose if you ask,” she adds.</p>
<p>In terms of her approach to doing something she has not done before, Andrea says: “Nothing is impossible; the sky’s the limit.”</p>
<p>If you think she might be able to help you solve you problem in Hungary, don’t hesitate to contact <a href="http://helpers.hu/about-us" target="_blank">Andrea at Helpers</a>.</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Budacast/~4/XBwtlgmLWI4" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.budacast.com/2012/03/01/budapest-problem-solving/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
<enclosure url="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/budapest_problem_solving_service.mp3" length="24877436" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:keywords>Budapest best thermal baths,Budapest expatriate services,Budapest expats,Budapest personal assistant,Budapest problem solving service,Budapest problem-solving approach,Budapest solving problems,eger hotel flora thermal baths,eger hungary,</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:subtitle>Coming up in this episode of Budacast, “Almost Anything.” First, we transport you to one of our favorite Hungarian cities, Eger; give you a nasty taste of Hungary’s walnut substitute, and talk about how you can do “almost anything” in Hungary if you kn...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Coming up in this episode of Budacast, Hungary’s online radio show, “Almost Anything.” First, we transport you to one of our favorite Hungarian cities, Eger; give you a nasty taste of Hungary’s walnut substitute, and talk about how you can do “almost anything” in Hungary if you know where to find the help. Call Helpers Hungary.</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:author>Uncle Drew</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:duration>15:55</itunes:duration>
	<media:content url="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/budapest_problem_solving_service.mp3" fileSize="24877436" type="audio/mpeg" /><feedburner:origLink>http://www.budacast.com/2012/03/01/budapest-problem-solving/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Hó, hó, hó, Hungarian snow</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Budacast/~3/d0pxABf_T3k/</link>
		<comments>http://www.budacast.com/2012/02/16/hungarian-winter-snowfall-2012/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 13:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>drew@budacast.hu (Drew Leifheit)</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Budapest Sites]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Take It Easy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cogwheel railway budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[public transport budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[snowfall budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[winter 2012 hungary Snow Budapest Train Cold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[winter in budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[winter in hungary]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.budacast.com/?p=482</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In this episode of Budacast, Hungary&#8217;s online media empire, enjoy a peak into the winter wonderland that Budapest has been this winter. Learn the word for &#8220;snow&#8221; in Hungarian. And check out a cool view of the cogwheel railway as it makes its way down the white hills of Buda.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this episode of <strong>Budacast</strong>, Hungary&#8217;s online media empire, enjoy a peak into the winter wonderland that Budapest has been this winter. Learn the word for &#8220;snow&#8221; in Hungarian. And check out a cool view of the cogwheel railway as it makes its way down the white hills of Buda.</p>
<p><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/1Pj5QhNJaK4" frameborder="0" width="640" height="360"></iframe></p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Budacast/~4/d0pxABf_T3k" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.budacast.com/2012/02/16/hungarian-winter-snowfall-2012/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://www.budacast.com/2012/02/16/hungarian-winter-snowfall-2012/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Business as Usual (Changes in Hungary)</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Budacast/~3/sRmDjoqW2Qs/</link>
		<comments>http://www.budacast.com/2012/02/02/hungary-doing-business-2012/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 10:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>drew@budacast.hu (Drew Leifheit)</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Getting settled in Hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Practicalities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vital Information for Hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[accounting advice hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[accounting surprises hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analysis changes in hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[anticipating changes in hungarian business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[big business hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blog for foreigners living in hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business consulting hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business partner search hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business planning hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changes for small business hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changes to company incorporation hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changes to hungarian legislation 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[company formation hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[company formation in hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[company transfer hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doing business in hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[economic turmoil hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[favorable tax rates hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foreign business owners hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[free guide to business changes hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[helpers hungary business set up]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian corporate law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian corporate tax rate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian dividend tax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian inflation 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian legal changes 2012 executive summary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian tax changes 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary business concerns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary business consultancy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary business risks 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary company formation changes 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary corporate legislation changes 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungary English language radio show]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary in the news 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary podcast English]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[legal advice hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[living and working in hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[low corporate tax rate hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[massive legislative changes hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[new rules company formation in hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[one-stop shop company formation hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[owning small business in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[preparing for changes in hungarian business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[project management hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[relocation service hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[small business hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[small business owners hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sme hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[successful business in hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tax changes hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tax liability hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[taxes on employment hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[unexpected expenses hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vague legislation hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vat number hungary]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.budacast.com/?p=460</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Coming up in this episode of Hungary’s online radio show (and podcast)… &#8220;Business as Usual (Changes in Hungary).&#8221; In the second of a series of Budacast episodes, Uncle Drew once again speaks to Barbara Ürögdi of Helpers Hungary who tells us that doing business in Hungary is always about changes, but last year’s wave of [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coming up in this episode of Hungary’s online radio show (and podcast)… &#8220;Business as Usual (Changes in Hungary).&#8221;</p>
<p>In the second of a series of <strong><em>Budacast</em></strong> episodes, Uncle Drew once again speaks to <strong>Barbara Ürögdi</strong> of <a href="http://helpers.hu/" target="_blank">Helpers Hungary</a> who tells us that doing business in Hungary is always about changes, but last year’s wave of new legislation could rock your boat.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-463" style="margin-left: 4px; margin-right: 4px; margin-top: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px; border-width: 3px; border-color: black; border-style: solid;" title="barbara_helpers" src="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/barbara_helpers-214x300.jpg" alt="" width="92" height="130" /></p>
<p>These days in Hungary, one might feel like they’re lost in the woods given all of the legal changes, protests, and economic turmoil. Lately, Drew says it can almost be a bit overwhelming if one pays too much attention to news about Hungary.</p>
<p>Not to worry – Barbara has some more tips for those living and working in Hungary, to help them sift through the facts and fiction. Hopefully she addresses any concerns listeners might have about what’s been going on.</p>
<p>First, she speaks about the kinds of clients that Helpers has to later address some of their specific concerns.</p>
<p>She says the basic idea of Helpers is to provide core services: to provide business consultancy and project management; and relocation – basically for small business owners, foreigners who do work or business in Hungary.</p>
<p>“In this, we are quite unique on the Hungarian market,” she explains, “because the services we provide are only typically available for big businesses, through consulting companies and big relocation companies – things like financial consulting, business planning, market research, partner searches, legal and accounting advice and also practical project management.”</p>
<p>Barbara continues: “I think what’s important is that our core client base is made up of small- and medium-sized businesses that are owned and run by foreigners, and that’s a very niche market because they typically have to rely on consultants and the local experts to make sense of the regulations and to run their businesses, not only compliantly but also successfully. But because of the size of their business, they generally do not have the same concerns as corporations have.</p>
<p>“Big consulting companies and also the media and government communication tends to focus on the interests of big business, so most of the stuff that you will read in the media does not directly concern you if you’re running a small business but finding out what does and doesn’t concern you is tricky business,” she explains.</p>
<p>“Legislation tends to be written in Hungarian and is very very long and basically incomprehensible to anyone,” Ürögdi quips, “so you have to rely on experts. And you get some of your information from the media, but that’s pretty much your only source of information, especially if you’re a foreigner. So what we try to do is provide targeted assistance and information, specifically for small- and medium-sized businesses – that’s why we’re here having this conversation.”</p>
<p>Helpers Hungary has actually reacted in a very targeted way to the tidal wave of changes in Hungary in late 2011 and early 2012.</p>
<p>“Two things kind of coincided over the last few months,” she explains. “One of them was expected: we knew that both corporate legislation and the tax regime are going to change from 2012.”</p>
<p>She says that in terms of legislation, things always change in Hungary, so that was no surprise.</p>
<p>“Taxes change every few months; it’s very difficult to keep track, but not only that – it’s also very difficult to plan ahead, which is essential for business,” says Ürögdi in terms of doing business in Hungary. “So this is something we’ve been preparing for for a while.</p>
<p>“We knew that there was a proposal on the table which would be voted on just before Christmas, for example, which affected, more or less, every piece of law that has to do with owning, running or transferring a company. What we didn’t know is that there would also be a modification, which would be passed on December 30<sup>th</sup>. So then we basically spent the first week of January sifting through those modifications and trying to figure out what actually changed and what didn’t.”</p>
<p>According to Barbara, Helpers also knew that the tax regime was going to change.</p>
<p>“Most of that was public, but until something is actually set down in law, it can always change at the last minute in Hungary. So it’s been a few months of trying to figure out what’s going to happen and trying to prepare our clients for it.</p>
<p>“Interestingly, that has coincided with the whole political and economic turmoil that kind of happened in Hungary over the last few months – we did not plan for that. We also didn’t plan for the inflation that happened. So there’s a lot of stuff that we’ve had to do on the fly and keep in contact with both our partners and advisors to make sure that we are as thoroughly prepared as possible.</p>
<p>She says that at the moment there are two concrete steps that are being taken by Helpers.</p>
<p>“One is that we have prepared <a href="http://helpers.hu/business-services/company-set-up" target="_blank">a document</a>, which is very short – two pages – and it’s literally the most relevant bits and pieces from the new corporate law and the new tax law that are specifically interesting for small businesses.</p>
<p>“Just to give you an idea, the new corporate law is 300 pages and the modifications which were passed are another 300. It’s lots and lots of stuff, so nobody actually reads that. But our lawyer show specializes in assisting small businesses has provided us with 10-12 pieces of information that are directly relevant, so we’ve compiled this all in a document. It’s on our website and accessible to anyone for free, so it’s not just for our clients.”</p>
<p>As a follow up to that, Helpers Hungary has started a blog.</p>
<p>Barbara explains: “We’re going to have about 1-2 entries every week, detailing the new experiences that we have with the new legislation in Hungary, since a lot of it is currently just information but we don’t actually see how it’s going to work in practice.”</p>
<p>She said the blog will also include reflections on the economic and political situation in general.</p>
<p>Ürögdi gave one example of some information in the document compiled by Helpers.</p>
<p>“One of the things that affects our business directly is that the procedure for incorporating companies in Hungary has changed completely and is actually still in the process of changing. One of the services that we provide, which is pretty much at the core of our service offering is setting up companies and launching them – starting them in their operations, for foreigners.</p>
<p>“Until last year this was pretty much the simplest process in all of Europe, and one of the cheapest, because it was basically a ‘one-stop shop’, all filed electronically and basically in a day or two you’d end up with a company with a new VAT number and you’d be ready to go. You can open a bank account and trading the next day.”</p>
<p>She says now a new step has been introduced for registering companies in Hungary.</p>
<p>“The trade registry actually has to request a VAT number from the tax authority before actually registering the company, so technically if the tax authority does not approve of the owners or the CEOs it could reject the application and basically the trade registry would not be allowed to register the company.</p>
<p>“We informed our clients about this last year, because we knew that this was coming; what we didn’t know was how this was going to work out in practice. So far we have found that in the case of foreigners it’s actually quite simple, because what the authority looks for is previous tax liability, and if there isn’t any, for example in the case of a foreigner who’s never done business in Hungary, the issue of the tax number is basically automatic.”</p>
<p>According to her, this is one aspect that might actually disadvantage Hungarian business owners that have a long tax history in Hungary.</p>
<p>Barbara continues, “In the document we do outline the procedure, but we also include reflections on how this is going to affect clients’ businesses. In this case, for example, it might end up just being a formality for them – something that they should be aware of, because there is a hypothetical possibility that it could hinder the registration, but in the end it seems that in practical terms it’s not going to hurt them.</p>
<p>“So we’ve tried to keep it sort of practical, rather than translating the law we try to publish our experiences and kind of warn clients about realistic pitfalls and not burden them with too much legislation.</p>
<p>She points out that the Hungarian business environment gets a bad rap.</p>
<p>“It’s true that in some things it’s quite harsh. Most of the time that has to do with employment: taxes on employment including income taxes, social security, pension payments and all those are quite high. That is true, although I have to say that there are places where it’s higher and where it’s lower, but our corporate tax is one of the lowest – it’s on the same level as Cyprus, at 10%. Cyprus is well known as a tax haven. Hungarian dividend tax is at 16% which is also not so horrible.</p>
<p>“There are a lot of items in our tax system which are favorable and some which are not, but that’s kind of how it is to do business, you kind of make your way through the good and the bad.”</p>
<p>Of the Helpers document, she concludes: “In the end we kind of try to keep it realistic and focus on stuff that can actually help our clients get started and focus on their business rather than spending a lot of time working on legislation and worrying about tax laws.”</p>
<p>She says if one is well prepared and well informed, it’s possible to do good business in Hungary.</p>
<p>“I think a lot of the time people run into walls, because they don’t know what to expect in advance, and then they are shocked and surprised when their accountant tells them that they have to pay this or that thing, but technically that is something that you can plan for. And if you plan for it, if you have a solid business plan and financial plan, then you won’t have those kind of surprises.”</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Budacast/~4/sRmDjoqW2Qs" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.budacast.com/2012/02/02/hungary-doing-business-2012/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
<enclosure url="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/hungary_business_challenges.mp3" length="20886654" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:keywords>Hungary English language radio show,hungary podcast English,doing business in hungary,hungary business risks 2012,changes to hungarian legislation 2012,massive legislative changes hungary,economic turmoil hungary,hungary in the news 2012,</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:subtitle>Coming up in this episode of Hungary’s online radio show (and podcast)… "Business as Usual (Changes in Hungary)." - In the second of a series of Budacast episodes, Uncle Drew once again speaks to Barbara Ürögdi of Helpers Hungary who tells us that doi...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Coming up in this episode of Hungary’s online radio show (and podcast)… Business as Usual (in Hungary).
In the second of a series of Budacast episodes, Uncle Drew once again speaks to Barbara Urogdi of Helpers Hungary who tells us that doing business in Hungary is always about changes, but last year’s wave of new legislation could rock your boat.</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:author>Uncle Drew</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:duration>13:30</itunes:duration>
	<media:content url="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/hungary_business_challenges.mp3" fileSize="20886654" type="audio/mpeg" /><feedburner:origLink>http://www.budacast.com/2012/02/02/hungary-doing-business-2012/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Alterations and Modifications (in Hungary)</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Budacast/~3/gG-B5S9soVo/</link>
		<comments>http://www.budacast.com/2012/01/23/hungary-legal-changes-2012-implications/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 09:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>drew@budacast.hu (Drew Leifheit)</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Foreign Affairs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Practicalities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vital Information for Hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advice living in hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bank deposit security hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Barbara urogdi helpers hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budacast podcast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burning eu flag hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business opportunities hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business risk hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business services hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chance of hungary leaving the eu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chances of hungary getting kicked out of eu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changes for business 2012 hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[changes for business hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[company set up hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[currency devaluation hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doing business in hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[economic changes hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[economic risk hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eu referendum hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[expat advice 2012 hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Expatriate services hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foreigner residence permit hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[helpers expatriate services hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[helpers hungay international clients]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[highest vat rate hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian economy panic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian laws 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian parliament fidesz dictatorship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian residency and hungary kicked out of eu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary advantageous exchange rate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary chaotic political situation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary currency decline exports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary dollar exchange rate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary EU status]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungary expatriate services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary hard currency earnings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary increase vat rate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary international reputation 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary kicked out of EU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary legal modifications and silver lining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary low real estate prices 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary Schengen country eu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary sensationalist media coverage 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungary viktor orban political situtation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[imf loan hungary January 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[international criticism hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[international press coverage hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[legal changes hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[living in hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[low real estate prices hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mortgages in hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[new hungarian constitution 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[numerous legal changes hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online radio show hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[political situation hungary facts versus fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[questions concerns hungary 2012]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[residence permit hungary traveling freely in Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stronger euro hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tips living in hungary]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.budacast.com/?p=450</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In this episode of Budacast, Alterations and Modifications… We talk to entrepreneur Barbara Ürögdi of Helpers Hungary about what Hungary’s tidal wave of legal changes in 2012 means for expatriates, their businesses and life in Hungary. If you’re even the slightest bit interested in what’s going on in Hungary, you’ve no doubt heard about all of [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this episode of Budacast, Alterations and Modifications… We talk to entrepreneur Barbara Ürögdi of <a href="http://helpers.hu/" target="_blank">Helpers Hungary</a> about what Hungary’s tidal wave of legal changes in 2012 means for expatriates, their businesses and life in Hungary.</p>
<p><a title="Hungarian Parliament Building by Mr. Vincent Freeman, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/vinszent/4316134251/"><img class="alignleft" style="border-width: 2px; border-color: black; border-style: solid;" src="http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2738/4316134251_fd9374893d_m.jpg" alt="Hungarian Parliament Building" width="240" height="160" /></a>If you’re even the slightest bit interested in what’s going on in Hungary, you’ve no doubt heard about all of the legal changes being enacted by the Hungarian Parliament and the subsequent international criticism.</p>
<p>Without getting into the politics, Budacast and Helpers Hungary’s Barbara Urogdi serve up some information and advice for those living and doing business here. Be sure to get this great summary (<strong>FREE download</strong>) compiled by Helpers:</p>
<p><strong><a href="Changes in Hungarian corporate law and related legislation (2012)" target="_blank">Changes in Hungarian corporate law and related legislation (2012)</a></strong></p>
<p>First of all, Barbara describes what’s been going on since last December in Hungary and says that numerous Helpers&#8217; clients have been asking her what the changes mean for their lives and businesses.</p>
<p>“A lot of our clients have been contacting us with different questions and concerns,” she says, “because there’s a lot of stuff written about Hungary in the media these days, and while a lot of it is disturbing and true, a lot of it is quite sensationalist.</p>
<p>“I think people are having a bit of a hard time teasing apart the two and finding out not only what is true, because that’s almost like a philosophical question, but what exactly is relevant for them, for their lives, for their business.”</p>
<p>For example, Barbara says that some of Helpers’ clients are concerned about the status of Hungary in the EU, “because there has been news or rumors that Hungary might get kicked out of the Union, which I think is quite unrealistic. As far as [clients] are concerned, that would affect their lives very deeply, because they are currently resident for example in Hungary and can travel freely in the EU.”</p>
<p>She says that the other issue regarding the legal changes concerns businesses.</p>
<p>“There’s a lot of panic over the situation of the Hungarian banking system,” she explains. “Most people know that the currency has declined around 15% over the past few months, which is quite drastic, and people are reasonably concerned, both about the fate of the currency, about the security of their bank deposits, about their mortgages and just the general reputation of Hungary and the international markets.</p>
<p>“Most of our clients are foreigners and they do business internationally, so they are concerned that having a Hungarian business might not be such a good idea after a while if things go as they are going now.”</p>
<p>But are such changes more likely to hit locals harder than foreigners living in Hungary?</p>
<p>“The decline of the currency actually favors foreign investors and also exporters, so basically anyone who does their business in euros or dollars and ends up having expenditures in forints is currently very happy. Not all of those people are foreigners, but most foreigners are in that kind of situation, so a lot of our clients – whether they get a salary or income from business – actually draw their income in euros or dollars. So for those people, actually until inflation catches up with prices, it’s a good thing.”</p>
<p>Additionally, Ürögdi notes that real estate prices are currently very very low in Hungary.</p>
<p>“Add to that the inflation that’s happened over the last few months, and the fact that real estate prices haven’t even begun to catch up with the inflation. The fact is you can buy property for 10-15% less now than three months ago, which was already quite low.</p>
<p>“So if you have euros or dollars to spend, that can actually be an advantage to you.”</p>
<p>She addresses the recent rise in Hungary’s VAT rate.</p>
<p>“The issue that people often mention is that VAT’s very high in Hungary – it was already quite high last year at 25% &#8211; and now it’s been raised to 27%. That is one of the highest in the world, it’s true. But, once again, people who do business to business transactions with foreign companies, or do wholesaling outside of Hungary generally do not pay VAT anyway on those transactions, so many businesses are actually unaffected by this.”</p>
<p>Barbara says in general there’s a silver lining to such changes.</p>
<p>“There are a lot of people who see an opportunity in the situation rather than an obstacle.”</p>
<p>Not panicking in the current situation in Hungary is the key, according to her.</p>
<p>“Until recently, almost nothing appeared about Hungary in the international press, and in a way that was a good thing, because most of our clients try to get information from reliable sources, so they would speak to consultants like us, or speak to Hungarian friends, their lawyer, accountant, and that’s how they would make their decisions.</p>
<p>“But in recent months there’s actually been a lot of press about Hungary in English, and a lot of that does seem to induce panic. So when people are reading stuff like people are burning the EU flag in the streets, and if there were a referendum Hungary would definitely step out of the EU, of course they get concerned.”</p>
<p>She continues: “If you get all your information from the media, then you will be tempted into sensationalist thought, but if you actually speak to experts, which is what we have been trying to do over the past few months: trying to make sense of what’s going on, and also trying to find opportunities for our clients in the current situation, they will tell you that the chance of Hungary actually leaving the EU has not risen by much over the past few months; it’s just the exposure that has risen, but the chances are still very very slim that that will ever happen.</p>
<p>“There’s really not that much to panic about, and as I said, a lot of the recent changes can be viewed as opportunities, and in that case you should be happy.”</p>
<p>Stay tuned for our next episode with Barbara from <strong>Helpers Hungary</strong> as we help you sort facts from fiction in the rapidly changing Hungary.</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Budacast/~4/gG-B5S9soVo" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.budacast.com/2012/01/23/hungary-legal-changes-2012-implications/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
<enclosure url="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/hungary_legal_changes_2012.mp3" length="4120922" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:keywords>advice living in hungary,bank deposit security hungary,Barbara urogdi helpers hungary,budacast podcast,burning eu flag hungary,business opportunities hungary 2012,business risk hungary,business services hungary,chance of hungary leaving the eu,</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:subtitle>In this episode of Budacast, Alterations and Modifications… We talk to entrepreneur Barbara Ürögdi of Helpers Hungary about what Hungary’s tidal wave of legal changes in 2012 means for expatriates, their businesses and life in Hungary. - </itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>In this episode of Budacast, Alterations and Modifications… We talk to entrepreneur Barbara Ürögdi of Helpers Hungary about what Hungary’s tidal wave of legal changes in 2012 means for expatriates, their businesses and life in Hungary.

If you’re even the slightest bit interested in what’s going on in Hungary, you’ve no doubt heard about all of the legal changes being enacted by the Hungarian Parliament and the subsequent international criticism.

Without getting into the politics, Budacast and Helpers Hungary’s Barbara Urogdi serve up some information and advice for those living and doing business here. Be sure to get this great summary (FREE download) compiled by Helpers:

Changes in Hungarian corporate law and related legislation (2012)

First of all, Barbara describes what’s been going on since last December in Hungary and says that numerous Helpers' clients have been asking her what the changes mean for their lives and businesses.

“A lot of our clients have been contacting us with different questions and concerns,” she says, “because there’s a lot of stuff written about Hungary in the media these days, and while a lot of it is disturbing and true, a lot of it is quite sensationalist.

“I think people are having a bit of a hard time teasing apart the two and finding out not only what is true, because that’s almost like a philosophical question, but what exactly is relevant for them, for their lives, for their business.”

For example, Barbara says that some of Helpers’ clients are concerned about the status of Hungary in the EU, “because there has been news or rumors that Hungary might get kicked out of the Union, which I think is quite unrealistic. As far as [clients] are concerned, that would affect their lives very deeply, because they are currently resident for example in Hungary and can travel freely in the EU.”

She says that the other issue regarding the legal changes concerns businesses.

“There’s a lot of panic over the situation of the Hungarian banking system,” she explains. “Most people know that the currency has declined around 15% over the past few months, which is quite drastic, and people are reasonably concerned, both about the fate of the currency, about the security of their bank deposits, about their mortgages and just the general reputation of Hungary and the international markets.

“Most of our clients are foreigners and they do business internationally, so they are concerned that having a Hungarian business might not be such a good idea after a while if things go as they are going now.”

But are such changes more likely to hit locals harder than foreigners living in Hungary?

“The decline of the currency actually favors foreign investors and also exporters, so basically anyone who does their business in euros or dollars and ends up having expenditures in forints is currently very happy. Not all of those people are foreigners, but most foreigners are in that kind of situation, so a lot of our clients – whether they get a salary or income from business – actually draw their income in euros or dollars. So for those people, actually until inflation catches up with prices, it’s a good thing.”

Additionally, Ürögdi notes that real estate prices are currently very very low in Hungary.

“Add to that the inflation that’s happened over the last few months, and the fact that real estate prices haven’t even begun to catch up with the inflation. The fact is you can buy property for 10-15% less now than three months ago, which was already quite low.

“So if you have euros or dollars to spend, that can actually be an advantage to you.”

She addresses the recent rise in Hungary’s VAT rate.

“The issue that people often mention is that VAT’s very high in Hungary – it was already quite high last year at 25% - and now it’s been raised to 27%. That is one of the highest in the world, it’s true. But, once again, people who do business to business transactions with foreign companies,</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:author>Budacast</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:duration>8:35</itunes:duration>
	<media:content url="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/hungary_legal_changes_2012.mp3" fileSize="4120922" type="audio/mpeg" /><feedburner:origLink>http://www.budacast.com/2012/01/23/hungary-legal-changes-2012-implications/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Mulling it over (Budapest Xmas Markets)</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Budacast/~3/6fT2U5UBuYg/</link>
		<comments>http://www.budacast.com/2011/12/09/budapest-christmas-markets/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 10:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>drew@budacast.hu (Drew Leifheit)</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Eats & Drinks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungarian Traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Take It Easy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budacast podcast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest Christmas market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest Christmas markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest Christmas traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest christmast market vorosmarty ter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest holiday activities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest holiday markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest kurtos kalacs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[buying hungarian handicrafts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christmas activities Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[christmas in europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christmas tourism Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[drinking wine in hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[european christmas traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[expensive mulled wine Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[forralt bor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[holiday drinking hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[holiday shopping Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[holiday shopping hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian ceramics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian Christmas market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian Christmas market mulled wine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian Christmas traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian cultural experiences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungarian online radio show]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian podcast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian spiced wine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Karácsonyi vásár budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Karácsonyi vásár forralt bor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Karácsonyi vásár Jókai tér]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Karácsonyi vásár kürtős kalács]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liszt Ferenc tér budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[radio show about Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[radio show about hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[traditional holiday drinks hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[traditional hungarian Christmas market foods]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vörösmarty Square Karácsonyi vásár]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vörösmarty tér foralt bor]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.budacast.com/?p=436</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In this archival edition of Budacast, Hungary’s online radio show and podcast: “Mulling it Over.” Hear what happens when some intrepid expatriates weather the cold to bathe in the sights, smells and sounds of one of Budapest’s traditional outdoor Christmas markets. A few years ago Maria Bredican and her friend Jennifer showed up at the [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this archival edition of <strong>Budacast</strong>, Hungary’s online radio show and podcast: “Mulling it Over.”</p>
<p><img src="http://farm4.staticflickr.com/3219/2950734899_29578a5afe.jpg" alt="Budapest Christmas Market" width="400" height="280" /></p>
<p>Hear what happens when some intrepid expatriates weather the cold to bathe in the sights, smells and sounds of one of <a href="http://hungarystartshere.com/Budapest-Christmas-Fair-Budapesti-Karacsonyi-Vasar" target="_blank">Budapest’s traditional outdoor Christmas markets</a>.</p>
<p>A few years ago Maria Bredican and her friend Jennifer showed up at the Christmas market (Karácsonyi vásár) on Vörösmarty Square in Budapest. Their mission? To warm their bones in the tradition that is drinking “forralt bor” or mulled wine: cheap wine that is spiced up with cloves, cinnamon and orange peel and served hot, preferably in a mug.</p>
<p>Jennifer says she doesn’t shop at this market, but enjoys the “semblance of Christmas past” there.</p>
<p>“There are lots of smokestacks, cooking, lots of fatty foods, sausages. You can buy your vinyl wallets, plastic calendars, marionettes, other faux handicrafts at any one of these stalls. I love the Christmas lights, odd shapes up and down the trees. Not too many bells; no Santa Clauses. Nice atmosphere. Folks sort meandering slowly. It’s cold so I suppose most are at home or – worse – at the shopping mall.”</p>
<p>As they stand beside a ceramics stall, Maria, is excited over the mulled wine that you can buy at the market.</p>
<p>“Lots of people seem to be wandering around and mostly drinking wine,” she says, noting that it’s an excellent idea.</p>
<p>Take note that in this – the most touristy Christmas market in Budapest – a mug of mulled wine can get pretty pricey, especially when you have to fork up a “deposit” to use one of the ceramic mugs instead of a plastic cup.</p>
<p>“I think you actually get your money back if you bring it back,” says Maria.</p>
<p>Jennifer fires up her order of two foralt bor. Only red wine is available.</p>
<p>Their tab is 900 forints – about 4 euro (even 6 years ago when we made this podcast).</p>
<p>Jennifer gives a 100 forint tip.</p>
<p>“I didn’t realize that the wines are served in these big, old fashioned ceramic pots,” she says. “I thought it was just for looks, but I’m looking at this now and it’s on hot stones on a woodburning stove – most of them are – so I guess this would keep it at the perfect temperature, right?”</p>
<p>“Because you can’t boil this; if you boil it you lose all the alcohol?”</p>
<p>Maria remarks: “Oh, really? Cause I boiled one at home the other night.”</p>
<p>“You want to have a little alcohol,” says Jennifer. “Let’s try this.”</p>
<p>“I really need this,” Maria says.</p>
<p>Jenn: “My only complaint about the forralt bor is you usually get it in a plastic cup, so the heat just comes right through. So if you’ve forgotten your gloves – like you have – your fingers get a little too hot to carry it.</p>
<p>“I will tell you something about this market – this is all handicrafts and very Christmas like – there are several other markets around town, like at Jókai tér and Liszt Ferenc tér where you can buy sweatpants and knit hats and shoelaces. Here it’s all handicrafts.”</p>
<p>Maria replies: “That’s why people come here – it’s for the ‘kürtős kalács,’” referring to the sugary, spongey treat that’s shaped like a chimney and is prepared before one’s eyes on an open fire.</p>
<p>“The big donuts, cinnamon cake, but thin and tall. Like a cinnamon cone soft cookie.”</p>
<p>“You see queues of people waiting to eat this and nibbling away,” Maria says.</p>
<p>Jenn says it means “smokestack” or “chimney.”</p>
<p>They watch the kürtős kalács being made and offer their observations.</p>
<p>“It’s like the pizza places when I was a kid,” Jenn explains. “You could watch them make the dough.</p>
<p>“They’re rolling it out with one of those big wooden cylinders – and she has to answer her cellphone. Just like 100 years ago.</p>
<p><img src="http://farm4.staticflickr.com/3444/3299936665_a58099b19e.jpg" alt="DSC_1969" width="500" height="333" /></p>
<p>“If I didn’t know that these were sweet, I would think it was like a pizza dough or a bread. It looks toasty and warm; I’ve never seen it cooked over the hot coals like that.”</p>
<p>Maria asks some visitors if they know what it is.</p>
<p>“No, that’s why we’re trying it for the first time. It’s sweet with the taste of cinnamon. Do you want some?” she asks Maria.</p>
<p>“No, I think I’m going to get one myself,” she says.</p>
<p>A bit later, Jenn reports that the Hungarian purveyors at the market start to pack up for the night.</p>
<p>Maria says, “Looks like it’s time to leave and everybody’s getting cold.”</p>
<p>“There are a few diehards getting chestnuts. It’s a lovely crisp night. Are you in the Christmas spirit now, Maria?”</p>
<p>“Yeah, I’m a bit better. Not as grumpy as earlier.”</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Budacast/~4/6fT2U5UBuYg" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.budacast.com/2011/12/09/budapest-christmas-markets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
<enclosure url="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/budapest_christmas_market.mp3" length="11901190" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:keywords>Hungarian online radio show,hungarian podcast,budacast podcast,radio show about hungary,radio show about Budapest,hungarian cultural experiences,Christmas tourism Budapest,Budapest holiday activities,Christmas activities Budapest,</itunes:keywords>
		<itunes:subtitle>In this archival edition of Budacast, Hungary’s online radio show and podcast: “Mulling it Over.” - Hear what happens when some intrepid expatriates weather the cold to bathe in the sights, smells and sounds of one of Budapest’s traditional outdoo...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>In this edition of Budacast, Hungary’s online radio show and podcast: “Mulling it Over.”

Hear what happens when some intrepid expatriates weather the cold to bathe in the sights, smells and sounds of one of Budapest’s traditional outdoor Christmas markets.

A few years ago Maria Bredican and her friend Jennifer showed up at the Christmas market on Vorosmarty Square in Budapest. Their mission? To warm their bones in the tradition that is drinking “forralt bor” or mulled wine.</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:author>Uncle Drew</itunes:author>
		<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:duration>8:15</itunes:duration>
	<media:content url="http://www.budacast.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/budapest_christmas_market.mp3" fileSize="11901190" type="audio/mpeg" /><feedburner:origLink>http://www.budacast.com/2011/12/09/budapest-christmas-markets/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Citizenshift (Acquiring Hungarian citizenship)</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Budacast/~3/_1nvQZKeDZY/</link>
		<comments>http://www.budacast.com/2011/12/06/acquiring-hungarian-citizenship-tips/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 12:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>drew@budacast.hu (Drew Leifheit)</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Family Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Foreign Affairs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Getting settled in Hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Practicalities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vital Information for Hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[acquiring Hungarian citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[andrea szalczer-leifheit helpers hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[becoming hungarian citizen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest expatriate services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[citizenship ceremony Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[citizenship ethnic Hungarians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[citizenship services Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[citizenship swearing in ceremony Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[depressing national anthems hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[documentary living in hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[drew Leifheit budacast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ethnic Hungarians Transylvania]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[everyday life Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foreigners experiencing hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foreigners living in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foreigners living in hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[helpers expatriate services hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[how to become a Hungarian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[how to get Hungarian citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian citizenship application]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian citizenship bureau]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian citizenship certificate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungarian citizenship procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungarian citizenship requests]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian citizenship requirements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian citizenship tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian grandparent citizenship request]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian national anthem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian nationality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungarian online radio show budacast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lifestyle guide for hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[moving to hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[procedure hungarian citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[process hungarian citizenship request]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[proud hungarian citizen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romanian nationals hungarian citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[swearing in ceremony hungarian citizens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[taking citizenship oath hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video living in budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vow hungarian citizenship]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.budacast.com/?p=427</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In this episode of Budacast, Uncle Drew files this special report on how to become a Hungarian, i.e. how to acquire Hungarian citizenship (if you’re eligible). Drew accompanied his wife Andrea and his mother in law to the district mayor’s office in Budapest’s 12th district for the swearing in ceremony. In connection with officially becoming [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this episode of <em><strong>Budacast</strong></em>, Uncle Drew files this special report on how to become a Hungarian, i.e. how to acquire Hungarian citizenship (if you’re eligible). Drew accompanied his wife Andrea and his mother in law to the district mayor’s office in Budapest’s 12<sup>th</sup> district for the swearing in ceremony.</p>
<p><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/pGk1UKdV-IE" frameborder="0" width="640" height="480"></iframe></p>
<p>In connection with officially becoming a Hungarian national, Andrea provides some tips for others who hope to become Hungarian.</p>
<p>Andrea smiles when Drew asks her if she’s excited to become a Hungarian citizen. She says the process took her about seven months (the Hungarian government has fast-tracked the process to swear in ethnic Hungarians living outside of Hungary’s borders, like those from Transylvania, like Andrea). Things weren’t so easy for her 13 years ago, when she tried to gain Hungarian citizenship when she first moved to Hungary. “They were not interested in me,” she jokes.</p>
<p>Drew says she’s interesting; that’s why he married her.</p>
<p>Andrea says the entire process of applying for Hungarian citizenship is no longer as complicated these days. She explains that she had to submit certain documents and prove relations between herself and her relative that was born in Hungary (her mom). In other cases, it could be someone’s grandparent as well.</p>
<p>In the Hungarian citizenship swearing in ceremony, a district government official makes some short remarks about becoming a Magyar, before the entire crowd repeats the citizenship oath and is officially handed their citizenship certificate.</p>
<p>At the end everyone makes a toast to the new Hungarian citizens, who receive flowers. Egészségedre!</p>
<p>After a bit of organization in the ceremonial hall, the Hungarian citizenship proceedings begin. Everyone stands to sing the Hungarian national anthem and then the participants take the oath, which contains the line: “I consider Hungary my home.”</p>
<p>When the ceremony is finished, everyone starts milling around and clinking glasses.</p>
<p>Outside, Drew realizes that his wife has officially become a Hungarian citizen, so he asks her how she feels.</p>
<p>“I’m so proud,” says Andrea, who offers a few tips for others seeking to redeem their Hungarian citizenship.</p>
<p>She says, “Don’t even start the procedure if you don’t speak the language, because you will need it through the entire process, starting with the application through to the very last step, when you take the vow. That’s the most important [tip].”</p>
<p>Andrea adds that becoming a Hungarian citizen take a heck of a lot of patience, because the process takes a lot of time (and effort).</p>
<p>To get started: gather all your documents, like birth certificates and supporting documentation to prove that one of your ancestors was Hungarian.</p>
<p>If you need help with your citizenship request, don’t hesitate to contact Andrea Szalczer-Leifheit, who heads Expatriate Services at <a href="http://helpers.hu/" target="_blank">Helpers Hungary</a>. She can offer you more information on Hungarian citizenship requests and even guide you through the entire process.</p>
<p>Stay tuned!</p>
<p>Uncle Drew &amp; Andrea</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Budacast/~4/_1nvQZKeDZY" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.budacast.com/2011/12/06/acquiring-hungarian-citizenship-tips/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://www.budacast.com/2011/12/06/acquiring-hungarian-citizenship-tips/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Searching for Souls &amp; Saints</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Budacast/~3/PmTVZN557JI/</link>
		<comments>http://www.budacast.com/2011/11/04/hungarian-traditions-all-souls-day/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 12:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>drew@budacast.hu (Drew Leifheit)</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Budapest Sites]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungarian Traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life in Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[all saints' day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[autumn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bartok]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budapest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cemetery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graveyard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hungarian traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hungary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[siberia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[soviets]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.budacast.com/?p=423</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In this video episode of Budacast, Drew, Andrea and her mom take a trip to the Farkasréti temető, a cemetery in Budapest, for All Souls&#8217; Day, when Hungarians typically visit local graveyards to pay respects to their loved ones. Among the numerous, often ornate graves, they happen upon the grave of Hungarian composer Béla Bartók, [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this video episode of <em><strong>Budacast</strong></em>, Drew, Andrea and her mom take a trip to the Farkasréti temető, a cemetery in Budapest, for All Souls&#8217; Day, when Hungarians typically visit local graveyards to pay respects to their loved ones. Among the numerous, often ornate graves, they happen upon the grave of Hungarian composer Béla Bartók, and light a candle for Andrea&#8217;s grandfather who was shipped off to Siberia by the Soviets.<br />
<iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/o1sXS6uN-c0" frameborder="0" width="640" height="480"></iframe></p>
<p>Stay tuned!</p>
<p>Andrea &amp; Drew</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Budacast/~4/PmTVZN557JI" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.budacast.com/2011/11/04/hungarian-traditions-all-souls-day/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://www.budacast.com/2011/11/04/hungarian-traditions-all-souls-day/</feedburner:origLink></item>
	<copyright>Copyright 2011</copyright><media:credit role="author">Drew Leifheit</media:credit><media:rating>nonadult</media:rating><media:description type="plain">Hungary's online radio show</media:description></channel>
</rss>
