<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>New England Journal of Medicine Interviews</title>
    <link>http://www.nejm.org/multimedia/audio-interview</link>
    <description>The New England Journal of Medicine (NEJM) Audio interview RSS feed. NEJM (http://www.nejm.org) is a weekly general medical journal that publishes new medical research findings, review articles, and editorial opinion on a wide variety of topics of importance to biomedical science and clinical practice.</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2012 Massachusetts Medical Society</copyright>
    <itunes:author>The New England Journal of Medicine</itunes:author>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 11:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>NEJM</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>perspective@nejm.org</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <webMaster>webmaster@nejm.org (NEJM webmaster)</webMaster>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title>New England Journal of Medicine Interviews</title>
      <url>http://podcast.nejm.org/_images/Googl_gadgt_intrvw.gif</url>
      <link>http://www.nejm.org/multimedia/audio-interview</link>
    </image>
    <itunes:image href="http://podcast.nejm.org/_images/Podcast_300int.jpg" />
    <itunes:category text="Science &amp; Medicine">
    <itunes:category text="Medicine" />
    </itunes:category>
 
 <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Arthur Kellerman on the increasing use of emergency departments and access to primary care.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/23</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/23</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Arthur Kellermann is vice president of the RAND Corporation and director of RAND Health, Santa Monica, CA.  Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. A.L. Kellermann and R.M. Weinick. Emergency Departments, Medicaid Costs, and Access to Primary Care– Understanding the Link. N Engl J Med 2012;366:2141-3.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-23.interview.mp3" length='16806135' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>13:59</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item> 
 
 <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Francesca Gany on undocumented immigrants and the U.S. health care system.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/22</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/22</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Francesca Gany is the chief of the Immigrant Health and Cancer Disparities Service at Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center and director of the Center for Immigrant Health and Cancer Disparities, New York, NY.  Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. J.O. Breen. Lost in Translation – Como se dice, "Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act"? N Engl J Med 2012;366:2045-7.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-22.interview.mp3" length='20920421' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>17:25</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
 
  <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Howard Brody on the ethics of rationing and waste avoidance in health care.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/21</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/21</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Howard Brody is a professor of family medicine and the director of the Institute for the Medical Humanities at the University of Texas Medical Branch, Galveston. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. H. Brody. From an Ethics of Rationing to an Ethics of Waste Avoidance. N Engl J Med 2012;366:1949-51.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-21.interview.mp3" length='29447833' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>24:30</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
 
 <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Susan Okie on the ongoing evolution of the primary care physician.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/20</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/20</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Susan Okie is a medical journalist and clinical assistant professor of family medicine at Georgetown University School of Medicine, Washington, DC. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. S. Okie. The Evolving Primary Care Physician. N Engl J Med 2012;366:1849-53.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-20.interview.mp3" length='20123686' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>16:45</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
 
     <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Allison Goldfine on statins, the associated risk of diabetes, and the FDA's response.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/19</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/19</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Allison Goldfine is the head of the Section of Clinical Research at Joslin Diabetes Center and an associate professor of medicine at Harvard Medical School. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. A.B. Goldfine. Statins: Is It Really Time to Reassess Benefits and Risks? N Engl J Med 2012;366:1752-5.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 9 May 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-19.interview.mp3" length='11950842' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>9:56</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
    
    <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Timothy Quill on balancing evidence-based medicine and patient-centered care.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/18</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/18</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Timothy Quill is a professor of medicine, psychiatry, and medical humanities and the director of the Center for Ethics, Humanities and Palliative Care at the University of Rochester School of Medicine and Dentistry.  Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. T.E. Quill and R.G. Holloway. Evidence, Preferences, Recommendations – Finding the Right Balance in Patient Care. N Engl J Med 2012;366:1653-5.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 2 May 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-18.interview.mp3" length='16875099' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>14:02</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
    
     <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Jan Blustein on the effects of pay-for-performance approaches for hospitals.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/17</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/17</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Jan Blustein is a professor of health policy and medicine at the Wagner Graduate School and the School of Medicine at New York University.  Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. A. Ryan and J. Blustein. Making the Best of Hospital Pay for Performance. N Engl J Med 2012;366:1557-9.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-17.interview.mp3" length='9687246' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>8:03</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
    
    <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Mark Hall on the recent Supreme Court oral arguments in the challenge to the Affordable Care Act.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/16</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/16</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Mark Hall is a professor of health care law and policy and medical and bioethics at Wake Forest University Schools of Law and Medicine in Winston-Salem, North Carolina. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. M.A. Hall. Supreme Court Arguments on the ACA – A Clash of Two World Views. N Engl J Med 2012;366:1462-3.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-16.interview.mp3" length='16083508' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>13:24</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
    
    <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Raynard Kington on the importance to medicine of the behavioral and social sciences.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/14</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/14</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Raynard Kington, a physician and the former director of the Office of Behavioral and Social Science Research at the National Institutes of Health, is the president of Grinnell College in Iowa. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. R.M. Kaplan, J.M. Satterfield, and R.S. Kington. Building a Better Physician – The Case for the New MCAT. N Engl J Med 2012;366:1265-8.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-14.interview.mp3" length='23750527' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>19:46</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
    
     <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Steven Schroeder on smoking-cessation efforts in the United States.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/13</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/13</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Steven Schroeder is a professor of health and health care and the director of the Smoking Cessation Leadership Center at the University of California, San Francisco. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. M.C. Fiore, E. Goplerud, and S.A. Schroeder. The Joint Commission's New Tobacco-Cessation Measures – Will Hospitals Do the Right Thing? N Engl J Med 2012;366:1172-4.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-13.interview.mp3" length='16588274' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>13:48</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
    
    <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Gail Wilensky on possible directions for bipartisan Medicare reform.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/12</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/12</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Gail Wilensky is an economist and senior fellow at Project HOPE. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. G.R. Wilensky. Directions for Bipartisan Medicare Reform. N Engl J Med 2012;366:1071-3.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-12.interview.mp3" length='19370885' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>16:08</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
    
    <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Sharon-Lise Normand on medical device approval and postmarketing surveillance.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/10</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/10</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Sharon-Lise Normand is a professor of health care policy and biostatistics at Harvard Medical School and the Harvard School of Public Health. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. F.S. Resnic and S.-L.T. Normand. Postmarketing Surveillance of Medical Devices - Filling in the Gaps. N Engl J Med 2012;366:875-7.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-10.interview.mp3" length='21710886' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>18:04</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
    
    <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Michael Barry on patient-centered care and shared decision making.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/9</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/9</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Michael Barry is president of the Foundation for Informed Medical Decision Making and medical director of the John D. Stoeckle Center for Primary Care Innovation at Massachusetts General Hospital. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. M.J. Barry and S. Edgman-Levitan. Shared Decision Making - The Pinnacle of Patient-Centered Care. N Engl J Med 2012;366:780-1.
]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-9.interview.mp3" length='32238901' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>22:22</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

    <item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Alan Weil on the states' role in the implementation of the Affordable Care Act.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/8</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/8</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Alan Weil is the executive director of the National Academy for State Health Policy in Washington, DC. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. A. Weil. The Value of Federalism in Defining Essential Health Benefits. N Engl J Med 2012;366:679-81.]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-8.interview.mp3" length='27355751' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>22:46</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>
    
<item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Robert Truog on issues in medical ethics and the physician-patient relationship.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/7</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/7</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Robert Truog is a professor of medical ethics, anesthesiology, and pediatrics at Harvard Medical School and a senior associate in critical care medicine at Children's Hospital Boston. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. R.D. Truog. 200th Anniversary Article: Patients and Doctors - The Evolution of a Relationship. N Engl J Med 2012;366:581-5.]]>
  </description> 
  <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-7.interview.mp3" length='26017956' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>21:39</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Pieter Cohen on the regulation of dietary supplements.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/5</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/5</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Pieter Cohen is a primary care physician at Cambridge Health Alliance in Somerville, Massachusetts, and an assistant professor of medicine at Harvard Medical School. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. P.A. Cohen. Assessing Supplement Safety - The FDA's Controversial Proposal. N Engl J Med 2012;366:389-91.]]>
  </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 1 Feb 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-5.interview.mp3" length='21081909' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>17:33</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Michael Chernew on the Medicare's physician-payment system and the sustainable growth rate (SGR) formula.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/4</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/4</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Michael Chernew is a professor of health care policy in the Department of Health Care Policy at Harvard Medical School. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. A. Alhassani, A. Chandra, and M.E. Chernew. The Sources of the SGR "Hole". N Engl J Med 2012;366:289-91.]]>
  </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-4.interview.mp3" length='12940588' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>10:46</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Cynthia Jackevicius on generic drugs and health care costs.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/3</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/3</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Cynthia Jackevicius is an associate professor of pharmacy practice at Western University of Health Sciences in Pomona, California, and an assistant professor in the Department of Health Policy, Management and Evaluation at the University of Toronto. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. C.A. Jackevicius et al. Generic Atorvastatin and Health Care Costs. N Engl J Med 2012;366:201-4.]]>
  </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-3.interview.mp3" length='12686979' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>10:33</itunes:duration> <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: I. Glenn Cohen on the constitutional challenge of the Affordable Care Act that will heard by the United States Supreme Court in March.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/2</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/2</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[I. Glenn Cohen is an Assistant Professor and Co-Director, Petrie-Flom Center for Health Law Policy, Biotechnology, and Bioethics, both at Harvard Law School. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. I.G. Cohen and J.F. Blumstein. The Constitutionality of the ACA's Medicaid-Expansion Mandate. N Engl J Med 2012;366:103-4.]]>
  </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-2.interview.mp3" length='23177250' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>19:17</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Allan Brandt on the history of the Journal as a window into the history of medicine, science, and society.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/1</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/366/1</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Allan Brandt is a Professor of the History of Medicine at Harvard Medical Schooland Dean of the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences at Harvard University. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. Brandt A. A Reader's Guide to 200 Years of the New England Journal of Medicine. N Engl J Med 2012;366:1-7.]]>
  </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 4 Jan 2012 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2012.366.issue-1.interview.mp3" length='26947225' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>22:26</itunes:duration> <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Robert Schwartz on the history of cancer research.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/365/25</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/365/25</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Robert Schwartz is a professor emeritus of medicine at Tufts Medical School, and a former deputy editor at the Journal, both in Boston. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. Supplement to: Schwartz R. The Emperor of All Maladies - The Beginning of the Beginning. N Engl J Med 2011;365:2353-5.]]>
  </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2011.365.issue-25.interview.mp3" length='15444269' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>12:51</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Elliot Israel on the risks and benefits of long-acting beta agonists in the treatment of asthma and COPD.</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/365/24</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/365/24</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Elliot Israel is a Professor of Medicine at Harvard Medical School and the Director of Clinical Research in the Pulmonary and Critical Care Division at Brigham and Women's Hospital, both in Boston. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. Supplement to: Chowdhury B et al. The Risks and Benefits of Indracaterol - The FDA's Review. N Engl J Med 2011;365:2247-9.]]>
  </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2011.365.issue-24.interview.mp3" length='19558281' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>16:16</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<item>
  <title>NEJM Interview: Dr. Jerry Avorn on the evolving approach to drug safety in the United States</title>
  <link>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/365/23</link>
  <guid>http://www.nejm.org/toc/nejm/365/23</guid>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[Dr. Jerry Avorn is Professor of Medicine at Harvard Medical School and Chief of the Division of Pharmacoepidemiology and Pharmacoeconomics at Brigham and Women's Hospital, both in Boston. Stephen Morrissey, the interviewer, is the Managing Editor of the Journal. Supplement to: Avorn J. Learning about the Safety of Drugs - A Half-Century of Evolution. N Engl J Med 2011;365:2151-3.]]>
  </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 7 Dec 2011 11:01:00 -0400</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="http://podcast.nejm.org/interviews/nejm_2011.365.issue-23.interview.mp3" length='18290417' type='audio/mpeg' />
  <itunes:duration>15:13</itunes:duration>
  <itunes:keywords>medicine, doctor, physician, primary care, clinical practice, health policy</itunes:keywords>
</item>

<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</channel>
</rss>
