<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">



<channel>

<ttl>60</ttl>

<title>Gnawledge HipHop International</title>

<link>http://www.gnawledge.com</link>

<description>Rhymes and beats from around the world.</description>

<language>en-us</language>

<copyright>&#x2117; &amp; &#xA9; 2010 Gnawledge</copyright>

<itunes:subtitle>Rhymes and beats from around the world.</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:author>Gnawledge</itunes:author>

<itunes:summary>Gnawledge is an outernational hip-hop collective of immigrant artists who make modern music rooted in traditional sounds. Composers of slow-cooked rhymes and boom-bap beats, Gnawledge is native to both sides of the analog/digital divide. Promoters of community gatherings [eg parties and concerts], Gnawledge fights for sustainable social movements [especially dancing].</itunes:summary>

<itunes:owner>

<itunes:name>Canyon Cody</itunes:name>

<itunes:email>canyon@gnawledge.com</itunes:email>

</itunes:owner>

<itunes:image href="http://gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/podcastimage.jpg"/>

<itunes:category text="Music"/>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>



<item>

<title>Gnawledge Podcastoff</title>

<itunes:author>El Canyonazo</itunes:author>

<itunes:subtitle>International hiphop podcasts since 1954</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:summary>Gnawledge Records debut podcast, released on DJ El Canyonazo&apos;s 22nd birthday.  The program features a guest appearance from Sean Dwyer performing &quot;Promises&quot; (Remix) from the upcoming JD Dyslexic album.  The show begins with my remix &quot;Emergency Xxplosives&quot; and features tracks from Brother Ali, Ozomatli, Edan, Soulive, mcenroe, J-Live, Lyrics Born and more.</itunes:summary>

<enclosure url="http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20Gnawledge%20Podcastoff.mp3" length="32778493" type="audio/mpeg" />

<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20Gnawledge%20Podcastoff.mp3</guid>

<pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2006 19:00:00 EST</pubDate>

<itunes:duration>34:08</itunes:duration>

<itunes:keywords>hip-hop, rap, international, underground, dj, cuba, hiphop, world, music, travel</itunes:keywords>

</item>



<item>

<title>Valentines Day</title>

<itunes:author>El Canyonazo</itunes:author>

<itunes:subtitle>Te Quiero. Te Adoro. Canciones de amor.</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:summary>While my rich friends in high school used their parents credit cards to order expensive Valentines Day gifts for their girlfriends, Id dub a cassette with sexy songs.  Without music to dizzy us up, falling in love would probably take a lot longer.  This weeks mix features music from Fiona Apple, Citizen Cope, Finley Quaye, The Roots, Willie Hutch, Bill Withers, The Black Keys, DAngelo, Charles Wright, Alvin Robinson, Lee Dorsey, Sufjan Stevens, and The Cure (in that order).  Happy Valentines Day!</itunes:summary>

<enclosure url="http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20Valentines%20Day.mp3" length="26141302" type="audio/mpeg" />

<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20Valentines%20Day.mp3</guid>

<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 19:00:00 EST</pubDate>

<itunes:duration>27:13</itunes:duration>

<itunes:keywords>hip-hop, rap, international, underground, dj, cuba, hiphop, world, music, travel</itunes:keywords>

</item>



<item>

<title>Funky Middle</title>

<itunes:author>El Canyonazo</itunes:author>

<itunes:subtitle>Getin funky on my turntables like an ol&apos; batcha collered shirts. </itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:summary>Funky and fast, starting at 110 beats per minute and headed to 135. I dare you not to wiggle to the riddim. Tracks from Double Dee and Steinski, The Go Team, Pete Rock, Q-Tip, Nickodemus, Gregory Isaacs, Cameo, Damian Marley, Cee-lo and more!  Check http://www.gnawledge.com for full tracklisting.</itunes:summary>

<enclosure url="http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20Funky%20Middle.mp3" length="26919915" type="audio/mpeg" />

<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20Funky%20Middle.mp3</guid>

<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2006 19:00:00 EST</pubDate>

<itunes:duration>28:02</itunes:duration>

<itunes:keywords>hip-hop, rap, international, underground, dj, cuba, hiphop, world, music, travel</itunes:keywords>

</item>



<item>

<title>OuterGnational</title>

<itunes:author>El Canyonazo</itunes:author>

<itunes:subtitle>Globalization&apos;s intergalatic winds spread hiphop across the seventeen seas.</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:summary>DJs like Z-Trip, Sean Dwyer, and Mixmaster Mike demonstrate unremorseful contempt for national borders, sampling Afro-Cuban jazz, Brazilian bossa nova, West African funk, and Indian Hindustani sitar with reckless abandon.  This Po-Mo rupture of the time&#47;space continuum was the scientific breakthrough necessary for Gnawledge hiphop international.  While we play with wormholes, rappers like MC Solaar and the Orishas are reinventing the wheel, finding new paths for flows in foreign tongues.  Hiphop is a lot bigger than the dirty south or bicoastal, it&apos;s global war and the weapons we choose are protools.</itunes:summary>

<enclosure url="http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20OuterGnational.mp3" length="27750818" type="audio/mpeg" />

<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20OuterGnational.mp3</guid>

<pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2006 19:00:00 EST</pubDate>

<itunes:duration>28:54</itunes:duration>

<itunes:keywords>hip-hop, rap, international, underground, dj, cuba, hiphop, world, music, travel</itunes:keywords>

</item>



<item>

<title>The Next Episode</title>

<itunes:author>El Canyonazo</itunes:author>

<itunes:subtitle>When keepin it real goes wrong. Heavy beats from the USA.</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:summary>After 4 months of international vinyl diggin, supporting indigenous bootleg cultures from Jamaica to Morocco, DJ El Canyonazo returns home to Los Angeles with a hunger for some good ol &apos;merican boombap.  Before we get back to our regularly scheduled programming of progressive, underground, organic hip-hop, it&apos;s time to bump that gangsta shit: pac, big, ra, jada, nasir, dp, eazy, etc. Email canyon@gnawledge.com for complete tracklisting.</itunes:summary>

<enclosure url="http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20The%20Next%20Episode.mp3" length="31550067" type="audio/mpeg" />

<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20The%20Next%20Episode.mp3</guid>

<pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2006 19:00:00 EST</pubDate>

<itunes:duration>32:51</itunes:duration>

<itunes:keywords>hip-hop, rap, international, underground, dj, cuba, hiphop, world, music, travel</itunes:keywords>

</item>



<item>

<title>Love Dust</title>

<itunes:author>Gnotes</itunes:author>

<itunes:subtitle>HipHop means never having to say I Love You</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:summary>A monster-mash record-obscura 4 mix from Gnotes, with mpc-style valentines day breakbeats. Listen in on how gNotes hears... ella fitzgerald,charlie parker,children of the congo, nile rogers, bernie williams, outkast, lost dreams, afro dz ak, peter frampton, placid, ladysmith black mombazo, jd dyslexic, lightning hopkins, diplo, the art of the japanese bamboo, tripple double, trouping the colour, timbaland, black watch, when radio was king, pbr, michael jackson, tribal surrealism, eddie cantor, various breaks remain anonymous and.</itunes:summary>

<enclosure url="http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/Gnotes%20-%20Love%20Dust.mp3" length="17606994" type="audio/mpeg" />

<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/Gnotes%20-%20Love%20Dust.mp3</guid>

<pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>

<itunes:duration>18:20</itunes:duration>

<itunes:keywords>valentines, love, hip-hop, rap, international, underground, dj, cuba, hiphop, world, music, travel</itunes:keywords>

</item>

<item>

<title>Dubious Bredren</title>

<itunes:author>El Canyonazo</itunes:author>

<itunes:subtitle>Rude bwoys and b-boys: Hip-Hop and Jamaica</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:summary>Behold how good and pleasant it is for breathren to dwell in peace and unity.  Immigrant musics born of emerging technologies, conceived en route from Boston Bay to Jamaica Plain.  Radio frequencies muddied by Caribbean storms. Outernational sounds merge and emerge anew.  In order to discourage a global chant, the twin towers of Babylon promote a confusion of tongues, under and around which patios and ebonics connect the margins.  Licks borrowed, slang ganked, and steez tiefed. Intertextuality in afro-diasporic post-modern urban electronic audio. Toast and flow.</itunes:summary>

<enclosure url="http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20Dubious%20Bredren.mp3" length="75787801" type="audio/mpeg" />

<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/El%20Canyonazo%20-%20Dubious%20Bredren.mp3</guid>

<pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2007 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>

<itunes:duration>52:35</itunes:duration>

<itunes:keywords>jamaica, hip-hop, rap, international, underground, dj, hiphop, world, music, travel, ethnomusicology, immigration, dub, reggae, dancehall</itunes:keywords>

</item>



<item>

<title>Granada Doaba</title>

<itunes:author>Gnawledge</itunes:author>

<itunes:subtitle>Flamenco hip-hop árabe from Canyon Cody + Gnotes</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:summary>Granada Doaba is a flamenco hip-hop collaboration album recorded in Spain, produced by Gnawledge and funded by a Fulbright Scholar research grant. Gnawledge is a praxis hip-hop collaboration between  Fulbright scholar Canyon Cody and rapper/producer Gnotes. Composers of modern electronic riddims rooted in traditional music, Gnawledge promotes participatory education through sample-based hip-hop. Please download, copy + share. Don’t forget to remix. Granada Doaba explores the broad roots and divergent branches of flamenco hip-hop. Inspired by the religious convivencia of Al-Andalus, the album features 16 musicians from around the world who all currently live in Granada, Spain. Spain’s history of multicultural confluence dates back to the early morning of mankind. Andalusia, the birthplace of flamenco and southernmost region of Spain, sits at the crossroads of Europe, Africa and the New World. Until the Christian reconquista of Granada in 1492, southern Spain was known as Al-Andalus, a Muslim Empire that controlled Andalusia for 800 years. Flamenco is Andalusian Gypsy music and dance with a diverse history of Arab, Jewish, Indian and Afro-Latin influences. As a result of convergent paths of immigration, rhythms from around the world have come together in Andalusia, where they evolved into an indigenous musical culture: flamenco.</itunes:summary>

<enclosure url="http://gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/Gnawledge%20-%20Granada%20Doaba.mp3" length="56188090" type="audio/mpeg" />

<guid isPermaLink="true">http://gnawledge.com/music/podcasts/Gnawledge%20-%20Granada%20Doaba.mp3</guid>

<pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>

<itunes:duration>58:31</itunes:duration>

<itunes:keywords>flamenco, hip-hop, rap, international, underground, dj, hiphop, world, music, travel, ethnomusicology, immigration, guitar, arab, arabic, middle eastern, cajon, darbuka, granada, spain</itunes:keywords>

</item>


<item>

<title>Wild Jack Salt</title>

<itunes:author>DJ Canyon</itunes:author>

<itunes:subtitle>New Bass and Old Drums</itunes:subtitle>

<itunes:summary>An international mishmash of electronic bass music with Gnawledge selector DJ Canyon Cody.  With 35 songs in 60 minutes, this global dance mix features cumbia, hip-hop, dubstep, funk caroica, salsa, drum & bass, kuduro and glitch.  For full annotated track-listing, check http://gnawledge.com/blog/?p=459

</itunes:summary>

<enclosure url="http://gnawledge.com/audio/djcanyon/Wild%20Jack%20Salt.mp3" length="112319667" type="audio/mpeg" />

<guid isPermaLink="true">http://gnawledge.com/audio/djcanyon/Wild%20Jack%20Salt.mp3</guid>

<pubDate>Mon, 8 March 2010 09:00:00 EST</pubDate>

<itunes:duration>60:22</itunes:duration>

<itunes:keywords>dance, party, remix, cumber, hip-hop, remezcla, baile, funk, salsa, kuduro, glitch, canyon cody, gnawledge</itunes:keywords>

</item>



</channel>

</rss>